I'm nervous.
I smell good.
Don't be nervous.
Open your mouth.
I'll show you a lot of kisses.
How do you feel?
It's messy.
I'm nervous.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I want water.
I'm nervous.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm nervous.
It hurts.
I'll make you feel better.
How do you feel?
I'm nervous.
Open your mouth.
I'll show you a lot of kisses.
I'm nervous.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'll make you feel better.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm nervous.
It hurts.
How do you feel?
I'm nervous.
You're cute.
I'm not good at being photogenic.
Are you popular?
I'm not sure.
I'm not unpopular.
I can make anyone fall for me.
Really?
That's amazing.
I'm conscious of a good body touch.
I see.
What do you do?
What do you think I am?
I can't guess.
Are you a college student?
I'm not a college student.
I'm an expert.
No one has ever guessed this.
What is it?
Are you an expert?
Are you an esthetician?
I'm called an esthetician.
No, I'm not.
You're not fashionable?
Are you a nurse?
No.
I'm a chef.
Are you a chef?
That's cool.
That's unexpected.
What kind of chef are you?
I'm a French chef.
That's cool.
It must be hard to be a French chef.
It's hard.
It's been four or five years.
I can't handle fire.
I can't handle a frying pan.
Is that so?
I'm still a beginner.
I can only do chores.
I'm a chef, but I don't cook.
Do you cook for your boyfriend?
I often make oyakodon.
That's Japanese.
I usually cook at home.
Why did you decide to do AV?
It's very simple.
I like having sex.
I can't do it if I don't do it every day.
Do you actually do it?
Actually?
I don't have a boyfriend every day.
I do it a lot.
With whom?
I'm a chef.
What's the most perverted
sex you've ever had?
The most perverted sex?
Yes.
I think it's a man and a woman.
A man and a woman?
A man and a woman.
In love.
I drink a lot.
I cook a lot.
I do it alternately.
Three girls?
Three girls and three boys.
How was it?
It was great.
It was so much fun.
I want to do it right now.
I see.
That's good.
You like to be perverted.
I like it a lot.
What's your weapon?
My butt.
What?
My butt is very big.
I'm a little complex.
Let me see.
It's good.
It's a tea bag.
Isn't it big?
It's good.
It's iron.
Do people praise you?
Yes, they do.
They say it feels good.
I'm good at moving my tongue.
Try it.
It's fast.
I move my tongue while I'm perverted.
You have big boobs, don't you?
Do I have big boobs?
Yes, you do.
What size is it?
It's B.
Can I see it?
I'm holding it.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
It's erotic.
It's an erotic bra.
I like purple.
It's cute.
It's like a lace.
It's like a nipple.
Here?
It's embarrassing to
show it through the screen.
Why?
It's good.
I want to be excited.
How do you feel?
How do you feel about your nipples?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's an erotic bra.
Can I see it closer?
It's an erotic bra that doesn't come out.
It's an erotic bra.
Do you have nipples?
I have nipples.
How do you do it?
I'll use a microphone.
What's that?
It's a microphone.
It's an erotic bra.
I've never done this before.
I'll try it on you.
I want to have sex.
I can't.
It hurts.
It feels good.
I'm sweating.
You said you wanted to have sex.
I want to have sex.
It's time to have sex.
It feels good.
I want to have sex.
I'm getting excited.
I don't like it if you're not excited.
I think I'm too excited.
You're wearing pajamas.
I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
I don't know.
When I go to a club.
Do you go to a club?
I go to a club.
I fell in love at once.
I went to a club about two years ago.
Really?
What club did you go to?
YARIMOKU.
Did you pick up girls?
I was waiting for it.
If you sit and talk to me.
If you say you would drink.
I'm going to invite you.
Are you going to your hotel?
Oh, I see.
There's also the other way around.
Oh, really?
Do you talk to him?
Yeah, I do.
If I think he's good-looking,
I go talk to him.
I sit next to him or lean on him.
But you said there's
no man you can't talk to.
I usually lean next to
the man I'm talking to.
Oh, really?
Like this.
Oh, I see.
You shouldn't be doing that.
Yeah, like this.
This is how you do it.
Then I go like this.
Like this.
This is how you do it.
Yeah.
If I think he's good-looking, I
say, I'm going to the bathroom.
Oh, really?
You should do that.
This is a technique my friend taught me.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Do you ever feel like
you're not good enough?
Yeah, a lot.
Even if I ask him to exchange
LINE messages with me,
he won't do it.
Oh, really?
So you never see him again?
Yeah, even if I see him at a club.
If he's good, I'll text him,
but if he's not good, I won't text him.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
What do you mean by good?
What?
Good?
What do you mean by good?
The way he moves his hips.
Oh, that?
It's not like he's good at kissing.
Oh, that too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not like that?
That's true.
Oh, that's true.
But surprisingly,
there aren't many
people who do that for me.
Why?
There really aren't many.
What?
Men I see at clubs are
usually one-night stands.
That's what I think, too, so I
don't think you need to be so polite.
How do you do it?
Do you force it in?
It's not polite.
Does it work?
It doesn't work.
It does.
Is it easy to kiss?
I might have said this on Zoom,
but kissing is a switch,
so you can kiss to get wet.
So it's okay.
Just kissing?
Yeah.
You can get wet just by kissing?
You can get wet.
It depends on the time,
but you can get wet when you can.
Do you ever fail at drinking?
I cry a lot.
I see.
You cry a lot?
I cry a lot.
Why?
When I'm waiting outside,
I don't cry when I'm drunk.
You cry a lot.
I cry a lot.
I have a failure.
What?
When I was in college,
I got drunk and cried a lot.
I see.
I didn't drink beer.
Do you usually do that?
No, I drink beer now.
You drink beer now.
When I told my mom that I was pregnant,
she told me to drink after-beer.
Do you tell your mom that?
I tell her everything.
I tell her about men.
About sex?
Yeah.
My parents know what I do.
Do they?
Yeah.
I take them to my house.
What do they say?
I tell them to know about prostitution.
I see.
My mom might have been like that.
My brother is like that.
He is very strict.
He takes me to a
different house every time.
He is a middle school student.
Are you okay with porn?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm a little scared.
That's why I'm nervous.
What about porn?
Did your parents tell you to do it?
No, they didn't.
They didn't?
Why?
You should tell them.
I can't tell them.
Why?
You should tell them.
I can tell them to play with me.
But I can't tell them to do it.
My parents might say that.
I see.
I'm a little weird.
They might get mad at me.
I see.
Before I applied for this job,
I was very worried about that.
What if my parents find out?
I see.
I'm still nervous.
You are.
I'm nervous.
Really?
Yes.
You're lying.
I'm serious.
You need to drink more.
I'm okay.
I drank too much.
That eel?
Yes.
It's good.
What do you think?
I like white.
White and gold.
This is a small area.
I was surprised.
I like this style.
I'm going to push you.
I like the left one.
I want to have sex.
I'm going to push you.
What's the setting?
I don't know.
You don't know?
What kind of person is she?
I'm looking forward to meeting her.
I think it's good to drink this.
Really?
Let's go.
I have a request.
What is it?
I want a highball.
Okay.
I'm nervous.
Are you that nervous?
I like alcohol.
I know.
But I only drink a highball.
Really?
You don't drink wine?
No.
I don't drink sour.
I only drink a highball.
How is your tongue?
My tongue?
Isn't it dirty?
It's not dirty.
I want to have sex here.
Really?
I like blue.
Are you excited?
I'm very excited.
I want to do it now.
There is no one here.
I want to do it at this timing.
Your tongue is dirty.
I want to have sex.
One more time.
What are you doing?
I want to have a soft kiss.
No.
Don't do that.
Turn off the light.
I want to have a soft kiss.
Give me a pen.
It's cool.
Turn off the light.
I want to have a soft kiss.
I'm drunk.
I smell something.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Does it smell?
It doesn't smell.
Really?
Yes.
Look at my face.
It's cool.
I want to have a soft kiss.
Do you want to have a soft kiss?
You are cute.
You think I'm cute, don't you?
Don't do that.
I want to have a soft kiss.
It doesn't smell.
It doesn't smell, does it?
Everything smells good.
You are cute.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Don't do that.
Look at my butt.
My butt?
What?
Look at my butt.
OK.
It stinks.
It's dark.
Does it smell?
Not at all.
Make it smell more.
It doesn't smell.
Doesn't it smell?
Yes.
It smells, doesn't it?
It smells.
Say it again.
My butt stinks.
Look at my butt.
It smells.
It feels good.
You are cute.
Let's have a soft kiss.
It smells.
Look at my butt.
What?
My butt.
It smells.
It feels good.
When you go to the bathroom,
please stop it with your tongue.
OK?
Look at my eyes.
It stinks.
Say that you like it.
What?
I'm scared.
I like it.
Please ring the bell.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Let's put our shoulders out.
I don't know what you mean.
I'm nervous.
The scenery is good.
Really?
I didn't expect this kind of place.
I thought it was a club.
Really?
Well,
I can drink alcohol in this music video.
It's good.
I can drink alcohol.
Don't you usually drink?
I don't care.
It's done.
Please stand up.
Come here.
I'm nervous.
I feel like I'm a girl.
Really?
Yes.
What are you doing?
There?
Look at me.
I can hear footsteps.
It smells good.
I'm nervous.
Come here.
Please open the door.
This is the last one.
Can you do like Ijiri Okada?
To the camera?
The high speed one.
That's right.
Thank you for watching!!