Hello, I'm Shizuha Takimoto.
Today, I'm going to a meeting place.
By the way,
my clothes are like this.
It's quite clean and cute.
It's been a long time since I
traveled, so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm nervous.
Thank you.
Sure.
Let's start.
Yes, please.
I'm nervous.
Yes, it's live.
I'm nervous, so I'll stop using honorifics.
Will you stop?
I'll talk like my friend's brother.
Please do.
That's nice.
She's my friend.
Do you not drive
often? No, I don't.
I see.
Just friends get along well
with each other, don't you?
How about in the past?
In the past, when I was a student,
I drove in the middle of the night.
That's nice.
But I didn't drive alone.
It was like a group of four,
going to the sea together.
Was there a lot of sea?
Basically, there was a lot of sea.
It's a place close to Enoshima.
Did you have a boyfriend at home?
I had a lot of houses.
I went to the city somewhere.
By train?
I've never gone out.
I've never stayed overnight.
Oh, that's strange.
I often say good-bye after half a year.
I think I can say
good-bye after half a year.
Do you say good-bye to yourself?
No, I'm often rejected.
What's the reason? I don't know.
I don't know what it was, but one of them noticed that it was not the time
to work and fall in love, and I thought it was a lie, but I thought there
must be someone else who likes it, but it's not a good excuse for work,
and the other one is also a job, so I don't think I'll be dumped again.
It's not a place where you can
see the night view all of a sudden.
I don't think so. I feel like it
was pretty sudden every time.
Do you think it's such a good woman?
I wonder if there was something wrong.
So you don't know the
meaning yet? I don't know.
I wonder what it is.
So the longest so far?
It's the longest relationship
I've ever had in a year.
It's still a year.
I see.
I don't know what to say.
It's lonely at first.
But recently, it's easier
without a boyfriend.
That's true.
I think it's better.
I think it's going to be a good day.
I think we should go to a
nice place with a nice view.
The hot spring is good, but...
It's a nice place with a nice view.
I hope it's sunny over there.
I think it's going to
be fine if it's like this.
I'm pretty good at raining.
If I get closer, it might rain.
It's been raining for the
past two days, even though
it was sunny until now
when I took the first one.
It was miraculously sunny when I took
it outside, but it was basically raining.
I see.
It was raining when I
took a photo in Watami.
I thought it was not good.
Me?
I thought it was going to rain.
But it is said that rain
clouds are very lucid.
I see.
It is said to be good.
There is a saying that if you like a dragon
It's pure white.
It's so cool.
I might like it.
You're so kind.
What are you drinking? This is.
..
Ham Shallow Beer.
English... It's a beer.
I found it.
Let's drink.
It's good.
Oh, it's pretty light.
It's light. It's easy to drink.
It's not that strong.
It's like a dango.
Yeah.
Meccha Miso.
Thank you for the food.
It's been a while.
This is going to be a
commercial, isn't it? Meccha Miso.
Meccha Miso.
I didn't understand anything.
This is MECCHA MISO.
I think my boyfriend is good, too.
First of all, you want to be a good wife.
Do you have any wishes?
To be honest, I don't have any.
You don't have any?
No.
I want to have a baby.
I want to live freely.
I see.
At my own pace.
I don't like being restrained.
I see.
I don't like being told,
I don't like being told, I
don't like being told, I
can't hold it for half a year.
That's why.
It's a lot of miso.
I wanted to notice it earlier.
I've been following you.
It's a lot of miso.
I'm glad you noticed.
I'm embarrassed.
Just a little.
This is the most embarrassing
thing I've done so far.
I got it.
How is it?
Great!
How is it? It's good.
It's spacious.
Can I open this? Of course.
Great.
It's nice.
It's hot, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Look this way.
Isn't it crispy? Yes, it is.
It's hot, isn't it? Yes, it is.
My throat is dry.
It's OK.
I'll put on my butt.
Is it wet? Yes, it is.
I may not be able to see inside
if I don't take off my clothes.
Yes, it is.
Do you want to take it
off by yourself? Yes, I do.
It's already wet.
Touch it.
Is it sweat? No, it's not.
It's not? No, it's not.
She's looking at it.
It's embarrassing.
Maybe it's wet.
No, it's not.
Are you tired? Yes, I am.
Can you lie down on
the wall? Look at me.
Stand up.
There is no hot water.
Are you embarrassed? Yes, I am.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
How about you?
You don't smell, do
you? I don't know.
I don't.
You don't? I don't know.
It's a little sour.
It's already hard.
Do you like it?
Do you like it? Yes, I do.
He is sleeping.
He is standing up, but he is not moving.
He is sweating.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
May I take your clothes off?
Did you wear this?
Yes. It was hard for me.
Wow!
It looks painful.
I did it.
Good job.
I finally got it.
One more time.
Let me wipe off the sweat.
It's hot, isn't it?
Let me wipe your back.
It's okay.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby sleeping on the floor.
Can I sleep here?
Do you want to sleep
here? It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Look at me.
I'm so tired.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I feel sick.
Are you okay? I feel sick.
Oh!
Oh! It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
It feels good.
Lie down on my back.
Wow!
Wow! I feel good.
I feel good.
゜゜゜゜゜゜゜゜゜゜゜いまっせ! I'm sorry.
。 。 。 I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a break.
This video was made in Cooperation
with the YouTube company Tokiwala.
Thank you for watching.
Today, I'm going to
show you how to make a
simple and easy-to-eat
Japanese-style rice bowl.
I'm going to show you how to make a simple
and easy-to-eat Japanese-style rice bowl.
You spilled it on purpose, didn't you?
You want me to lick it, don't you?
One, two, three, four.
I want you to spill more.
Your legs are white.
I'm so tired.
This side is bleeding a lot.
You're wet.
I'm so tired.
、、、、、、、、。
Oh... Oh...
Oh...
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
Do you like this one? Yes, I do.
Ouch, it hurts.
This is your favorite one.
You got some on your arm.
【The sound of a man struggling to get up】
笑
わぁ…
笑 笑 笑
笑 笑
笑
Let's stop eating.
Where are you
throwing up? My neck.
It's hot.
Is it good? Yes, it's good.
Look at me.
It hurts.
Yeah.
Do you like it? Yeah.
Let's make it like an axe at home.
Make a window.
Yeah.
Are you ready?
Are you okay?
Why are you sitting
down? It feels good.
Are you okay? Yeah.
Mom is struggling to get out of the car.
Let me see.
It's wet.
Can you tell me
the taste? It's sweet.
Is it sweet? Let me see.
Stick out your butt and lick it.
You can open your butt.
I'm back.
I'm going to the hospital.
Neko-Kichi, can you show me how
to spread your legs with both hands?
Try moving your legs.
Neko-Kichi, are you sleepy?
Do you want to sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
It hurts! I feel sick.
I feel sick.
Do you want to drink water?
Yes.
It feels good.
I feel good.
I feel sick.
Are you okay? I feel sick.
※This is not a still screen.
Ouch! It hurts! I'm hurt.
I'm so happy.
I love it.
I feel so good.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
Come here.
Oh, my God!
Which side do you want? Inside.
Oh, it hurts.
Are you all right?
Oh!
I pulled out the tail.
Do you want more?
More?
Wow!
It's so good!
One more time!
Yes, I understand.
I am sorry.
It's alright.
She is in a bad mood.
Show me your mouth.
What?
Is it gone? I drank it.
Did you drink it?
There is a little bit left.
Did you drink it? Thank you.
It was unpleasant.
I'm going to take off my makeup.
Today, after arriving at
the hotel and having a meal,
I'm going to do a double eyelid surgery.
I'm a little tired, so I'm
going to take off my makeup.
Are you ready to sleep?
I'm ready to sleep.
Can I take it off?
I don't want to, but... I'm
going to take off my bare face.
You look cute.
Look at me.
Come closer.
I don't want to because
you have a big face.
I don't think your bare
face will change much.
I think it will change a lot.
Your skin is very beautiful.
Very beautiful.
I don't know what will happen if I drop it.
You may say, nice to meet you.
I may say, nice to meet you.
I may say, who
is it? You may not.
I don't want to.
You can shake it like a cosplay.
What should I do?
You look so different.
Look over here.
Look at this.
It's moving.
It's completely different from before.
Can I sit down?
You don't like it? No, I don't.
Do you massage
your face? I try not to.
I've heard that it causes wrinkles.
So I don't do it.
I go to bed early and get up early.
No, I go to bed late.
I go to bed early and get up late.
I sleep about 9 hours a day.
I have a lot of hair on my head.
You don't have a lot of eyebrows.
I have a lot of hair on my stomach.
You have a beautiful face.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
Can I hold you? I'm sorry.
Let me hold you.
Put your tongue out and come closer.
Do you like it?
Look at the camera.
It's getting warm.
oh
What's wrong?
I feel sick oh
You can sit here
You can sit on your back
Open your mouth and raise your legs.
Show me your open mouth.
I'm going to take a bath.
Do you want to take a bath?
I'm getting wet.
Do you know you're wet?
Yes.
I feel sick. I can't go back.
I'll put you on the floor.
This way.
Do you want to lie down?
Yes.
From the bottom.
I'm scared.
Look at Mamenyan.
He is licking his face.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
It's hard to hold it in.
I feel so good.
I can do it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
It's so hot.
I have a runny nose.
You have a leg cramp.
It was great.
I could go to many places.
It was a great and fun trip.
It was fun.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
It's been a long time since I've
had a cat, so I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's close.
It's a camera.
I'm going to eat it.
I'll do it.
I'm done.
You're done.
I'm embarrassed.
You're going to eat
it, right? Come here.
Can I sit here?
Hi guys, welcome back to my channel.
Today, I'm going to show
you guys how to make
the most delicious
ice cream in the world.
I'm going to show you how to make
the most delicious ice cream in the world.
I'm sorry, I just can't help it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Hello, I'm Harami!
Sit back & enjoy my full performance!
Thank you for watching my full performance!
Please subscribe to my
channel if you like my videos!
See you in the next video! Bye~!
※This is not a sound effect.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
What's wrong with your
bangs? My bangs hurt.
I'm going to feed you in 6 hours.
I'm going to give you honey.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm going to put the cat in the cat room.
Lie down on the bed.
Do I look like a bug?
Do I smell like sebum?
It's raining a lot.