Hello, I'm Harami!
Sit back & enjoy my full performance!
Thank you for watching my full performance!
Please subscribe to my channel, add
comments and share with your friends!
My Twitter is also in the description box!
Don't forget to like this video
and subscribe to my channel!
Thank you so much for
watching my full performance!
Don't forget to subscribe to my channel,
add comments and share with your friends!
Thank you so much for
watching my full performance!
There you go.
It's good.
It tastes good, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Are you going to feed me?
It's good.
Let's do it again.
You don't have to drink it anymore.
I want to drink it forever.
I'm so lucky.
It's white.
I can see it.
It's good that you're sweating.
Maybe I'm shaking.
That's good.
Show me your underwear.
Underwear?
It's a room.
Let's take off your clothes.
Kiss me.
Show me your butt.
Your butt is beautiful.
Show me more.
It looks good on you.
Really?
What are you doing?
I'm touching you.
It's cool.
Do you want to take off your clothes?
Yeah.
Let me touch you.
It's sweet.
Is it sweet?
Does it taste like sweat?
Yeah.
I thought it was transparent.
It's so transparent.
You're right.
It was transparent.
It's good.
It's a cute underwear.
Is your waist moving?
Is it moving?
Yeah, it's moving.
It's connected.
It feels good.
You have a lot of hair.
Really?
It's true.
I'm sleepy.
I'm getting sleepy.
You still have a lot of hair.
Really?
Yeah.
You sweat a lot.
It's embarrassing.
It's hard.
Yeah, it's hard.
It's because it's a new underwear.
New underwear is hard.
I'm going to take it off myself.
You're going to take it off?
It feels good.
I want to put it in my mouth right away.
You have a weak neck.
It smells sexy.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Can I lick you?
Lick me.
It's the best.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
You're going to talk to me all the time.
I love to lick you.
Do you want me to lick you?
It's hot.
I want to kiss you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Put your hands on your back.
It feels good.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm going to lick you.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I licked you.
It feels good.
Don't move.
It's hot.
Let's go to bed and sleep.
It feels good.
It's hot.
Don't you like it?
Calm down and get up.
It's hot.
What's wrong?
Does it tickle?
It tickles.
Put your tongue out.
Put your tongue out more.
It's hot.
You can put your tongue out more.
Where do you want me to put my tongue out?
Do you want me to put my tongue out?
I want you to put your tongue out.
Put your tongue out.
It's hot.
Is it good?
It's good.
Put your tongue out more.
It's hot.
It's easier for you to bite, isn't it?
You've grown up a lot.
Put your tongue out more.
It's hot.
It's easy, isn't it?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to put your tongue out directly.
Directly?
What should I do?
I want you to put your tongue out more.
Tell me what you want me to do.
It's hot.
Is it good?
It's good.
What should I do with you?
I want you to lick me.
Do you want me to lick you?
You have a lot of hair.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
You have a sensitive tongue.
Put your tongue out more.
Put your tongue out.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Is it good?
It's good.
You have a lot of hair.
It's hot.
Put your tongue out more.
Put your tongue out.
It's hot.
You have a lot of hair.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to put your tongue out more.
Do you want me to put your tongue out more?
I'll cover your eyes.
Open your eyes.
It's hot.
Can you see me?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Is it good?
It's good.
It's hot.
I'll give you an injection.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll give you an injection.
It's good.
Don't hold it in.
I'll give you an injection.
It's hot.
Don't hold it in.
I'll give you an injection.
It's hot.
Open your eyes.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll give you an injection.
Don't hold it in.
It's hot.
It feels good.