Humming
This is a small rural world.
How many more summers
will I spend in my life?
At the end of summer, there is
something I always remember.
Hey, Take-chan?
Megumi-san, you're finally back.
I have a favor to ask you.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Come here.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm begging you. It's a lifetime request.
Come here.
But I'm really busy.
Come on.
Sit down, sit down.
Mr. Yoshimura, I brought him as promised.
Oh, you came.
I thought you would run away again.
You are a bastard, aren't you?
You really have a strong bad luck.
Hey, Ake-chan, please explain the movie.
Miss,
Didn't you hear anything from this bastard?
What do you mean?
To put it simply, you were sold.
What?
I'll explain it to you.
Meguri, I'm really sorry.
I don't have any money left.
I was told that Kumicho-san
doesn't have anything valuable,
so I immediately told him
about Meguri, and this happened.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, you bastard, are you
protecting yourself again?
Miss, do you want me to tell
you what he said? Kumicho-san.
Shut up!
There is a woman who can say anything.
She is very cute.
She said she will definitely become rich.
This bastard.
What?
Mr. Meguri, please help me.
Please.
Mr. Meguri, help me.
You don't like it, do you?
Hey, you bastard!
You know what to do if you
can't pay me back, don't you?
Sign the life insurance, you bastard!
Yuri-san, please help me!
What are you doing?
Why are you screaming in front of a woman?
Sign it or not!
Help me, Yuri-san! I'm going.
Meguri-san.
I don't want you to die.
Are you sure?
But I want you to promise me something.
Will you love me forever?
Don't you want to be with me forever?
Are you going to sacrifice
yourself for the man you love?
It's a waste to be such a bastard!
Come on, let's go.
Come on, this way.
It's from now on.
Have you ever
used it? It's a toy.
Do you feel your neck?
How do you feel?
If you feel good, say it.
Come on.
Be honest.
Open your mouth.
More.
This side, too.
Open your mouth.
Don't close your mouth.
Hey!
Don't be scared.
Do like this.
Here?
What?
Do you feel good?
I can't hear you.
I feel good.
Please do more.
Please help me.
Like this?
Don't be afraid.
Stand up.
You are amazing.
You have a big butt.
Don't do that.
If you don't listen to me, I'll hurt you.
Hiwa! Come here.
You look great.
What would that idiot
think if he saw you like this?
No.
Come here.
Don't go without permission.
Don't be afraid.
I'm sure you'll say,
Can I go with you? OK? Come on.
Hang in there.
It's not over yet.
Come on.
OK.
That's it.
Open your arms wider.
Like this.
You are a good boy.
How do you feel when you
are seen by your boyfriend?
Please look at the dog.
I can't hear you. Speak louder.
Look at the dog.
Please lick the dog.
Open your mouth.
You have a beautiful face.
How do you like it?
My stupid boyfriend
doesn't lick me like this.
I'm going to eat it.
How do you feel? I can't eat it.
Come on.
Don't be a fool. Come here.
You're sweating a lot. Swallow it.
Let me swallow your sweat.
Please let me do it.
Yes, do it.
Don't lick your nipples.
Don't lick them.
Don't lick them more.
Huh? Don't lick me.
OK.
Look.
I'm getting hard.
I said, let me serve you.
Let me serve you.
Not yet.
Can you do it properly?
How is it? I can't do it.
Put your hands up.
OK?
Open your mouth.
Open your mouth and feel it.
How do you like it compared to
your stupid boyfriend, Chimpo?
Which one is better?
If you don't understand,
I'll make you understand.
Hey, what are you
doing? Come on, do it.
Do you like it?
Hey! Go to the back.
Oh, I see.
You are sweating. Drink the medicine.
Do you like it?
I can't hear you.
It's delicious.
Please let me lick you more.
Stand up.
Yes.
Open your hands.
Put it in the sink.
Are you going to put it in the sink?
You want it, right?
Put it on the sofa.
Open it again.
Open it again and
say, Put it in the sink.
You always say that.
Hey! Come on, relax.
Don't whine.
Do you want more?
You want me to give you a big one?
Please get well soon.
Please lie down here.
Lie down here.
Today, I'm going to show you a video
of a baby who is eating a baby food.
I'm going to show you a video of
a baby who is eating a baby food.
Hey, hey.
It's very tight.
Look.
Not yet.
Come on.
Just a little more.
It's a pacifier for your pussy.
Put your hand out.
I said, put your hand out from behind.
Put your foot out more.
Please put it in from behind.
Do you feel better than
your stupid boyfriend?
Do it by yourself.
Look at here.
Yes, it's hurt.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes. Do it by yourself.
You are a pervert.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to put it in?
You can put it all in.
You can put it in.
I can't.
You can't.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Today, you are mine.
OK? Here you are.
No! Please take it.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Here you are.
Wow, it's great.
Please feel good with my mango.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
You're making a sad face.
I'm sorry.
Who told you to take it off?
Come on, get on my lap.
Put your hands up.
Do you feel good? Look at me.
Do you want to be my girl?
Do you? Come on.
It's been a long time since
I've had a baby, so I'm a little
nervous, but I'm going to do
my best to take care of my baby.
I'm going to do my best
to take care of my baby,
so I'm going to do my best
to take care of my baby.
Are you okay? It hurts.
It's not over yet.
It hurts.
Do you want me to take you to a nice place?
No.
What? You don't want me
to take you to a nice place?
No.
Hey, don't make yourself feel bad.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
You're bleeding.
Hey, open your eyes again.
I told you to be quiet.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I feel sick.
Here?
Come on, open your mouth.
Say something.
Mom, please say something.
Mom, please don't make me feel sick.
Don't leave me alone.
Don't be sad.
Let's go.
Come here.
Lie down.
Take a deep breath.
Open your mouth.
Take-san, don't worry about it.
You'll be fine.
In this countryside,
I can't do anything but buy pachinko.
But I'll be fine in a little while.
Oh, yeah.
What's this? It's a present.
I made it myself.
It's beautiful,
isn't it? Thank you.
I don't have money, so I've
never given you a present.
How is it? Do you like it? Yeah.
Thank you.
Wow, that's wonderful.
But I won't give you any money from now on.
Let's kiss.
You're going to try to
fool me again, aren't you?
Then let's do it as usual.
Please, please.
Here? Please, please.
I don't care.
Just for today.
Really? Thank you.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
You are not afraid of anything.
You are wearing underwear.
You are so stiff.
I can't stand it.
Hurry up.
あ。
う。
キムチ。
う。 う。
Today, I'm going to show you how to
make the most delicious ramen in the world.
I'm going to show you how to make
the most delicious ramen in the world.
【The sound of a baby eating】
【The sound of a baby coughing】 【The
sound of a baby blowing a nose】 It's hot.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Yes.
It's not good temperature.
Stand here.
Take off your shirt.
Take off?
I'm embarrassed.
Are you okay?
Nobody is watching you.
Nobody is watching.
【Taking a bath】
You like it, don't you?
Give me a little more... More?
Is it good?
Yeah! Ouch! Oh, no.
..
Oh, no?
You should not go.
It's hot.
It's so good.
Oh, no? Oh, no.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Ouch! No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Hold on, Kuromu.
Do your best, Leo.
Today, I'm going to show
you a video of me eating.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to wake up.
Don't do that.
I thought it would be important.
Hey, don't you want to
talk to me? I'm working.
You haven't called me recently.
I'm sorry.
I want you to call me a little.
I said I'm sorry.
I don't know what's going
on with our relationship.
I don't know.
What do you want to say?
Our relationship as lovers is broken.
Hey, can you do that later?
I'm looking for a job now.
Don't run away. Let's talk.
I don't know about Megwin, but I
want to concentrate on my current job.
I know, but we have to think together.
Hey, I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey, wait a minute. Let's talk.
How is it?
Well, I'll tell you.
You don't know how I
feel when I work in the
countryside and spend
my time comfortably.
You want to break up because
you don't know, don't you?
But you don't tell me, so I don't know.
I'm thinking about the future.
Have you ever thought about money?
You can't imagine what the future
will be like in a country like this.
You can say such a terrible thing.
I'm thinking about it, too.
Have you ever wanted to leave such
a small country and learn the world?
Is it so difficult to work in Tokyo?
It's not like that.
They might be chit-chatting here, but when
they go out, they don't communicate at all.
Is there no house in Satoshi's future?
I can't think of that now.
Do you like me?
It's not like that.
I just wanted to be with you, Satoshi.
That's enough.
Hey.
I'm sorry about earlier.
What's the matter? You know.
..
Let's break up.
It's the limit, isn't it?
I don't know if I can do that.
I don't know.
I can't be happy.
Don't you change your mind?
I'm sorry for everything.
Why do you love me so
much, but it's so painful?
Don't apologize to me.
I just feel empty.
Thank you for loving me.
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
This is a video of a
baby eating a baby's food.
The baby is crying.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby eating a baby's food.
It's a baby eating a baby's food.
I'm so sleepy.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Give it back to me.
Give it back to me, Nakoshi.
I was high.
I'm hungry.
I'm sorry.
Ahh!
Hello, everyone.
It's been a long time.
I don't know when I'll see you again.
It's been a while since I've been home.
You're not coming
back this year? No way.
I was looking forward to seeing you.
You've been on a business trip?
Really?
When will we meet again?
Next year?
We've known each other for a long time.
You're heavy.
We are a family of five.
We are not good friends.
It's delicious.
Do you want to eat grapes?
You just tasted it,
didn't you? I'm sorry.
I'm going to close my mouth.
You're getting closer and closer.
How's Tokyo?
Are you used to it? Well, yeah.
I haven't heard from you at all lately.
I'm sorry.
I'm busy studying and working part-time.
You're just playing with students.
No, I'm not.
That's good. I'll call you every day.
It smells so much.
It's embarrassing.
It's smelly.
No, it's not.
Brother.
Oh, it's painful.
You like it, don't you?
You don't have a dog, do you?
You like here,
don't you? Yes, I do.
Itadakimasu.
Let's eat.
Meguri, isn't it too big?
It's better to eat it in this size.
It's almost the same size.
That's not enough.
Really? It's sweet.
It's really sweet.
It's sweet, isn't
it? Oh, I'm happy.
I'm happy to spend time like this.
I think so, too.
By the way, I went to
a reunion the other day.
Oh, did you?
Yes.
And Take told me that he likes me.
What?
I was a little surprised.
I see.
What? Are you a little
nervous? No, I'm not.
Come on, be honest.
Just a little.
You... Stop it.
I'll get back at you.
I'm going to kill you.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
What's this? It's a skull.
Do I have to do it,
too? Yes, you do.
It's better not to drink too much water.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel? I feel great.
Look at your head.
Come on, let's go.
Grandma and grandpa will come soon.
But it's cold.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy...
I'm happy.
Don't cry.
Why can't I do it? It hurts.
I'll do it.
It hurts.
I'm tired.
How many?
What's that?
What?
Is it picnic?
Did you finish? I finished.
Why do you study?
What?
Isn't it to make studying a habit?
I'm not going to be able to get
good grades or bad grades in my life.
No.
By studying like this, you're
learning how to deal with things.
Are you going to be a
teacher today? Here it is.
The answer of the top student.
I don't know anything.
I'm not going to study.
Hey.
Do it.
I'm not in the mood.
By the way, are you going to Tokyo?
I'm going to Choson.
I want to escape from this
country and see various places.
Is Tokyo such a good place?
I don't know, but I want to see it once.
Is it the last time to see Satoshi?
No, I'll be back in the summer vacation.
I'm lonely.
I'll give it to you.
What's up? A present.
Do you remember I taught you sunflower
language in the previous class? Oh, I forgot.
It had nothing to do
with the entrance exam.
What's up? Oh, never mind.
What's up? It's okay.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
What?
Hey, wait!
※This video was recorded
on July 22nd, 2016.
Megwin! Here.
I remembered the
words of Himawari.
One is love at first sight.
Three is love at first sight.
I have something to tell you.
I like you.
You are late.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to bed.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's sour.
I'll try to eat slowly until I can.
I'm going to get up.
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
【Crying】 I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
My butt hurts.
Your butt? I'm sorry.
※This is the first time I've ever heard
of it, so I'm not sure if it's true or not.
I'm sorry.
I want to die. I want to die.
My aunt...
〔Crying〕
〔Breathing〕 I'm sorry.
I'm sick.
You're tired.
I thought so.
You know, I've been in love
with you since I was a little girl.
Why don't you tell me?
I want you to tell me that you love me.
I see.
You don't have a girl's heart at all.
I don't buy it at all.
I'm sorry.
I'll be with you forever.
If so, I have to go to
a good university in
Tokyo, get a good job,
and make a lot of money.
I don't need money.
That's all I need if I have you.
Meguri, I love you.
I love you too.
When I touch a little child, hand
in hand, in the sun, I feel so sweet.
Every time summer comes, I feel pain.
The sky clears out, and I can't breathe.
If I could see you again now,
If I could see you
again in a different form,
If I could meet you again, I
would imagine only such things.
I wonder if the summer will end like this.
I'm here because I'm here
Meguri-san, you'll catch a cold.
Thank you.
I'm not good at it.
What's the matter?
You are ticklish.
I tickled you too.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
You are a big cat.
Do you want me to touch you?
Do you want it? This is big.
Do you feel good?
There is something inside.
Do you lick it?
I've talked to my mom about having a baby.
So that's why she's got a stomachache.
I had to move her house
because it was raining.
I'm still half asleep.
Today, I'm going to show you how to
make a simple and easy-to-eat egg roll.
I'm going to show you how to make
a simple and easy-to-eat egg roll.
Do you like it?
Oh, it is broken.
I made it wrong!
What's the matter?
You are ticklish, aren't you?
You are a sensitive cat, aren't you?
Today, I'm going to show you how to make
a cute and delicious kimchi fried rice.
Cut the kimchi into bite-sized pieces.
Today, I'm going to show
you how to make a simple and
easy-to-eat bread that you
can easily make at home.
I'm going to show you
how to make a simple and
easy-to-eat bread that you
can easily make at home.
I'm going to show you
how to make a simple and
easy-to-eat bread that you
can easily make at home.
I'm going to show you
how to make a simple and
easy-to-eat bread that you
can easily make at home.
I'm going to show you
how to make a simple and
easy-to-eat bread that you
can easily make at home.
It's been a long time
since I've had a baby, so
I'm a little nervous, but
I'm going to do my best.
My legs are moving.
Does it feel good?
80 83 It's bitter.
You ate a lot.
You were strong.