Is this recording?
Hello.
I'm Rukawa.
It's embarrassing.
I'm going to the studio for shooting today.
Let's go.
It's cold today.
I forgot. Today's clothes are like this.
White knit, white down, black short pants.
It's cold. Can you see it?
Let's go.
Let's get started.
Today's shooting is...
It's embarrassing to talk to myself.
This is the first time I'm
doing this with a selfie stick.
Today's shooting is...
It's supposed to be a staycation.
It's a live staycation.
What do you think? I cut my hair.
This is the first time I've cut
my hair and taken a picture.
This is the first time
for me to use this app.
I always use the app for selfie.
It's weird.
It's like, my face is like this.
What the hell is this?
There was a cat earlier.
There was a stray cat.
It was so cute.
Black and white and brown.
It's time to meet up.
Let's go.
I'm nervous.
My heart is pounding.
It's probably around here.
Oh, there it is.
Today's studio.
It says Prestige.
Well, I'd like to go inside.
Thank you for your hard work.
What?
Good morning.
Nobody's here.
What's going on?
Good morning.
Nobody's here.
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What's that?
What?
Oh, wait!
Oh, my God.
I was really surprised.
You didn't ask me, did you?
No, I didn't ask you all of a sudden.
What did you ask me today?
Today, I'm going to stay at your house.
I'm going to stay at your house.
You didn't ask me when I could
stay at your house, did you?
No, I didn't.
I didn't ask you all of a sudden.
I thought he wouldn't talk for a long time.
I'm sorry.
I was so surprised that I was sweating.
I'm so happy that my son is happy.
I'm so happy that I don't know what to do.
I don't want to be alone.
I want to be a happy family with my son.
Oh.
Oh Oh.
Um.
Oh.
Um I'm so hungry.
I'm so hungry.
She is getting harder and harder.
I'm sorry.
You're too soft.
You're wet.
I'm sorry.
You have a butt.
Ah!
She's whining.
No, no, no, no, no!
The baby is a little out of breath.
Oh, the baby is out of breath.
It's been a long time since
he's been out of breath.
Yes, he's out of breath.
He's been out of breath for a long time.
Oh, baby, you're tired.
Are you tired?
I want a drink.
You're so cute.
It's good, it's good.
Aah!
You're not crying, are you?
You're not crying.
There, there, there,
there, there, there, there.
Aah!
It's so good.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Look at this.
Yes, it is.
Is it good?
It is really good.
Yes.
You are doing good.
Sit down, Chimpanzee.
It's warm.
It feels good.
Is it warm?
It's warm.
It was more comfortable than I thought.
I think the baby is more
comfortable than the mom.
I'm happy that my son likes the baby.
I couldn't help crying.
I hadn't felt so good at
the hospital for a while.
Mom got a call and I visited her.
Mom is carrying my dad to the hospital.
She is also giving birth to a baby girl.
No, don't do it.
I'm going.
I'm going to go.
You can do it.
Are you okay?
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It feels so good!
Ah, it feels good.
Everyone is so warm.
No, no, no.
I'm going.
Ah, I'm going.
It feels good.
The baby is in the middle of the toilet.
So I'm washing her.
I'm focused on her and washing her.
It's like I'm doing
something, but it's not!
I'm filming, I'm filming!
The baby is in the middle of the toilet.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm going to die.
Ahh... Ahh...
You're not gonna get up?
No.
Ahh...
Ahh... Ahh... Oh, it feels good.
It's getting better.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
What is that?
I'm sorry.
The day she was
born... Mother's voice.
I'm so happy.
I feel so good.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, God.
Hey, Aty.
Come on, relax.
I wanna go inside.
You do?
Go inside, please.
Please.
It's so hot.
It's amazing.
Yeah….
※I'm not a spy I'm scared.
Yeah, you're fine.
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's hot.
Wow, it's warm.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Give me more.
Oh, it hurts.
You had a lot of them, didn't you?
Yes.
Did you like them?
Let me touch them.
Spread your legs.
Sit down.
Wow.
There are a lot of them.
It's for three people.
Wow.
It was warm.
Was it?
Yes.
Did you feel good when you were kicked out?
No, not at all.
How did you feel when you
were suddenly kicked out?
I was surprised, but I felt good.
You were kicked out right away.
But the fun is yet to come.
Oh, there's more?
It's just started, isn't it?
I see.
What are you listening to?
Otomari?
It's just started.
It's just started, isn't it?
It may come out suddenly again.
I'm scared.
It may come out suddenly from somewhere.
What is it?
It's on the left.
This is a fun corner.
Let's have fun together.
Is that Ryujin?
There is Ryujin.
It's great.
It's big and long.
Please express how long it is.
It's this long.
I wonder how many people there are.
It's so long.
Were you surprised?
Yes, I was surprised.
It looks good on you.
Does it?
It matches your outfit today.
It does.
It's like a celebrity.
Thank you.
It's great.
It's amazing.
This way.
This way?
It's so shiny.
Let's take a picture.
Okay.
It's not started yet.
Please press the button.
Here?
Yes.
Let's go.
Has it arrived?
It's moving!
Let's go!
Yay!
What is that?
I got a bit of a shock.
It's funny.
I don't know what to say.
Where do you like to go
when you go on a date?
When I go on a date?
If I'm with someone I
like, I like to go anywhere.
I like to go home or go for a drive.
I like to go out for a meal.
I think so, too.
It's good to have someone you like.
Do you want to go to a place like this?
I want to go to an amusement park.
I want to go anywhere.
Do you have a place you want to go?
I don't have a place I want to go.
Do you want to be with that person?
I want to go anywhere.
Don't break it.
I can't put it in.
I see.
It's wonderful.
I'm sure you'll take me anywhere.
Really?
I'll take you to my house.
It's a little cold, isn't it?
Yes.
After all, there are men who want
to walk with such a cute person.
Is that so?
If it's just a house,
it's a little wasteful.
I want to show off.
Is that what you mean?
Yes.
What is today's theme?
Today's theme is...
It's cold, but I'll show my legs.
That's what it is.
That's the best.
Your legs look long.
I'm happy.
I'm barefoot.
Even though it's cold, There are a lot of
people who don't wear underwear, right?
Yes.
I'm happy to take a video like this.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Thank you for the massage.
There are a lot of people wearing
short underwear like this, right?
Yes, yes.
The bottom?
The bottom is pretty good.
It's pretty good.
Please show me a little.
I took it off right away.
Oh, really?
I want you to show me
that you're wearing it.
Someone... Yes, yes, yes.
Who?
I was like, this way!
And I got in.
I'm a little embarrassed.
This one.
It's the best.
It looks like a panty.
It's embarrassing.
It's a panty.
This is a real limousine.
Wait a minute.
Is there such a limousine in the limousine?
Is there such a limousine?
This is not a normal limousine.
This is a fancy limousine.
Do you like to spin?
Yes, I like it.
Is the sound okay?
Can't you see outside?
I just noticed.
I can't see outside.
I think so.
Can you see outside?
Can you see from Yu-chan?
I can see.
It's dangerous if you can see.
It's a service.
No, no, no.
You're so mean.
I'm not.
Do you have a problem with that?
No, I'm embarrassed,
so I don't want to say it.
You're going to do it, aren't you?
I don't want to say it.
You don't want to say it.
I'm embarrassed, so I don't want to say it.
Where do you hit?
Here?
Where?
Yes, it is.
How do you feel?
It's embarrassing.
You were quiet a while ago.
Yes, I was.
Were you?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I'm getting hot.
Have you ever done something
erotic while riding a car?
No, I haven't.
It's my first time in a car.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Cars move on their own.
It's like a temple.
Can I get in?
No, you can't.
Oh, it's coming out.
Oh, it's out.
Oh, she's out.
You're eating a lot.
That's a lot.
It feels good.
I'm going to get a tattoo.
You got a tattoo on your hand.
I got a tattoo.
You got a tattoo?
I'm sad, but I'm going to die.
I'm usually an ED.
Really?
I'm going to be the first to die.
You were the first one
to jump out of the car.
It was too cute, so I took it.
What's your favorite shape of your penis?
I don't know.
A normal size?
A little bigger than normal?
I think so, too.
I like this style.
I like it, too.
How do you like it?
Do you?
Yes.
Your style is beautiful.
Yes, it is.
It's thin.
Wait a minute, I'm sweating.
Sweating is delicious.
I'm sorry, I'm sweating.
This swimsuit looks good on you.
Wait a minute.
It's really beautiful.
Come here.
The underwear and the body
are perfect for a limousine.
It's really beautiful.
It's comfortable.
The face is beautiful.
Have you ever done this in a car?
No, I haven't.
I want to do this.
I want to touch it.
It's wet.
I don't know.
Does it feel good?
I don't think so.
While looking at the camera.
He is still a baby.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
It's so hot.
You need to drink more.
It's hot.
What's hot?
My mouth is hot.
I'm so hungry.
What are you doing?
I'm being hit by a car.
Where?
In front of me.
You're being hit by a car
in the middle of the road?
Yes.
Look this way.
I'm scared, En-chan.
Let's go.
This is dangerous.
It's getting bigger.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh.
Treasure.
No more.
I feel so good.
I'm dying.
Captain!
Egg!
Thank you.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
Are you going?
Yes, I'm going.
Are you sure?
Take care of yourself.
I'm going.
I'm sorry.
You're out a lot.
I'm excited.
I didn't mean to get out.
I don't know why, but it felt good.
Did you feel good?
I'll wipe your face.
Thank you very much.
Your face was a little cold.
You told me to take it out.
I just felt like that.
You look like you're in a good mood.
Show me your hand.
I'll show you.
Wow, there's a lot.
It looks like a meringue.
The lower and upper mouth are very good.
There were a lot earlier.
There's a lot again.
I'm asking when you're going to poop.
I've heard that it's good even
if you don't do it many times.
Is that so?
This stay?
I've heard that it's good even
if you don't do it many times.
That's great.
I want to poop.
It's okay.
It's so beautiful.
It's so pretty!
Isn't it great here?
You said you like shiny
places, so I came here.
It's so pretty!
How do you like this illumination?
It's so nice!
Do you like men who
take you to different places?
Yes, I do.
I like men who lead me.
Why do you want to be confessed to?
Confessed to?
You want me to do that?
Do you want it to be straight forward?
I want it to be straight forward.
I want it to be simple.
I want it to be something
like... I like you.
Please go out with me.
Do you want your partner to do it for you?
That's right.
I want to make him turn around.
I want to make him chase me.
I want to receive it.
What?
I had a lot of fun today
and I fell in love with you.
Will you go out with me?
What's your answer?
Of course!
It's dangerous.
I was surprised.
Do you put your arms
together when you go on a date?
Yes, I do.
How about this? I'll hold it.
Thank you.
That's good.
Like this.
Do you put your arms
together when you hold hands?
Yes, I do.
I like it.
That's good.
It's nice.
I can't stand it if you do this to me.
Is it good to come here on a date?
Yes, it's good. It's quiet.
It's calm now.
It's not noisy.
This atmosphere suits you.
Yes, it's good.
In a place like this,
secretly.
Here?
Here Here, here, here
Because there are people,
they will definitely find
out It's okay, it's okay.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
It's embarrassing I did it
It's embarrassing I did it.
Look at those two.
They are staring at us They are staring
at us Scary You seem to be envious of her.
Why don't you call one of them?
One of them?
I can't see them.
Here they are.
Thank you.
With both hands.
Wait, wait.
Someone is coming.
No, no, no.
I'm so envious.
If you go there, both
of us will notice you.
Both of us?
Yes.
I'll be there.
It's cute that the tip
of your nose is cold.
It's cold.
I'll be cold again.
That's great.
It's cold.
Do you like Korean food?
Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
This is marmalade, isn't it?
Don't you need the spicy one?
No, I don't.
Are you going to eat it as it is?
Yes, I'm going to eat it as it is.
Let's eat.
How is it?
It's delicious.
Do you want to eat it as it is?
Tuna and avocado go well together.
It's delicious.
It goes well with Korean seaweed.
It's good.
It's delicious.
What is this drink?
What are you drinking?
Grapefruit Sour.
There are many sour drinks.
There are many sour drinks I
don't drink beer and highball.
I drink Japanese
sake Japanese sake?
Soju?
This is Japanese
sake I don't like it
I have drunk it This is delicious
It's easy to drink, isn't it?
I can smell it.
It's easy to drink.
Thank you.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's still good.
It's a high level.
The beer is expensive.
Do you know the sake from Okinawa?
Yes.
Awamori.
I drank a lot of that as well.
It was easy to drink.
What kind of person do you like?
What do you mean?
I like a person who is
kind and drinks with me.
I see, so there are people who calm down.
Even if I don't say
anything, it's like air.
It's like air?
It's like air, but in a good way.
In a good way.
When I'm speechless, I
think about what to say.
If you're dating, it's
going to be like that.
What do you think?
You're pretty careful.
I wonder if I'll be careful at first.
What do you think about
this kind of sexiness in private?
In private?
While eating?
No, not at all.
What?
What did you say?
Nothing.
I don't know.
You don't know about that kind of world.
You are a little stupid.
I said I was a self-sufficient person.
No, no, no, no.
I get it.
Did you get it?
It's the opposite of what I said.
No, it's not like that at all.
It's kind of...
No.
I like this kind of thing.
But do you like to be blamed?
I like to dance, so I did
a neck-tightening check.
That's amazing.
I like it.
But I was beaten too much once.
I got a scar here.
It's like a menstrual cramp.
Yes, it's like a menstrual cramp.
I was in a hurry.
You're asking too much.
You should be more conscious.
Is that so?
What do you mean?
Because if you do too much,
you will lose consciousness.
Dangerous.
It's really dangerous.
So after that, I decided to quit.
It's hard to make a good plan.
I'm scared.
So it's an M.
I think it's a five-star type M.
I usually don't do that.
You don't do that?
You look good when you do that.
I think so.
I'll eat Ebiten.
It's good.
I don't know.
How many people have you dated?
I've dated only one
person the same age as me.
But I've dated someone
older than me for 3 days.
Have you?
I don't remember.
So you didn't have a lot
of respect for him, did you?
No, I didn't.
Because he was already dead?
Yeah, he wasn't a nice guy.
So you had a good relationship with
him, and then you had sex with him?
Yeah, I did.
Oh, I see.
So you had a good relationship with him.
It's a strange and memorable place.
What?
It's a memorable place.
A memorable place?
It's a strange place.
Yeah, it's memorable.
I wonder where it is.
I don't know.
But...
The one I dated before
and the one before the trip.
Before the trip?
What was it like?
What do you mean?
Before the trip,
it's normal to be in a hotel, right?
Is it normal to be in a hotel?
It's normal to record in a hotel.
I see.
But it's a different
environment than usual.
It's not at home.
It's in the country.
For example, I went to
a hot spring hotel there.
And I had sex in a private bath.
I've never done that.
Did you have sex in a private bath?
It's normal.
You are good at it.
I'm kidding.
It's different from the one
you eat in a restaurant.
I ate it when I was a student.
I didn't eat it in a restaurant.
I want to do this kind
of work in the future.
Is that what you want to do?
You've been doing it for
a long time, haven't you?
How long have you been doing it?
I've been doing it for 19 months this time.
You're a big veteran.
I don't know anything yet.
I've been doing it for a year and a half or more for about
a year and a half or more, so I'd like to do something
like this in the future, but there are still a lot of
things I haven't done yet, so I'd like to do it, but it's
I don't know much about it,
so I don't know what to do.
What I haven't done yet is...
If I know what I want to do, I
want to learn how to draw a picture.
I want to learn how to draw a picture.
And I want to learn how to draw a map.
So you're going to do it yourself, right?
Yes.
You don't have to learn
how to draw a picture.
You've already experienced a lot.
Do you have any plans to do
something you want to do in the future?
I want to do something.
It seems difficult.
But are you interested in it?
I'm interested in it.
I want to do various things.
I see.
And... I want you to do it.
Do you want me to do it?
Yes, please.
And...
It may not be a work at
all, but it's a flight binding.
It's amazing.
I want to do that.
Are you interested in that?
I saw a person who
made it art on Instagram.
It's art.
It's art, isn't it?
I thought, wow, it's going to be art.
The next day.
Okay.
King's room.
It's just a king's room, isn't it?
Oh, you're here.
Let's go.
Good evening.
Let's have a toast.
Can I have this?
This is champagne.
Champagne.
Let's open it.
Don't spill it.
It's okay.
I'll open it.
Thank you.
You didn't peel it.
I'll open it.
Don't turn your back.
I won't.
Wow.
Cheers!
Yu-chan, please drink this.
Let's toast.
Yu-chan, please shoot
the toasting temperature.
Let's toast to a fun night!
Is alcohol strong?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
I don't think it's strong.
You don't think it's weak.
Do you get a little sexy
when you get drunk?
What do you think?
I don't know.
Are you angry?
I don't enjoy it.
You don't enjoy it.
Yeah.
Wow, you're fast.
You can do it.
I have a dream.
A dream?
What is it?
I want a beautiful woman to kiss me.
A kiss?
Maybe your dream will come true today.
Really?
No way.
I don't think so.
I don't know if I can do it.
You can do it.
Can I do it?
Yes, you can.
How can I do it?
What are you doing?
I want you to kiss me.
What?
I don't want to spill it.
You can change your clothes.
You can put your head here.
Put your head here.
Can I make my dream come true?
That's good.
It's good, isn't it?
How is it?
Put it in your mouth.
It's quite a lot.
Yes.
It's a lot.
Ta-da!
I don't want to waste it.
It's good.
It's the best sake I've ever had.
I'm glad.
Thank you for the second time.
You're welcome.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to hear that.
What's up?
You look so stylish.
Your face is getting red.
Really?
You were embarrassed.
I don't care.
If you go on a date with such a
cute girl, you can die on that day.
What?
I'm going to die.
I'll die I'll die I'll die Then, can you
go on a date with me for a while?
A date for a while?
Can you go on a date with me for a while?
Wow, it's connected!
Yay!
Yuu-chan, look at this!
It's so pretty!
Isn't it a great night view?
The feet are completely different.
I made a reservation for you Oh, really?
Thank you I'll make you happy too I see.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Do you like this kind of person?
Yes, I do.
You're funny.
Don't make me say that.
I have two dreams now.
Really?
You said you would die
if your dream came true.
Today is your lucky day.
I'm so happy.
It's my birthday.
Thank you.
I have a dream, too.
What is it?
I want to give you a deep kiss.
You're not going to do it?
What?
I don't think I can.
You've done it before, haven't you?
No, I haven't.
I've only done it three times.
You have!
Me too.
Don't be nervous!
Was it the same dream?
Maybe... Let's play
rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors?
Rock-paper-scissors.
I'm going to kiss you on the lips.
I'm going to kiss you on the cheeks.
You're going to kiss me
on the bottom of my lips.
Oh, my God.
Are you excited to kiss me?
I'm excited.
Are you excited now?
Yes, I am.
Are you excited?
Be excited.
Can you put this on?
This?
We'll get excited if you wear that.
Show me how you wear it.
I want to see it.
Where can I buy this?
On the Internet.
You can buy it anywhere.
What do you think? Are you
excited to be seen with erotic eyes?
Yes.
Look at this.
Maybe it's a little wet.
What do you think?
I don't think so.
Isn't it too stylish?
No, no, no.
Do you usually wear that kind of underwear?
There are a lot of them.
Yes, there are a lot of them.
It's embarrassing, so don't look down.
From the top.
Later.
Oh, later.
Which one is which?
This way.
Don't come this way.
Oh my gosh.
It's too narrow.
It's hidden well.
It's amazing.
Look.
What? Is it a defective product?
It's not a defective product.
You can't see it, it's like this.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's not a defective product.
No, it's like that.
Oh, it's like that.
You can see it.
Oh, my God.
Don't take it off.
You're used to it, right?
Let me wear it.
Don't be mean to me.
Are you going to wear it from above?
Can you do it?
No, I can't.
I can see it.
No, you can't.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Yuu-chan.
I can't see it.
I'll do it.
Wow, it's so high-waisted.
Su-chan, it's the other way around.
What? The other way around?
Wait a minute.
No way.
No.
It's right there.
Really?
Wait a minute.
It's too high.
Are you kidding me?
No, I'm not kidding.
I saw it on the Internet.
Really?
Wait a minute.
I can't open my eyes.
It's good.
What's behind you?
What's that?
It's cold.
What is this?
This is oil.
This is amazing.
I want to eat this.
Can I do this, too?
Oh, no! It's transparent!
Wait a minute!
It's a little erotic, isn't it?
I can't see it.
Look!
Oh, no!
I think she's feeling it.
Oh, no! It's transparent!
I can see everything.
Do you want me to go this way?
No, no, no.
Don't run away.
Wait a minute.
It's too high.
Does it feel good to rub your neck?
Yes, it feels good.
Really?
Look at me.
What do you want?
You're drunk.
You can do whatever you want.
What do you want?
Everything.
Everything?
Look at you, Hajime.
Wait a minute.
Isn't this too much?
Isn't it too much?
No, no, no.
It's more beautiful than the
night view I saw on the Sky Tree.
It's more beautiful than the night view I
saw on the Sky Tree on Christmas Eve.
Hajime, I want to lick you.
I want to lick you.
What should I do?
I'm going to put you on my lap, okay?
No, I don't want to.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to touch you.
You're not going to leave, are you?
I'm going to leave.
Really?
It feels good.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
He's been raised.
He's sweet.
He's healthy.
Which do you like, inside or outside?
I like both.
He's a boy on the second floor.
You are in a good condition.
It feels good.
No, no, no, no!
You are in a good condition.
I'm going to die.
Your back is shaking.
Show me your belly.
Wow, amazing.
It's embarrassing.
I can't see anything.
It feels good.
How about here?
No, no, no.
I am glad she is okay now.
This is so good.
Do you want to be licked again?
I want to be licked.
It's sweet and salty.
It feels good.
How is it?
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
I'm going to die.
Wow.
You are getting better.
Let's do more.
Let's do many things.
Wow.
It's getting harder.
It feels good.
Ahh!
Ahh! It's so nice.
It feels so good.
Ahh!
It's so nice.
It's so good.
It's good, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Wow.
Hey, you should drink this glass.
Yeah.
Oh... Oh, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
I want you to forgive me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Look at me.
You are cute.
I was looking at your eyes.
I'm going to rub your belly.
Is it hard?
It feels good.
It's warm.
I'm going to rub your belly.
I can't do it anymore.
Give me your hand.
I want you to put it in your mouth.
Do you really want me
to put it in your mouth?
It's okay.
Look at this.
I'm going to take a bath.
You are wet.
I'm here, mom!
I'm here!
I can't drink it.
It's disgusting.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
I'm going.
It feels good.
What?
No!
I'm going!
Stop it.
Ah! Ah!!
Your back hurts?
Yes, my back hurts.
Ah, it feels warm!
Whoa, whoa.
Ah, ah, ah, it feels good, ah, I can do it.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I can do it, I can do it.
Ah! It hurts, it hurts.
Ah! Ah!
It looks like you're completely all right.
This side.
Open your eyes and look around.
I'm going to put this on you.
It feels so good.
I'm going to give you a hand.
Uuuuuggghhh Uuuuuuuuuuuugggghhhh
Uuuuuuuuugggghhhh Uuuuugggghhhh
Ah, I can't take this anymore
This feels so good Uuuuuggghhhh.
No no no Uuuuuugggghhhh
I'm gonna throw up Ah, no!
I'm gonna go.
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu I'm sorry.
She has a lot of dung.
Look at this.
Do you want me to rub your back?
I'm going to put a bandage on your back.
Does it hurt?
It feels so good.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow. It feels good.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's hot.
It's tickling.
Do you want me to do it for you?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Don't worry about it.
Show me your sexy back.
Like this?
It's not good.
I'm going to sleep.
It's Aty.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Your waist is moving.
It's moving.
I'm going to fall.
You can put it on your head.
It feels so good.
It's so warm.
No, no, no.
It hurts.
Eek!
I can't do this anymore!
No, I can't.
Eek!
Let me do it again.
It's scary.
It's okay.
I'll do it for now.
It's hard.
Like this?
It's scary.
It hurts.
You are so cute.
I feel so good.
You are going to sleep soon.
I can't take it anymore.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
It feels so good.
How is your mental state?
What should I do?
You want it?
I want you to put it out.
Like this?
Yes, like this.
Put it out.
Oh, it's coming out.
Can you see it?
It's warm.
I'm relieved.
I'm here again.
Look at the bottom of your mouth.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
It feels good there.
It's scary.
I'm going to fall.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to die.
Stay there.
Please be careful not
to hurt your baby's ears.
Please do not force the baby.
You just have to play with the baby.
What?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Come here.
Oh, I feel good.
Oh, it feels so good!
Oh, no.
Oh, it feels good.
Please let me out.
Oh, no.
You are very close to him.
He is licking you.
Don't be so serious.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It's so warm.
It feels good.
I'm crying.
I'm sorry.
You are in pain.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean your wound.
Can I put you on the bed again?
Yes.
Ah!
It feels so good!
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
You're crying a lot.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
It's so good that it
makes my heart feel good.
Can you close your eyes?
You can sleep in a cosy bed.
It's so good.
I touched her and she began to crie.
Your back is benign.
It's so warm.
Wow, it's so warm.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
It feels good!
Here?
I'm going to give you a big pat on
the back and you're going to let me go.
This side is not hard.
Yeah, it's really hard.
Do you want me to let you go?
Yeah.
Give me a lot.
Oh, shit.
Are you okay?
AH~~~
Zzzzzzzzzz.
ah AH~~~~
AH~~~~.
ahh ah, feels good.
AH~~.
ah ah ah Ahhhh.
Ahhhh.
Ahhhh Does it feel good?
It feels really good Ahhhh.
Ahhhh.
Ahhhh Ahhhh Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Oh, it's nice.
Yeah.
Kengo-chan, can I get you a drink?
Yes, please.
I'll kill you!
No!
Please stop it!
I'll kill you!
Let me see your stomach.
Ouch!
It was good, wasn't it?
Yes, it was good.
It was really good.
Can I mix it?
Oh my….
This is sake.
Do you drink sake from Nakadashi?
I'm enjoying it.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Look at the sweat.
Touch it.
Do you know how old you are?
I don't know. I don't remember.
It feels good.
Good job.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry, I was sleeping.
What?
I'm doing something naughty.
Look at me.
Yes.
Is it okay?
Just a little.
You're so mean.
I'm sorry.
I'm sick of this weird sound.
In the meantime, I'm getting
more and more sick of it.
Yui-chan, you're wet.
Why are you so wet?
You're so cute.
I think you need more love.
It tastes like a monkey.
It's delicious, isn't it?
You like it, don't you?
Can you see the camera?
Is it delicious?
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, it's still in there.
Lick it, lick it.
Can I lick it too?
I licked it yesterday.
Shake it a lot.
Are you hungry?
I'm fine.
I'm going to feed you a lot.
Help me.
You're so erotic.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
Let me see your face.
What's wrong with your face?
Let me clean your neck.
It feels good.
Your neck is stiff.
Look at me.
I'm going to put a bandage on your wound.
Do you want to put a bandage on it?
Does it feel good?
What?
Do you want to kiss me?
You don't want to?
Then I'll kiss you.
You two are romantic, aren't you?
You're so kind, Yuki-chan.
It's getting really hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Slippery feet.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed.
You're wet.
I feel good.
Turn your back.
Look at this.
Wow.
This fluffy fur is so cute.
This.
Isn't it comfortable?
Yes, it is.
I can't wait to see your butt.
I'll take this off.
Wow.
You have a nasty butt.
It's getting really hot.
How do you feel when I touch you like this?
It feels good.
I only touched you a little.
I'm going to go.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good to be patted?
It feels good.
I can't do it.
Let's go.
Haru-kun.
Why?
Can you open it yourself?
By myself?
Yes.
Yes, you are.
You look so cool.
Let me see your belly.
Let me see your belly more
Let me see your belly more.
You look so cool.
You are so erotic.
Ah...
Hmm...
Ah... Ah... It's so good.
It's so warm.
Wow.
Ah... Ah... It feels so good.
Ah... It feels so good.
Ah... Ah... Hmm...
Wow No No pega You should eat
more Oh, no Pero-no Stinky Eek.
Ah.
Oh.
Ah no Oh You ate it You did.
Oh Ahhh Ahhh Oh Ah No Don't.
No Ah No Eek
Eek.
Ahhhhh.
Ahhh Ahhhh Ahhhh Ahhh
It feels so good It's so warm.
Ahhhh Let's get out of here.
Ahhhh Ahhh Ahhhh.
This feels so good
It feels so good!
Oh no, it's going away.
It's going away.
It feels so good.
It's so soft!
It feels so good!
I can't take it anymore!
Good girl.
I can't get used to it.
Let's go.
It feels good.
Good girl.
Ahhhhhh!
Ahh!
Are you okay?
It feels great!
You're so grumpy!
Ahh!
Come here!
Do you want to lick me?
Ahh!
Can I lick you?
Yeah, lick me.
You want to talk, don't you?
Yes, I want to talk a lot.
Even if I make you sad.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
What do you think?
Is it good?
Yeah, it's good.
Oh, wow.
Are you trying to eat it?
Don't try to eat
it No, you can't.
You can't do that.
She is serious.
Do you like my nipple?
Yes, I do.
Then, I'll lick it a lot.
Do you want to look at the camera?
Yes.
You are so cute.
Here is your tongue.
As expected, Mamedaifuku
is very good at sucking.
Ah, that feels good.
You are good.
As expected, I'm surprised.
I'm touching your neck.
My neck feels good.
I'm sucking.
Good boy.
Wait a minute.
You are a good boy.
Oh!!
What is this?
It's good!
Oh!
This is the best one I've ever had.
It's hot!
It's hot.
You are slurping.
You don't have a good look.
That's right.
It hurts.
It's in my neck.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's so good...
Oh no
up...up!
Built it up.
no no no no no no no no no
Up!
Up...
Ah!
The chin is dirty.
Wow, that's great.
Wow!
Let's pour a little more.
Wow.
Oh!
Is it good?
Oh, it's good.
Oh!
Wow!
It's great.
Oh, great.
Wow!
Good girl, good girl.
Ah!
Take a deep breath.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Take a deep breath.
Yes.
Ah!
It's ticklish.
Ah! It's very warm.
Yes.
Ah!
Don't you need to put on the gloves?
No, I don't need to.
Why?
I like it fresh.
Yes.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's warm.
Do you want it?
I'm going to put it in.
It's warm.
You can put it in.
It feels good.
It's warm.
Ah...
Ah... Ah, it feels good!
It feels good... You can
lie down comfortably.
Ah...
Wow, you are going all the way in.
Hmmm.
Ah... How is it?
Ah, it hurts!
What?
It's not good.
It's going to be pulled out.
Hmm... I can't pull it out.
Good, good.
Look at the camera.
Show me your hand.
It hurts.
It's tight.
Show me your hand.
Like this?
I can't breathe.
Let me help you It feels
so good Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Oh, no.
I can't go there.
I'm going.
You look great, Yuka!
It feels so good!
I can feel you are wiggling.
Are you feeling good?
I feel so good!
It's warm!
I can't do it!
You can't?
I can't!
Wow!
Oh!
It feels good!
Oh! No!
E-chan!
Oh!
It feels good!
Please turn your back.
Turn my back?
Yes, please turn your back.
Wait a minute.
I'm sweating.
Why are you so excited?
You're right.
It feels so good.
You're growling a lot.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
You're growling a lot.
Oh, no! I'm going to fall again.
Oh, it feels good.
Let's go.
You are so tense.
It feels good.
It's so hard.
You like the bag, don't you?
I love the bag.
You are so naughty.
You are so naughty to
stick out your buttocks.
I'm going to go inside.
OK.
Are you OK?
I want you to stick
out your buttocks a lot.
Oh, no.
I feel sick.
Ahhhh!
I feel so good!
Ahhh!
Ahhhh!
Hmmm!
I feel sooo gooood!
Ahhh!
Ahhhh!
Yes.
Your mouth is about to tear.
Ah!
It feels good!
It's amazing.
Ah!
It feels good!
Wow!
I'll give you a lot of it.
I'll give you a lot.
Oh, my God.
It's disgusting.
I'll give you a lot of it.
I'm going to take it out.
Wow, it's really deep.
It's gone.
Can I really take it out?
Can I?
Yes, you can.
What should I take out?
I want you to take out a lot inside.
I want you to kiss me.
I'll give you a kiss.
Oh my god Wait a
minute It feels good.
Oh my gosh... I'm
gonna take it out.
Here we go.
Oh my gosh... I'm so hot!
It's cold.
Oh my gosh...
Wow, it's dripping.
Yui-chan, it really came out.
Did it come out?
Yes.
How is it?
It was really hot.
Wow.
Come here.
Can you lick it?
Yes.
The baby is crying.
I'm sorry for you.
Look at the camera.
I'm sorry.
Can I do a little more?
Are you okay?
Can I look at you again?
Is that okay?
It's a little tight.
Are you okay?
I'm breathing.
It feels good.
Hold her legs.
It feels so good.
What is it?
It's still hard.
It's really hard.
Are you okay?
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Mmm.
Chu.
Ah.
Mmm.
I'm so happy.
I feel so good.
I'm getting a lot of pus.
Please let me out a lot.
Give me a lot of money, please.
I'll give you a lot of money.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
How do you feel?
Oh, no.
It feels good.
I'm so happy.
I'll hold you and take you out.
I'll take you out.
I'm going to take you out.
Look at me.
I feel good.
I'm going to take it out.
I'm going to take it out a lot.
Oh, my God.
I love you.
Can I take a peek?
Look up.
Do you want to look at this side?
You look unpleasant.
Are you okay? You have a lot on your face.
I'm fine.
I'm glad you feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you want me to clean your mouth again?
Yes.
Please be careful.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Did you feel good?
Yes, I did.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
You should take a break.
Good morning.
I'm in the hotel now.
Everyone is here.
Good morning.
Today, I'm going to do this Pico
Pico Hammer while I'm in bed.
I'm going to do rock-paper-scissors.
Are you sure?
I'm serious.
Have you ever done this before?
No, I haven't.
I've seen it before.
Do you know how to do it?
I know how to do it.
I see.
If I win, I'll hit you.
If I lose, I'll cover you with a net.
I'll protect you.
I see.
Can I win with rock-paper-scissors?
Yes, you can.
You can win with a net.
I see.
I should have done it with a net.
Nice to meet you.
Is rock-paper-scissors strong?
Rock-paper-scissors is very strong.
Oh, really?
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
If you lose, you have to do this.
If you win, you have to do this.
Let's get started.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, no!
You're acting like an adult.
No, I'm not an adult.
You're not an adult.
Wasn't there a key?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Let's do it seriously this time.
I can't do it.
It's not fair to be an adult.
You can shout.
OK.
Rock-paper-scissors!
That was dangerous.
It was the other way around.
I'm sorry.
I'll protect you.
You are weak.
You were so energetic.
So fast!
This is hard.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Out!
So fast!
What should I do?
One win?
You do this after the game is over, right?
Yes, after the game is over.
Please!
I'll win this time.
I won once.
We are connected.
Thank you.
1,2,3
Rock-paper-scissors!
Wait!
1,2,3
Rock-paper-scissors!
I lost.
Let's do the punishment game.
What is this?
I recorded it.
Yu-chan said it.
I'm lonely.
There are people who lost.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
I'll do it.
It hurts!
It hurts, doesn't it?
It's so numb.
It's tingling.
It's tingling, isn't it?
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
You got angry, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I had a lot of fun.
I haven't cut my hair yet.
I wanted you to fix your hair.
We have a gift for you.
A gift?
Oh, yeah.
What did you say?
China or maid?
You want to wear one of them.
You want to wear it, right?
I want to wear it.
Do you have one?
I have one in the bathroom.
I see.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
Which one?
Do you have one?
I want you to change your clothes.
I see.
I'm going.
We're waiting for you.
I'm going back.
I'm looking forward to it,
so please leave it there.
Oh, is that okay?
I'll go.
Oh, it's done.
It's done.
Wow, it's really close.
How is it?
Wow, it looks great on you.
Really?
How about the back?
I want you to say,
What do you think of
the scene where you say,
There are four of us.
You wanted to come to the park, didn't you?
Yes.
The number of people is increasing.
Is it increasing?
Kinosene?
It's Kinosene.
I made a mistake.
It's the fastest.
It's too fast.
It really looks good on you.
You don't have a husband, do you?
No.
But you have four children.
I have a lot.
The cat's mood has changed.
The cat is a sexy maid.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
Please lick my boobs.
It feels good.
Oh.
Oh, I feel good.
I feel good.
I will do whatever you say.
It's okay, it's okay, reach out your hand.
It's effective, isn't it?
What is that?
It looks good on you.
It doesn't move.
Raise your hand.
You can use your hands now.
You're so beautiful.
You're smiling.
You shouldn't smile.
Look at this.
I'm going to feed you.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Don't laugh.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Open your eyes and look at me.
Look at me.
Show me your butt.
That's a good butt.
What's wrong with you?
It's difficult.
You shouldn't say such a thing.
I'm sorry.
I'll punish you.
Hey!
Please pat my butt more.
I will bully you with this.
It feels good.
What is it?
She's so excited.
No, no, no.
She's going to go.
Hang in there.
No, no.
She can't protect her husband.
It feels good.
She's going to go.
I'm going to cry.
No, no, no.
I'm going.
She's gone.
She's not saying, go, go.
This is a more embarrassing school.
I'm going to give you a little more.
I'll make you feel embarrassed.
I'll make you smile more.
I can't do it anymore!
Ah, it feels so good!
Ah, this feels good!
I can't do it anymore!
I'm going to die!
I'm going!
Don't stop.
I can't.
You haven't opened it yet.
Open it.
Oh!
It's so wet.
I can't.
You are a very sexy maid.
You are very wet.
I don't like it.
Do you want me to take it off?
You want me to take it off, right?
How do you feel?
I don't like it.
Take it off.
Where are you touching right now?
It feels so good.
You are doing the best you can.
Not yet!
No, not yet!
You are such a naughty girl.
I have to give you a massage.
What do you like?
It feels good.
Oh, it's painful.
It hurts.
It's painful.
I can't.
I'm going!
Who told you go like that?
I'm sorry.
Chikubi, come on.
Oh, it feels good.
Chikubi is happy to be petted.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, it's hot.
Awwww Look, look,
he is trying to lick you.
Awwww, feels good!
Awwww.
Awwww No!
Awwww, feels good!
Awwww Awwww Awwww.
No! No!
No! He is going!
Let's go.
Who said you want to go?
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Let's eat dirty food.
I'm sorry.
She licked it.
You should clean up the dirty part.
What does it taste like?
It tastes like a poop.
What?
Poop?
Yes.
Oh, my.
You are so cute.
I'm going to clean your
buttocks and buttocks.
You are grumbling.
I'm going to clean your
buttocks and buttocks.
I'm scared.
Come on.
You're going to be okay.
I'm scared.
Come on.
It hurts.
You can't do that.
You still have a little bit.
Do you want to lick?
Yes, I want to lick.
Let me lick you.
You have to lick yourself.
It's not just one baby.
There are so many of them.
Look at me and lick me.
Look at me.
You are a good boy.
I'm sorry.
You can't eat half of it.
You can eat the other half.
He seems to be in a good mood.
Look at this.
I think it's enough.
What are you eating?
It's hot.
No, no, no.
Oh, Himawari.
No!
No no no!
Oh, you need to pat him on the back.
He is pushing out his ass.
Look, he is putting his hands on your back.
Be careful.
He is trying to suck you.
You have a scar on your face.
Now, it's your turn.
It feels so good.
You wet your face.
This way?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Ok, I will do it.
No, no.
I'm going.
Ok, this way.
Turn around.
You're not going to cry, are you?
Licking his arms.
Would you please lick a lot, Yo-ran.
Look at this side.
Open your eyes.
Please punish me.
I'm going to put a lot
of candy in your hat.
What are you going to do with this candy?
Please put a lot of candy in my hat.
Do you like candy?
Yes.
It's warm.
Let's go to the master.
It feels good.
Make a louder voice.
I'm going.
You can't go yet.
You can do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
You can do it.
Let's do the other side.
It feels so good.
Open your legs a little bit.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Good boy!
Ouch!
I'll tell the people around
you that you're in the room.
I'm in the room.
It's warm.
That is the best!
Ahh... feels so good!
Feels good?
Nice!
It feels so good!
I'll make you feel better!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Leave me alone!
I want to go there.
It's gross.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's go, let's go.
It's in.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Ah, it feels so good.
No, no, no.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I'm going. I'm going.
I'm going.
I'm going to take you to the bathroom.
You're already full.
Do you want to live with me?
Please wait.
Let's go to the master.
Yes, sir.
Oh, it feels good.
I feel so good.
You should get some rest.
Really?
Yes.
I feel so good.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's go.
Hang in there.
It's going to hurt.
It's okay.
It feels good.
Don't leave me alone.
E-chan!
Go away!
Don't leave me alone.
I'm so happy.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
25, 30, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50,
51, 52, 53, 4, 3, 2, 1 woooow!
Feels so good!
I feel so good.
Do you feel so good?
There you go.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to massage more?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
Does it hurt a lot?
No.
I want to hug you.
I can't help but feel good.
I want to hug you a lot.
Really?
Oh, I'm so tired.
I'll clean your ears.
It feels so good!
Ohhhh.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa...
Ahhh you feel good!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaa Don't let it go!
Ahh you feel good!
I feel so good!
Do you feel good?
I want to get out of here.
I can't breathe...
I can't breathe... I can't
breathe... Oh my god...
I'm sorry.
You are here.
I can't believe you are here.
You are cleaning your nose.
I'll help you.
It feels good.
Ahhhhhhh Feels so good.
Ah, feels good
Ahhhh, it's no good.
Feels good Ahhhhhhhhh No, no, no
It's okay, it's okay Ah, no, no Ahhhhhhhh.
Wow Good boy, good boy Feels
good I'm going to put it in your mouth.
It feels so good.
Please let it out a lot.
Please let it out a lot inside.
Oh, it's cold.
Ahh... I'll give you water.
Ahh...
Ahh... Ahh... I feel so good.
Ahh... Ahh... Ahh... Ahh...
Ahh... Ahh... I'll hold
you for a moment.
Let me take this off.
I'll take this off.
Look, look, look, look.
Look, look, look.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
No, no, no.
It's getting better.
It feels good.
Can I lick you?
Please lick me a lot.
I'm going to lick you.
I'm going to lick the back of your legs.
Ahh….
Ahh… Ahh….
Koshi-San, you should
get rid of that sheet.
Ahh… Good girl.
Ahh…
Ahh… Ahh….
Ahh….
Ahh… Ahh… Ah...
It feels so good.
Ah... Ah, my nose.
I can't do this anymore.
It hurts.
Oh, my.
She has her butt and
front paws outstretched.
Oh, my.
Oh, my. She is crying.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Oh, my. She is going to sleep.
Ouch!
It feels so good!
OK.
It got a lot better.
ining...
Feels good.
Here?
Yes, it feels good.
I can't do it.
It feels good.
Ahhhh.
It feels good, right?
Oh!
It's hot Yeah, it's hot Oh!
What should I do?
Now you're going to hug me like that.
I'm going to hug you.
It feels good.
Hey, what are you doing?
Please give me a lot of money.
Are you ready?
Ouch!
It's hot.
I'm so tired.
Give me a kiss.
I'm Yuu.
Yuu channel.
I can see you!
Yeah!
Hello.
I'm Ruka Ayu.
Today,
I'm going to try an
interesting project.
I'm going to try it.
What are you into these days?
Do you have a favorite food?
I'm into Sushi right now.
I ate it yesterday, today, and tomorrow.
My favorite food is Japanese
sea bream, Negitoro, and Torotaku.
Today's video is a video using this.
Do you know what this is?
It's a wrap.
Today, I'm going to wrap
this wrap around my body
and see how much I
can get rid of my nipples.
I'm going to start wrapping
the wrap around my body.
I'm going to take it off.
How is it, pink?
Isn't it fresh?
I'm going to take it off.
I took it off.
It's done.
I'm going to roll it.
Oh, no. It's stuck.
OK.
How long do you think I can roll it?
This is the third round.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm being ignored.
I forgot how many laps I did.
I'm counting.
I've been hiding a lot.
How is it?
Can you see it? It's hidden, isn't it?
Then, I'm going to peel it off from here.
I'd like to see how long
it will take to make it.
Can you hear this?
Oh, I did it.
I'm going to start.
The first round.
The second round.
I haven't done it yet.
The third round.
The fourth round.
5th week.
Are you okay?
You look fine.
5th week.
Oh, it's broken.
I don't know where it is.
Wait a minute.
What?
Oh, I found it.
I can't find it.
I'll go get it.
I'm back.
Excuse me.
Let's continue.
I'll do my best.
How many weeks has it been?
6 weeks?
It's been 6 weeks, right?
How do I look?
Is it transparent?
Can you see?
Is it still okay?
I think it's almost transparent.
I'm going to take it off.
It's getting really hot.
I feel like I'm being watched.
It's good.
I feel like summer is almost over.
I feel edgy.
I'm getting hot.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it feels so good.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry that I feel good on my own.
Thank you for watching until the end.
If you like this video,
please subscribe and like it.
See you in the next video.
Bye.