I remember a little while ago.
I remember when I was with my
childhood friend whom I loved so much.
He was a joker, a
playboy, but a kind person.
At that time, I couldn't
say I loved him honestly.
He seemed close, but he was far away.
As time went by, another hot season came.
I'm home!
You're so cute!
It was the last summer vacation of my
college life, so I came back to my hometown.
After graduating from high
school, I studied abroad.
I still have a bit of
self-deprecation left in me.
While I was studying, I
couldn't go back to my
hometown because I was
too busy with my research.
But there are other reasons
why I couldn't go back.
It's because I have
a younger childhood
friend, Mai, who is two
years younger than me.
So, what's the story?
Well...
I haven't told you yet, but... What? I
said I wouldn't hang out with Masumi.
Oh, I see.
What do you mean, I see?
Oh...
Well...
Do you like me?
What?
What are you talking about?
What? What's wrong?
That's enough. I don't like you.
You don't understand how I feel at all.
Hey.
I wanted to tell Mai how I felt
before I went to study abroad.
I was embarrassed, so I
wrote only my feelings in a letter.
I hesitated to give her the letter.
I couldn't chase Mai.
I couldn't say anything to Mai, and I
left Japan without saying anything to Mai.
Because of the light, Mai
looked a little more mature.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Why are you in my house?
I came to deliver vegetables to Mr. Ikumi.
Then he told me that Sakuni was there.
I see.
Saku-nii, you're still as sleepy as ever.
You've been calling girls by their names.
Like Michiko.
Huh? Who's Michiko?
I'm just kidding.
You don't change when you get serious.
Don't come here again.
By the way, you're going
to get a job in Tokyo.
Oh, I knew that.
Of course you did.
I know. The only thing that
matters is that you're smart.
What's that?
What are you doing now? What about school?
I can't go to school. You know I'm poor.
I'm sorry.
I wanted you to tell me that
you're going to study abroad.
It was a long time ago, wasn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
But it's all right. It's all in the past.
You know, the atmosphere
has changed, hasn't it?
How should I put it?
I don't know.
I've grown up, too.
In a place where I don't know Sakuni.
No, it's nothing.
No, I haven't.
What did you put away?
Nothing.
I've always loved you.
I put away the letter I wanted to give you.
I wanted to tell you that I love you.
Sakuni, what's wrong?
Why all of a sudden?
Mai.
I like you.
I couldn't tell you.
Never mind.
Let me do it.
Let me see your ear.
Does it look good?
I wanted to do this.
I'm sorry.
Show me more.
I'm embarrassed to see you like that.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Ah, it's so hot.
Ah, I can't. I'm going to go again.
I can't go there.
You're sweating a lot.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Are you okay?
I want to do it again.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I like you.
Thank you.
I'll be here until the 5th of August.
Can I see you during that time?
The 5th?
Yeah.
Do you have anything planned for the 5th?
No, nothing.
What do you think?
Well, if it's just a little...
I'll see you tomorrow.
Time stopped.
But Mayu didn't know if she liked me.
Let's eat.
It's good.
Is it cold?
It's been a while.
How many years has it been
since I ate watermelon with Saku-nii?
It's been a long time.
It's delicious.
Hey, Saku-nii.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's slimy.
Which part is the most pleasant?
I don't know.
Next, Asakura-kun,
please sleep on this bed.
I'm nervous.
I'll pour it for you.
What's wrong?
No, no, no.
It's going to spill.
Can you open your eyes?
Not yet.
I can't stand it.
I'm nervous.
Not yet?
Not yet.
Hang in there.
It was heavy.
Are you ready?
Can I take it out?
No, not yet.
Why?
It's going to burst.
Can I?
I'm going to throw up.
Not yet.
Hang in there.
Does it feel good?
What about this time?
I want to take it out.
I can't.
Do you want to take it out?
I want to take it out.
It can't be helped.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I want you to do it with your mouth.
With my mouth?
I'm about to throw up.
I'm really going to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
I feel like I'm going back
to the old days a little bit.
I wonder if that's the case.
What kind of place is it?
I don't know.
Oh, you smile a lot.
What's that?
I know. You don't have an umbrella today.
What should I do?
It's fine.
Aren't you going out?
No, I'm fine.
I'll go home today.
I'll text you later.
Oh, okay. I'll text you later.
No, it's okay. I'll text you later.
What were you doing so late at night?
I'm sorry.
You didn't answer my question.
No, I didn't.
I asked you what you were doing.
I was making tea at my friend's house.
You're so bad at lying that it's funny.
Hey, do you think it's okay to be silent?
I'm sorry.
No, I'm not.
I'm so sick of you.
To be honest,
if I told you that I had
sex with my ex-girlfriend,
I would forgive you.
Right?
Why do you say that?
You know, You know, the
countryside is a narrow world.
That's why I hate animals
that act without thinking.
Hey, there's a wedding coming
up the day after tomorrow.
From now on, you're going to
be the rightful heir to the throne.
Think about what you
lack and act accordingly.
You're trying to be my wife.
That's unresistive.
You're a fool.
If I get serious,
I can crush you easily.
I'm sorry.
I won't do that again.
So please don't do anything to Sakurini.
Don't hurt the one you love.
Please. I'll do anything.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
Follow me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hurry up and get up.
Hey.
I'll show you exactly how to do it.
Mai.
I'll show you how to do it.
One is what your face likes.
What do you think the other one is?
That's...
Erosion.
You know...
You've been screaming in your
heart that you want to have sex.
That's right.
She's a woman who sleeps
with another man right away.
Hey, do something.
You said you didn't
want to be in love with me.
You keep saying you don't want to do it,
but you're making Maoko mad, aren't you?
That's the proof.
Let's do it.
The sex you like.
Show me your tongue.
Show me more.
Look at me.
If you don't feel good,
You have to say it feels good.
I don't care what happens
to your beloved brother.
You really want to make a sound, don't you?
Have you ever done such
a nasty look in front of him?
How is it?
No, I don't.
I see.
You don't have it.
Then I'll make you feel
good until you scream.
No, you can't.
You're trying to sleep
on your own, aren't you?
No, you can't.
Hey, you want me to
let you live, don't you?
Please.
Let me live.
More.
Please let me go.
More!
You're the one who said that.
I'm fine.
Go.
You are crazy.
It hurts.
You don't have to cry anymore.
What's wrong with you?
No, no.
Do you like being licked?
She likes being licked.
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of it.
I'm going to give it to you.
You like this, don't you?
Don't let go of it.
I'll lick yours, so lick mine.
Can you do it?
Open your eyes.
I'm going to put you in here.
I want you to put me in here.
Don't do it, please.
I love you so much.
If you can't say it, beg me more.
Don't do it, please.
You don't want to have sex, do you?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh.
You're so big.
I'll show you.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh Ahhhhhhhhh
Come on, pull yourself up.
Next, the other side.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Shout more.
It feels good.
You like to be hit like this, don't you?
It's an animal, so walk like an animal.
Who the hell are you?
Akira-San.
Who?
That's right.
Akira-San.
Ah...
Come on, scream more.
I can't... I can't.
Ah...
Is Sakuni here?
Oh, what are you doing in my room?
What are you doing there?
Come on, get up.
Stay where you are. Don't look this way.
What's wrong?
I can't see Saku-nii anymore.
From now on.
What's wrong?
Why all of a sudden?
I've been keeping it from you.
What?
I'm going to marry Akira Saionji.
I'm sorry, Sakuni.
I was happy to see you after a long time.
I wish I could see you earlier.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep up with her.
I couldn't help it.
I hadn't grown up since then.
Why are you getting ready to go home?
What are you talking about?
It's Mai's wedding, isn't it?
Yes, it seems so.
What are you talking about?
I have nothing to do with it.
I'm glad I got married to a rich man.
What are you talking about?
Look at this.
What's this?
Go.
Look at you. You like Mai-chan, don't you?
Why do I have to listen to my mom?
You left her behind when she was a student.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It doesn't matter. It's over.
How long are you going to be a kid?
What do you want to do?
Why don't you try to be hot
for someone else like a fool?
Come on, go ahead.
Well, it's just a rumor,
but Mai-chan's house
is in trouble with a
lot of money, isn't it?
There is a rumor that Mai tries to make her
parents happy and refuses to get married.
Come with me Come with me.
Come with me.
Remaining snow is shimmering.
This is the first time I've
heard of it, so I'm not sure if
it's a good thing or a bad
thing, but I think it's a good thing.
I don't know if it's a good thing or a
bad thing, but I think it's a good thing.
I don't know what to do with my life.
Mai!
Oh, this is Saku from Hirajima.
What happened to your club? Go home.
Hey, you guys!
I'm here to save Mai.
From this stupid wedding.
I love you.
Cut it out!
Who the hell are you?
Come here, Mai.
I won't run away anymore.
I love you.
I want to be with you.
You're really beautiful.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Mai, wait.
You don't have to get married.
Don't worry about us.
Mai, marriage is not for someone.
It's for yourself. For your own happiness.
What are you talking about?
Mai, tell me the truth.
I've always loved you. I still love you.
You're the best in the world.
I won't lie anymore.
I'll be honest with myself.
Me too.
I love you from the bottom of my heart.
That's funny.
That's a good one, Mai.
Don't make it easy for me to listen to you.
Are you against me?
Don't you have a human mind?
You're like an animal.
I won't listen to your orders anymore.
Let go of this dirty hand.
You!
Shut up!
I'll decide my own life.
I've already decided.
Mai, come here. Hurry up.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and get the ice cream.
Yes, sir.
I...
Hurry up and put it in.
I don't want to use a cup.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to give me a kiss.
Is it delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
I want that one, too.
It's good.
I'll give it to you.
Put it in your mouth.
Can you eat it?
I want you to eat it.
I want you to sleep.
Please give me a warm hug.
I want to do it more.
I can't do it anymore.
I want to go home.
What is your favorite food?
I like Sushi.
Thank you for your hard work.
What is this?
I also have alcohol.
You can eat and drink whatever you like.
Yes.
What is your favorite food?
My favorite food is... I like
tomatoes the most in the world.
But I ate too much.
If I ate like every day,
I would have a heart attack.
Yes.
I thought you liked it, so I bought a lot.
I've been waiting for this.
Almond.
I'll have this.
Can I really drink this?
Of course.
I'm sorry. I'm drinking alone.
Cheers.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's delicious.
It's been a while since I drank this.
If you don't mind, I'd like you to eat
your favorite sweets and desserts.
Cororo.
What is this?
I'm sorry, I forgot to explain.
There is an instruction on the back, and if
you do it, you can eat anything you like.
I see.
Can I eat this?
It's safe, so please.
I'll eat it.
I like corn the most in Gumi.
It's like this.
It's good.
What should I do with this?
I can't decide because there are too many.
What should I do?
This?
What are you writing?
It's a phone call.
If you do that, you can eat it.
Excuse me.
You can eat what you like.
This crab?
Of course.
I prepared a lot of rewards for you.
I want to eat it, so I want to choose it.
I'm nervous.
What should I do?
This is it.
It's a toy.
Isn't it strong?
Ah, wait.
The back is dangerous.
I was hit for the first time.
Which one should I choose?
This one.
I'm going to paint one piece of clothing.
I have a sore neck.
I'm embarrassed.
Do you like sweets?
I eat a lot, but I don't
have any new sweets.
I eat everything.
Is it delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
The cream is delicious.
I'm sorry, I can't say it.
It's still moving.
Dango.
It's cool.
It's a rotor!
It was a rotor.
Thank you very much.
Double?
You can eat it.
Mai-San, there are still a lot.
I couldn't eat at all.
Are you done?
What should I do?
It's all right.