Is it recording?
Wow, it's so bright.
Hello, I'm Mai Nanashima.
I'm going to the place where
my boyfriend is waiting for me.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Wow, the weather is so nice.
To be honest, I've been a
sunny girl lately, haven't I?
The wind...
The weather is so nice.
The wind was stronger than I thought.
Look at my high heels.
I'm wearing high heels.
They're about 10cm high.
Well, this is my 20th work.
It's already my 20th.
Time flies.
I'm still nervous.
I'm nervous.
I'm sweating a lot today.
It's really hot right now.
Look at this nail. Isn't it cute?
I've been into simple nails lately.
This is a nail called Baby Boomer.
That's the name of the nail.
It's hot.
I don't know what I'm going to do today.
I heard that there is a place to
stay, but I'm excited about what to do.
I'm excited.
I'm heading to the station.
I'm going to get on the train
and head to the meeting place.
I have my hair curled today.
Does it look good on me?
My hair grew, didn't it?
It grew a lot.
Which do you like, my
short hair or long hair?
Which one do you like?
I can see the station!
I'm at the station!
I'm going to take the train now!
You mean you want to get rid of it?
Yes, I want to get rid of it.
Recently?
Last year, I got rid of it
when I went out of my house.
That's terrible.
How did you get rid of it?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
I really want to get rid of it.
Thank you.
Mai-chan, what did you hear today?
What do you think?
Do you want to stay here?
Yes.
That's fine.
I'm looking forward to it.
The atmosphere has changed, hasn't it?
Has it changed?
It has changed a lot.
You look different.
I look different?
Yes, you do.
You look more like a girl.
Really?
I see.
You look like you're going to take it off.
Oh, my.
Let me see.
You look great.
I feel like I'm being watched.
What's the right way to wear it?
Isn't it nice to take it off?
It's one of them, isn't it?
Yes, it's one of them.
Oh, my!
It's a little...
It's amazing.
I'd like to fix it.
It's a little dangerous to do it here.
It's a little dangerous.
It's a little dangerous
if I stretch my hand.
I think it's about time to come into view.
Is this it?
Yes, yes, yes.
It's so long.
I've never seen it before.
Can you see inside?
Yes, I can see inside.
By the way, how about you?
I haven't seen inside.
You haven't seen inside?
No, I haven't.
You can't see inside from outside.
Yes, I can't see inside.
Because it's private.
Then, let's go inside.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it from here.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
How is it?
It's beautiful.
It's like a welcome drink.
There is also a welcome champagne.
It's amazing.
It's a strange feeling.
Is it strange?
It's good, isn't it?
Oh!
It's amazing!
It's a success!
It's cute!
Isn't it cute?
It's so cute!
It's so pretty.
I feel like I'm an influencer.
I agree.
It's even more gorgeous.
How about you, Mai-chan?
Do you drink alcohol?
I don't drink strong alcohol.
Strong?
What?
Really?
It's really cold.
Of course I prepared it.
That's great.
I usually drink a lot.
I don't think so.
You're different from your character.
He's an old man inside.
He's so cute.
I think he was definitely
a man in his previous life.
He's quite... And
he's not sloppy.
He's not sloppy.
Why is he not sloppy?
He doesn't drink expensive bar.
He's a man who really wants to drink.
To what?
Eh?
First limousine?
First limousine!
Nice sound.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Cheers Cheers Cheers.
I can do it.
You can do it!
You won't have to do it again.
Huh?
You're doing it!
You're doing it, Mai!
Wow, she's fast!
This girl is fast!
She's fast!
I was getting thirsty...
She's gone already.
I'm getting thirsty... No, no!
Not at all.
Well, it's like water
compared to soju, isn't it?
When you smile more, it
means you're drunk, right?
That's right.
And you sweat a lot.
How do you sweat?
Ah!
I want to take this off more than before.
But I was hiding it.
It's a possibility that
all the jeans are soaked.
But I'm going to take it off properly.
What do you call it when it's really bad?
When I was riding, I got sunburned.
I see.
Which part of your body is
the easiest to get sunburned?
My arms and legs.
Your legs?
Yes, my legs.
Really?
My heels.
My legs are in danger.
Now?
Yes, they are.
I like it.
What do you mean?
The nails look good.
The outer part.
Can you show me?
The nails.
I'm so sweaty.
I can't do it.
The nails are beautiful.
Are you blushing?
No, I'm not.
It's not blurry at all.
I'm so embarrassed.
You'll slip if you walk barefoot.
My legs are so strong.
It's so tight.
I don't want to. It's so tight.
It's so shiny.
You're so shiny, Mai-chan.
I don't want to. I'm so embarrassed.
This is... It's so slippery.
I can't wear my seat belt,
so I slip in front of you.
I see.
I'm so embarrassed.
That's how it is.
I don't want to.
This is definitely for mania.
It's for mania.
This is for mania.
There's a lot of garbage on it.
It's fine. It's beautiful.
I don't want to.
But it's blurry.
I thought it was just sweat.
It's different.
It's hot. I'm sweating.
Sweat is up to my forehead.
Not here?
I'm sweating on my armpits, too.
It's narrow.
I don't want to.
If you dress like this, you
can show your armpits, right?
You have to show your armpits with this.
How many people came to the cafe today?
I came by train.
How do you wear a fishing rod?
Like this.
People like this never grab a fishing rod.
Is that so?
It's not a fishing
rod, it's a vertical one.
I like the stick.
I feel like I'm curious about your eyes.
Like this.
Show me.
I'm sweating.
I don't know.
How is it?
I'm sweating a lot.
Wow.
I just touched it.
Let's eat.
I don't like it.
I've tasted it.
It's the most delicious.
Do you think you've become
a little erotic doing this job?
A little bit.
These nails.
I don't know what you're
going to do with that nail.
What are you going to do with it?
For example, like this.
Thank you very much.
Here?
Over there.
Thank you very much.
It's getting harder.
It's dangerous.
I'm about to swear an oath of loyalty.
This is it.
Can I have a double service?
Oh, it's a cafe.
Great.
It's wonderful.
It's amazing.
This is a little... We
can do it anytime, right?
Can we do it anytime?
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
You can take it off anytime.
Look.
You can take off your
panties from the side.
Oh, really?
You can take it off from the side.
Mai-chan.
It's getting bigger.
It's coming out.
It's coming out, Mai-chan.
I washed it with my nails.
It's so hot.
I'm going to apply hand sweat.
It's great.
It's so luxurious.
You're so kind.
I'm going to touch your nipples.
Wait a minute.
You're so kind.
It's going to come out.
It's fun.
How was it?
It was a success.
It's dangerous.
Let's go over there.
Let's have a champagne kiss.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's getting hot. I'm sweating.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's good.
Oh, there are two.
Two.
Two at once.
Ai-chan, you're doing amazing things.
In the limousine.
What do you think of this kind of date?
I'm embarrassed to be seen.
From around?
Can't you see the light?
I think I can see the light.
But I can't see the light.
I can see it.
You said you could see it, but
you didn't let go of your penis.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
I've been watching you all the time.
Chikumi, did you stand up?
You're sweating a lot.
I think you should take this off.
The density of the car suddenly increased.
Did you care about the car next to you?
It was a high-rise car.
I'm looking at it.
You're looking at me, aren't you?
I'm embarrassed.
I don't mind if you look down from here.
I can't see the back of the car.
The driver is just looking ahead.
He's not looking at you.
I don't think it's about you.
Try this on.
It's like a naked apron.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Like that.
Wow!
It's coming out!
One side.
Show me.
I can't see the ground at all.
I can see a little.
I can't see anything.
Wow.
This is amazing.
This horizontal ground.
The horizontal ground is amazing.
Can you look at the camera for a moment?
So cute.
Can you see this?
Yes, I can.
I can't understand what he is saying.
This is very good.
Do you like it?
Yes.
This is very good.
It's hot.
Champagne tastes good.
Are you thirsty?
Yes.
But you still have some
alcohol in your mouth.
Alcohol is good.
Alcohol is good, but what about your mouth?
Is it wet?
No.
It's not wet.
This is the one you like.
There are two of them.
The black one.
It's embarrassing.
Look at the driver's eyes.
Look at this side.
No, it's embarrassing.
What are you doing?
I'm getting used to it.
Are you getting used to it?
How do you usually use it?
Do you want me to hold your hand?
It hurts.
I'm going to cry.
You were in pain, but you got better.
I don't want to die.
How is it?
It's better than before.
What?
I feel like an adult.
It's a little moody, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
I'm so nervous.
Can I do it?
Of course.
I'm so nervous.
Are you getting used to it?
Not yet.
I'm nervous.
Can't I touch it?
You have to hold the weird part.
I'm a little worried about this.
I'm curious about this place.
Can you show me your butt?
Your panties are cute.
Is it for today?
Yes, it's for today.
You're eating.
You're eating, Ai-chan.
It's so beautiful.
Oh, I saw it.
I saw your butt.
Did you see it?
Yes, I did.
Oh, really.
Let me see from the other side.
Let me zoom in more.
Let me smell it.
Wow.
I can smell it.
Mayu-chan, can I lick your butthole?
What?
It's embarrassing.
It smells good.
It doesn't smell.
What are you doing?
Hey, look at the camera.
You have a big mouth.
I'm glad you're okay.
You're crying.
You're messy.
Your eyebrows are messy.
Let's go downstairs.
I'm sorry.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know I was breathing.
I'm still breathing.
It's so hard to breathe.
I'm holding my breath.
I can't breathe.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Do you want to lick it?
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better after the bath?
Yes.
Look at this.
Do you feel better?
What's wrong?
It hurts.
I feel sick.
You have to drink this.
It's hot.
Show me your hand.
It's so beautiful.
I'll show you this before that.
Can I put this in the water?
Help me.
I'll hold your hand.
It's cold.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I want to go outside I want to go
out While no one can touch you.
I'm scared!
She's scratching her back.
Mai-chan, you're great
at scratching your back.
Does it feel good to have a live chin-poo?
Yes, it feels good.
Do you like a live chin-poo?
Say you like a live chin-poo.
I like a live chin-poo.
I'm going to cry again.
I'm going to cry.
I want to cry too.
Do you want to cry?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
It's amazing how you use your legs.
You're moving.
I'm moving.
Oh, no, Moe-chan.
It's not good to tighten
your legs like this.
My legs are so tight.
I don't feel good.
Do you feel excited?
Do you feel excited in such a place?
I can't do it.
How do you feel?
You like toys, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Let's go.
I don't want to die.
No...
I can't do it.
No, no, no.
You don't want to get in trouble?
I can't get in trouble.
I can't do this.
I can't do it.
Help me.
You can do it.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I'm going to cry.
You're so happy.
You're so happy that you're going crazy.
Hang in there.
Let me see your back.
Your back is amazing.
Does your back feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Slippery.
Moe-chan's lens is broken.
Moe-chan, can you do it by yourself?
Moe-chan, let me see your face.
There, there.
I'm going to put it out from the bag.
Can I have a bunch?
I'm not bringing it.
I want it in there.
Do you want a bunch?
I want a bunch!
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to put my
hands on you from below?
Are you okay?
Put your feet up here.
Put your hands together.
Look at this.
It's so dark.
Do you like this?
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, great.
Here, here.
Mae-chan.
There are various stickers.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Do you feel good to lie in a dog's belly?
I feel great.
I want to take the dog out of the room.
I want to go home.
Take the dog out of the room.
Let me go.
You can do it!
Mayu-chan, touch it.
There's a lot down there.
Ma-chan, would you
like to clean up a little?
I was nervous.
Would you like to sit inside?
Yes.
Ma-chan, you're sweating a lot.
Come over here.
You're soaking wet.
I'm sweating all over.
It's full of sweat.
Look at the sofa. It's wet.
It's terrible.
What's this?
It looks like a person's hair.
It's full of sweat.
It's beautiful.
You are a good boy.
No, I don't want to.
Look at this.
Mai-chan's sweat.
Yummy.
It's hot.
I'm soaked.
Are we going on a date?
I'm a little hungry.
I'm looking for a restaurant.
I don't think there is a restaurant.
Let's go for a walk.
Let's go.
It's so cute.
It's amazing.
It's so big.
It's as big as your eyes.
You like it.
It's amazing.
You like it, don't you?
It's so big.
It's as big as your eyes.
It's a pineapple.
Isn't it amazing?
This is what Hawaii is all about.
It's amazing.
It's Hawaii.
How is it?
Is it beef?
I think so.
It's good.
It's warm and good.
What kind of meat do you eat?
My favorite part is...
Hormone.
I like pork cutlet.
I like Motsunabe.
I see.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I only eat this before I die.
You are amazing.
I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
I'm shaking.
It looks so good.
I got a spoon.
I got a spoon and ice cream.
I can't eat whipped cream.
Where do you eat this?
I eat it from ice cream because it melts.
I eat it with pancakes.
You have a good face.
I cut this.
He's eating.
Oh, wait.
Slow down.
He's eating.
Wait, wait.
Oh, no.
He's in his mouth.
I wanted him to eat more slowly.
I wanted him to eat
more slowly like we did.
He's eating.
Where is it?
Let's check it with this.
It's on your eyebrows.
You said that the person
you like is your type, right?
Yes.
But it's not about appearance.
It's about compatibility.
That's important.
It's important.
I'd like to do it before the month.
Do you want to do it before the month?
Yes So you want to do
it once and have a taste.
Yes I think so No, I don't I'd like
to do it before the month I see.
What do you want to make sure?
The compatibility What
kind of compatibility?
What is the most important
thing in a relationship?
I don't really know.
Please tell me.
Well... What is the most
important thing in a relationship?
Well...
I don't know.
Size?
Body?
I don't know.
Hold this.
I can't hold it anymore.
I think this is enough.
How about this?
It's easy to understand.
What if this is real?
Yes.
What do you think?
It's too small.
What?
Isn't it too small?
Mai-chan said this is not enough.
Isn't that enough?
So, it's a little short.
Well, it's... It's
about this long.
How about the thickness?
It's medium.
How is it?
This is not good.
This?
Well...
What is important?
The length or the thickness?
The hardness and... Yes.
The thickness and... What?
Hardness and length.
Hardness and length are important.
Hardness is important.
How long is the length?
I'll measure the length.
Isn't it just this long?
Isn't this long?
No, I don't have this much.
I don't have this much.
I think it's quite long.
I think it's about 20cm.
No way.
I didn't get it.
You mean I didn't get it?
No.
Let's do it again.
It's good.
It says kiss.
Kiss?
How about this?
It's good.
Great.
Let's take a picture.
Let's take a look.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, K?
K?
Kiss's K.
Like this?
Oh, good, good.
It's not K.
It's not X.
Kiss's... Look.
Oh, it's true.
Oh, where did it go?
Where did it go?
Oh, there it is.
Yay!
Are you having fun?
I'm glad.
I was so surprised.
I didn't expect you to be so cautious.
We are like that.
Let's go over there.
Those three are opposite 3P.
We are opposite 3P.
You are right.
We are 6P.
Let's go together.
No, no, no.
We'll get mixed up.
I guess so.
We've booked a hotel,
so we can't fit everyone.
There's a heart.
It's cute.
Who's got a heart?
Concentrate.
Everyone's got a heart.
It's cute, isn't it, Mai-chan?
It's like a sunflower.
It's different from the previous one.
What's this?
Goldfish?
It's like a aquarium.
What's this?
Everyone is looking over there.
Sometimes there are
fish that react like this.
Yes, there are.
They are looking at us.
Aren't they looking at us a lot?
Can they see us?
Yes, they can.
I see two of them.
I see three and four of them.
Do you see them?
I see them a lot.
I feel sorry for them.
It's funny.
Is it a goldfish?
It's a pink fish.
Did you say fish?
What?
Did you say goldfish?
What is it? Fish?
Goldfish is also a fish, isn't it?
No, it's a kind of fish.
It's a kind of fish.
I don't know what it is.
I thought you were just apologizing.
No, I thought you were looking down on me.
Mai-chan, I don't look
down on you in such a place.
But isn't it good to
have a thrill like that?
What is it?
Like going to a park
where there are people.
Really?
What do you mean by that?
I like that too.
Oh, is that so?
I want to kiss someone.
What?
It's exciting, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh, she's here.
She didn't see me, did she?
Hold on a second.
To the left and right.
Let me kiss you.
I'm embarrassed.
Mai-chan said she was nervous.
I was taken to dessert after dessert.
I'm embarrassed.
It suits you.
I thought you were going to start dancing.
That's a zombie.
There is a zombie here.
Yes, there is.
Did you hide it because it was a lie?
The real one is in New York.
There was a zombie here.
Let's do it again.
Great.
It's amazing.
It was here.
That's why it's not in New York now.
No, no, no.
I was about to be deceived for a moment.
I brought it by ship from New York.
It's a big deal.
The next day.
It's very cold.
Is it cold?
It looks delicious again.
It's delicious.
It's cold.
I brought it.
Welcome!
Good evening.
I've been waiting for you.
Are you drinking already?
Yes, we are.
Thank you.
Do you want to drink?
Yes, I do.
Which one do you want?
Let's toast to the beautiful night view.
Cheers!
Cheers, Maruyama-chan.
Cheers.
You can do it.
I just did it.
Can you do it from here?
Don't be naughty.
You can do it.
Oh!
It's funny.
Can I lick it?
Oh!
It's delicious champagne.
It's cute.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh!
It's cute to lick.
It's good, isn't it?
Is it good?
It's good.
You can drink it with your mouth.
I can't drink it with my mouth.
Put it in your mouth.
You're in the way.
He wants to drink it.
You should do like this.
I'll do it.
Let him drink it from the top.
Stand up.
Don't be shy.
He's getting closer.
How is it?
Graccia!
What language is that?
Graccia is Italian.
That was too fast.
I said it as soon as you started.
Graccia.
A man with a shield has to be a grudge.
A man with a shield.
You're a man with a shield.
I brought something good.
This is a swimsuit.
It's cute.
It's pink.
It's a present.
Shocking pink.
It looks good on you.
Where did you buy it?
Gyaru.
It's nice, isn't it?
If you don't mind, could you please stand
up for a moment and change your clothes?
I think it's good.
It's cute.
Do you want me to wear it?
Do you want me to change my clothes?
It's hard to look like this.
Can I ask you a favor here?
Can I?
What are you doing?
You don't like it?
It's embarrassing.
But I like your style.
What?
Do you have small panties?
It's a micro bikini.
I don't have it.
No, I didn't.
Why?
You were so cute just now.
I left it behind.
You left it behind?
Yes.
Really?
Because it's a duet.
Oh, it's a button.
It's not a button.
It's always like this.
Really?
You're a pervert.
It's always like this?
Yes, I took it off just now.
I took it off.
You were taking it off a while ago.
Why did you take it off?
I wanted to surprise you.
You got caught.
It's a surprise.
There's not a single grain of cake.
I'm getting excited.
Can I touch it?
I'm getting hot.
You're getting hot?
You're getting drunk, aren't you?
Do you want a drink?
Let's have a drink while we change.
It's good.
The taste is different, isn't it?
Is it different?
It's easier to drink than before.
What do you mean?
The characters are like that.
This is a happening bar.
In this state.
Everyone's voice is spinning fast.
It's good.
It's the best.
Do you know how to wear it?
How do you wear it?
Like this.
You don't have this, do you?
You wear it like this.
How is it?
Can you move this up a little bit?
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
I don't like it.
Do you want me to stretch it?
Yes.
Your hair looks good, too.
How about this?
Oh, that's good.
It looks good on you.
Thank you.
He's doing something like a Showa gag.
I want to see a gag-like pose.
A gag-like pose?
I have something.
This is a trend.
Wow!
TikTok.
It's a trend.
This is my sofa.
It looks good on you.
How about a face heart?
A face heart?
This is called a pig heart.
Pig?
It's not a pig, is it?
It's a pig.
Is it a pig heart?
He's sweating a lot.
He's getting drunk.
You should have told me if you were sober.
If you're drunk, you'll know what to do.
It would be great if
this gal went to the sea.
It would be great if we
could go to the beach.
The sea and the pool are beautiful.
What do you use in the pool?
Please tell me where you
want me to touch more.
It's so smooth.
It's embarrassing.
You look like you're about to die.
I'm sweating a little.
Are you sweating?
I love this place.
I love it.
She is licking my armpit sweat.
Because it's so cute.
I like armpit sweat.
A cat that licks a cat's leg.
Do you like being licked?
Kitten, how should I lick you?
Good boy.
I'll touch your butt.
I'll put more ointment on your butt.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Wow.
It's shining.
It is.
It's really shiny.
It's amazing.
I can't stop.
It's fun.
The wheel looks great on you.
Yeah.
I'm going to apply it to your nails.
How do you feel?
What's going on with you?
Why do you like her so much?
Maya is very seductive.
Maya, where are you touching?
Where are you touching?
I'll be there soon.
I'm going to put my hand in there.
What's going on there?
What's going on?
Oh, that's what it feels like.
He's purring.
I'm sorry.
You are really a mess.
Your eyes are drooping.
I have a lot of pee.
There are so many, so it's okay
to do it one by one, so it feels good.
It feels so good.
You're all over the place
right now, aren't you?
You're all over the place.
Oh, it hurts.
Your tongue is long,
so it feels really good.
Look this way.
It's a face that is so cute!
Why don't you pet me?
I'm a huge fan of you!
I'll hold you.
Do you like it?
Wow.
It feels good.
Hmm.
Hmm Hmm.
Hmm Hmm Hmm Hmm Hmm Hmm.
Let me lick your teeth Hmm Yes.
Can I warm your back?
Yes.
Are you thirsty?
Do you want some water?
Yes.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
If you eat a lot of
food, you will be licked.
Where are you licking?
Where are you licking, Mai-chan?
My butthole.
How does it taste?
It's good.
Does it taste bitter?
Bitter?
It's good.
You can do it κακάα Like this.
like this.
Try it Your shoulders, too.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's amazing.
Can I see you for a moment?
How are you?
I'm fine.
It's good to have a lot.
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
Do you want to stop eating?
No, I don't want to.
You are eating in a pleasant place.
It's okay.
The baby is crying.
I've got a lot of blood in the baby's eye.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, you're pushing.
You're pushing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's like a pillow.
It's slippery.
How do you feel, Man-chan?
Oh, you feel great!
You feel great because you are so smooth.
Is it warm?
Yes.
Man-chan, let me hold you.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
What do you want to do, Man-chan?
I want to put it in my mouth.
You want to put it in
your mouth, don't you?
I'll put it in your mouth.
It's hot.
It's a mess.
ahhh
ahhh ah.
ah.
ahh ah ahh.
ah ahh ahh Ah...
I'm going to throw up.
You're going to throw up.
You're so wet.
It feels so good.
If you lick my neck, it'll get harder.
I'm going to throw up.
It feels so good.
Ah!
Oh!
Poo!!!
Poo!
Ahhhhh
Poo!!!
Ahhh...
!!
You want to poop?!
Let's see...
One day, you will...
Ha... Ah...
One day...
Oh...
Oh... Oh... Oh... Oh...
Oh, it's hard.
Can I move it?
Be careful It's hot.
It's hot.
It's hot It's hot Can
you get on this chair?
This one.
This one is here.
Can you stand on both legs?
It feels so good.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Don't pull my groin!
Always...
Don't pull my ass!
Sleepy... Sleepy...
I'm sorry.
Did you suck it all out?
Does it feel good there?
Stomach is also swollen.
There are too many.
Misaki, come here.
You don't want to eat pizza, do you?
It's amazing.
I did it.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm going to take a break.
I'm scared.
Are you all right?
I'm still going to be able to do it.
I feel good.
Are you all right?
It's all right.
Can I put it back in?
I don't want to.
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
You can stay here.
You're still very tight.
It feels so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let go of me.
Look.
It feels so good.
Stretch your legs.
That's right, that's right.
I wonder if this is it.
I'm scared.
It's tight.
Ah!
Aww, feels good?
Aww.
Look Show more of your
edgy side Show it to all around.
I'm sorry I couldn't do it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you want to go home?
I'll go home.
Oh, it's hot.
Get up.
How many shots did you get?
Do you know?
How many?
I don't know.
She gave me a lot.
How is it?
Is it hot?
I think it's still inside.
It's very warm.
How was it?
It felt good.
She's still a baby.
We gave her a lot.
You put out a lot, didn't you?
You were too nervous.
I was nervous.
Are you happy that I put out a lot?
Yes.
I was so nervous.
You can sleep soundly.
What are you doing?
Are you sleepy?
No, you were sleeping so
much Your eyes are so cute
Look at you You've been
lying down for a while.
You're so sleepy.
Are you feeling good?
What's wrong?
Are you feeling better?
Good boy.
Let me know when you
are ready Don't say no.
You can't move your hands.
I'm so sleepy.
Don't you feel excited?
Take off your pants.
You're soaked.
Can I touch you more?
Show me you're sitting.
Can you show me what you're doing?
Do you feel good?
Can you do it?
You're cute
Let me touch you.
Panda is doing something erotic.
Can't you touch yourself?
Can you do it?
Stop it.
I'm going to cry.
Ahhhh.
He went to sleep.
He is wet He is hungry.
Will you try rubbing his puffy face?
Rub it?
Put a lot of acupuncture
points on your feet.
Does it feel good if you put it in?
Don't you want to put it in if you push it?
I want to put it
in Can't I put it in?
Put it in as it is.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm getting angry.
Oh, no.
I'm so angry.
I'm sensitive because I'm sick.
Oh, no.
You're moving a lot.
It's uncomfortable.
I can't do this.
I can't do it here.
I'm going.
You're in a lot of pain.
Are you nervous?
How do you feel?
Oh, it's hot!
It's easier to breathe if you go once.
Oh, it feels good.
I'll let you go.
Let's do this.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to cry.
Let's go.
Let's shake hands.
I don't feel good.
I'll put you on my lap.
Do you feel good?
I can't do it anymore.
It feels weird.
Are you sleeping?
Are you awake?
I can't do it.
I can't do it at all.
I'll move you a lot.
I'm sorry, I'll go to the doctor's office.
I'm sorry.
I'm really going.
You can do it.
Thank you.
You're right.
You're so cute.
I gave you a lot.
Are you satisfied?
Is it not enough?
No, it's not enough.
Can you lick me a little?
Can you do it again?
Do you want to do it again?
I want to do it again.
Look at his head I'm sorry
for the trouble you're in.
I'm sorry for the trouble you're in.
Can you put it in?
It's squeezed.
You are sleepy, aren't you?
I'm going to clean your ears.
I'm done.
Can I take your ears off?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so nervous.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm out of my mind.
I fell asleep.
Good morning!
It's morning.
Can you see the breakfast in front of me?
Ta-da!
Here it is.
Looks good.
Just a glance.
Oh!
I spilled it.
How is it?
It's good.
I spilled something.
Isn't this cute?
Which one?
Oh!
Hey!
What is this? Panda? Bear?
What is this?
Doesn't it look like a panda?
It's a cute panda.
It's really cute.
I've never seen such a cute panda.
You're kidding.
Don't you think so?
You said it was a bear, didn't you?
It looks like a panda to me, too.
It can be a panda or a bear.
Mayonnaise.
What's your favorite food?
Tomatoes.
What else?
Grilled meat.
Tomatoes.
Are you going back?
Tomatoes and grilled meat are rare.
There are many people
who don't like tomatoes.
Dressing.
Dressing is this.
Salt and pepper.
It's good as it is.
Is it good?
Yes.
Do you have any dressing?
Dressing?
This?
This is maple.
This is honey.
Honey?
Yes.
It's a luxurious breakfast.
Do you eat this kind of breakfast?
In the morning?
In the morning...
Yes.
What do you eat for breakfast?
What kind of food do you like to eat?
I like simple food like mentaiko,
nori seaweed, and egg on rice.
I've been curious about this.
There is a punishment game.
Would you like to play the game?
I want to play it.
Really?
Is that so?
It's a penalty game, isn't it?
It's a penalty game.
It's a penalty game to eat
extremely spicy yakisoba.
What's that?
It's a bitter one.
It's the first time in
a long time, isn't it?
But this yakisoba is
more like a penalty game.
It's definitely a very spicy one, isn't it?
Let's eat it if you lose.
Yes.
Oh, I'm scared.
This is...
Oh, it's fast.
Men eat it, too.
Wow!
That was fast.
So fast!
I'm getting a heart attack.
You are?
I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
Oh no.
I'm scared.
The momentum is important.
Under the black.
I think... Go!
Go, go, go!
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm scared.
I'm scared. It's hard.
Did you feel it?
It was hard.
I was surprised.
Did you feel it?
Yes.
I can't eat all of it.
Which one should I eat?
This one?
Wow, look at the color.
Is it red and black?
You're very careful.
It looks delicious.
Wow, it's spicy.
Oh, it's coming.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
It's coming later.
I'm thirsty.
Don't you sweat a lot?
I don't sweat that much.
Can't you see it?
Oh, my God.
It's spicy.
It hurts after drinking.
It hurts.
My gums hurt, too.
What? Are you serious?
If it's hot, you should take it off.
You can take it off.
It's really dry.
You should take it off.
It's hot. My armpits are sweating.
Your armpits?
It's going to get dirty,
so you should take it off.
You should take it off.
Right now?
Yes. It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
You're always naked, aren't you?
If you take it off, you'll
eat a little more, won't you?
I'll eat it later.
I'm so embarrassed.
It's so hot.
If I eat a few of these, I'll die.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Let me eat it.
Please do.
I think we have a lot of food.
Yeah, I'm jealous.
We can't eat it until it's over.
Please try just one.
Yeah, I'll try a little more.
It wasn't good at first.
No, it's been good from the start!
Really? No, it's been good from the start!
Here it is.
Wow!
It's huge.
It's open.
Show me your face.
What is this?
This is the other side.
Show me your butt.
You came out of yourself.
You are quiet.
I'm going to give you a shot.
I'm very embarrassed.
Do you like my finger?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to drink water?
Yes.
You like to lick, don't you?
You like to lick fingers
and tongue, don't you?
Do you like to lick?
You like to lick, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I want to lick you.
Oh, wow, you're tied up.
Do you want me to put a bandage on you?
No, I don't.
Do you want me to put a
bandage on you directly?
Oh, wow.
Ah.
There's no point in tying
it up You've grabbed a lot
Ah As it is.
Ah Ah.
Ah Ah Ah
Ah.
It's so hot.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
I can't do it.
Do you like to be touched by me?
No, I don't like it.
I'll put my hand on your hip.
Do you feel good?
I can't do it.
Oh, no!
You've got a lot on your face.
Are you okay?
Oh, no!
Let me see.
Here you go.
I'll give you some ice cream.
You're drooling a lot.
How do I eat this?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Here, I'll put this on your mouth.
Oh, thank you.
I'll put this on your mouth.
I can't stand up.
Are you standing up?
You don't move at all.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You don't move at all.
I move a lot.
You move a lot.
This is the result of the
counselling we give her.
I'm sorry for you.
The doctor's office.
Good boy.
You fell asleep again.
It's okay.
It's hot.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
So, every day from now, I'll
be able to see my daughters.
After this, I'll be able to see
my daughter's grandchildren.
I'm sorry.
Can you stop?
I can't stop.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
Help me.
Please let me sleep.
How is it?
Wow.
It's messed up Wow.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Can you open your mouth?
Can you?
Here.
What's wrong?
Oh, no!
You're messy.
Good boy.
He is getting full of milk.
I feel so good.
Are you full?
You are eating a lot.
Please don't... Don't...
I'm going to take a bath.
Good boy.
Wow.
Can you see it?
Good boy.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to hold you more?
Wow.
You are amazing.
Your neck is burning.
Let's go together.
You are still breathing.
You have a lot of hair.
You have a lot of hair, right?
Yes, I have a lot of hair.
You are touching a lot.
Do you want to wash your hair?
Do you want more?
Let me go!
You can't get up?
I can't get up.
I'll make you feel good today.
Yes.
Where should I attack first?
Is your nipple so weak?
Yes.
Does your nipple feel good?
It feels good.
You're reacting a lot.
I'll put it in for you.
Your neck is very stiff.
I'll massage this side as well.
I've been massaging your chest for a while.
It smells sexy.
Why are you so big?
Because it feels good.
Are you so excited?
Yes.
What should I do with this kiss?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to touch me directly.
Directly?
Yes.
It's hot.
It's getting warmer.
It feels good.
I'll touch you while licking your nipples.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I'm about to fall asleep.
Let's go out.
You can't go out yet.
You feel great.
What should I do next?
It's good.
There's a lot of gummy juice coming out.
Do you feel a lot better?
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
You can't do that yet.
But...
I'm going to give you a lot of milk.
I'm sorry.
Give me a lot of milk.
You're giving me a lot of milk.
You're still giving me milk, right?
You don't like it?
He's coming out Well,
next time He came out a lot.
That's enough Let's continue.
1.What about me?
2. I can't do that.
4. I don't know, why?
5. I don't know, what did I eat?
8. I can't do that, I can't do that.
9. I'm not going to marry.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, my God!