In both cases, a
Hey, who are you?
You, who always appears in my dreams.
But in the end, you always go to the place where your hands can't reach.
But in the end, I always go to a place where my hands can't reach.
I want to know you.
Where are you now?
I'm going home.
It's been a while since I came back to my hometown.
It's been a while since I moved to Tokyo a few years ago.
But there was a reason why I didn't want to come back to my hometown.
It's because of my childhood.
It's because Yuu Rukawa, a childhood friend of mine, is here.
I'm so lonely.
I'm sorry.
It's my parents' fault.
I don't want to get married.
I see.
I don't want to do it.
I don't know.
Hey, write a letter.
What? A letter?
Yeah.
Not on my phone?
No.
I want a letter with my heart.
Oh.
Let's do something on August 25th, the anniversary.
I promise.
You promise?
Yeah.
Are you done?
Takuya, please take care of Yu.
You're the only one I can count on.
Okay.
You're my best friend.
Leave this to me.
Mom, there's a customer.
Mom?
I'm so lazy.
Yes, yes.
Thank you for your time.
Here.
This is the billboard.
Wait.
Could it be that you're Ikue's son?
Yuru.
Yuu?
You're Yuu, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Nice to meet you.
Don't talk to me like that.
Hey, get up.
Oh, yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Hey, Yu.
Yes?
How long are you going to keep joking?
No, I'm not joking.
It's just that I lost some of my memories.
What?
The doctor said that stress comes from the heart.
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
I will protect Kimura.
I've been with you since I was a kid, and we've been together since we were little.
Besides, we've been dating.
What? Wait a minute.
It's okay. Listen to me.
I transferred and we broke up.
I've been sending letters to you, but since then, I haven't been able to get a reply from you.
I thought I had found another boyfriend for you.
I thought it would be nice if you were happy.
So I told myself.
I'm Mamoru.
Do you know the name Mamoru?
Huh?
There was a letter from you at home.
And...
On the diary you wrote when you were a student.
It said you'd protect it.
Hey, do you have any other photos?
I don't think I have any photos of you.
Can I see your room?
Huh? Why?
What are you looking at?
I might be able to remember something.
I see.
I understand.
Come with me.
Yes.
This way.
This is me.
That's right.
It's us from when we were students.
How do you like it?
Do you remember anything?
I don't know.
But I feel nostalgic.
I see.
I always have the same dream.
Someone always hugs me gently,
And then he gently kisses me.
But at the end, he disappears somewhere.
Um...
Can you hold me?
Oh, no.
Wait, that's...
I know you're being selfish, but I'm begging you.
It's been a long time since I've had a meal like this, but it's so delicious that I want to eat it again.
I'm going to eat it again.
It's so delicious.
Are you feeling good?
Ah...
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Please take this off.
Mmm, yum.
Yeah.
Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Mmm.
I'm so tired.
It feels so good.
I got so tired.
I feel so, I don't know what to do.
Something's up but I can't seem to make a sound either.
Stacy left and got a little loud for me.
Lucky me.
Why does it feel so good?
I feel like I'm going to die.
It feels so good.
I'm getting a lot of pressure.
I feel like I'm dying.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Wow, it's so warm in here.
It feels so good.
I feel so good.
No, no, no, no.
No! I'm going!
No! No!
I'm going, I'm going.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
I feel so good.
It hurts!
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no
Go! Go!
It feels so good.
Hey!
I can't.
Why...
Why do you keep getting
this and that and this?!
It's warm.
Where am I?
It feels so good.
No, no.
No.
No, I feel sick.
No, I'm going to die.
No, no, no.
No, no.
I'm going to die.
Ouch!
Ah...
Please, go to sleep soon.
It feels so good.
It's gone.
Feels good?
It's so hard.
It feels so good.
No!
No, no, no.
I'll go again.
What? What? What?
What? What?
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Aou, Aou, Aou, Aou.
I feel so good.
My legs are in the clouds.
It feels good.
No!
No, no, no!
Ichan, Ichan!
I'm going, I'm going!
Go, go, go!
No, no, no!
It hurts!
Ouch! Ouch!
Go!
Ah.
Ah…
I can't do it anymore.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm so tired.
It feels good.
No, no, no.
I'm so tired.
Feels good.
Oh no.
No, no.
Iku! Iku!
It hurts!
ouch
ahh
Ouch!
It's okay.
Ah...
Mmm...
Feels good, huh?
Ah...
No...
I'm gonna fall...
Mmm...
Ah, no...
Ah...
Mmm...
I'm going...
Ah...
I'm so sleepy.
I can't do it...
No, no, no, no, no!
No!
It hurts, it hurts!
Ouch, ouch.
Nihon-chan, here.
I'm going.
Oh, my God.
It's unbearable.
I feel great.
Wow.
Oww, gross.
This is horrible.
I feel so good.
It's really hard.
It's gone.
Oh, it feels so good over there.
Oh, it feels good over there.
No, I can't do it.
No, no, no!
I'm gonna get hurt!
That feels good!
No, no, no!
Not there!
That feels good!
No, it hurts!
No, no!
No!
Oh, it feels so good.
No, no, no.
It feels so good.
What's going on?
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Oh, no!
It feels amazing.
So good...
It feels so good to have you here.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
Why are you doing this to me?
You're annoying.
You' whoa!
You're annoying!
He's got it!
You're annoying me back there!
I'm so tired right now.
You're annoying!
Why are you doing this to me?
Damn it!
I'm sleepy.
Oh, it hurts.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
E-chan...
Go, go, go!
Yes, it feels good.
Un crystals
Alright.
Come on.
Hey, did you remember something?
My heart is still fluttering.
I see.
But I feel shy.
By the way, don't you want to quit keigo?
What?
Mamoru-san is also...
That might be true.
Then, Mamoru.
Don't be shy.
Um...
Can you meet me tomorrow?
If I'm with Mamoru...
It might be a chance for me to get my memory back.
Okay, I got it.
See you tomorrow.
I can't breathe.
I'm sorry.
Itadakimasu.
It's good.
I'm going to eat it with a glass of soju.
By the way, this is a diary.
When I read this diary, I always thought it was kind to protect.
Don't be shy.
But there's one thing I'm curious about.
This diary page here is also distorted for some reason.
What are you doing?
I wonder what it is.
Thank you for washing the dishes.
Give it to me.
Yeah?
You're not getting anyuc付了
Huh?
It's delicious.
You got me down, huh?
This is the end of the video.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Please subscribe to the channel if you like.
Thank you for washing the dishes and giving me this carrot.
I'll give you a present.
What? No, it's okay. I just gave it to you.
What? It's fine.
No, it's not.
It's fine, it's fine.
Really?
It's a thank you gift.
It's cute, isn't it?
Ah, it's hot.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Hey, it's hard to do. Can you sleep for a while?
Yeah.
Let's touch Chikkun.
I'm going to drink yaen-chang tea.
What's this sound?
I'm close friends with him.
Half of the
It was so delicious.
It's the best!
Is it good?
It's good.
You want to go?
No.
You can't go yet.
No?
You'll feel better if you wait.
I'm not drunk yet
Are you drunk?
Hurry up, hurry up
I'm not drunk yet
Don't drink too much
I'm not alone
Don't drink so much
I just barely drank
That's how you organization affect its quality
I can only drink three of a kind
I know this is too bittersweet.
But your blood is the reason why I believe we must be careful.
You need to spend more effort to find love, less of a stomach ache...
That alone is what makes me, much moreים.
Alright sometime later my baby will finally recognize you.
Take good care of yourself along with buttons on the wall.
What?
I think I can do it
You think you can do it?
You can't go yet.
What?
I can't go?
You can't.
It's too early to go.
Please be patient.
It was more delicious than Amore's chin-chin.
By the way, the anniversary of our date is tomorrow, August 25th.
You always wanted me to do that and that.
It was hard.
Oh, really?
It's nostalgic.
I want to remember you as soon as possible.
Hey, it's been a while.
Did you meet Yu?
Yeah, but I forgot about me.
I see.
What are you doing? Tell me.
I'll give this to you.
Aha.
What's going on?
See you later.
Huh?
Hey!
The letter I received from Takuya had something shocking written on it.
That was what happened when I wasn't there.
August 25th, the anniversary of our first date.
Suddenly, memories began to flow like a soma-tou.
There were so many memories in my head that I couldn't get rid of them.
On August 25th, my part-time job was off and I was hanging around at home.
This year was also the beginning, but the cooler of the house was broken, and the fan was the last hope.
At that time, I got a message from Kenny, who I used to play with a lot when I was little.
Kenny graduated from the medical school and is a super elite who works at a university hospital.
It's been a long time since we've met at Ken's house because he's coming back here.
All right, let's open it.
Thank you, Ken.
I'm going to drink it now.
Really?
Yeah.
That's weird.
Oh, it's good.
Yeah.
It's good.
I did it.
Cheers.
It's good.
Yes, it's delicious.
It's delicious.
You've grown up a lot.
Really?
Shut up.
You've grown up a lot.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Boyfriend?
Suddenly?
There are, but it's far away, so it doesn't go well.
Aren't you lonely?
Well, to be honest, I'm lonely.
Do you have any relatives?
No, I don't.
Because I'm not popular.
What? That's not true.
Because I'm the most popular person in the neighborhood.
I don't want to leave you alone.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay?
Kenny.
Wait a minute.
Ah...
No...
Please stop...
Ah...
Are you angry?
No, I'm not.
Then, let's meet tomorrow.
But, after all...
What's wrong with you?
It's okay.
I see.
It's been a while since I've been to your house.
You haven't changed a bit.
Really?
I brought this for you.
What's that?
I'll use this for you.
No, I don't need that.
It's okay, isn't it?
I don't want to.
Come to me.
Okay, okay, okay.
I, who was weak in my heart,
I couldn't do it.
I'm sorry.
Don't be mad.
You're the best.
I wanted to do the same with you.
Really?
What were you doing last night?
Didn't you notice?
I can't see anything.
Look at my mouth.
Cute, isn't it?
Put your tongue out.
Look at my tongue.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
I feel good
Oh, do you like it?
What's wrong?
You're the best.
Are you feeling good?
Yeah.
Huh?
Yeah, I'm feeling good.
You're feeling good?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Oh, it's cold.
Oh, this is good.
It feels good.
Is it good?
Oh, it's cold.
Oh, it's cute.
What's going on?
It hurts!
Let's go, let's go.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Oh, that's amazing.
He's looking at you like that.
He's looking at you.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I was crying.
Show me your cute eyes.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I'm so tired.
Mmm...
Mmm?
Everyone's in trouble.
Ah...
Oh, no, no...
Yama, come here.
I'm coming.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
No.
I'm okay.
No, no, no.
I'm so tired.
Stop it.
It feels so good.
Min-chan, Min-chan.
No, no.
No, no, no.
Go, go.
Oh, my God.
Calm down.
It's okay.
Ouch!
It's the best.
Do you feel good?
It's ok.
It hurts.
I can't do it.
I'm going to fall.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts
What are you talking about?
Come on, come on.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I feel like I have to go to the hospital.
Oh, my God.
You are not feeling well, are you?
I am.
Huh?
Are you okay?
I am.
You are not feeling well, are you?
No, no, no.
I'm going to be fine.
No, no, no, no.
I'm going.
Ouch, ouch, ouch
So funny
It's really difficult and tiring, but I'm happy because of the
Oh, my God.
What is this?
It feels good.
No, no, no.
It's too cold.
Ikku! Ikku!
No, no, no, oh, no, no, oh, no.
So talking too much!
What the hell is that?
I can't do it anymore.
Let's go.
No, no, no.
That feels good.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Kimchi.
Kimchi...
Are you okay?
I'm going.
No, I'm going.
Are you okay?
Open your mouth.
I can't take it anymore.
What's wrong?
On August 27th, I wanted to talk to Kenri.
I couldn't get in touch with Kenri anymore.
I couldn't get in touch with Kenri.
I can't reach him.
Oh, Keiko.
What are you doing?
Oh, how's Shoichi?
Oh, he's fine.
Oh, I see.
I'm going home tomorrow morning at Shinkansen.
Hmm.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Mamoru?
Are you there?
I remembered everything.
Why didn't you remember me?
Really?
You remembered me?
Kimura Mamoru.
He was my childhood friend.
And the person I loved the most in the world.
The person I love the most.
Yuu.
I know everything about you.
I see. I'm sorry for everything.
Yeah.
I'm so glad.
Yu.
I...
I like you.
I love you.
I love you too, Mamoru.
Will you marry me?
Of course.
Um...
Ah...
It feels so good.
No, no.
No, no, no!
I'm going!
Eek!
It's gross.
Ah!
Ah, it feels good!
Ah, no!
Ah!
Ah, it feels good!
Ah, no!
I'm going!
Ah!
Ah...
Ah, it's so painful!
No, no, no, no!
Ouch!
It hurts!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Oh!
Oh...
It feels good.
No, no, no.
No!
It feels good.
I'm going to the mountains!
Hmm...
I feel good!
Ahh nooo
Nooooo
I can't
Ahhh no
Ahhh
Hmm...
Ahh
Ouch!
I can't...
Ah, it feels so good.
No, no, no, no.
It feels so good.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Stop, No, no.
I can't stand it.
I'm going, I'm going.
What is that?
Oh, thank you.
No!?
What was that?
Hi.
Oh, hi again.
Ah...
No...
No, no...
Oh no, no, no...
Oh, no...
No, no, no...
Ah!
Mmm.
Oh!
It's a little hot.
You can't get cold.
I'm so hot.
It's so hot.
Are you feeling good?
Yeah.
It's so hot.
Be careful.
I want to go inside the house.
So much power.
Turn it around.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, wow. I can't reach it.
No!
No! It's too much!
It's too much!
No!
It hurts!
It feels so good.
Hmm...
Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
Ouch
I feel like I'm going to die.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Ah, g-
Ah, that's right, I feel good.
I feel good.
I feel good too.
Plus more
Ah, no... no... no...
Ouch!
Feels good.
This feels so good.
This is bad.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I want to put it in.
Do you want me to put it in?
Yes, put it in.
I'm going to put it in.
Oh, it's hot.
Hmm...
Are you feeling okay?
Phew…
Well, I'll welcome them.
It feels nice!
No!
Ouch…
Mm.
Ah.
Feels good.
Ah, it's cold.
I feel so good.
Oh, no. Oh, no. I feel so good.
Mmm, uh!
I'm in trouble.
No way...
Let's get out!
Let's go!
Rika...
I'm so tired.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
It hurts.
It's going to hurt.
Ouch!
I'm going!
A-ah!
Feels so nice!
I can't do this.
Oh, no...
I'm okay...
No, no, no, no...
I'm going!
Oh, I'm so tired.
I'm so tired.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
Mom, I can't. It hurts.
Ah, ah...
Ah...
Yes, yes.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh, whew, whew...
Oh, oh, oh...
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh, oh!
Whoa, whoa!
...Oh, oh, oh!
...Oh!
Oh, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
No, no, no.
I'm going.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
A little to the side, came back.
So we're almost there.
Ah, it feels good.
I want more.
Oh, it's so painful.
It feels so good.
Oh, it feels good.
Mm.
I have to這是!
Oh.
No...
I have to....
Yeah.
I feel good.
I want more.
Oh, I see.
Oh, no.
It feels so good.
Electric shock
You feel good?
Yeah
It'll be fine.
We'll get them in there.
Give me a hug.
We are welling here, our love to share
Today the day where your book really begins
Days were too soon, in the sky we find our roots
We're on a separate way, setting paragraphs
Separated by the same paragraphs
To let your life be one to light the way
Forever and a day
We'll be best friends as we do today
We're moving on, our life's been opened up
Remember all the times we had together then
Our memories will never fall away
Thank you very much for watching this video.
Please subscribe to my channel and give it a high rating.
RUKAWA YUU
Hello, I'm RUKAWA YUU,
who played the role of Yuu,
in the movie,
which is a daily life of just having sex in a quiet countryside and sweating.
Nice to meet you.
What is the content of this work?
This work is a love drama.
This time, it was hot sex.
How was it?
It was very hot, but I think I was able to have a hot sex.
Did you find it difficult to act when you were acting?
Even though I knew the story, I had to pretend that I didn't know the story.
It was tough, but I think I had a good experience.
That's what I wanted to say.
You played the role of memory loss.
Do you have any past that you want to forget?
A past that I want to forget?
It's something I can't forget, so I forget a lot.
I don't know.
Do you often forget things?
I do a lot. I can't forget.
I think you played Yuu this time, but what kind of woman is Yuu, the main character you saw from Yuu?
I thought she was a very pure girl.
Do you have any similarities with Yuu-san?
I don't want to forget.
There is a scene where you forgive your senior.
Have you ever had an issue with your seniors?
I don't think I have a senior.
What was the hardest part of this project?
The most difficult thing for me was to manage my facial expressions.
What was difficult about managing your facial expressions?
I thought it would be difficult to make a sad expression or to be surprised.
This time, I think it was a winter shoot, but was it hard?
That's right. It was cold.
It was hard because it was the opposite of the season.
Do you have a favorite scene?
I have a lot of favorite scenes.
What do you want to do when you grow up?
I want to get along with my childhood friend again.
That's how I want to develop.
Do you have anything in common as a child?
I have a boy, but I have never had any flirting with boys.
I thought you wouldn't talk.
Then when did you start in school?
When was my third year in high school?
What kind of role do you want to play next?
What kind of role do you want to play?
I want to play a role that I've never played before.
For example, what kind of role do you want to play?
For example...
I can't think of anything right now.
Do you have a situation you want to try?
A situation?
A situation is...
Yeah.
This time, you were in the countryside.
And your work was love-struck.
What kind of love-struck work would you like to try next?
I want to try something like a lovey-dovey kind of thing.
Do you like lovey-dovey sex?
Rather than being intense or painful, I like that kind of feeling.
This time, you were sweating a lot. How do you feel?
It felt so good.
I'm going.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
It's the first time, so I'm still nervous and anxious.
You guys are so annoying.
Let's go take a break.
Okay, let's go.
I'm really tired.
I do have a lot of work to do.
I'll do my best.
I'm sure you are tired.
I'm sure you are.
Go!
How did you feel when you watched the last shoot?
Yes.
I had a hard time, but I did my best, so I want you to watch it a lot.
Thank you very much.