Please be careful.
Oh, thank you.
That's great.
It's fun.
Everyone, please take a break here.
After that, please go to the inn.
Excuse me.
Can I make a phone call?
Yes.
Oh, hello.
Hello? It's you?
I just got to the inn
and I'm taking a break.
I'll be there soon.
Oh, you're taking a break?
Are you okay?
Are you sick? I'm fine.
My boss and the employees are all married.
I'm serious.
That's it.
Call me again when you arrive at the inn.
OK. I'll call you again.
See you.
Husband? It's hard.
And you look like a newlywed.
I made a promise.
If I accept the employee's
request, I will call you.
I'm 6 years married.
I'm a very worried person.
You are boring.
Do you have a child?
Yes.
I see.
Well, during this trip, be free
from your husband and have fun.
Thank you very much.
I have been working as a
full-time employee since last month.
It's a small advertising
agency for men, but it's an
at-home company that supports
me who is inexperienced.
It's hard to keep my
worried husband, but I
found out that I wanted
to build a new couple.
I would like to build up
the shape of the future.
Yes, that's right.
I'm relieved that the
diagnosis came out properly.
What? Divorce? Wait a minute.
I don't think about divorce.
Because I can't have children.
His heart disease is a disease.
I know you don't like
it, but it can't be helped.
Instead, I'm going to start working.
As a full-time employee.
It was hard to convince you.
But you managed to convince
me, and now you're supporting me.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Even if we don't have kids,
we can still be a married couple.
So you don't have to worry about it.
See you later.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good morning.
Please take a bath.
We will have a party from 6 p.m. to 6 p.m.
Please don't be late.
Ms. Natsume.
The party room will be
our large guest room.
Thank you.
I'll see you at 6 p.m.
Please.
I'll give you the key.
Here you are.
Hello, Senpai.
Thank you.
Hello.
Hello?
I just arrived at the hotel.
It's calm.
It looks like this.
Can you see it?
I'm going to take a
bath, so I'm going to go to
the dinner party after
I finish taking a bath.
What? Do I have to eat dinner with you?
You can refuse, can't you?
Hurry up and eat.
Wash the ice cream
and go back to your room.
And don't drink alcohol.
I took a bath and feel refreshed.
I'm sorry.
The bath here was the best.
I agree.
And the food was delicious.
By the way, where is Natsume?
Why did you love her?
Well, to put it simply, you're my type.
I thought so.
You're married and inexperienced,
so you don't have a strategy.
You're right. You're a little sexy.
This job interview may be a chance to
shorten the distance between you and her.
You're really sexy.
Really?
You said you couldn't get
enough of Natsume's eroticism.
I know, but...
I've gotten tired of going
to the Happening Bar lately.
Isn't it more fun to
sleep over? Excuse me.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, Natsume-san, sit here.
Look, it's on.
I'm not good at drinking.
No, no, it's okay. Just have
a drink with me, okay? Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
Let's have a toast while deepening
our relationship with Natsume-san.
Cheers!
By the way, Natsume-san,
you're married, right?
Why did you decide to start working?
What do you think now?
I feel bored every day as a housewife.
But your husband is worried about you.
He must be worried when
he sees such a beautiful wife.
No, he isn't.
Let's forget about your
husband and have a drink.
Do you still have
alcohol? Oh, I'm sorry.
Then, drink it.
I heard that crab is delicious here.
You should go there.
Please go there.
Natsume-san, please eat a lot.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
―Second part―
My sparring partner
gets tired, doesn't she?
If I were her,I wouldn't do it.
And she doesn't know it
even if she cheated just a little.
I'm just kidding.
Are you OK?
Well, let's have another drink
and then we'll say good-bye.
OK.
Thank you.
It was too late when I woke up
because my consciousness was far away.
It was already too late when I woke up.
My boss, who had changed his
appearance, covered me with a blanket.
It's nice to be alone.
Is it beautiful? It smells good.
Are you tired? Please stop.
Please let me go.
Mitsune.
Look.
This is a company trip.
There are also such happenings.
No.
Right?
It's a big deal.
Let's enjoy it.
No.
It's okay.
That's right.
Please stop.
You've been drinking too much.
You've lost your strength.
You're under a lot of stress
because of your husband, aren't you?
You need to relieve your stress.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm so happy.
There is a lot of hair.
What's wrong? You're wet here.
It was my dream to have
you do this since you came in.
I'm glad you're here.
I want to hold you.
It's okay.
You're not here, so
let's have fun like this.
I'm your boss, so you have to listen to me.
You are beautiful, Natsumi-san.
Natsumi-san, when did you
last have sex with your husband?
I'm just going to rub you like this.
It's okay.
I'm just going to rub you.
You haven't done anything yet.
Don't you want it? Please stop.
It's OK.
Please be honest.
You want to put it in
your mouth, don't you?
I can't stand it anymore.
I finally got into your mouth, Natsume.
I'm going to move.
I'm sorry.
Natsume, you are connected to me.
Can you see me, Natsume?
Natsumi, are you okay?
Which do you prefer,
your husband or Natsumi?
Natsumi, you are so sensitive.
It's easy for you to get angry.
It's good, isn't it?
I won't give up.
If you are so big and kind,
your subordinates will get up.
Natsume-san, let's have
fun on this business trip.
Natsume-san, your cell phone is ringing.
Hello? What are you doing? Are you okay?
I'll be back soon. I'll call you later.
What? Are you drinking? Are you okay?
What?
Are you the husband of the patient?
Yes.
It must be hard for you.
Natsume-san, I'm so glad.
Asu... Moto...
Asu, really... I
want to do it again.
You didn't feel sick,
did you? Please stop.
Please stop.
You are a big girl now.
I'm sorry.
You're having fun, aren't you,
Natsume-san? Please stop it.
Stop it.
It's still messy here.
I'm sorry.
It's going to work.
That's good, Hatsune.
Do you still care about your husband?
Let's forget about Ayano and have fun.
Don't stand up.
Mamedaifuku is in a bad mood today.
Be honest with yourself.
It's great.
It's tight.
I can't stand it anymore.
Yatsune-san, can I go again?
Natsume-san, you can do it
as many times as you want.
Do you want to do it one more time?
Do you want me to give you a massage?
I'll give you a massage.
I'll start from the bottom.
I told you to go to bed early.
You forget your husband.
Hello?
Were you really sleeping?
Are you OK? I'm tired.
Really.
Hey, I can hear a man's voice.
Where are you?
I'm going to have breakfast.
Anyway, I'll hang up.
What?
It was a good thing.
Hey, uncle.
Let's have a drink.
No, no.
Uncle, please.
Sorry.
Cheers!
Natsume, you drink too.
It's not bad to drink in the daytime.
Let's toast.
Cheers! It's delicious.
How was your trip? It was
fun, wasn't it? Yes, it was.
It was fun yesterday, wasn't it?
Right?
Let's have more fun in the future.
It's a shame.
You're like this again.
It's all your fault.
Can I ask you to do it
again? Let's have fun.
Again.
Are you serious?
Come on, sit down.
You still have a long way to go.
You're fine, aren't you?
If you're with Natsume,
you can do anything.
You can do it.
You have to be more open-minded.
Put your hand in your panties.
How do you feel?
How do you feel? It's hard.
Don't worry.
I'm taking a bath.
Are you ready? Look at me.
You are still energetic, aren't you?
I'm not going to lose
to a young man like you.
As expected of Mr. Sabe.
Come on, touch it.
Mr. Natsume.
This was in it.
Don't be so embarrassed.
Come on, look at me.
You are so beautiful, Natsume-san.
Your husband is jealous of you.
Come closer to me.
Slowly put your tongue out.
Good girl.
Please do not use your hands.
Which is bigger, your
husband's penis or my penis?
Please answer me.
Oh, I see.
Well, I'll ask you more.
You have to enjoy it.
It's a private trip.
Can I take a close-up of you?
Show me your face.
Peace, peace.
Natsume-san.
I'll never forget you.
Don't be so embarrassed.
Please.
Please take a look, Mr. Omori.
Mr. Omori.
Please continue.
This is very soft, isn't it?
First of all, with your hands.
Mr. Omori, please let me lick your wings.
My chimpanzee.
Ohoho
Hatsune-san, it's time for you to lick me.
Ahahaha
That's right, that's right.
The back of the head.
You're good at it, aren't you, Hatsune-san?
I'd like you to lick me as it is.
Please give me a high-five.
I'll suck your head.
I'll lick your head and go up.
Lick it up to the top.
Just with your mouth.
Ah! Look this way.
Good.
Peace.
You are so nice, Natsume-san.
Let me play with you.
Faster.
Use your hands.
Look at me.
Squeeze it.
Wow~!
Oh, photos and photos.
Great.
Look, Nagisa-san.
Look, Mutsuki-san.
See, you have to do it with a smile.
Look, peace is being eaten away.
What the hell is he doing?
What is he doing? Thank you.
May I? I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Wow.
You're sweating a lot.
Katsume-san.
It's fun to travel with
employees, isn't it?
Yes.
It's nice to be able to do
a lot of pleasant things.
Can I take this off?
I'll take it off.
I'll take it off as a memory
of the employee trip.
Fingers, fingers.
It seems that he is in a good mood.
He is so erotic.
Natsume-san's fur feels really good.
I feel like I'm going to go there soon.
It's getting cold.
Hey, Natsume.
Hey, Shimizu.
Show me your body more.
I'm going to put my butt on your neck.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel so good.
I can't stop.
You are doing great, Natsume-san.
Your buttocks are the best.
Look at your face.
Natsume-san,
here? Please tell me.
Where is it?
Please tell me where it is, Natsumi-san.
Here?
The baby is crying.
The baby's nipples are hard from the bra.
Is it here?
How many times did you go to the vet
this time, Natsume-san? I don't know.
Are you going to sleep?
You look sleepy.
What's the matter?
You are such a mischievous boy.
You are scratching your own back.
What's wrong?
Are you satisfied with this?
Do you want more?
You are scratching your own back.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Your shoulders are stiff.
It's over.
Let me see your butt.
How do you feel?
Your butt looks round.
It's a good day, isn't it, my wife?
I'm taking a video of you, too.
Oh, you're in the video again.
It feels good.
I'm going to touch you.
Are you OK?
Where do you feel pain?
Be careful, be careful.
I'm glad I adopted you.
Huh?
Let me see your mouth.
I'm going to give you a bath.
Wow, that's amazing.
You are so good.
I'm so happy to have such
a good father, Natsume-kun.
Natsume-san, you are my treasure.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The movement of the tongue is wonderful.
Mr. Hayatsume, please look at me.
You must be happy to
have such an experience.
Did it work well? Yes, it did.
It's wonderful.
I'm counting on you, Tama.
You're doing great.
Let's throw it together this time.
You can throw it together,
but let's do it this way.
You've never had such
an experience, have you?
Your tongue is also...
You've never had such
an experience, have you?
I was worried that he would
get sick, but he was fine.
I thought he'd be fine if I did something,
but I thought he'd be fine if I didn't.
I was so worried that I
didn't know what to do.
I'm going to give you a treat.
Do you want more?
Do you feel good? It's so fun.
It's fun, isn't it? Look at me.
Don't push me.
Relax your legs.
You are very sleepy.
You feel good,
don't you? I'm sorry.
I can't let you go.
I feel good.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
That's right.
That's right. Move, move.
That's right. Rub, rub.
That's good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my!
It's incredibly painful.
I've overdone it.
I'm strangled.
Ah, my poor back.
My back is frizzing.
It won't hurt so soon.
Oh, I see.
Can you see it?
Can you see it? I can't see it.
Mamedaifuku, your mouth is dry.
Mamedaifuku, you can
move your mouth as you like.
Your mouth is dry.
Are you happy to touch
your mouth and tongue?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
The baby's crying is so cute.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I'm glad I adopted you.
I'm going to take a look at your back.
I can't see your back.
Oh, wow.
Let me see your back.
Show me your face.
Good girl.
Do you feel good?
You are about to fall asleep.
I want you to get out of the bed.
Do you want me to get you out of the bed?
I'm open, I'm open, I'm open,
I'm open, I'm open, I'm open.
Natsume-san, you want more, don't you?
Oh, you've got a lot out.
I'll give you back.
Natsume-san, you can put your arm on it.
I'm sorry.
You're covered in blood.
I wonder what your wife
will think when she sees this.
Do you feel guilty?
Then, do you want to stop?
Do you want to
continue? I'm sorry.
It's tight.
Natsume-san, please put
your elbow on my shoulder.
Look at your face.
Good.
Look, peace, peace.
Nice to see you all.
Nice to see you.
Mom, please go to the examination.
It's going well.
And I'm really sorry for
making you worry about me.
【Translated by 7 MEN 侍 fan, thank you!】