Hello, Mew?
What are you doing?
You said you would
come back this afternoon.
Hey, hello?
Hey, honey.
I...
I can't go back to you anymore.
Because... I...
With my colleagues...
This summer, I came to a
one-night trip with the men of a
small IT equipment sales
company that I work as a dispatcher.
The department we belong
to seems to be making a lot
of money in this area, and
the head office paid for it.
That's how it is.
I'm so tired.
Really?
Then,
do you want to do it today?
Huh? What?
What do you mean?
Making a baby?
Ah...
I think my back hurts a little.
Well... It's about time
for me to have a baby.
It's only a few days away.
You don't have to rush.
I'll do it by the time you're 35.
I'm going to bed.
3 years after marriage.
My husband's salary was good.
I didn't have any problems with my life.
But my desire to have a
child was against my will.
My husband couldn't take it, and I
was embarrassed, but I was full of desire.
I started working as a dispatcher a
year ago, hoping to change my mood.
Thank you very much.
This is the dispatcher's office.
Please come in.
It's nice.
Thank you very much.
It's great.
It's amazing.
I'm going to kill my parents-in-law.
This is a good one.
Then I'll put the tea in.
I'll help you.
You don't have to do that.
It's a trip, so make it easy.
But Miyu-San is a good woman who
is serious and thoughtful, isn't she?
No, I don't think so.
Mr. Takemoto, that kind
of thing is like Morahara.
What? Is it harassment just by praising?
Well, I'm sorry to invite
you on a trip all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's a trip with people
who are taking care of me.
I'm glad to hear that.
That's good.
Take your time as your husband says.
Yes.
Then, it's time for dinner.
Would you like to come
to this room at 19 o'clock?
Yes.
Then, it's time to use the open-air bath.
From now until 19 o'clock, women.
After that, men are
allowed to stay until 10 P.M.
After that, you are allowed to
have sex, so please be careful.
Sex?
Are there any other customers?
No, today, only you
are allowed to have sex.
Oh, I see.
Shiromine-San,
why don't you go take a bath?
You must be tired to come all the way here.
Is it okay?
Of course.
Then, I'll prepare your yukata right away.
I'll do as you say.
This way, please.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
Chief, the reception
from the office is bad.
Chief, are you listening?
Shut up!
I can't believe it.
It was terrible, wasn't it?
We were all in the company's debt.
But you stole the company's
money and ran away.
Shut up!
We've been working hard.
That's how we were treated.
It's only 5 million bucks. It's cheap.
What the hell are you talking about?
But if we don't do
anything, we'll be arrested.
Shut up!
You'll feel better if you drink alcohol.
Are you sure about Miyu?
Yes, you said you like her.
Yes, but she's not a bad person.
You guys don't know anything, do you?
That woman is...
She's not the kind of woman who does
delivery oil at home with a cheap salary.
Her husband is a famous businessman
in the city and an elite who works hard.
He's an elite, beautiful,
and he's got a lot of money.
But why do you think he's
working with a cheap guy like us?
It's to look down on us
and be enthralled by us.
Besides, a woman who lives such a
wealthy life is greedy and unhappy.
That's why...
Hehehehehehehehehehe.
Ahhhhh.
Oh, Shiromine-San
You took a long time.
Sorry, but I started earlier I'm
sorry, the hot water was really good.
Oh, I see.
How about a drink, Shiromine-San?
I don't drink alcohol A little.
Really?
But it's easy to drink.
Take a sip.
Well, thank you.
It's good.
Right?
More, more.
A little.
Thank you.
Oh, that's good.
No, no.
You're happy, right?
Yes.
Hiromine,
you're quite a talker.
No, I'm not.
Director,
since we're so lucky,
let's play a game.
Ta-da!
The King's Game.
You!
The King's Game?
That's not good.
But you've done it before, haven't you?
Kissing someone you don't like.
That's nice.
I want you to kiss me, Miyu.
Well...
If it's just a cheek...
That's nice.
Let's get started.
Let's do it.
Who wants to go first?
Miyu?
Go ahead.
Who is the king?
Yes.
Well, it's the first time, so
let's go lightly for the first time.
Let's go easy on this one, shall we?
Okay, number one...
...will massage number three's shoulders.
Who's number one?
It's me.
Oh!
Number three is me!
I'm so jealous of you, boss!
Okay, I'll massage your shoulders.
Oh, that's good.
Good, good.
It feels good.
Is this okay?
Yes, it is.
Is it done?
Isn't it too early?
Let's eat.
Who is the king?
It's me.
What should I do?
Should I say my name?
Shiromine-San.
Kiss Takimoto-kun.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Kiss him.
On the cheek?
I'm scared.
Hurry up and kiss me.
That's nice.
Who's the king?
It's me again.
I'm going to be a master of war.
I'm going to be a king forever.
Okay.
I have an idea.
What?
Usagi-kun.
Usagi-kun, kiss Shiomine-San.
What?
Listen to me.
I'll never do that.
Deep kiss.
No.
Show me your tongue.
Let's move on to the next one.
Sachi-kun and Tanimoto-kun.
Both of you have to suck
on Shiromine-San's breasts.
Me?
The king will say it.
Please don't.
King, can I kiss you while watching?
No, I won't.
The king will say it.
I'll make him drink sake.
Good.
I'll do it.
You do it.
Come on.
Hiromiya.
Open your mouth.
Good boy.
You are so colorful.
Next,
I'll make Tanimoto drink sake.
You are... You are...
How do you feel?
Here you are.
Because there are low-ranking officials.
Next, Saki-kun.
Time-bending boobs.
Akimoto-kun is stepping.
Please don't do it.
I'll take it off.
The king is the first one to do it.
I'm sorry.
My husband is here.
My husband told you to grow your hair.
I'm sorry.
The king will cut your nipples.
I'll take it off.
Give me your neck.
Wait.
Open your legs.
I'm thinking about the people.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I know.
Let's drink Wakame sake.
Wakame sake?
I'll make you sleep.
Wait.
Please stop.
Where are you going?
The king's order.
He's a good man.
It's good, isn't it?
I'll show you the king's butt.
Stop it.
Show me your butt.
It's the king's order.
I'll help you.
Listen to the king's order.
Lie down.
It smells good.
The king is going to smell it.
It's strange.
I feel like I'm in a hot
spring and my skin is smooth.
I'll allow you to sit on the king.
You can sit on the king's throne.
Rub it on the king.
Don't lie to me.
How do you feel?
Hiromine.
Don't lie to me.
Or I'll move.
Sachi.
Give her a kiss.
Give him a kiss.
Akimoto, give him a kiss.
Yes.
The king has been captured.
Put your legs together.
Good.
Rub the king's face.
Good boy.
Next, face the front.
Keep your yukata on.
Why are you so shy?
You got wet in the bath, didn't you?
Take off your sleeves.
Take it out and cut it again.
This is the right style of our people.
Let's lick together.
Come on, drink it!
It's okay.
Drink it, Reiko.
I'm going to drink it, too.
I wonder how much it feels.
No, wait!
Stop it!
Do you like it sweet or bitter?
I don't know.
No, I don't want to.
You still don't know?
Tachibana, put on your underwear.
It's the king's order.
It's an order.
No, I don't want to.
I'll take care of you.
No, no, no.
Sajimoto, Saji.
I'll give you a big beer.
No, no, no.
Tell me the color and condition.
The color is already pink.
It's beautiful pink.
You're so cute.
Next, tell me how it tastes.
How does it taste?
I'll give you some water.
Stop it.
It's delicious.
I'll see how you lick it.
Look at me.
You can't say that.
I can't say that.
I'll tell you where you are licking.
It's an order from the king.
Why can't you say that?
You can't say that.
I'll bite your mouth.
What?
What did you say?
We want to see Shilomune-San's face.
Okay, let's see his face.
Boso-San, please.
I want to look at his face.
You want to look at his face?
Oh, you want to look at his back?
Yes.
Oh, Shilomune-San, please.
Please give me away.
Please let me look at his face from here.
Can I spit it out?
I don't want to.
You don't want to, do you?
You can lick the king's nipples.
Lick his nipples.
You can lick more, can't you?
You are the best.
You are a girl.
You are cute.
You are so cute.
How do you feel?
Do you feel warm?
I'm so excited.
Shiromine, look at this.
What is this?
I'm so excited.
Hiromine-San will eat the meat of Kaji-kun.
I don't want to.
I won't.
What are you saying?
Please talk more.
Open your mouth.
Are you ready?
Sashiko, open your mouth.
Here we go.
It's okay.
Let's take your tongue out.
Take your tongue out.
Do you want me to fix it?
I'll fix it.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Let me see your tongue.
Okay.
Let me taste it.
I can feel the taste of the cat.
This beautiful woman touched the cat.
Come on.
Hey, you guys.
It's time for the king to go.
Come on.
I'm making good use of the new microphone.
Dad, where are you going?
Here, here, here.
I was told to lie down here.
That's so gross.
You're so gross.
I know.
I'm so pissed off.
Look, it's in your cheek.
Ok, Tachiboto-kun.
Sachi-kun, you sleep here.
You two sleep side by side.
Ok, Shiromine-kun.
You sleep between the two of them.
Ok.
You have to shower them one by one.
Ok, this hand, this hand.
It's a good thing.
It's really good.
This massage is the best.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it alternately.
You're right.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
You're right.
It's a little hard.
Don't stop.
I'll give you a little more.
I'll take it.
First of all, you have to
drink sake while you do it.
Swallow it while it's still in your mouth.
That's it.
Oh, my God.
That's it, that's it.
Ok, ok.
It's ok, it's ok.
It's ok.
It feels good.
It's not that bad.
It's ok, it's ok.
It's ok.
Ouch!
Dad...
The three of us, just the two of us...
I'm so sad.
I'm so sad and sad.
You're getting drunk again.
You're taking a bath.
We'll clean it up for you.
It's late at night, so...
Let's go take a bath.
You're going to be okay.
I'll be back.
Hiromine-San, the kiss I gave you
earlier, how did you feel about it?
Please stop.
Let me do it.
I see.
You are so beautiful.
I'm glad to see you again.
You are so cute.
Let's kiss.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
I'm not sure if I can do
it, but I'm doing my best.
I'm glad I was able to do it.
No, no, no, no!
Do you feel good?
Are you comfortable?
No, no, no, no!
It's about to melt.
I'm sure it's a good texture.
No, no, no, no!
Move your hand.
I'm cold.
What's wrong?
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it at all.
What's wrong?
Why are you shaking?
I can't stand it.
Give me a kiss.
I'm sorry.
You are feeling it, right?
You like it, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Which one do you feel?
The one between your breasts?
I'm sorry.
Do you feel it on both sides?
Yes.
Then, you should also wash your face.
I'm sorry.
You've had a lot of water, haven't you?
Don't say no.
Why are you licking me?
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
You are so good girl.
You have a lot of hair.
You're doing great.
Do you want me to wash you?
I'll wash you.
You, you shouldn't have done that.
Don't do that.
You shouldn't have poured the water.
Please don't do that.
Please.
That was a good bath.
Please, no!
No! No!
You're so beautiful, I
need to take this off.
You're trembling.
Can you feel it, Michi?
Let me get more.
It's hot!
You want to drink more, don't you?
Thank you!
I'm going to close the lid.
It's hot!
Don't do that.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Raise your head.
Give me a kiss.
I'm going to wash your face.
Your hands are beautiful.
What?
I'm going to wash your face.
Let's go.
Mr.Shiromine.
We can't hide it anymore.
Our future will be gone in this summer.
We can't run the company anymore.
We were all the tail of the lizard.
That's why I made a lot of money and thought
I'd take you with me for the last time.
As I thought, you were
a terrible evil woman.
It felt good, didn't it? It's not over yet.
Did you wash it well?
No, I didn't.
You don't have to wash it.
I'm so happy.
Please don't do this to me.
Shiroomi, you pretend to be a quiet wife.
You should be more open-minded.
I didn't know you were so open-minded.
No, I'm not.
You felt it, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Let's find out which part of
your body you feel the most.
The one who feels the most is the winner.
How do you like it?
It's the best, isn't it?
How do you feel?
Chikubi-chan, you are groaning.
You have long legs.
Your legs are surprisingly cute.
You are still groaning.
Your legs are surprisingly comfortable.
You look like a model.
I can feel your butt.
You look like you're having a good time.
You're wearing these erotic panties again.
You're so erotic.
Let's have a good time.
You can do it.
As if you did nothing wrong.
I'll do it for you.
This is my honor.
I'll make a hole in your buttock.
Can you feel my butt?
You, please don't.
Do you feel it?
Here, I made a hole in
your butt using my free hand.
There is a hole in the
buttocks that has been
used for a long time
and has become beautiful.
What does it taste like?
Do you feel it in your buttocks?
I haven't told you yet.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm a woman who can
feel the hole in my butt.
You already said it.
I'm a woman who can
feel the hole in my butt.
You shouldn't be quiet
when I'm licking your butthole.
Can you tell me?
I'll tell you.
I can't do it.
Your buttocks hurt, don't you?
My buttocks! It hurts!
You are a pervert.
I will not let you come here anymore.
I put you in a hole.
You are a pervert.
I'm sorry.
You don't resist to be petted.
What's wrong with your hand?
Please lick me more.
I'm not wrong.
I'll lick you when I'm with you.
I'm sorry.
Tell me that you are a woman
who feels good when you are licked.
I'm sorry.
You are the wife of an upper-class person.
You feel good when
you are licked, don't you?
I'm sorry.
Tell me that you feel good.
I feel good.
Don't do it!
Which one do you want to be licked?
Or touched by hand?
Which one?
Don't do it!
Or both?
Both?
You want to be licked by both?
Oh, you did it.
You are a good girl.
No, I'm not.
You said shut up.
Why did you say shut up?
Why are you sweating so much?
Do you feel that you are
touched by a man's hand?
I can feel the poison in your body.
Stop it.
I can feel it all over your body.
Is your body all the same?
Stop it.
What's wrong?
My mouth...
Look at her.
You're already like this.
Your mouth is full of saliva.
My mouth...
It's all over your body.
I can see you're pulling a string.
Don't do it.
What kind of saliva is this?
You're pulling a string
from your salivary gland.
It hurts.
Let's go.
Do you want to go with Manko?
It's a terrible pleasure, isn't it?
It's a terrible pleasure to
be touched by a man, isn't it?
You move your waist
without moving your hands.
No!
You've been in a lot of pain.
I hope you feel better.
I wonder how far you can go.
I'm sure you're in a good mood.
You're in a good mood.
No!
Massage! Massage!
What? Massage?
Why? You don't want a massage?
Why are you feeling better?
Because you're a tosukebe, right?
Say, I'm a tosukebe woman
who feels better by massaging.
Say it.
I'm a tosukebe woman who
feels better by massaging.
Oh...
You look so tired.
Please stop...
I'm not going to stop.
What's wrong?
You have sweat on your back.
You're a girl.
You're a woman.
You have a good voice, don't you?
What's wrong with you?
You can't feel it, can you?
Oh, you look happy.
You look like you're in a good mood.
You look so happy.
You can't stop crying.
He's still sleeping.
Let's go.
Can you do it?
I can do it.
oh, my god.
What's wrong?
It's not a break yet.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Good girl.
You've been so quiet.
What's going on?
You were so quiet.
Why are you so quiet?
You're so funny.
We're going to get a cold again.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't be out of
breath even if you're funny.
Oh?
Oh!
You're all wet.
Help me!
Oh!
You are so cute.
You like it, don't you?
I'm sorry.
You don't resist at all.
You want to do it yourself.
You can do it You can do it.
Good, good.
What are you doing?
I'm going to put it in.
You are a clumsy woman.
I was bullied by my boyfriend.
You are a good girl.
Don't cry.
His upper and lower mouth are being combed.
He is being combed.
It feels good, right?
I'm not going to let you go.
You're in a bad mood again.
You're in a bad mood, aren't you?
It's hot.
I'll give you a kiss.
Are you leaving?
Are you going to go to
the doctor's clinic again?
I'm going to the clinic again.
You are eating the cat food.
Raise your hand.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be late.
I'm going to go.
I might be late today.
I see.
So, you're not going
to make it today either.
Don't rush.
Kids take their time to think.
No, I'm not.
What's wrong?
Hey, honey.
What would you do if I cheated on you?
What are you talking about?
If I did that...
I'm just kidding.
Well, have a nice day.
I thought I was kidding
when I said I cheated on you.
But maybe I was looking for someone
other than him somewhere in my heart.
If not...
After all, hot Springs are
only in the morning bath.
I've been sweating all night, so
it doesn't feel particularly good.
Oh, Miyu-San, you're awake.
How many shots did I shoot?
I don't think you'll be
able to get pregnant.
Listen, Miyu.
I'm sure you know this.
You've become our
captive in just one night.
I'll tell you this, but we have
no place to go back to Tokyo.
Why don't we go somewhere together?
That's a good idea.
I can't believe it.
What?
Even if I go home,
I can't leave my husband.
I can't.
What?
You're the same.
You've been betrayed by someone important.
We're friends, aren't we?
Me, too.
Then, let's fall together.
Let's go all the way down to the
bottom of the mountain, shall we?
Then we'll go all the way down to
the bottom of the mountain, shall we?
We've been doing it all night,
but we're still not good enough.
Yeah.
There, now you can do it.
You can hold my face and rub it in.
Rub, rub, my child.
I'll make you pretty.
You're so witty.
What are you doing?
You and I have a good relationship.
You are a mess.
You two look like
you've been through a lot.
Does it feel good?
It's enough, isn't it?
Tell me that.
You don't have to cry.
I don't have to cry.
I'm so happy that I
don't have to do anything.
I know, right?
I can hear the sound of
your stomach rumbling.
Don't forget your stomach.
Thank you.
Where did you get your finger?
I got my finger in Dosuke's hand.
You are so mean to Dosuke.
I'm sorry.
(*´∀ゝ∀ゝ∀ゝ∀*).
You're so cute, but you're just talking.
(*´∀ゝ∀ゝ∀ゝ∀*)
Oh...
I can't believe we've been this together...
Oh... Oh... Oh...
I wonder if we still have the last shot.
You have a lot of hair.
Do you like this side better?
It's so hot.
You look good.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's good.
It's good for your husband, isn't it?
Yes.
It's good for your upper and lower mouth.
It's all over your face.
Look at the other
person's face and lick it.
Is it good?
It's good.
It's better than your father-in-law's.
Don't make me lick your feet.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
You're drooling so deliciously.
Is it delicious?
A little more.
Ms. Mari, don't you know?
Here, here, here, here.
Here, here, here.
Oh, dear.
Ah!
Ah...
I miss you so much.
Tell me, where are you licking?
Please say it loudly.
My butt...
He's licking my butt.
I'm touching your butt,
and you're licking mine.
He's licking my butt.
I'm still licking it.
Have you ever licked something like this?
Let's have a good bath.
the other is alas.
as this good
hard.
for.
the.
Steaming struggling
Ah... felt terrible.
Ah... super...
feels really bad.
Ah... Ah...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
Look at me.
I'm taking a picture of us.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
You have to sleep.
She is going to sleep.
You are doing great.
If your husband knows
this, he will be surprised.
You must be tired.
Let's go to the manager's room again.
That's right.
This side, too.
You'll get better.
I don't know what to do with this.
I just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You love Kimpo, don't you?
Yes.
Do you love Kimpo?
Yes, I love Kimpo.
You love your husband's Kimpo, don't you?
Yes.
I don't want to die.
I'm going to give it to you as it is.
Let's go.
I'm scared.
It's okay, it's okay.
Are you alright?
It's OK, it's OK.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I feel good, too.
I'm so sorry.
What's wrong?
Hello, Miyu?
What are you doing?
You said you'd be back this afternoon.
Hey! Hello?
Hey, honey.
I can't go back to you anymore.
Because I had a lot of sex
with the guys at the company.
I've had a lot of sex, so
I've been reminded of the
joy of being a woman by
these people more than you.