This is good.
Welcome back.
I love you.
I love you, too.
The rice is ready.
I don't need it.
Eat it first.
Later.
I don't need it.
Half a year ago, I had
an older boyfriend named Shigeki, but I got
married to a young Shunji from the same
company who had already attacked.
Shigeki, a playboy,
quit the company and became normal.
My choice was not wrong.
I'm sorry.
He comes home every day,
without a detour, and hugs me right away.
So I always wake up late at night.
Oh, no.
Not there.
What? No, not there.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was in a hurry.
I didn't want to tell you.
It's okay. I just took a short nap.
Oh, I'm sorry. What am I doing?
I made a terrible mistake.
Don't worry about it. I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
Really?
Yes.
But it's cold.
It's not my
fault, is it? Yes, it is.
Why?
It's not your fault, is it?
What? Is
it my fault? No, it's not.
Really?
I may have known a new pleasure.
When the tip of my husband's genitalia,
which I had not expected, was pulled out,
At that time, I was surprised at the feeling
that something was going to come out.
But I can't say that to a serious husband.
I've never been worried
about it before, but
the hole in my butt
is still a sexual organ.
It is said that you get
pleasure when you make a hole in something.
Certainly, when I entered
and left my husband's room last night,
I had a pleasant feeling
that I had never felt before.
I can't see well.
I can't go.
No, I can't. What am
I doing? It feels good.
The messenger was my ex-husband, Shigeki.
Why didn't I block him when we got married?
When I found out that my husband couldn't
accept this, my desire became even bigger.
Shunji, why?
I was wondering if you were
happy after leaving me and marrying Shunji.
Do you feel like you
have to clean your ass during the day?
Hey, hey, hey,
you've become a ridiculous pervert.
No, no.
What's the difference?
I've been watching you all the time.
What is it?
Don't make a noise.
What are you
doing? Hey, hey, hey.
Your butt is hitting me.
Are you trying to seduce me?
No.
You are, aren't you?
It's not like I don't know you.
What?
Do you remember
the taste of the ass hole? Let me see.
No, it's not that.
What? Please, don't.
It's a little spread, isn't it?
No, it's not that.
What?
When did you learn the taste of blood vein?
Does he know?
No.
Please.
What? You learned the taste
of blood vein, didn't you? Don't do it.
Don't do it.
Do you want me to give you a butt massage?
No, I don't want to.
You've had a lot of sex, haven't you?
Have you had a lot of sex?
How do you feel?
How do you feel? Oh, I see.
Oh, I see.
Stay still, Natsuki.
Stay still.
Don't cry.
Hey, hey, hey,
you can feel it, can't you? No, I can't.
No, I can't.
Hey, Asuki.
I'll teach you the goodness of blood.
It's been a long time
since I did this with you.
How is it?
Did you have a good marriage life?
Maybe you didn't have a good marriage life.
That's why
you were playing with your butthole.
You were playing
with me, weren't you? You are a girl.
I'm scared.
You are quiet.
Manko is getting wet.
It's bitter.
I'll make you feel it with my butt.
I'll give you a massage.
Be quiet.
You have a lot of blood vessels.
It's been a long time
since you had a pussy.
You still have a lot of pussy.
How's the blood?
No.
What? No, no, no.
Stay still.
You'll get hurt if you go wild.
I'll show you the good side of a butt.
Here.
How is it?
Tatsuki, how is it?
How deep did you put it in?
Did you put it
in deeply? Here? Coco.
Hey.
Which one of you feels better?
Hey, Nasuki, answer me.
Which one do you prefer?
Like this?
Hey, hey, if you
move your butt, your butt will get wet.
Good boy.
You have a little more space.
You are too fat. Look at this.
How about this? Here you are.
Look.
Hey, hey, hey.
You have a big hole in your butt.
I'm going to sleep.
Did you fall asleep?
Do you feel good?
Oh...
OK, stay still.
Stay still.
Hey, it's easy to get in.
Next, the butthole.
I didn't tell you to give
up your body, did I?
You feel it, don't you?
I didn't tell you
to give up your body, did I? No, I didn't.
You did.
No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
You feel it, don't you?
Do you want
to go to the bathroom? Hey, Natsuki.
I'll let you go to the bathroom.
It's been a long
time since you went to the bathroom.
Come here.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'll let you sniff my dick.
It's okay.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Please do more.
You don't have to apologize.
You were happy to eat this before.
Hey, Natsuki.
OK.
I don't want it.
Take off your clothes.
Stay still.
I don't want it.
You don't know if you don't do it.
Take off your clothes.
Stay still.
Don't do that.
Come on.
Don't be wild.
What's wrong? Come on.
Come on.
This is the first time for me.
You don't want
to be touched, do you? Here you go.
You don't want to be touched, do you?
I can't do it anymore.
Are you getting
better? I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Stop it.
Stay still.
I'm sorry.
Do you have a hole in your butt?
I'm going to break.
You're getting used to it, aren't you?
Okay, I'm going to do more.
Stop it.
How do you feel, Natsuki?
Show me your face when you feel pain.
Oh, it's painful,
isn't it? It's painful.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Don't look at me.
It feels good,
doesn't it? I love you.
Come here.
Hey.
Stay still.
Look, I love you.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Say you feel better.
You feel good
this morning, don't you? No, I don't.
I love you so much.
It feels good, doesn't it, Natsuki?
If you feel anything,
say it with your butt.
Stop it, Sarai-chan, stop it.
I can't stop.
It's heavy, isn't it?
Here you are.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Don't touch me!
It's just a hole in your butt.
No!
No! No! I'm sorry.
Get out of here.
Anna, don't be angry.
What's wrong with her?
She is late today.
What's wrong with
you today? Hi, Natsuki.
Shigeki.
Natsuki, long time no see.
It's Senpai, Senpai.
I happened to
meet you on my way back from work.
I've been drinking all this time.
Senpai.
Natsuki-san, it's been a while.
You look happy.
Senpai, let's continue drinking.
Come over here.
That's right.
Well then, excuse me.
Here you are.
Have a drink.
Thank you.
It's been a while.
Thank you, Natsuki.
It's so delicious.
What's up, Natsuki? Have a seat.
Hey, why did you quit your job?
Well, I wanted to be independent.
I'm glad I quit my job.
I'm so sad to hear that.
I'm so glad when you two became my
subordinates.
We wanted to invite you to our wedding.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you were gone.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're okay.
What's wrong with
you, Natsuki? Drink it.
Well, well, well.
You have a lot of things.
A lot of things?
What do you mean?
What's that, Natsuki?
Look, look, look.
A lot of things.
I can cut a man who
doesn't understand his wife's feelings.
Oh, really?
You're going to be cut?
We love each
other, don't we, Natsuki? Here you are.
Thank you.
Senpai, can you stop drinking today?
Can I?
I don't know what to say.
Are you OK, Natsuki?
Yes, I'm fine.
Please stop.
OK, I'll stop.
Don't just stand there. Come here.
I heard you do it every day.
I'm here today, so
if you can't do it, you'll be disappointed.
Please go home.
Shunji told you to stay.
Shunji, what do you
think if you find out that you like butt?
I'm sure you'll get burned.
I'm sure you'll be able to do it.
Do you want me to
make a hole in your butthole again?
You didn't look like you wanted to do
it at all when you first did it.
You'll get
a cramp if you think you can do it again.
Do you understand, Natsuki-san?
Show me your butt.
I can feel it.
Do you understand, Natsuki-san?
Oh, you're getting excited.
I want to put you in this butt again.
Don't run away.
Stay still.
What are you doing?
Is this your butthole?
Your body is trembling.
Here? Here it is.
Show me.
Stay still.
Natsuki, are you making a baby cry?
You can spread it by
yourself, can't you? Do it.
Do it.
You like your
buttocks, don't you? Spread it more.
That's right.
Use your strength.
Do you feel it?
Huh?
You are getting excited just by looking
at the camera, aren't you? That's right.
That's right. More.
Huh?
Do you get a cramp if you tilt your butt?
You look excited.
I'm sorry.
It's too early.
If you're in a hurry, you'll hear it.
It's too early, Natsuki.
Keep your voice down.
You are so cute.
Let me see.
Here you are.
Look.
Do you feel your butthole? Look.
【Neko-kichi's
mom】 【Neko-kichi's brother】
【Neko-kichi's mom】
【Neko-kichi's brother】
Matsuki, I brought you something nice.
I hope you like it.
What is it?
I'll make you
feel more of your buttocks with this.
I don't want it.
I'll keep quiet.
Can you see? She's crying more and more.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel better? Okay.
Please do more.
I can't hear you.
This is not an android.
This is a baby.
Oh? Not yet.
One more.
You can eat one more.
Here we go.
Here you are.
It hurts.
It doesn't matter. Open your chest.
That's right.
One more time.
Here you are.
It's going in smoothly.
It's easy, isn't it?
I can't hear you. What
did you say? I feel bad.
I'm sorry.
I'm going
to open your eyes and your buttocks.
It's a good girl.
Good.
You're moving again.
Look.
You're getting a new outfit.
You can't live like this.
You want to be a nun, don't you?
You do, don't you?
I'll give you a head-butt.
I'll do my best.
This time,
I will talk about the story of the old man
who fell asleep
while playing in the middle of the night.
The story of the old man who fell asleep
In the middle of the night,
he was sleeping with his back to the bed.
You like it, don't you?
It's good for your butthole, isn't it?
Oh, I can't stop.
Okay, I'll give you a shot in the butthole.
Natsuki, I'll give you
a shot in the butthole.
I'll give you a shot in the butthole.
Put your hands on your belly.
Now, beg for more.
Open your buttocks and beg for more.
Yes, yes, please put
one foot in my buttocks.
Please put one foot in my buttocks.
Are you a corpse?
Yes, I want to do it.
Please.
Is this it?
thank you very much.
More, please.
You have to use your hips if you feel good.
Here you go.
Try to use your hips.
More.
This is a video with no sound.
This video is
a derivative work of the Touhou Project.
If you are okay with
this video, please give us a high rating.
Thank you very much.
The baby's crying
is getting louder and louder.
The baby is crying
while putting his face on the baby's back.
Give me more blood.
You look like you love the butthole.
What do you like?
You like it?
I like the butthole.
Tell me you like the butthole.
Give me more blood.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? All right.
Put your head down.
Oh, you're getting better.
I'm happy.
All right.
He is taking a bath in the hot spring bath.
He is cleaning his butt.
Do you clean your butt?
Look at my butthole.
I'm going to take it out today.
It's my favorite night,
so I'm going to leave it.
I'll take you to the station.
Please come to play again.
Thank you.
But it's too much for two people.
Don't worry about that.
I see.
Then I'll get in the way again.
Yes, I'll go.
Mrs. Aoki, I'm sorry to bother you.
See you later.
I betrayed my husband.
But I can still get him back.
I can get him back.
Welcome back. You're early.
I'm here again.
Your husband told me to come.
Please, don't get involved with us.
What are you talking about?
I know your personality.
Do you like your husband?
You like a hole in the ass.
Be honest.
Are you okay? I'm fine.
Take your time.
Tetsuki,
I'm going to cut your favorite butt hole.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Let me see your face.
Don't look so sad.
Look at your pretty face.
What's the smell of your butthole today?
Please look at me.
Hey, hey, Natsuki.
Do you feel it? I feel good.
I can't hear you.
I feel good.
I want to put it in this hole soon.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
Say more.
Do you want me to make you feel better?
Yes.
She is crying.
She is so
excited that her eyes are wide open.
What happened to
you? Stay still.
Show me your butt.
Yes, yes.
Show me, please.
It's smooth, isn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
I want to show this face to him.
I want to show you my face.
I want to show you
my face with a hole in my butt.
I'm going to put it in deeper today.
OK, you can go to the back side.
OK, let's go.
This side, OK.
What?
Are you going to wash
my butt? OK, let's open.
It's time to open.
I feel sick.
You are a sloppy woman.
I'm sorry.
No, you are a sloppy woman.
Look at me.
I'm a sloppy woman.
I'm sorry.
Let me feel good with this scar today.
Yes.
Who is the father?
Please put my scar in the father's scar.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to stab you in the butt hole.
Come on.
I'm going to put you on my lap.
I'll put you on my lap.
OK.
Let's go.
I'm coming.
Natsuki.
Where are you? I'm going out.
Are you going out?
Yes.
Can I come in? Wait a minute.
Can I wait a minute?
Yes, wait a minute.
Still? Natsuki.
I'm ready.
Come in.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I'm home, Natsuki.
Welcome home.
You've been waiting for me.
You're so cute today.
I'm home, Natsuki.
Welcome home.
You're so cute today, Natsuki.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
You are so aggressive.
I couldn't do it
yesterday because my senior came.
I'm trying to be patient.
I'm sorry.
I feel sorry for you today.
Take this off, too.
This is the first
time I've ever seen a baby cry like this.
It's so cute.
I was able to take off my underwear.
You didn't take off your underwear?
I didn't take off my underwear.
Manko, you are wet.
You are very wet.
It's getting hot.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating?
Yes.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's because you worked hard.
I'm relieved.
You're feeling better, aren't you?
Put it in your mouth.
It's so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good,
doesn't it? It's so good.
doesn't it? It's painful.
It's painful.
Do you feel better?
Yes, I feel better.
You are strong.
You can do it.
Ah, it feels good.
Natsuki, you're more aggressive than usual.
It feels good.
It feels good, Natsuki.
Put your head on my lap.
And lean back a little.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It feels good.
I'm getting cold.
I'm going to put a towel on your back.
It's hot.
Please wait a while until I wake up!
Gosh… Please wait, Yaejin.
Go! Go home, go home!
Wait a while, please! It's hot.
It's hot.
I want you to lie on top of me.
It feels good.
I'm so happy.
I love you.
I love you so much.
It's hot.
But I heard that
your wife has a strong determination.
Senpai!
I'll put it in for you.
Senpai, what
are you doing? Stay still.
What are you doing?
Senpai! It's in.
It's a good body.
How is it?
It's a good thing that
both of your legs are in.
It's sour.
You should move too.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
You look like you're in a bad mood.
No, I'm not.
You two look like perverts.
How do you feel? I feel bad.
You are a baby.
Which one do you feel bad? Both.
You are a pervert.
Both.
I feel bad.
Ken and Marco, what's wrong with you?
I'm going to go.
Are you going
alone? I feel sick.
What's wrong? I'm sick, too.
Then do it.
You're doing it again.
It's so itchy.
Go.
Hey, hey, hey.
You two are a couple after all.
You're getting into a fight.
Hey, get out of here.
I'll show you that this
woman is really a pervert.
I developed this anal.
Don't complain. It's all her fault.
Listen carefully.
You are a woman
who feels pain in the buttocks, aren't you?
Look at her face.
I am a woman who feels pain in the
buttocks, aren't I?
Do you understand now?
Do you understand
that you are a terrible woman?
Did you get it?
Ouch!
I've put it in your ass many times.
I'll do it again today.
Look at me.
Ouch! It's hot.
From that incident,
the dinner never gets cold.
However,
the relationship with Shunji
is getting cold.