Where do you want to go?
Oze is Oze.
Oze? Where is Oze?
I thought so too.
Bunma?
Don't you want to go to Shichitai?
Kyoto is better.
If it's autumn.
Is it a rental car for 8 people?
I don't want to drive.
He said he didn't like hot springs.
He is very shy.
He doesn't want to show his skin.
I don't have skin.
He doesn't want to show his skin to women.
That's right.
I searched on the Internet.
It's hard to drive, so I'll do my best and go to Kyushu.
What is this?
Airplane.
Oh, it's an airplane.
I've only been on an airplane once.
I want to go on an airplane.
Circulation trip.
What is this?
Video?
What kind of video?
Interesting video.
What is this?
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
What is this?
What was this?
This is a video that was on Sora's computer.
It's on the screen.
What is this video?
It's a 4-person video.
What was it called?
A file...
Maruhi...
Maruhi?
Maruhi circle trip.
It was a trip to Japan in 2012.
The air is so fresh.
I want to open it, but I can't.
Oh, my God.
The air is so fresh.
It smells good.
I took out the camera.
We're shooting it every year.
Everyone is showing cute faces.
Memories.
I want to do a BBQ.
BBQ.
I'm preparing it.
Did you bring it?
Of course.
I want to play a game.
Let's introduce ourselves one by one.
Let's take a selfie.
The mountains are beautiful.
The mountains as far as you can see.
Let's introduce ourselves.
I'm Nonoka.
I'm Nomukki.
I'm Sora.
Thank you for your hard work.
Congratulations.
I'm Yuna.
Are you nervous?
I'm a little nervous.
I have to put it in early.
I'm the type who doesn't get excited.
I'm scared.
Let's get excited.
I'm still shaking.
I'm shaking like this.
I'm a strawberry.
I'm going out today.
We're going to drink a little bit at a time.
Let's have a drink together.
Is it fun?
It's nice to have two beautiful girls together.
I want four of you.
Are you shooting?
They are taking pictures of us.
They are men.
They are light.
They are drinking.
They are rampaging.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
You are worried.
I don't know.
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Yes.
They are cute.
Did you say it?
Yes, I did.
You're so serious.
I said it.
I'm scared if someone gets mad at me.
Why are you angry?
I don't think I'll get caught.
Did you say it?
I said it.
What did you say?
Did you say it in English?
No, I didn't.
That's bad.
I said, go on a trip.
We're not like men.
We don't look like men.
I didn't say it because I thought I'd get caught.
I don't think I'll get caught.
As expected of Parisians.
I want to get in the car!
I want to drink sake!
I hate alcohol!
I want to eat meat.
I want to eat strawberries.
I don't want to eat strawberries.
I want to eat Rattle.
I love Rattle.
I want to eat mango.
I want to eat sausages.
I want a sausage
There are 4 of them
Today, we're eating in a size-cub
Wait, it's not good
It's going to spill
Like this
I'm sorry
Tora-chan's up
Up
Ah, it's cool
Are you drunk?
How do you feel when you're drunk?
I feel good
I feel better than now
You're too high
You're gonna disappear
I do what I want
Let's do what we want
What do you want to do?
I want to do what I want to do
Me?
I want to get more excited than usual
Really?
Yes
I've never seen it
I feel like I can drink
I'll drink today
I have to drink today
Are you okay?
I'll drink
The best pension
We're waiting for you.
How did Misa drink?
Misa...
Can you drink a little?
Her face is getting red.
It's a strawberry.
Her face is turning into a strawberry.
Misa is always cute.
I think I can talk more than now.
She's talking more than usual.
She's getting excited.
She's like a light river.
She gets lighter, right?
It's like a light rafting.
I can talk more when I drink.
I can't talk because I'm left-handed.
What do you do when you go?
I'm looking forward to it.
You don't tell me.
It's a rafting.
What do you start with?
I'm hunting.
I'm looking forward to it.
One is already in the local area.
It's a local area.
It's so fast.
It's right next to my house.
Let's have a BBQ.
I'm hungry.
BBQ.
BBQ BBQ
I think it's a gathering of the circle.
It's not like that.
It looks like it's going to be fun.
I know.
Self-introduction.
What's this?
It's something we said the other day.
We were like, we'll be back soon.
Something like that?
Something like Maruizawa will be coming back soon.
I didn't hear anything.
Who is this?
Who is the person who was filming this?
It's burning!
I'll buy you a strawberry juice.
What do you want to drink?
I want a strawberry juice.
Strawberry?
This is really good.
What are you drinking?
Beer.
That's cool.
Beer for now.
What about you, Hime?
Pitch is fast.
He's coming.
Let's have a toast.
I thought you were already drunk.
Sora-chan, Sora-chan.
Sora-chan will prepare it soon.
Let's have a toast.
Sora-chan, please give it to Sora-chan.
I'll give it to you.
It's ready.
Let's have a toast.
What are you going to do?
Let's have a toast to our body.
Cheers!
Take a video!
Cheers to the calories!
This is delicious!
Have a bite!
I'll post this on social media later.
There was a sausage.
I'll post it later.
I want to eat it.
Please give us a thumbs up.
I want to take a picture of this scene.
Thank you very much.
I'll take a picture of this.
I'll bring more.
Thank you very much.
This is the wall of light-hearted people.
I like it.
Is it good?
Let's see your reaction.
It's good.
It's cute.
Is it good?
It's good.
The cheese is good.
It's not easy to taste the grilled fish.
That's true.
It's really hard to taste.
What's your specialty?
My specialty is rice.
I like rice.
Really?
It's good.
Wow.
It's leaking.
This is delicious.
Is it delicious?
There is no strawberry.
I want to go to pick cherry blossoms.
Is it hot?
Hold it here.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Do you want me to bite you?
If you bite me, I'll bite you.
It hurts.
It's hot.
Don't bite me.
It hurts.
I want to bite you.
I'm tired.
Are you okay?
Hime, meat.
It's hot.
I like the way you spread your legs.
It's empty.
Are you holding it?
Thank you.
It's a Turkey Lasso.
It's fun today.
It's fun.
It's good.
Don't drink too much.
I got it.
It's okay.
It's better to drink here.
It's good.
It's too hot.
It's burnt.
It's burning.
It's hot.
Don't push it.
Watch out.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
What a bad boy.
It's hot.
What kind of eating style are you doing, captain?
I'm thinking of spilling the sauce.
It's hot.
Oh no.
I'm spilling the sauce.
You should eat it when it spills.
That's too new.
That's how you eat it.
Oh.
Yes, yes.
Great.
Is it okay?
There's a white one.
Thank you.
Is it good?
It's good.
Thank you.
It has strong female power.
Let's take a picture together.
It's in the picture.
Yay!
Thank you.
I was thinking, but this salad looks like it's going to be a bad one.
What?
Aren't you drinking too much?
No, it's not like that.
I know, I know.
What is it?
I added a special sauce.
Did you add something?
I just added it.
Really?
Don't drink too much.
I understand.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Why are you so kind?
I don't know.
Why are you touching it?
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
You don't eat it?
You're so funny.
Hime is so erotic.
I'm jealous.
Then, I'll eat it in your place.
It looks fun.
It's good for BBQ, isn't it?
It's good.
It's good for BBQ in autumn.
It's amazing.
I'm hungry.
He's eating so much.
I know.
He's pretty handsome.
I haven't heard of him.
He's good.
He doesn't want to be in front of me.
He doesn't drink.
He drinks a lot.
He says he drinks a lot.
Does he still drink?
He might get cold in the morning.
He wasn't in a good mood.
My legs are...
Let's drink inside.
Oh, yeah.
Let's go.
No, you don't have to do anything.
You don't have to do anything.
Just me.
You're going to get burned.
Let's clean up properly.
Can I go in?
Can you clean it up?
Are you okay?
Your face is red.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Please take care of her.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You can't say that.
You're red.
You're cute.
You can do it.
I'm okay.
Be careful.
How much do you want to drink?
I want to drink.
It's so cute.
It was fun.
There are still many more.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
What about strawberry?
I'm not sure.
I don't like it.
Let's play a game.
What is this?
I'm going.
If you see a monkey on Amazon, who will you beat?
How to beat?
Sorry sorry.
Oh!
One hit.
Bap Bap.
This is Bap, right?
I can't beat my own Oppa anymore.
Oh!
Yay!
Good luck!
I want to drink it!
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
There are five left.
I think they are coming.
Yes, they are coming!
Yay!
It's done.
4 more to go.
How many?
3 more.
It's coming.
Hime-chan.
2 more to go.
It's 1 out of 2.
Hime-chan has it.
If you don't drink it, you can drink 2 more.
I'm scared.
This is it.
1 more to go.
Let's go to the park.
This guy is a judge.
That's it.
Ready first.
Why is it like this?
To the back.
It's a mess.
It's a crisis.
I don't understand.
I think it's good.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's still going up to the end.
I think I have it.
Who is it?
What are you holding?
I'm holding it.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Give me a word.
Can you still drink?
I can drink.
Wait a minute.
I can still drink.
I don't like Pocky.
Let's do it together.
Wait a minute.
It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
What about the rest?
Did you eat it?
I ate it.
Where should I put it?
This is scary.
It's hard to put it on.
He's putting his life on the line.
Oh, he dropped it.
He dropped it.
There's a tear.
What is it?
It looks like he's going to cry.
He's going to scream.
It's impossible even if you think about it.
I don't think it's possible.
It's impossible.
In the middle.
Oh my god!
What happened?
There's a ghost.
Wait a minute.
There's only one ghost.
There's a ghost.
Can't you see us?
Why are you here?
Oh my god!
Oh, wait a minute.
It's almost over.
One game is over.
This side is bad.
What did you do?
It's a game.
It's amazing.
What should I do?
You can put it anywhere.
Ok,ok,ok.
Ohhhh.
She swallowed it.
She swallowed it with her mouth.
I didn't swallow it.
No,no,no.
Oh,no,no.
It became soft.
It's good.
Oh,no,no.
It's open.
Next.
I want to open it.
I'll bring it.
What do you want to drink?
I want something with alcohol in it.
Everyone is good.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing. It's very high level.
I can't drink anymore.
This is really difficult.
What? What? What?
What is this?
Ahhhhhhh!
MisaMisa!
MisaMisa! This is a Bap!
Bap!
It's not on!
MisaMisa!
What?
Bap! Bap!
Up! Up!
Oh, it's a waki.
No, no, it's dirty.
It's dirty.
Cheers!
Everyone, drink.
It's weak.
It's weak. I'll release it.
Let's play a game.
If you don't feel like it, tell me.
Don't drink too much.
You can drink the cake.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
I'm going to break it.
I'll take care of it.
Okay.
Who's going to draw?
I'm going to draw Sora-chan.
It's a chance.
Please get excited.
It's time.
Do it.
It's a beauty.
It's a weak body part.
Where is it?
What is this?
It's cute.
Here?
Princess Chan.
I want to drink a sexy drink.
Don't you want to drink a lot?
Who do you want to drink a sexy drink to?
This way.
Don't get wet.
Left and right.
Sexy!
It's like Misamisa is sexy.
Misamisa is sexy.
But there's something good about this.
It looks sexy.
Sexy.
It's sexy.
The bell is long.
The bell is long, isn't it?
I want to be a can.
Long tongue.
Oh, I got it.
I drank it.
I want to see Sora-chan's.
Makorin knows.
Makorin is cute.
It's good, it's good.
It's good.
The game is still in the middle of the game.
Did you pull it?
I didn't pull it.
I pulled it.
It's really long.
Is it okay?
The tongue is long.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Did you cut it too long?
There's something amazing.
What is it?
The first experience will be announced someday.
Aren't you guys girls?
There are a lot of girls.
You're boyfriends.
Are you girls?
I want to say that I'm a girl.
When I was a girl, I was a strawberry.
You're good at talking.
Your head is terrible.
When I was a strawberry.
I was 14 years old at that time.
When I was in the second grade of junior high school.
I was in the second grade of junior high school.
You're a girl.
No, no. I'm 17 years old forever. I'm in the 2nd grade.
I'm so tired.
You are a middle school student.
I'm not a teacher.
You are not a teacher.
A teacher with her neighbor?
Who is it with?
I want to hear it.
Who is it?
Teacher, right?
Let's hug each other.
This is the most embarrassing game I've ever played.
What is it?
Hime-chan, you must be surprised.
I'm not.
Is there something embarrassing?
I'm sure there is.
What is it?
In the car.
What?
It's not a car.
Tissue?
I don't need tissue.
Is there a place with tissue?
No.
Really?
It wasn't a play, it was during the day off.
During the day off?
What was that?
During the winter.
It was cold during the winter.
It was cold.
The toilet was the limit.
What was that?
Did you pee?
I got it while I was walking.
You didn't notice?
Let's do it.
I want to see who's the winner.
What are you doing?
I'm doing it.
Are you excited?
Are you having fun?
Carly's here.
It's like a club.
Let's play a game.
Let's do it until the last minute.
Who's going to do it?
I'll do it.
Please do it.
You're shooting a video.
I'll do it.
Leave it to me.
Go!
Just a little bit more.
His face is so annoying.
He's getting angry at his boyfriend.
Yeah, he's getting angry at his boyfriend.
Let's eat.
What are you talking about?
Punchline.
Because I can see it.
Look at this.
It's a cave.
Lavender color.
Lavender.
Karuizawa is conscious.
Pension color.
It's a little dusty.
What is it?
Pension color.
This is hot.
Is this okay?
It's okay.
It's about to burst.
Oh, it's from the pension.
What happened?
It's from the pension.
Is this a fake?
It's not a fake.
It's from the pension.
I can see it.
It's a fake.
No?
It's a yutose, isn't it?
Look at this.
It's a pants.
It's a big deal.
What?
Wait a minute.
Let's check.
Check. Check.
The hair.
I'm going to check the hair.
The hair hurts.
Check. Check.
What's the game?
It's like a cross-section.
I want to see your underwear.
Do you want to see my underwear?
Your underwear and swimsuit are the same, right?
They are the same.
Wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
What's that?
Emerald!
Emerald Green!
Sora-chan!
Oh, the best Emerald!
Oh no!
Welcome!
Wow!
He has a beard!
Why did you take it?
It's in your hand.
Welcome.
Thank you very much.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
OK.
The boobs are big.
You can do it.
You are so soft.
I'm surprised.
It's a game.
What is game?
Let's have fun.
Let's drink before that.
Let's drink.
Let's drink from the outside.
I don't want to drink.
Why?
Will he come?
His face is so cute.
His face is so cute?
You can do it, you can do it, you can do it
Isn't it finally that?
Finally, the last one
Oh, it's bad
That's right
There is no one left
Then, Hime is left, Hime is left
Is that okay? Thank you
Thank you
Yay, I did it
I'm saying I did it
It's fast, it's fast
Kink, Kink, Kink is fast at making up stories
Where is Kink? Who is Kink?
Can you do it, Santa?
Misa-chan, I wanted to experience something like this
Who is it?
It's Jun-kun.
It's Osamu.
Osamu is a little young.
Don't pretend like that.
Stop it.
I don't know the number.
It's Nono.
What is it?
The king licks the weak point of No. 7.
He's dancing.
The weak point of No. 7.
The king licks the weak point of No. 7.
Who is No. 7?
Yes, that's right.
I'm sure you peeped at me.
Please show me your weakness.
You still peeped at me.
You're nervous, aren't you?
Why?
Your face is stiff.
What?
Oh no.
Me too, me too.
I'm watching you.
Why did you start here?
What?
You're drunk.
I'm drunk too.
I'm responsible for the group.
You're responsible for the group.
I want it.
What?
What's this?
Your ears are weak.
Your ears are weak?
Everyone plays alone too much.
I'm a king now.
Something is starting.
It's a game.
You can't play.
You were doing something here too.
I couldn't see it from behind.
You can't play.
Finally, I found out.
Number 4, please.
Number 6?
It's a girl group?
It's embarrassing.
It's a girl group.
The order changed.
That's how you eat a barbecue, isn't it?
That's how you eat a barbecue.
You can't get sauce on it.
No, no.
It's cool.
I couldn't eat chocolate at all.
It's impossible.
It's amazing.
That's too much!
I'm just going to scream!
I'm the king now, so you all know that, right?
No, we don't!
We know that's bad.
Well, it doesn't matter what the king says.
It doesn't matter if it's a number.
Hime-chan's relationship is important.
I want to kiss all the girls.
Really?
I want to kiss the king.
All of them.
I want to have a boyfriend.
No, no, no.
Isn't he stronger than his boyfriend?
It's a big kiss.
No, no, no.
I want to have a boyfriend.
Is he stronger than his boyfriend?
No, no, no.
It can't be helped.
If it's dead, kiss it.
Isn't it soft?
It's too soft.
It's okay.
Amazing.
Danger!
What does it taste like?
I don't know.
I'm the king.
It's good.
Danger!
No!
Let's show them.
Danger!
No!
Why?
You are going to get drunk.
Go, go.
Give me your tongue.
How was it?
It was delicious.
Kalbippi.
Oh, no.
Are you okay?
Look, look.
Sawa-chan is here.
Look.
Sara, Sara.
Give me your tongue.
Why?
Sara, Sara.
Give me your tongue.
I'm drunk.
More, more, more.
Who is it?
Don't do that.
Go, go, go, go.
Who is it?
I'll say it with this.
That's not funny.
I didn't take it.
Who is it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
No.1 and No.2 look good together.
Because they are two.
He's a good king.
I'm so excited, Haru.
The king will also get bitten.
By himself?
He's a good king.
Who's number one?
I'm number two.
I knew it.
The king is fast.
Well, well, well.
Junkyun, didn't you bring a camera today?
I did.
Double camera?
Let's take a lot of pictures.
Camera.
You have a brother?
I have to rub it.
Rubbing.
I want to rub it.
Do you want to be rubbed?
If you want to be rubbed, say it.
I'll rub the double camera.
I was the king.
I'll do it.
Why did you do it?
Please rub it.
Is it Japanese?
Even though it's On-sama.
What is On-sama's order?
Absolutely.
It seems to be happy.
It's fun.
It's big.
The top is coming out.
Hello.
The king is angry.
The king feels good.
The king's top is angry.
What are you doing?
Let's do it again.
I can see the pants, but is it okay?
Look, I can see the pants over here.
What are you doing over there?
It's a princess.
It looks like a princess' boobs.
What does the king say?
Absolutely!
This is the king's order.
Is it a princess' boobs?
No, so it's a prince.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's so pretty.
It's a beautiful color.
It's amazing.
Her skin is white.
Show us.
It's the Miso.
Maybe if the king orders.
I want to see Misa's boobs.
Misa, come here.
I hate videos.
Don't show it.
Show it to me.
I won't show it.
Misa, show me your boobs.
Show it to me.
Everyone is enjoying the food.
Everyone is getting more and more free.
Is it free?
Is the rice cake free?
It seems that the rice cake is free.
The rice cake is free.
Misami-san, you can eat too.
Everyone is showing, so I'm not afraid.
This is bad.
This is bad!
There is a fire.
It's burning.
Let's try again.
What is it?
It's a fire.
There is a fire.
What?
This is amazing.
This is a bad situation.
This is so embarrassing.
Oh!
It's big!
This is bad!
This is big!
Oh my!
It's green!
The top of your head is standing up.
I'm not standing up.
Misami, you're thinking of something erotic, aren't you?
I'm not thinking of anything.
I don't want to talk to Pippi.
Pippi?
What is this?
You're playing a game, aren't you?
Why?
You're being buried, aren't you?
She's my girlfriend.
Is he drinking?
He is drinking, too.
Stop it.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
This is my memory.
You can see it.
I can't say something like that.
I'm the only one who can't see it.
Kachikochi station.
It's raining.
They are being touched.
They look happy.
Oh, wait a minute.
The game has nothing to do with it.
Hey!
No one is watching.
Oh, no.
Damn it.
I'm so angry.
I want to see Sora-chan's boobs, too.
Why did you take it off?
Sora-chan's boobs.
Let's see Sora-chan's boobs, too.
Everyone's showing it.
What should I do?
It's a ride.
It's a momentum.
You don't have to take it off with a bra.
Bra?
You can take it off.
I don't know what to do.
It's embarrassing.
I don't want to show this to anyone.
Let's take a look.
It's white.
It's a cute thing.
Is it pink?
Everyone.
Sora-chan, Sora-chan is coming out.
It's okay.
Sora-chan, your cheeks are no good?
My cheeks are no good.
The last pine cone.
It's pretty big.
I don't like it.
Even though it has a face.
I didn't think it was that big.
What are you shy about?
It's big, it's big.
If you see that, you'll get angry.
Sorry, sorry.
Is it over?
It's over.
Let's continue with the king's game.
Sora-chan, Sora-chan, Sora-chan, please show me your bra.
Please show me your bra with the order of the king.
The second one?
I want to see the second one.
What is it?
Bring back the earth.
You can't make it back.
It's awful.
It's terrible.
I can't do this.
It's the easiest way to do it.
Is your phone okay?
Okay.
Here it comes.
The king.
Who is the king?
Misa.
Who is it?
It's Misawa!
Oh, Misawa is here!
Congratulations!
I did it!
What's going on?
I'm looking for someone who can sleep with Misawa tonight.
What's going on? Are you lonely?
What do you think?
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm here!
Where is Asumi-chan?
Misawa...
What's going on?
What do you do?
No, no, no!
I'm going to sleep with Hana-Hana.
Hana-Hana.
Okay, who wants to sleep with me?
I don't want to.
I don't want to sleep alone.
I'm lonely.
Who do you choose?
He is sleeping.
He's sleeping.
Go to the other side.
I'm sorry.
He didn't notice.
Oh no.
He's pushing.
He's getting stiff.
What?
Oh no.
How about Yasu?
Yasu is very good.
He doesn't listen to Osama at all.
What are you doing?
Osama doesn't listen to Osama.
Osama, everyone except Misa kisses.
What?
Everyone except Misa kisses.
I don't need Misa.
You don't need a man, do you?
Yes.
You kiss everyone you like.
I kiss the person I like.
Yes, kiss the person you like.
Me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Other than the king?
Other than the king.
Everyone is in love.
Haru is coming!
What happened?
Everyone is coming.
No!
I'm falling.
Me too.
Why are you touching Oppa?
I want to touch too.
Why?
Oh yeah, peace.
Hello.
I didn't drink alcohol just now.
Here, here.
Hello.
Oh no.
You don't refuse anything, do you?
It's Balmie.
It's hard, it's hard.
That room.
It's hard.
Hey.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
It's amazing.
Why?
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't know where to go.
Everyone's underwear.
I'm embarrassed.
No, no, no, no.
I'm doing it here too.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm hungry.
Thank you.
What's happening?
Hey, hey, hey.
Will you come?
Is Chuck coming?
It's standing.
Oh, it's here.
Oh, no.
It's stuck.
Is it a tea bag?
What is this?
It's a skeleton.
It's eating a lot.
Why is it not being peeled off?
It's a piece of a cup.
It's not a piece of a cup.
Piece, piece, piece.
Like this.
I've been thinking about it for 3 years now.
Let's take a picture of the boobs.
I'll take a picture of you.
Let's take a picture of you.
3 shots.
Is it okay to take a picture of the camera?
It's okay.
Let's take a picture of the camera.
I want to see it.
Let's take a picture of Hime.
I'm taking a picture.
Let's take a picture.
What are you going to decide?
Your hair is thin, isn't it?
Your whole body is thin, isn't it?
Good, good.
Drink, drink, drink.
What are you doing? You're alone.
What are you doing?
Aren't you wet?
I'm not wet.
You're naughty.
Hey!
What's wrong?
Mako, can you take it off?
Yes, yes, yes.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's a little...
You're pretty drunk, aren't you?
Hey, hey, hey.
Come here, come here.
I want to take a break.
I want to sleep.
Hey, hey, hey.
Are you okay?
Let's go upstairs.
Which room is upstairs?
There is a place to rest upstairs.
Here?
Wait a minute.
Pull it.
What's wrong with Kimori-chan?
I can't stop here.
Why can't I stop?
What's wrong?
I can't stop here.
It's a little cool here.
It's cool.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Help me!
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Why?
I can't do it.
Can I touch it?
No.
Lick it.
I can't lick it.
It's okay.
What is it?
I can't lick it.
I really can't drink.
Let's drink.
Drink it up.
Hey!
I really don't know what to do.
Huh?
No, it's not.
It's delicious.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you want to eat it?
Can you open your mouth?
I can't hear your lower part of your mouth
I can't open my mouth
Really?
Can't you open your mouth?
I'm going to put it in the bottom
Do you want to see it?
Can you come here?
Come here
What kind of place is there in the bottom?
I can't see the bottom
Can you see it?
I'm scared
What?
Why?
I don't know.
It will be hot.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Why do you look like you don't know anything?
Why do you think that?
Yes, yes, yes.
What is this?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
I'm so tired.
I'm tired.
Do your best.
I'm sorry.
Are you ok?
A little more.
You're feeling good, right?
I'm feeling good.
Come on.
The sound from up there.
Is it okay?
Ok, let's start.
No, that's not the right hand.
I see.
Let's play games together.
Yeah, let's play games together.
I wanna see the stars.
The other side is cut off.
It's cut off.
Oh, it's cut off.
What is it?
I'll do it.
Do you want to stop?
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
I'm so tired.
There was a cushion.
I'll bring it.
What is it?
I'll bring a cushion.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
I have a cushion.
I want to go to the bathroom.
Do you like this?
Yes.
Are you OK?
What are you doing?
Are you seriously not going to sleep?
I want to see it.
I'm not going to sleep.
I'm so happy.
Is it okay to say this?
Okay.
What is it?
It's an H.
There's only pink here.
He drew my butt.
That's good.
I feel like he's going to do it.
Don't you want to do it with that?
You like idols, don't you?
Just a little bit.
You're quite an idol.
Do you feel hot?
I'm glad you feel hot.
This bath is beautiful.
I want to take a bath in the sun.
Hime-chan is very sad...
I'm sorry.
You're not crying.
I don't think we should do this.
You should be angry.
Wait a minute.
Should we say it?
I don't know what it is.
What is this?
It's a circle gown.
Wow, everyone's pants are the same.
Mine too?
Wait a minute.
Denis is always wearing a black shirt.
You're taking off something like that.
That's right.
It's a pant.
Wow!
It's good.
I'm sorry.
He is so cute.
He is so sweet.
He is drinking too much.
He is so cute.
What?
He is holding the camera.
You want me to touch it?
Yes, you want me to touch it.
Then why did you leave me alone?
You're a camera.
It's far away.
If you want to kiss, come here.
Oh,
Oh!
Sorry, I'm being too hard on you.
No, no.
Don't hurt your hand.
It tastes like chocolate.
It does.
I want to eat a raccoon.
It tastes like chocolate.
It does.
Oh!
It's a bento.
That's the best.
He's the best, isn't he?
I'm glad he's alive today.
He's the best.
He's the best when he's so light.
Look over there.
What are you doing?
Good, isn't it?
I want to drink something deep.
Something good.
I drank too much.
I'm alive.
It's good.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
It's so light.
The environment is so nice.
Why are you licking your nails?
I'm licking your nails.
What?
I'll make it for you.
Earth.
This is the best.
Earth, not Earth.
Not Earth.
I'm grateful to the Earth.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
It's good, right?
Yes.
That's good.
I can feel it.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Hime is sorry.
Look at this.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I said I was sorry.
Really?
Can you do it for me?
No, you can't.
Poor thing.
Poor thing?
No, no.
Like this.
Give me your hand.
Here.
What's wrong?
Do you like Tsukubi?
Do you want a kiss?
I do.
It's coming.
Give me your hand.
Let's go.
Something has started.
Let's take a look.
We can see there.
How is it?
Can you see it?
Is it starting?
It's starting.
It's not just us.
It's the first time I've seen someone.
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's have a toast and have a drink.
You drink a lot, don't you?
I drink a lot.
Really?
It's better to go home.
That's good.
It's good to drink a little.
Do you usually drink alcohol?
I can drink, but I'm weak.
Really?
Are you pretty drunk?
A little.
A little?
There is something inside the bag.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm not.
You are not?
Why?
I want to go to the gym.
I see.
I'm tired.
I want to go back
I thought you were playing with me.
I didn't notice.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to do it a little bit more.
You're sorry?
It's cold, isn't it?
You are doing a very beautiful work.
I've never done this before.
You've never had it?
Now that you're so chubby, you're such an idiot.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Let's lick it.
Delicious.
You're not waiting for me, are you?
Wait a minute.
I'll call you later.
What? Later?
Are you okay?
No, I'm not.
You're not in a rush, are you okay?
I'm just touching you.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it feels good.
You're my boyfriend.
I didn't expect you to have sex with me.
I didn't expect it.
Do you care if I do something wrong?
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
There's a lot of it.
There's a lot.
I'm tired.
Oh, great.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
I'm going to die.
It's gone.
This is the first time I've ever done this, so I'm a little nervous, but I'm going to do my best.
I'm going to do my best, so I'm going to do my best, so I'm going to do my best.
I can't do it anymore.
This is hard.
It's a scene of a man who was so excited and started crying.
I'm sorry...
I can't help but laugh...
Oh, it hurts.
It hurts...
Wait...
I'm sorry...
Ah...
I'm getting a little tired.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
I did a lot.
She's definitely doing it, isn't she?
She's doing it.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
You've been hurt.
Is your boyfriend's phone okay?
It's okay.
I want to go to the hospital.
Look at me.
What are you doing?
I'm kissing you.
It's important to kiss each other.
It's tickling.
Why?
I'm sorry.
I want to make you feel better.
You're so cute.
Yasu?
Yasu is so cute.
You're so cute.
Yasu has a sexy voice.
I like you.
I'm sorry.
I like you a lot.
I was surprised at first.
I don't remember.
I suddenly kiss you.
Kiss.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Let's do it together.
In the same position?
In the same position.
Both sides?
Yes.
I see.
You can do it.
Your hands are high.
It's the other way around, isn't it?
Why are you so hot?
I don't know.
Aren't you too popular because you drink too much?
I'm so excited.
I want to take a picture of myself.
I want to take a picture of Tsukumi being licked.
No, I don't want to.
What do you think?
Why don't you two do it?
You two do it.
What do you mean?
Both sides.
I'll take it.
Give me the sake.
Here you go.
Drink it.
Let's do it together.
You don't mess around.
Shut up.
Do you want to drink it?
Let's take a picture together.
Look at the camera.
How is it?
Hime-chan is erotic.
Hey, hey, why are you like this?
You're so pitiful.
Chichi, come out quickly.
I want to take out my penis.
Do you want to take out your penis?
I want to kiss you.
I want to kiss you while kissing you.
Do you want to kiss me directly?
I want to kiss you.
It's stuck.
It hurts.
Next.
I like this.
Do you like this?
I can't do that.
Do you want me to lick it?
I want you to lick it.
Please
Look at this
She looks cute
Which do you like better?
Which one do you think is better?
What else?
O-Ten-Pin?
O-Ten-Po
O-Chin-Po is Shiko-Shiko
Shiko-Shiko
It's a bit edgy
What? For example?
Chimpo...
Chimpo-Kin-Kin
You're drawing
O-Chin-Po is very energetic
What do you want this energetic O-Chin-Po to do?
More
I'm not sure if it's okay to do it with you two, but is it okay to do it with your boyfriend?
I haven't said anything about it today.
I don't care because it's dry.
I don't think it will be exposed.
What will you do if it is exposed?
I'll say, I'm sorry.
I might forgive you if you're my boyfriend.
Do you want to do it again?
Let's do it together.
Cute.
I don't want to.
You can do it.
I'm drunk, so it doesn't matter.
I can't drink alcohol.
Alcohol is the best.
I love alcohol.
I like the two of you more than alcohol.
I'm glad I drank it.
I thought you were really cute when we met today.
Are you having fun?
What is this?
Do you want to eat it?
I'll give it to you.
Do you like it?
Do you like me?
I'm scared.
Can I touch it?
It's cute.
I have something I want to do.
Me? Monkey?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I also want to see.
I want to see that.
Look.
Are you feeling good?
Hey.
It's heaven.
It's amazing.
This is a big hit.
It's a big hit.
I'm sorry.
I'm about to cry.
Yasu has a good face.
I'm scared.
Yasu, take it out.
I still want to take it out.
How do you feel?
I'm happy.
Yasu, you're cute.
I want to kiss you.
It's cheap, isn't it?
It's a very romantic place.
It's a heaven.
I'm going to sleep now.
What about Niyodo?
It's cute.
Hey, hey, hey.
Niyodo is cute.
Niyodo is cute?
Stop it.
Stop drinking.
Hello
Cute
Hey
What?
Canary?
Watering
Here
I want to die
What happened to your butt?
My butt
What's going on?
It's a chikubimbi.
It's dangerous.
It's bad.
Really?
Is it dangerous?
It's dangerous.
No, no, no, no!
F***!
Please, stop it!
Wait!
That's too much!
It hurts.
It's painful.
Wait a minute.
Please give me a piece of water.
A piece of water for girls.
It's like a attraction.
It's painful.
It's melting.
You look like a person who is in a game.
I'm sorry.
Didn't you put salt in it?
You put salt in it, didn't you?
My butt hurts.
How was it? Was it good?
It was good.
What is this?
I'll wipe it for you.
I'll lick it for you.
It looks like an SA.
It looks like it's bleeding.
It's dangerous.
You're kind.
I can't stand it.
Chocolate?
Is it delicious?
Is it sweet?
It's delicious.
She licked the chicken.
Yasu has a great attitude.
He looks like a pervert.
He looks like a boy who is being bullied.
Open your mouth.
Was it funny?
It was really funny.
sex is the best
I'm surprised
you are the best
do you feel good?
cute?
do you want to do it?
sorry
Do you want to sit down?
She is standing.
Oh my god, she is moving a lot.
Please calm down.
Naro-chan, are you in a panic?
Oh my god.
Naro-chan, listen to me.
Is it fun?
Yes, it is.
It is fun to play with her.
Really?
Naro-chan, can you stand up?
Which one do you like better, your underwear or...
I want to see it directly.
You want to see it directly?
Yes, I want to see it directly.
That's crazy.
I'll give it to you.
Your underwear.
Is it okay?
It's a present.
You're happy, aren't you?
I'll give it to you.
It smells good.
It's coming.
It's amazing.
Do you want to lick it more?
Yes, I want to lick it more.
I want to lick it.
I want to get used to it.
More.
Don't worry.
I'm scared.
Nobody is saying that with a face like this.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
I want to take a bath.
I'm so sleepy.
So sleepy.
I'm started to hold the camera.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm so excited.
I want to hold it.
I want to take a video of you licking it.
I feel like I'm getting used to the power of alcohol.
I feel good.
It's weird, isn't it?
I think it's good to put it on your butt.
I'm sorry
What do you want to do with this?
This
That's what happens when you come this far
Say it properly
I'll put it in
Where?
I'll put it in the basket
What?
Jinpo
What are you doing?
Throw it properly!
I want to put the ball in the bag.
You want to put it in the bag?
You want to put it in?
You haven't put it in yet?
It feels good, Chien-chan.
It feels really good.
I'm going to sing a song.
Why don't you put it in?
Why do you do that?
I'm a pervert.
Did you make your boyfriend go out a lot today?
I don't want you to go out like this every day.
I don't do it with my boyfriend.
Look at this.
What are you going to do?
I'm already wearing it.
What should I do?
What should you do?
Please put it in.
More?
What do you want to do?
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
Yes.
Please.
Is it okay?
It's because you're wearing a tie.
Is it that much?
Wow.
You're putting it in so quickly.
You're putting it in.
My hips...
What?
I'm going to go straight.
Where are you going?
My knees are cramping.
Do you want me to put it in too?
Congratulations!
Wait, wait! I want to put it in too!
What is this?
Are you going to put it in?
It's too close.
Don't grab it.
It's in.
Yasu, it's in.
This feels good.
HimeRin.
This is bad.
I think I can take it all.
It feels good.
You look happy.
Say more.
Whose mark is it?
It feels good.
You're going to die.
Give me your bag.
Hey!
Who said that?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You can't do that.
Lend me the camera.
Amazing.
I'm scared.
Put a lot of weight on your back.
I will.
I'll move you a lot.
Stand up from the back.
Do you want to sit down?
Oh my god!
Harumi-san, you're amazing!
You have to show it.
Oh, wait a minute.
If I were you...
Take a picture.
Look at the camera.
Peep, peep.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
More.
More!
Go!
I'm scared!
Nothing, nothing, nothing!
I'm so happy.
Why are you so happy?
Sex is the best.
How do you feel?
I'm so happy.
Is it good?
Did you come here?
Yes
Do you want more?
Look over there
What about there?
No
This one is OK
OK
Do you put this one in?
Yes
Let's put it in.
Who wants to put it in?
Hold it.
I'll hold it.
Look at the camera.
It feels good.
It's really in.
Does it feel good?
It's dangerous.
What's dangerous?
Sex is the best.
Kissing is the best
Why are you pulling it out?
Don't pull it out
It's coming out
You are good at jumping.
How is your jump?
I can't jump.
You are very excited.
I can do it.
You can do it.
Yasu, hold this.
What is it?
It's dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
I'm going to die.
No, no, I'm going to come out.
Who do you think you are?
Stop, stop, I'm going to come out.
No?
No? Then should I do it here?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no!
What?
You're gonna live?
No, I don't want to.
No, no, no!
You're gonna live?
I'm gonna die.
You're gonna live, right?
I'm gonna kill you.
You're gonna live?
No, no, no!
You're gonna die?
I want to have sex more.
I don't want to laugh.
I want to put it in.
I'm sweating.
Are you okay?
I'm okay again.
I'm sorry.
I'll take it off for you.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Open your eyes.
What is it?
It's dangerous.
Oh my god!
Shin-san!
Are you okay?
I feel good!
It's me!
I'm happy.
I'm sorry.
I want to die.
I'm not done yet.
I can't do it.
It's too painful.
I'm not done yet.
Let's make it fast.
What?
Are you going to die?
I'm going to die.
It's okay.
No.
I'm going to move.
What?
Nono-chan.
I'm going to move.
Do you want this photo?
I don't think you need this photo.
I don't need it either.
What if I use it?
I want to move it.
Do you want to move it?
Please.
I want to move it.
You're so quick.
You can move it.
Thank you.
Let's go to the bathroom.
I can't stand it.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Yes, please.
Let's go to the bathroom.
How do you feel?
Let me see.
Are you serious?
Are you trying to move by yourself?
This is erotic, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
This picture is dangerous.
Is it dangerous?
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom.
It's faster than zoom, zoom, zoom.
It's really fast.
Are you going?
I did my best.
You did your best.
Am I?
I'm just saying because I want to tease you.
I don't know.
Am I?
It's love. Love.
Is it love?
Love.
That's not love.
It's love in Karuizawa.
Give me a kiss.
That way?
Not that way?
What's going on?
Love...I'm sorry.
That love...
What are you doing?
No, no.
Like this.
It's like heaven.
It's amazing.
It's biting.
How is it?
What is this?
This is the birth of Karuizawa.
This is dangerous.
What are you doing, Momo-chan?
Look at her.
Look at the woman.
That's right.
Chikabe, Chikabe, Chikabe.
Do you want to try it?
Good job!
You drank too much!
I don't want to do this!
I'm going! I'm going!
This feels good!
I want to do a backflip!
I want to hug you.
I want to hug you from behind.
I love you.
I love you too.
I'll open your hips.
I'm sorry.
Good!
Can you see it?
I can see it
I feel so good
I'm going to be killed if I get caught.
It's okay if you don't get caught.
It feels good.
Spread it out.
Can you see it?
I can see it.
You wanted to see it, didn't you?
I'm glad you're here.
What are you doing?
Hurry up.
Hime-chan is waiting for you.
I'm talking about Kuri-onna Shora.
Hurry up.
Where do you want to put it?
Back.
It's dangerous, so move to the side.
Gumi-chan, sorry.
Thank you.
I'm great.
Come on, come on.
Don't put your head down too much.
You'll get a cramp in your neck.
It's not here.
Is it in?
I don't like this
This is good
This is really good
It's hot
It's so hot
This is so hot
I'm so hot
It doesn't have air
No, it's not good
You are so hot
It's like a boyfriend
Don't you want to show your boyfriend?
It's annoying
It's annoying because it's the first week
That's right, I don't say anything
That's right
But in fact
You say it
I don't want to come when I'm sleeping
That's right
You want to go?
You went?
Oh no
I'm so tired
Do you want to go in more?
Are you okay?
Do you like to move your hips?
No, I'm fine.
I'll listen to you.
Are you okay?
I'll open the door.
I'll open it.
Are you okay?
You're in there.
I'm so hungry.
How do you feel?
I feel so good.
I feel like my husband.
Ouch!
It really hurts.
It's scary.
It's blood.
No, no, no.
I wanted to go.
Sorry, sorry.
Look at the camera.
I'm sorry.
What?
Let go of me.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
Oh my god!
What?
I got it!
Did you see it?
Did you get it?
I got it!
You drank too much!
Oh my god!
It's amazing!
Who is it?
Tissue?
I want to shoot too.
I don't like this guy.
It's boring.
What do you mean?
It's a cat fall.
Let's do it together.
I'm sorry.
This is not funny at all.
This is very erotic.
What is this footwork?
Please do this with one hand.
This is a good memory.
It's coming out.
I want to see it coming out.
I'm going.
I'm going to do it.
It's like a grudge.
It's still coming out.
It's not coming out yet.
It's not coming out anymore.
It's really coming out.
That's amazing.
You're licking it.
What's the taste of the food?
It's hot.
This is amazing.
It's the one from Karuizawa.
Is it dirty?
It's light.
It's dirty.
Give me a tissue.
Sorry.
Come on in.
It's a living thing.
It's dirty.
It's really dirty.
It's more dirty than a boyfriend.
It's like a dirty gelatine.
It feels really good.
What is it?
Thank you.
Thanks.
It's over.
Yasu, get in the car.
Yeah!
He got in the car.
It's the best when you go home.
The best when you go home.
Can you say something to your boyfriend?
I'm sorry that I'm more comfortable than my boyfriend.
Me too.
Can you pay attention to me?
Really?
Are you really paying attention to me?
It's good.
Let's drink.
We can still go.
It's a long night.
This is really bad.
Monoko.
He's doing it with Yuna.
Really?
He's really attacking the guy.
He's totally drunk.
He's drunk.
He's stubborn, right?
I don't want to say this, but...
Wait a minute.
I'm going to hit you.
I'm sorry.
You're so mean.
I've never seen such a mean actor.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm going to hit you.
I'm so pissed off.
I don't care about myself.
It's fun!
It's the best.
It's delicious!
What are you doing?
I don't know.
You were spinning around before.
Wait a minute.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
Gather around.
It's too good.
Let's drink.
Cheers!
Let's drink!
Oh, it's coming!
It's coming!
Cheers!
Oh, my God!
I'm a little dizzy.
Do you want to drink something?
I drink!
Then I'll bring it.
Let's read it together.
What are you guys doing?
I don't know. I'm still sleepy.
It's pretty easy.
It's a rare reaction.
Bring it here.
It's amazing.
What's with the pants?
Isn't that yogurt?
It's a dot com.
I don't feel good when I do this.
I want to talk too much.
Come here.
I'm not talking to you.
What?
What are you doing?
What is that?
What?
They are all naked.
What are you guys doing?
You can tell by looking.
It's a sacrosanctus.
What are you doing?
You guys are so dirty.
The last one.
I haven't seen the last one for a long time.
What are you doing?
I'm talking to you.
Is it a Jack?
Why is it an item Jack?
What are you doing?
Don't throw it away.
It's really dirty.
Did you write something to drink?
Let's drink.
That's crazy.
There's nothing to say.
It was nice.
Let's drink.
Let's drink something to celebrate.
What is it?
Kuruizaki?
Solari.
Solari for everyone.
Don't you want to draw Solari's face?
What is it?
Hakurei's expression is getting softer.
He is being embraced by kindness.
What is it?
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Be honest.
I was talking to you.
Let's toast to what we've done.
Let's toast to the next sex!
Yeah!
Sex is the best!
Oh, no!
Cheers!
Sex is the best!
You're the best!
You're so annoying.
You shouldn't have done that.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
It can't be helped.
You're so annoying.
You're not going to do this in the fall, are you?
What?
You're not going to do it?
No way.
I should think about it.
You should talk about it.
I can't.
You can't do anything.
But I'll be a little bit nervous.
Seriously.
What are you talking about?
Ah!
Sorry.
Well, well, well.
Once.
I'm sorry.
You should talk about it once.
But again.
It's starting.
What?
I don't know.
Really?
Sex is the best!
I got sex is the best!
What?
Sex is the best!
Telo-telo!
I know these three are going to do it, but I didn't expect it.
What is this?
I'm sorry!
I was talking about it earlier.
It's very erotic.
I said it's very erotic.
I was wearing clothes and I didn't do anything.
This is because I went to the bathroom.
What?
I'm sorry.
It's very bad.
Good job.
I don't like the troublemaker.
What does that mean?
I can't forgive you for that.
What?
Misa, didn't you say you love Kareppippi?
I love Kareppippi.
What are you doing now?
You saw something, didn't you?
I did.
What did you do?
There was a chinko in the mango.
Replay it. Replay it.
Replay it. How was it?
Like this.
It's perfect.
Replay it.
Other parts.
Replay VTR?
I heard it when I was patting my butt.
Like this.
Wow, that's great!
Attack! Attack!
It's been a while since we did this.
Can you lick it?
I'm sorry!
Me too?
Wait!
Cute!
I'm sorry!
I don't need it anymore!
It's delicious.
Chimpanzee, do your best.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
Yes, it's delicious.
Chimpanzee, is it delicious?
Yes.
Good job.
She said she didn't do anything.
You're amazing.
I didn't do anything.
What is that eating?
Don't underestimate me.
What?
I lick it as long as there is a chimp here.
It's like I've heard of it.
It's cool.
Oh no, oh no.
Misa's body.
Misa's body is so strong.
Oh no, oh no.
How about that one?
Oh, no, no.
It's so good.
I'm going to train you a lot from now on.
She's a good girl.
Good girl.
Let's sit over here.
Let's compare.
You want to compare?
Good girl.
She's amazing.
Was Sona really that erotic?
She's really erotic.
It's amazing.
This way, this way.
This is amazing.
Let's take a picture of you.
Everyone is moving their chips.
I'm also a chip.
What do you mean?
I'm a chip.
I'm working on a chip.
Let's exchange.
Let's move around and go around.
I'm also a chip.
Oh, that feels good.
Oh, that's a little...
Oh, Chikkun, no, it's coming out.
It's coming out, it's coming out.
Oh, stop it, Chikkun.
I'm so happy.
It's like that.
Oh, that looks fun.
Oh, I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
It's hot.
Oh, my God.
I haven't seen it yet.
She is so beautiful.
Yes, she is.
I thought I couldn't see her.
Let me help you.
I'm sleepy.
Let's talk.
I want to lick my butt.
I want to lick it too.
He's licking it.
Amazing.
I want to lick it.
So cute.
He's licking something.
You're the best.
You're the best again.
Amazing.
It feels good. Is it good?
Give me a kiss.
You want me to lick it?
I want to lick 699.
You want me to lick 699?
You are very good at it, Soma.
It's surprising.
You are the best at it.
What?
Give your husband a word.
I'm sorry for today. It's fun.
Which do you like more, your boyfriend or us?
I like this one.
You like your boyfriend, don't you?
Do you like this one?
Yes.
You're so cute.
I don't want to go.
What?
Can I go?
Yes, you can.
But I don't want to go.
If you go, I won't let you in.
I don't want to go.
Why are you trying to put it in another child?
No, I won't put it in.
You won't put it in?
I won't put it in.
You're going to open your buttocks a lot.
Are you trying to put it in so that you can't put it in another child?
Hey, please.
I won't put it in.
The country is amazing.
How do you do this?
It's the other way around.
No way, I'm over there.
It's like this.
You can do anything as long as you have a chinchin.
But you don't like chinchin, do you?
I want to put it in my mouth.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to cut it.
It's a little embarrassing, but...
Oh, my God.
It's okay. Just a little bit.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Mango is disgusting.
Mango is the best.
Thank you for your hard work.
Chimpanzee is the best.
I told you that everyone's chimpanzee is mine.
Everyone is licking me.
It's terrible.
Isn't it the smallest?
Shut up!
I'm worried.
You'll get tired.
Try to get tired.
High-speed technique.
You haven't won yet.
Really?
You didn't like strawberries.
I like strawberry one more.
I like the strawberry one more.
You like strawberry one more.
But you like the chimpanzee one more.
Which one do you like more?
I like strawberry one more.
But I like chimpanzee one more.
Yeah!
Cheese!
I can see the chimpanzee one more.
I can see it.
Look!
Captain!
You didn't say a word to your boyfriend, did you?
I love Kareppippi.
Is it okay? We do this kind of thing.
Because I don't see this, Kareppi.
I don't see it, but let's say you were watching this.
A word of thanks.
If you were watching.
Kareppippi has a small population, so it's hard to do it.
Bye-bye.
It's terrible.
It's a princess.
It's coming.
What is this?
Wow, look over here.
Something's coming out.
The alcohol has come out.
It's detoxing.
There's a lot of it.
No, that's mine.
I'm the one who's crying.
You can't do that.
You have to lick it.
Double penis?
No way.
Look at Beech-kun.
Beech-kun is waiting.
Cute bunny.
Amazing.
Why are you filming the camera?
It's not raw.
No, it's not.
It's going to break, isn't it?
It's the best.
I want to put it in.
Do you want it?
I want to put it in, too.
It's the last one.
Do you want it?
Let's put it in raw.
Let's put it in.
I told you not to do so!
No, no, no, no.
I said so.
No, no, no.
Look, she is going to go in.
No, I'm not.
She is going in.
I told you not to do so.
No, no, no.
No, I can't.
Wow, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
This is the view I can see from here.
It's amazing.
Sorai-chan is amazing.
Can I put it in raw?
Hime-chan's?
Sorai-chan's is raw.
Can I put it in raw?
Why do you put it in raw?
Do you want me to take it off?
It's gross.
Can you take it off here?
I can't do it.
It hurts.
It hurts so much.
I'm scared.
It feels great.
Amazing.
It's intense.
Do you feel good?
You are not feeling good?
Not quite, you know.
Why???
Ah!
Mino-chan, what do you think?
Ochi-in-po!
Why?
What??
Ochi-in-po!
Why??
Soran-chan, you are not feeling good?
Ochi-in-po!
Why??
Why?
Ochi-in-po!
I don't want to do it.
It feels good.
Don't let go.
It feels so good.
Wow, look at that.
Amazing.
Oh, no.
Everyone, do you feel good?
Do you feel good?
It's so funny.
Is it funny?
It would be great if you were my boyfriend.
I don't care.
It's so funny.
Oh my god.
I feel so bad.
What do you want to eat?
Lasso Fella?
You don't talk much, but you have the most potential to be a skater, don't you?
I have the most potential.
I don't talk much.
Wow, over there.
You're wearing it.
Say a word to your boyfriend.
What?
I'm sorry.
You think so?
I think so.
What are you doing?
I want it.
Next Jinpo?
Drink while you go.
I'm the strawberry princess.
You are so cute.
You drink here and talk here.
Good, good.
Amazing.
It's amazing.
There's something in there too.
Amazing.
It's disgusting.
Oh, but it's still 1.
What is this?
My legs...
I'm scared.
You're so good.
Oh no, I'm the best today.
I'm the best today.
I'm scared to scream.
I'm serious.
It hurts.
I'm scared.
What is it?
I'm shivering.
Shivering?
Is it reflected on the back?
Yes, it is.
You're so cute.
I'm so scared.
I'm scared.
I can't feel it.
This way?
A little more.
I can't feel it.
This?
Yay!
Sutan is the most excited today.
Why?
She is excited.
Look over there.
Amazing.
She is excited.
Be careful.
Mom! Mom!
You are so cute.
Don't move your hands.
It's dangerous.
Oh my god.
They're coming.
It hurts!
Oh, no.
You were very energetic.
What's wrong?
It's good.
Can I touch it?
Yes, you can.
It's good.
It hurts!
It feels good.
What?
It feels good?
It feels good.
It feels better than the spicy one.
It feels better than the spicy one?
I'm getting called.
Let's go to the spicy one.
Who's the spicy one?
We're going to the spicy one today.
Oh, no!
I'm being hugged.
I thought I was going to fall.
Did you hit me?
Oh, no!
I'll give it to you.
It's so hot.
It's normal.
It's a good feeling.
Oh, great.
Oh, my God!
What do you think of this Chimpanzee?
I like all of them.
I think this Chimpanzee is more comfortable than the previous one.
What?
I like it.
Hey, behind you!
Behind you!
Hey!
Isn't this crazy?
Let's get started.
This is crazy.
Are you happy?
Haru, do you want to do it in the middle?
Everyone do it in the middle.
Let's see how Sora-chan is doing.
How is it?
I want to eat Sora-chan's kiss.
What?
I want to eat it.
Everyone, look at this.
Look at this.
I want to eat it.
You like this.
What is this sweet potato?
I love you.
I love you too.
I want you.
Is it because you don't drink alcohol?
Is it because I love you?
If you look at my boyfriend like this, he will get angry.
He will get angry.
I'm going home.
It's painful.
They are all coming to me.
I'm going to call them.
They are scared.
Is this right?
Yes, yes.
Is it ok?
It's sticking out.
Ok, ok.
Ah, it's that way again.
That way.
I can't.
If you drink alcohol, you'll be like this.
It's almost done.
I want to be in the picture.
Come on, come on, take a picture.
Come on, take a picture.
I want to be in the picture, too.
Come on, come on, take a picture.
Good, good.
You are in the picture.
I'm in the picture.
Peace, peace.
I'm sorry.
You love to be petted.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
I don't have a boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
You're good.
You're hot.
I'm sorry.
Someone drop the camera.
Where?
Someone drop it.
I'm sorry.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I'm so happy!
This is Minari.
Minari-san.
What's wrong?
She's crying.
Are you okay?
It's dangerous.
It feels good.
So cute!
You are all so cute.
So cute.
No!
I want to cry!
I'm sorry.
Everyone, please come here.
Yay!
Is there anyone?
Everyone, please come here.
Oh, it's cold.
Everyone, the training camp is the best!
The training camp is the best!
Is it the best?
It's the best!
Oh, that's good.
Oh, it's cold.
It's so cold.
Oh, it's cute.
Are you still teasing her here?
Hurry up!
Hold on.
I've seen Mala-chan and Misa-chan.
Yes, Mala-chan and Misa-chan.
So cute.
Bye bye.
I can't see.
I can see.
Can you see?
Yes, I can.
No, you can't do that.
It's because it's a baby.
What is this?
This is too much.
He's not coming out.
Oh, no.
He's coming out.
That's it.
What?
I'm going to put it in.
You're going to put it in.
What's going on?
Hey, hey.
You're going to put it in.
Nama is the best.
Like this?
Yes.
Ah!
He's so kind!
He's so kind, too!
It's ok.
He's so kind, too.
It feels good to do it live.
It's ok?
It's ok.
Oh, it hurts!
Oh!
Oh, it came out.
Oh, no.
Show me.
It came out a lot.
It's really coming out.
Oh, no.
Noisy
It's good
Wait
The princess
The princess is also noisier
Noisy
Where
So noisier
More
Wine
Noisy
You are in a mess!
Are you going to get into the mess?
Are you going to get in?
Are you going to be in a mess?
What?
Are you going to get in?
Are you going to be in a mess?
Do you want more?
It's fun to take pictures, but what is this?
Who is taking pictures?
It's me.
How do you feel?
Do you want to have a drink with me?
You feel good, don't you?
Hime-chan's voice is amazing.
I'm scared!
Are you okay?
I'm scared too.
Are you going to take it out?
It's gone.
I took it out.
Do you think it will come out?
Really?
The last one!
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Huh?
The last one!
What about Sora?
She's doing a double-up.
Sora is going for the fourth one.
Do you think I'm doing a double-up?
I think so.
It's obvious.
Let's get it on!
Okay.
What's up!
I'm so sorry!
I think Sora is about to die.
Let's do a Sora call.
It's Sora!
Sora!
Sola! Sola!
Sola!
It's good, isn't it?
It's amazing.
How is it, Yoko?
I can't do it.
Yoko, this is bad.
Be careful.
Oh, my God!
It's coming out!
You have to hold it tight!
Hold it tight!
Is it coming out?
Oh, my God! It's coming out!
It's warm!
Oh, my God!
I think you can eat a little more.
Ah!
You're the fourth one.
Nakanishi! The first one!
The second one!
The third one!
The fourth one!
Yay!
Isn't it bright?
Let's eat!
Yay!
It's bright!
Nakatoshi, you're the best!
Oh, oh, oh.
Wow, that was nice.
That was so much fun.
Yay!
That was fun.
What? Really?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't be silly, really.
Seriously?
They're really angry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Seriously?
Hold on.
You're kidding.
You're being called out.
Seriously?
Wow.
Don't be silly, okay?
Say a word to your boyfriend.
Say a word.
A word?
Yes.
No, I don't have anything.
What do you mean?
Are you saying that you don't have anything?
No, I don't have anything.
I've been having sex lately, so I'm self-sufficient.
I'm self-sufficient.
Oh, that's scary.
Well...
What is it? What is it? What is it?
What is it?
I really want you to be this cute.
What? You suddenly...
You were so cute earlier.
Are you back to the morning mood?
Wait!
What?
Actually, I love Pippi, but...
But you were really scared of Chimpo earlier.
I want to be with Chimpo!
Say it to your boyfriend again.
Please take care of Chimpo.
I'm not talking to my boyfriend today, so I don't think it's a good idea not to talk to him.
Is that okay?
But say something to your boyfriend.
Say something to my boyfriend?
If you were watching this...
Sorry, I felt good today.
This is good for the blood circulation.
It's not gonna happen.
It's gonna happen.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
Wow!
I can't believe it!
Do you want to have a toast?
Let's have a toast.
Let's drink.
You're kidding!
Wow!
1, 2, 3, 4!
Yaaaaaaaay !!!!
M
This is hell.
Thank you for watching!