Hello?
How is Tokyo?
How is your job? Yeah.
You don't have money,
and the hotel is expensive.
I asked Sora's mother to stay
at the hotel, so let me stay there.
No, I'll take the hotel by myself.
You don't have to spend so much money.
But it's okay.
We were good friends when we were little.
I want you to stop it.
What? No.
Mom? Mom? Come in.
Long time no see.
Long time no see, Aoi.
I haven't seen you for a while.
Are you nervous? No, I'm not.
I'm so happy.
Come in.
Excuse me.
It's hard to get a job.
I have to do it in two years.
I wonder if I should join the
same company as Aoi-kun.
Oh, Suzu, don't be so clingy to Aoi-kun.
It's okay.
It's been a long time since we met.
You see, Aoi-kun is in trouble, right?
Oh, my sister was next to
Aoi-kun, so I'm jealous. I'm scared.
That's not true.
Oh, I'm angry. Aoi-kun, help me.
I'm really angry.
Aoi, you say something.
Aoi.
Where are you going tomorrow?
I'm going to Shinbashi tomorrow.
Shinbashi?
It's a little far from here.
There are a lot of subways
in Tokyo, so it won't take long.
Will you come to Tokyo
when you get a job? I think so.
I see.
What's wrong? Nothing.
Do you still like my
sister? I don't know.
I haven't met her at all.
I didn't like you, and I
don't think I like you, Sora.
Yes, you're a liar.
Today, I'm going to have a
barbeque to celebrate Aoi's new job!
Yay!
Hey, you used to cook
a lot, didn't you? Yeah.
Let's eat.
Itadakimasu.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
You'll be fine if you eat vegetables.
Don't you eat
vegetables? Don't worry.
I have vegetables.
I'm eating vegetables.
Thank you.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Congratulations.
Don't eat meat. Eat vegetables.
You can eat grilled meat.
If you eat grilled meat, it's grilled meat.
That's not true.
It's true.
I remembered the old days today.
It was fun.
Thank you.
I had fun, too.
Then I'll go to bed soon.
OK.
Good night.
Do you still like
Aoi-kun? No, I don't.
You know we're
not dating, right?
So you won't complain
if I date Aoi-kun, right?
With Aoi-kun?
I won't say no, but... There's someone
better than Aoi-kun, right? I like Aoi-kun.
I like Aoi-kun.
If you like him so much, you
can confess your love to him.
I'll confess my love to him.
What's wrong?
What are you
doing? I like Aoi-kun.
It's good, isn't
it? No, it's not.
I like Aoi-kun.
I don't know if it's okay.
Do you still like my
sister? Well, that's.
..
Isn't it good for
me? It's not good.
But my sister doesn't like Aoi anymore.
What?
Really?
I'll make you feel better.
Give it to me.
No, no, no.
I won't give it to you.
What are you
doing? Don't do that.
I'm fine.
What's fine?
You don't like it, do you?
You don't like it, do
you? It's not good.
It's not good.
It's all right.
I have to tell my sister.
If she finds out, she'll kill me.
It's all right.
My sister doesn't like you.
She doesn't care.
It's all right.
It's hot.
Be calm.
I can make you feel better.
What do you mean?
Do you feel good?
Are you going to take off your clothes?
My boobs are bigger than yours.
You don't have to show them.
Why don't you take
them off? It's hot.
You like bigger boobs, don't you, Aoi?
You are bigger than
your sister, aren't you?
I don't know my sister.
Boys like boobs,
don't they? I like boobs.
It's hot.
Don't do that.
You're standing up.
Don't look at me. It's embarrassing.
Do you want me to pinch you?
Pinch you?
Yes.
What? Pinch you.
What? Here.
What? Like this.
What?
You can pinch me like this.
What? No way.
How is it? Oh, no.
Wow.
※This video is a derivative
work of Touhou Project.
It's hot, so I'll take it off.
No, stop it.
I'm taking it off.
No, no, no.
You'll be seen by the sky...
Are you okay? No, no, no.
You're misunderstanding.
You're already asleep, aren't you?
You may wake up.
I'm not going to die.
You'll be fine.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't breathe.
But it feels good, doesn't it?
Let's get comfortable together.
It's better to touch
you directly, isn't it?
Let us know if you have any questions.
I can't breathe.
Is it good?
I'm suffocating.
It's fun, isn't
it? It's not fun.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to
sleep? It's okay.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you really not going
to wake up? I'll be fine.
Really? I'll be fine.
Aren't you light? I'll be fine.
What will you do when you wake up?
I don't like waking up, so I'll be fine.
I'm going to make a cup of coffee.
No, no, no.
I think my sister will scold me.
Please turn down the volume.
I'm going to faint.
Are you okay? I'm okay.
Can you hold your voice?
I'll do my best.
No, I can't.
I love your voice.
I can't hold my voice.
No, you can't.
It's over.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You're my childhood friend.
Why?
You're not?
What?
You don't like Aoi, I like Aoi.
So, I can have an affair with you.
What?
An affair?
Yes.
It's just you two.
Are you OK? I'll put more.
No, you can't.
Ai-chan, you can't.
Ai-chan, you look so comfortable.
Ai-chan, you'll wake up.
Don't touch my hips.
I have your hips.
Then, I'll touch your hips.
Do you want to
attack me? Attack you.
I feel good.
Do you feel good? I feel good.
Don't move.
Look at me.
What? Look at me.
Can you see me?
Do you feel good?
I feel so good.
Do you feel good? I feel sick.
I feel sick.
I can't speak.
Shut your mouth.
I feel sick.
It feels good.
I love you.
Hang in there.
It feels so good.
I'm going to cry.
It's true that I like you, Aoi.
Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
Oh, I forgot that I have a class today.
I'll take this.
OK.
Now I'm motivated.
See you.
You get along well with Suzu.
You two get along pretty well, don't you?
What do you mean?
You're bold, aren't you?
You didn't say anything to me.
Don't be silent and say something.
You didn't say anything to me, either.
You know that, don't you?
I know, but I don't know.
If you don't know, say it!
Come out!
I told you!
I've always loved you.
Me too.
You're so cute.
You too.
You hurt me a lot.
You too, right?
Wait, I'm not that big.
Why? I'm not that big.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not saying that.
Show me.
It's difficult.
What are you talking about?
I'm taking off my shirt.
I'm going to take you to
the vet for your condition.
I'm not going to take you to the vet today.
Of course, I'll take you to
the vet for more information.
I've been taking the cat to
the vet for about a month.
It's been a month since the vet
came, and now he's coughing.
This is a video of me eating a baby's food.
It's hot, so I put it in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but I have to eat it.
I love you.
I don't know.
It smells good.
It feels good.
Do you like this?
It looks painful.
You look like you feel good.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
My baby.
Do you want to quit? I love you.
I love you.
It feels so good.
It's so hot.
I feel sick.
But I can't move.
幼稚園生徒たちのパパは、運動会にビックリした。
その時、パパは、貧血を感じている。
パパは、遺伝子でも、明らかに貧血を感じている。
I'm sorry.
It's painful, isn't
it? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
What a pain!
I'm sorry that I woke you up.
I'm going to go too.
Hey, Aoi, let's go to the
convenience store after this.
I want to go with you.
You have a little homework, don't you?
Wouldn't it be better
to go with three people?
No, no, no, it's an important time.
Shopping.
Hey, Aoi, you want to
go with me, don't you?
You want to go with me,
don't you? Leave it to me.
Why?
Aoi-kun, do you want to eat strawberries?
Yes.
I feel like my sister is going to do it.
I can't help it.
Did you see my condensed milk attack?
Is it delicious?
Yes.
Aoi-kun, I want to eat
strawberries with condensed milk.
Condensed milk?
Yes.
It's sweet.
What? You can eat strawberries on your own!
You said you don't like strawberries
with condensed milk, didn't you, Suzu?
Oh, so that's what you do, Suzu.
Hey, Aoi-kun, I want to eat
strawberries with condensed milk, too.
Put it on, put it on.
Aoi-kun.
I'll give you half.
I love you.
Hey, it's great. Let me eat it too.
I want it too.
You give it to me first, right?
I want to eat it with condensed milk.
Let me eat.
Say ah.
I want it too.
Hey.
What's going on?
You said you didn't like Aoi.
I did, but I don't anymore.
Why? I don't get it.
You said you liked me.
I did, didn't I?
No, you said you liked me.
Aoi?
What time is it?
Aoi? I'm in a hurry.
Hey!
I'm going to take a bath and go to bed.
What's going on?
What is that?
I can't believe it.
I don't know what it means.
What is that? I know.
It's annoying.
I know.
Let's go.
I don't like it.
Hey, what are you doing?
Why are you in
the bath? Get out.
Get out.
It's not the time
to be in the bath.
It's not like that.
Let me make it clear.
It's time to put on black and white.
It's not a little.
Don't choose properly.
Which do you choose,
me or Suzu? I can't choose.
Can't you choose? No, I can't.
Really?
I love both of them.
What? What? No way.
It's not like that.
It's not like putting them in order.
Which one do you like
better? Both are good.
Both are good, right?
Chinchin is the one you like better, right?
I like mine better.
It's been a while since I've had a baby, so
I'm worried about how the baby will react.
It's been a while since I had a baby, so
I've been taking care of
the baby since last year, and
I'm worried about whether
I'll be able to raise my baby.
It is said that if you eat a lot of sweets, you will be able to eat a lot of sweets
OK!
I'm going to put it in a bowl.
Oh, great!
I'm better at it, right?
I'm getting used to it.
You like it, don't
you? Yes, I do.
You're so good at it, Binbin.
Wait, I have a lot too.
I have a bigger one.
It's important to wrap it up, but
there is also a direct technique.
It was delicious.
My husband and I have been living in this house for a long time
My husband and I decided to give
him a bath for the first time in a while.
It's a bath that is not
a bath for cats, but
I will give him a bath, but I am
afraid he will be too scared to go out.
It's me, isn't it?
It's me when you go, isn't it?
How do you feel?
It's me, isn't it?
You like Suzu, don't you?
You can't be together.
We're not together.
I'm so nervous.
I want to go, but I can't.
I'm not going to stop.
Oh no, Chikubi is also feeling sick.
Are you sick, Chikubi?
Chikubi is weak.
Then I'll give you a lot to drink.
I can't help it.
I can't drink at all.
It's fun.
I'm sorry, I can't help it.
It's a bell, isn't
it? Yes, it is.
Which one is it?
Hurry up and decide.
You have to decide.
It's a bell, isn't
it? Yes, it is.
Which one is it?
I can't decide the first one.
What are you talking
about? I'm sorry.
You're so honest, but you're so hard on me.
You can't do that.
I won't let you go.
It's painful.
It's painful, isn't it?
You have to be patient.
I'm scared.
You can't do that.
Mom, I'm going to the bathroom.
I told you, didn't I?
Well, that's a bit of a
no-no, isn't it? Yeah.
Because you didn't decide.
After all, you don't usually change.
Which one? No, really.
Which one?
I really can't believe it.
Make it clear.
I'm going to ask you the answer today.
Answer?
Which one is better? Make it clear.
Oh.
Which one?
Both Both?
Both?
Which one?
I don't know What do you mean?
I can't choose
What is this hand?
What?
Are you turning me down?
Hey, wait
Make it clear which
one you want Hey, wait
Hey, I can't do that
Which one do you
like? I don't know.
I don't know.
Both are good.
Both? Both.
I got it.
Then, think a little more.
Which do you like better,
left or right? Right, I guess.
Right?
You like me better.
That's right.
Oh!
Are you done?
No, I'm not done yet.
Yuji is the worst.
You're right.
Oh, no.
Which one do you like
this time? I like both.
Which one do you
like? I like both.
like? I can't decide.
I like both.
You like both?
Yes.
Which one is better?
Which one is better? Look.
Don't run away.
It's not me.
The bell looks good on you.
Show me.
Let me see.
Both of them are great.
Which one do you like?
This one is a little transparent.
The red one is cute.
Which one do you
like? Both of them.
Why? Both of them.
Let me see.
It's me, isn't it?
It's soft, isn't it?
It's big, isn't it? It's big.
Sensitivity is important.
Touch me more.
Do you love me, Aoi?
Aoi, you didn't say anything until
now, but you liked to be bullied.
I'll give you a lot.
Ah...
It feels good, doesn't it?
Which one feels
good? Both of them.
Which one is
better? Both of them.
Why?
Why? Both of them
are bad? No, no.
Which one?
Both of them felt good.
I thought so, too.
Don't run away.
Why are you running away?
Why are you running
away? No, no, no.
You're mean.
It's not fair.
My feather is the hardest, isn't it?
No, mine is better.
You like it, don't
you? No, I don't.
But it's so soft.
It feels good.
No, you don't.
No, I don't.
I love both of them.
Do you love both of them?
Which one do you like?
Let me feel good.
If you like both of them, let me feel good.
Touch it and decide.
Touch it properly.
It's still 40g.
Let me feel good.
It's not enough.
More.
Which one do you like?
Touch it and make me feel good.
Let me kiss you.
Which one do you like?
Well, both of them.
Why?
Both of them are lovely.
Lovely?
Which one?
What?
Well, Suzu and I are lovely, too.
If you say you like both of them,
I have to make you feel good.
Take responsibility.
What?
You don't like it?
If you don't like it, I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
I don't care anymore.
Both of you are very wet.
Thank you.
It's sweet.
Are you satisfied? Why? Not yet.
How can I be satisfied?
You haven't touched my boobs yet.
Boobs? Look.
Look.
Which one do you like more?
This one or this one.
Both.
Both?
Idiot!
Why don't you decide
properly? Do it harder.
It's not that easy.
Do you like the bigger one?
You've been grooming only Suzu.
You have a lot of energy.
This is why men...
Touch it properly.
I love the way you lick my boobs.
Please lick my boobs too.
I feel good.
You are satisfied with this.
No, I'm not.
What are you satisfied with?
What is this hand?
I think you both feel good enough.
If we don't feel good
together, it doesn't make sense.
Do you like both?
Do you feel good?
Both of you are standing.
Oh, my legs.
Do this.
What is it?
It's a joint work, isn't it?
Wait, what is a joint work?
It's the first time to do a joint work.
It's the first time, isn't it?
Next, make me feel good.
It's not fair.
I did a joint work, so look at me.
I have a new cat.
This is my first time to use the cat room.
I'm glad there is a big cat here.
There are many cats here.
I thought they would be
small, but they are not.
You are so kind.
I don't want to take a rest either.
But you like both, don't you?
I take responsibility for both.
I want more.
It's hard.
Which one do you
like better? I like both.
Both?
Which one?
How about my horse? It was good.
How was it? It was good.
It's mine, isn't it?
No, no, I like your horse better.
How was it?
How?
Why are you so indecisive?
My ferret is the best, isn't it?
No, mine is better.
Your mother was also pulling it.
It's hot.
I feel good, too.
Which side do you
feel good? It's hot.
You are trembling.
Which side do you feel good?
Are you okay? Here you are.
Touch here.
Oh, my.
It feels so good.
I want to do it more.
It's hot.
Is it hot? Touch me.
Aoi-kun.
It's not fair.
It's OK, isn't
it? It's not fair.
Make yourself comfortable.
I'm going to put it in.
It's my turn next.
Oh, it's cold.
Don't just scratch me.
Scratch this side, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How do you feel? It feels good.
How do you feel?
Mele-chan, it's my turn.
Wait 10 seconds.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0
Did you eat well? Yes, I did.
I'm full.
It's my turn next.
Make yourself comfortable.
Look at me.
Can you see me? Yes, I can.
Smile.
I'm glad you're all right.
Don't put your hands on my eyes.
You like my pussy, right?
Which one?
You still don't
understand? I'm sorry.
Don't make a mess.
It's time to go, isn't it?
It's not over yet.
I can't let Aoi go.
Let me go.
Aoi, are you comfortable?
You shouldn't go out.
I'm ready to go out anytime.
I'm getting warmer, Aoi.
This baby is the first child of the family
who were born in the same hospital.
The first child is a girl in the family.
I'm going to give you a pacifier.
Does it feel good?
Do you want me to touch
your neck? I feel tired.
..
boo-boo, you're scared.
Attack from behind.
From the back.
I feel sick.
I don't want to.
I don't have time to rest.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying in front of
me, and I'm so happy that I
can't help but cry when I see him.
I'm so happy that I can't
help but cry when I see him.
This way? It's too early.
Do you feel good? It's hard.
It's hard.
Yabai.
Let's kiss a lot.
Do you like me? Yes, I do.
I like you, too.
Yabai, don't make me wait.
Do you like me, too? I love you.
I love you, too.
I love you.
Oh, it feels good.
I love you so much that I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cry.
Don't cry.
Let me out.
Wow! A lot.
You can still get out, can't you?
I put her inside.
What should I do? She got out.
I'll take care of you.
I said I'll take care of you
and make you feel good.
Then, I'll take care of you, too.
You can still go out.
You're still a baby.
You just gave birth, so you
can't stand up right away.
But you're still a baby.
A little while after birth, I
decided to take care of her.
I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
You're so cute that I'm
going to leave you soon.
Give me a lot of candy.
Give me all of it.
Wow! There are so many!
Wow!
Is this your first time?
There are so many.
Aoi, you are responsible for
having two kids, aren't you?
You are responsible for them, aren't you?
You made friends with them.
Let's live with three of us.
I did it!
I'm the winner!
You've become a man.