We're here, everyone.
It's here.
Wow!
There are so many.
Let's go.
I heard that this year's
hot spring trip is a success.
I want to go to the hot
spring as soon as possible.
But it seems that this
place is quite crowded.
Everyone, let's check in.
Yes.
We said we were coming together.
Then we decided to come to the room.
Can you go to another room
from now on? Thank you.
But I'm already in the room.
I know that.
I'm looking forward to it, but I
need to meet Tokushin Umiya.
I want to get married like Aoi.
Please.
I'm in trouble.
Well, I wonder if it will work out.
Well, good luck.
Thank you.
I'll take care of this Umiya.
I'll make sure to do it.
Don't mess up the room.
I won't.
See you.
The room wasn't open.
What should I do? Oh, Mr.
Abe.
What are you doing with
the luggage in such a place?
Actually, Actually,
my room is gone.
What?
My room is empty.
I feel sorry for you.
Well, two people in the same
room got to know each other.
I've heard that you've known
each other for a long time.
Oh, is that why you were kicked out?
Yes, that's why.
Oh, poor you.
Why don't you come to our room?
Oh, that's a good idea.
Our room is very spacious.
No, I can't do that.
What?
Chief, if you stay here, you'll
have to sleep next to Robin.
I'm worried about you.
I'm really grateful, but I can't do that.
It's okay. Please come.
I'm married, so it's a little bad.
But we don't deny it at all, so it's okay.
The room was wide, so it's okay.
But... Katsuo-nyan is always taking
care of me, so let me thank you.
But it's a little bad.
When you're in trouble,
it's for both of us.
What should I do?
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
I'm hungry.
I'll take the luggage.
But... We'll go this way.
Let's go.
Don't be shy.
I'm shy.
You helped me a lot at work.
What's wrong with you today?
You made me suffer.
I'm fine.
Are you thirsty?
Would you like some
tea? Here you are.
Thank you.
Don't be so nervous.
It's a little close.
Why? Is that so?
I didn't mean to hit you.
It's okay.
Oh, I see.
The sweets here were very
delicious, weren't they? Yes, they were.
You like sweets,
don't you? Yes, I do.
I remember.
I'll give you a bite.
Here you are.
Please open your mouth.
No, no, no.
It's OK.
Do you eat it by
yourself? Yes, thank you.
Oh, no.
Do you want some tea?
No, I'll drink it myself.
You can get rid of the water.
Yes, but I want to drink it with you.
What's the matter?
Chief!
Don't you have a stiff shoulder?
You always take care of
us, don't you? No, I don't.
I love bonito!
I'll give it to you.
Here we go.
It's already in your mouth.
Thank you.
Are you going to eat it?
Tenka, you're so cute.
I'll put a little more pressure.
I'm going to put it in.
You're a professional.
I don't want anything more than this.
What's wrong with you?
You're angry, aren't you?
What's wrong? Nothing.
Why are you hiding it?
What?
What's wrong? Nothing.
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
Please move away.
No, it's not like that.
Wow!
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
Boss!
What are you doing?
It's amazing!
Why do you have so much on your pants?
What are you doing? This is.
..
What is this?
Do you like my
boobs? No, I don't.
I'm going to hit you.
I'm going to hit you, too.
Wait a minute.
Your boobs are getting bigger.
They're getting harder and harder.
Ah...
Oh, stop it... Um,
we are married.
This is dangerous.
But, you're not.
But, you are.
We're the ones who made you do that.
We should be responsible.
You shouldn't do that.
That's right.
It's not that kind of problem.
You always take care of us a lot.
Today, we are
going to... ...eat this.
No, no, no.
That and this.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wow!
It's all over the place.
BINBIN KACHO NO CHINCHIN
What?
Do you have a weak nipple?
What's wrong?
No, it's not like that.
I want to see it.
It's hard.
No.
I'm married, so I can't do this.
Why?
It doesn't matter.
Calm down.
Katsuo, if you touch his nipples,
he'll get more and more angry.
Katsuo, it's better to leave him alone.
That's right.
Let him be.
If you leave him alone, he'll kill you.
Come on, look this way.
Please give me a kiss.
I'm married, so I can't do that.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
Why do you say such a thing?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Hachio?
Hachio's tongue is soft, isn't it?
It's already swollen.
I'm waiting for you.
Your lips are really soft.
What?
Why are you doing this? Wait.
Stop it.
What's wrong?
Can I stop?
You are so cute.
Can you stop being so grumpy?
Calm down, everyone.
You are drooling.
No, I'm not.
Why?
You are so cute.
Honey, don't go out so early.
Don't go out so early.
Kachou-san doesn't want to let you sleep.
Don't you want to?
Don't you want to let me sleep?
What is it? It's a bonito.
Look, your boobs are warm.
Your boobs are warm.
You look so happy.
It's a bonito.
Do you like boobs?
Do you?
What?
Do you want to see my boobs?
Do you like boobs?
Do you want to see our boobs?
No, I don't want to.
Kacchou!
You like boobs, don't you?
I'll show them to you for you.
Only for you.
Kacchou is so cute.
Kacchou!
Don't you want to touch my boobs?
I'm going to take it off.
Calm down, everyone.
Your boobs are very flat.
Oh, Papa! No, that's.
..
Don't you want to touch the chief's boobs?
No, I can't do that.
Don't you want to
touch them? Well.
..
Chief!
The chief is looking at our boobs.
You really want to touch them, don't you?
Do you want me to
take off your bra for you?
You are so cute!
I'll take it off, too.
I want to see it too.
I want you to see it all.
I can see your mouth.
Don't you want to touch it?
Don't you want to eat it?
No, but it's not good.
No, no, no, wait a minute.
Do you still hate boobs?
You like boobs, don't you?
Your hands are moving erotically.
I'm holding you.
No, it's not.
It's good.
Please touch me a lot.
You're getting bigger.
I'll touch you directly.
Oh, wait...
Your little bum was sticking out.
Hey, dad, look at this.
It's gone.
It looks so soft.
You're staring at me.
No, I'm not.
Me, too.
How is it?
Do you want to drink it?
Do you want to touch me?
Please touch me.
Do you want me to touch you a lot?
Do you like it?
You look like you like it.
You have a lot of boobies.
Do you like the boobies
of the otter? I can't choose.
Why?
Do you have one?
You like the boobies of the
otter, don't you? Oh, oh, oh.
Well then,
Kako-chan,
Kako-chan, look.
Ah, ah.
Your nose is getting hot.
It's getting cold.
It's time to go to bed.
I'm not cold at all.
You are addicted to it, aren't you?
You are so cute like a baby.
You are eating it by yourself.
Do you like it?
Please eat as much as you like.
You are getting more and
more comfortable, aren't you?
You are getting better and better.
Oh, you are tickling me, aren't you?
What are you doing? You are so cute!
Wait a minute!
It's too fast!
It's not coming out yet!
Wait a minute!
It's coming out!
Was it about to come out?
It's too fast!
You shouldn't do it so easily.
Next, I'll do it.
You have a lot of blood in the middle.
You're breathing heavily.
Your body is stiff.
Relax, relax.
No, I didn't mean it.
I think you should be quiet.
Don't you like it,
Kacchou? Kacchou.
You always say you have to be honest.
Yes, I do.
You have to smile.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You are sweating a lot.
You are a good boy.
I'll give it to you.
No, you can't.
Oh, that's...
Oh, you're drooling.
No, you can't.
What? I also.
..
I also...
I also... I also... What
are you doing? I also.
..
I also...
You got bit by your favorite boobs.
Boss, you love boobs, don't you?
No.
Your boobs ate your penis.
Does it feel good, boss?
It's coming out.
Wow.
I can see your penis.
He's licking me.
You're so nice.
You're sweating.
Are you all right?
You are making a lot of noise.
I am making a lot of noise.
Are you so excited?
Do you feel good? I'm so sorry.
It's so uncomfortable.
Lots of juice came out.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Look, it's all good.
What's the matter?
Your boobies are shaking.
Do you feel good?
You are getting more and more energetic.
You are shaking your body to the limit.
It's hot!
It's so hot!
You shouldn't be like that!
I'm still a human!
Really?
Are you a human being?
I want to be like that!
I want to pinch you with my boobs!
Wow, it's still warm.
It's still warm here.
Do you feel good?
You're drooling.
It's amazing that your
boobs can become this big.
It's hard.
I'm tired, too.
It's so hard.
The tip of your tongue is bleeding again.
I'm so happy.
You're crying a lot.
Does it feel good?
What's wrong with you?
Again?
You can still do it?
I'm still waiting for you.
You haven't recovered yet, have you?
Your skin is getting red again.
I want to lick your penis, too.
I can't believe you can do that.
This is the taste of a penis warrior.
It was very strong.
So, you are getting married.
You are excited, aren't you?
Are you going out again?
I like to be teased.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
You have a runny nose.
Are you excited?
Wow! It's scary.
It's dirty.
You don't want to go to bed?
Do you still want to go to bed?
No, I don't want to go to bed.
Give me a break.
I know.
You'll get tired if you do it three times.
Do you feel better
now? It was so warm.
I'm sweating a little.
It's been a while since I've been to
a hot spring, so I'm getting excited.
I've been in too much.
It's been a while since I've been to
a hot spring, so I'm getting excited.
I know.
I'm always in a hurry.
I feel like I'm on vacation.
I feel like I was able to take a picture.
The last one was not good.
I shouldn't have done that.
The hot spring was...
But it felt good.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
What's up?
Were you taking a bath alone?
I was in the bath. It was fun.
You have something in your ear.
Oh, really?
I thought there was some water in my ear.
Oh, really? That's terrible.
What is it?
What? Wait, wait.
Oh, no.
What?
Yes.
What? Please relax.
Oh, no.
Oh, my.
Is your ear weak?
Oh.
You look like you feel good.
Oh, no.
I don't mean that.
Oh, you're right.
It's a little wet.
Oh.
Oh, a little.
What's the matter? Nothing.
Are you out of breath? A little.
Do you feel better? Thank you.
I want to do something.
Me too.
Please come here.
I'm going to put on make-up.
I'm going to moisturize your face.
I don't do that.
You have to moisturize your face.
Thank you.
How is it? Is it getting moist?
I'm going to put some lotion on you.
What's wrong? Nothing.
You look so comfortable.
Thank you.
I feel bad that you have to do this for me.
Do you want to moisturize your hands?
Do you want to have
a bath? It's important.
a bath? It's okay.
Please put your hand out.
It's good for you.
Do you want to have a bath?
I'll give you a bath.
Your hands are dry.
I have to put you to sleep.
I'm fine.
Do you feel good? I'm happy.
Hey, boss.
Have you been staring at their boobs?
That's not fair.
Look at mine.
Please look at my boobs.
Why did you look at my boobs?
Please look at my boobs, too.
Did you look at my boobs that much?
You like my boobs, don't you?
You always look at my boobs.
Please touch me.
Hatsune, please lick me a lot.
Do you like my licking?
Do you like it?
She is licking her belly.
Let's lick her belly.
Are you happy?
You are licking your belly very much.
You are so cute.
Please lick your belly, too.
What?
She is licking her belly.
You look like you're in a good mood.
I feel good.
What about me? Please lick me.
This is how you do it.
You're using your tongue very well.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you like the sound of my mouth?
I want you to lick this side, too.
What? I'm wet, too.
I'm wet, too.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Please turn around.
Are you sleepy?
I'm so sorry to hear that.
She is a little bit scared.
I'm so sorry.
You can't see
her, right? I can't.
You have to ask her directly.
I'll go to ask her directly.
I'll ask her directly.
Mom, I want you to turn around a little.
Where is it? Here.
Kuu-chan, how are you doing?
Are you sleeping well?
It's so hard just to lick it, isn't it?
Chai-chan, you are eating a lot of katsuo.
I want to eat more katsuo.
You like katsuo, don't you?
What?
What is it?
Do you like my butt?
Who likes your
butt? I can't choose.
Please touch it.
Touch it?
You don't know if you don't touch it.
You don't like it, do you?
I don't like it.
Let's watch it together.
I want to touch it.
Here?
I don't like it.
This is the best vacation ever.
You miss me too, don't you?
Can I pet you here? I'm sorry.
I'm out of strength.
Are you out of strength?
You are really cute.
What's wrong with you?
Do you feel good?
How are you doing?
How is your condition?
Is it getting worse?
You've been hit all the time.
I want to see it.
Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm not.
What are you going
to do if you hide it now?
What are you going to do?
Do you like such a cute butterfly?
Wow, it's so warm.
Tickle tickle
Is the temperature going to rise?
What is it?
Kacchan also licks it.
You can't bear it, can you?
It's the same for us.
It's a little... Is it no good?
What is it?
It's already rubbed.
Do you want some water?
If you put it in later...
Let's eat.
You put it in my bowl.
I have to tell you now.
Are you OK?
This is not good.
It's not good.
But you don't resist at all.
Our daily exercise is over.
You can move.
You can move, can't you?
This is not good.
What is not good?
Nothing is not good.
My neck is going to be cut off.
My...
Hey, Kacchan.
It's my turn next.
Kacchan, I told you many times.
Let's get along with each other.
So,
let's get along.
I have to take a bath.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
But it felt so good,
didn't it? It's so warm.
It's like a butterfly's nest.
It's so warm.
My hands got in.
Look at him. He's so cute.
He's become stiff again.
Please touch him.
I'm sorry.
Look at this.
Oh, no!
Don't do that!
I don't want to let it go.
It's going to go in again.
It went in!
I can see inside of your body.
You want to have a bath, don't you?
You are so happy.
Let me see your face.
Let me put you in the bath.
Can you put it in your mouth?
Does it feel good?
Can I have some too?
It's good, isn't it?
I've only had a little bit.
It's Mei-chan's turn.
Let's have a toast.
You were so good at having
sex, weren't you? No, I wasn't.
You were so cute.
You were big and hard.
You were the best.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I like you, too.
I like you the most.
You are so manly.
You are so cool.
You are a sweet potato.
Give me some power.
You are so red.
You are getting smaller and smaller.
I can't do it anymore.
What's wrong?
You are sweating a lot.
It feels good.
You still have a long way to go.
Let me see.
I'm going to sleep.
It's so sour.
I feel ticklish.
I'm still taking a nap.
It's just right.
I want to take a nap.
I'm still going to take a nap.
I think I'm going to cry.
I'm a romanticist.
I will put it on you.
You have a long neck.
I will give you a crampon.
A crampon is painful.
No, I don't think so.
Because it is hard here.
There is a crampon.
It's almost done.
Oh, wait.
Oh, great.
It's round.
I can't do it.
Oh, wait.
It's done.
What? No, no, no.
I can't see anything.
Did you light the
fire? No, I didn't.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
Let go of me.
You made me cry, too.
You cried.
I'm so happy.
Hey, Kacchou.
Do you have something to say?
Why?
I thought I was next.
It's OK.
I'm not alone.
The chief said that you are alone.
No, I'm not.
Amelie is still being pushed.
Chief, you are all friends.
You are all friends.
Chief, you feel good, don't you?
Chief, your waist moved.
Wow, it's moving!
It's moving! It's twitching.
What's wrong? Do you want to get out?
Let's move!
It's intense!
It feels good!
Kachou, you want to feel
better, don't you? Yes, I do.
You are too energetic.
I'm getting bigger and bigger.
How about your muscles?
What's wrong with
you? Hey, boss.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to go to bed.
You're amazing, boss.
What?
You're the best, boss.
Wait a minute.
You're amazing.
You're the best, boss.
I love bonito.
I love bonito, too.
Let's have more and more fun trip.
Wow! Let's eat.
Thank you for the meal.
It was a good reputation.
That's right.
Captain,
This was delicious.
That's right.
Look at this.
It's OK.
It was delicious.
It was good,
wasn't it? It's good.
Is it good? Thank you.
This is good, too.
It's good.
Are you all right? Thank you.
Is this good, too?
Let's eat together.
Oh, you kissed me.
I thought so, but all three
of us only ate the green one.
That's true.
I'll give you a sweet one.
Is it good? Eat a lot.
You are hesitating, aren't you?
No, no, I'm fine.
How about a drink?
I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
Then, I'll have you spill a lot.
Are you okay? No, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
It's painful.
I'll do it.
I'm fine.
You're drinking too much.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no.
I'm a man.
I don't want to practice hunting.
I'll do it.
Please, don't.
I can't drink it all.
You have to drink it all.
Oh, it's so bitter.
I'm sorry.
I can't drink it all.
Don't lick it.
You don't have to lick it.
What is this?
Why did you take
it? I got a cold.
I have a cold.
What are you
doing? It's slippery.
I'm going to catch a cold.
I've grown wet.
Well...
You're wet.
Hey, girls...
You must be hungry.
Are you ok? No, I'm not.
I'm hungry.
I'm getting sleepy.
I can't.
Oh, no!
I said, no!
Why?
Kuu-chan, look at this.
I took it.
No, no! I'll do it.
Oh, no!
You've never been licked
because you're hungry?
Don't you have anything to do?
No, I don't have anything to do.
Me too.
I want to lick the president's ring finger.
No, I don't.
You made it shiny.
What is it?
I want to lick the president's ring finger.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm so happy.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
Please show me your face.
No, I want to see your whole body.
I can't touch your face.
What are you talking
about? Why? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's been a long time since I've had a
baby, but I'm so happy to have a baby.
I'm so happy to have a baby,
but I'm so happy to have a baby.
Oh, my God!
Oh, it's intense.
I want to drink a cup of tea, too.
Oh, I'm dizzy.
Oh, it's great.
It's so soft.
You've grown up again, haven't you?
Is this your first meal?
I want to have a hamburger steak.
Do you want to eat?
You can eat in this state,
can't you? Good boy.
※Please be careful not to hurt the baby.
It's coming out.
No, no, no!
Get it out.
I'm sorry.
The president who is patient is cute.
Do you want to drink cacao?
I want to drink with three people,
so please buy me a cup of coffee.
Mocchan, you're sweating a lot.
Mocchan, you're starting
to smell like sweat.
I'm back.
I love the smell of the butterfly.
This is the first time
I've ever had a baby, so
I'm a little nervous, but
I'm going to do my best.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's short, isn't it?
Oh, my voice is coming out.
Are you all right?
I'm so sleepy.
I can't do it anymore.
Did you sleep well?
Is that so?
Kacchou, you are sleeping well.
I'm tired.
Are you nervous?
Your hair is messy.
Good night, Kacchou.
Wait!
Good morning, Kacchou.
Good morning!
It's not morning yet, it's night.
Hey, what?
We were so sleepy and
we couldn't sleep at all.
That's right.
It's only a little bit until morning.
Let's do something fun.
The butterfly is making
us dizzy, so don't move.
I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
Are you looking forward
to it? Hey, I'm here.
I'm here.
Omaha baby is crying.
The baby is crying because he is angry.
Oh, it's hot.
It doesn't feel good.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
What's wrong? Let's eat.
Oh, no.
I'm hungry.
It's hard.
I'll show you my back.
I'm tired.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Are you going to wake up?
What? I don't know.
Wow!
I can't stop crying.
I'm going to sleep.
It's normal now.
Wait a minute.
What's going on? Wait a minute.
It's normal now.
It's okay.
I can't do it.
Kacchan, I want you to sleep.
You are sleepy, aren't you?
You are moving again, aren't you?
My friend, I miss you.
I miss you.
Oh, it's cold.
I can't stand it anymore.
Show me your butt.
How far can you reach?
I'm going to cry.
I'm sorry.
She is a baby of the first age.
She was born in the year of the bear.
She is a baby of the second age.
Mom, don't do that. I'll stop you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't pull me.
I'm scared.
I'm shivering.
Let me help, to your back.
It feels so good!
Oh my gosh!
No, no, no!
No, no!
Oh my gosh!
The baby is crying.
I want to go out.
No, you can't.
Ah!
Hello!
..Ah!
Ah!
Hello!
Oh, Hello!
Ah!
Um!
It's the best!
Ah! Ah! It's hot.
It's hot.
It's 5 o'clock, isn't it?
It's 3 o'clock, isn't it?
It's 3 o'clock,
isn't it? It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's so hard.
Let's get out of here.
Are you OK?
I'm going to make a baby.
Chief, please give me a baby.
You are the most energetic, aren't you?
Let's take a bath.
Let's go home.
You've been crying all the time.
Let's go to bed.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Ah!
Thanks to the chief,
it was a really fun autograph session.
The chief was really cute.
Let's go to the 4th
anniversary concert again.
Fufu.