Let's take a look at the camera.
Can I ask you some questions?
Yes.
May I ask your name?
Yes, I'm Utaba Kremia.
What's your current job?
I'm a regular worker.
Are you going back to work today?
Yes, I'm going back to work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Are you married?
I'm not married, but I got engaged last month.
Oh, you got engaged. Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Who is your partner?
I'm in a relationship in the company, so I got engaged with my colleague.
How long have you been dating?
About two years.
I see.
Then you got engaged and got engaged.
This is a matter of consultation.
Yes.
Is it okay to have a cream?
You seem to be worried.
Yes.
Isn't it a bright type?
Yes. It's a dark side.
I see.
Is it a so-called dull?
That's right.
What kind of marriage partner is it?
It's about the same as the marriage contract.
I see.
Do you know that you were engaged?
Yes, I do.
Did you announce it?
Yes, I did.
I see.
Pamela, Cremia, congratulations on your engagement.
Thank you.
Congratulations!
Murase,
I'm going to ask you to go to the Cremia next week.
Thank you.
Please take good care of Primia.
Yes.
Keep up the good work.
I'm going to be the mayor of Sendai.
Just the two of you?
Yes.
The person in charge this time was Mr. Murase, right?
Is she your boss?
My name is Choshi.
What kind of person do you usually meet?
I'm usually kind.
I met Murase-san at the hotel in Chosaki.
We became a couple.
A couple in the same room?
Yes.
Just the two of you?
Yes, just the two of us.
You couldn't go back to the room?
We couldn't go back by hand.
Who told you that?
Murase-san.
So that's what you said, I see.
Were you okay with that?
I thought it couldn't be helped.
That's what I was doing at first.
Is it the same room as the boss's room?
Yeah, I think so.
I wonder if it's the same as the boss's room.
Look, the hotel is like a conter this time of the year.
You know, Tamura and I are getting married.
I don't have a ring, but I have a wife.
It's okay.
Nothing weird will happen, right?
Yeah.
Anyway, let's get ready for the next meeting.
Okay?
Yeah.
Nice to meet you.
This is a great project.
We're going to start this project next month.
Thank you.
I'd like to hand over the contract to Ms. Cremia.
Is that okay with you?
I understand.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, this way please.
Let's go.
Boss, the documents are ready.
Oh, thank you.
Are you going back to the hotel?
But before that, if you don't drink the tea that was served, it will be rude, so drink it all.
Yes.
Then let's go back to the hotel.
Yes, ma'am.
I don't remember much after returning from the meeting.
Where did you go from the meeting? The hotel?
I went back to the hotel.
You don't go to school on the way home?
I feel like I'm losing my strength on the way home.
Do you remember anything?
Yes.
I see.
What happened after you got back from the hotel?
After I got back from the hotel...
I realized I was naked.
Naked?
What do you mean?
I was raped.
I see.
It's hard to say, isn't it?
Yes.
Thank you for telling me.
Is your heart okay?
I'm fine.
Did you wake up in the middle of the night?
I woke up in the middle of the night.
How did you feel?
I was so sad.
Wow
Oh...
Hmm
It feels so good.
It feels like I'm in a dream.
This feels like a dream, doesn't it?
I love you
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Are you feeling good?
I'm sorry.
Please don't do this to me.
It's too late to hide it now.
What do you think?
It's all stretched out.
Stop it.
That feels good.
I said it in my dream, right?
Stop it.
Please don't do this to me.
No!
Feels good, huh?
Please stop.
Your hips are moving.
Why are your hips moving?
Please stop.
That's enough.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
No, no, no, no, no, no...
Is it good to give me a massage?
No, I don't feel like it.
Then why are you moving your hips?
Do you like this?
No, no, no...
Ouch!
It's so tight.
You're kidding me, aren't you?
I shouldn't have slept too much...
...
It was too early to clean up.
What are you doing?
I felt so good.
I'm sorry.
It was really good.
Please don't touch me.
It feels good.
What are you two doing?
What?
What did you do?
You're all wet.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
If you find out about this, you'll be in trouble tonight.
You'll be in trouble, right?
Shut up about this.
What about the engine?
You'll be in trouble, too.
You look like this.
Well, don't look so sad.
Have fun.
What?
I see. That's a bit too much.
Yes.
I'm sorry to say this, but this is a recording.
How was it?
I really didn't like it.
But even if I refused,
it continued.
Did you resist?
Yes, I resisted,
but I couldn't get any strength.
Maybe something strange
You may have been involved in it.
You don't remember, do you?
No, I don't.
That's a bit scary.
What did you do after it was over?
After I regained consciousness, I called my boyfriend.
You called him?
Yes.
Do you remember what you said on the phone?
Did you tell him?
No, of course not.
I see.
Yes.
So you broke up with Murase?
Yes, but he still threatened me.
That's all I could do.
Hello?
Yes.
I'm alone at the hotel right now.
I'll go back to Tokyo when I'm done tomorrow.
I'm lonely because I can't see you.
I'll make you dinner when I get home tomorrow.
Okay, then see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Oil, huh?
You can't do anything about it, can you?
Right?
If you find out about this, you're going to throw out your marriage contract, right?
If you find out about this, you're going to break the engagement, right?
Is that okay?
Why don't you say anything?
You don't want to say anything at all, do you?
Please tell me.
Did you feel that way earlier?
But you have such a nice body.
Mom...
Tell me.
Do you like this body?
I like it.
You're not satisfied, are you?
You're not interested in sex, are you?
You're a whore.
What do you think?
What?
What's wrong?
You're not interested in sex, are you?
Are you going to do it again?
I'm a strong man.
He's back.
What's wrong?
What?
I'm just having fun.
It doesn't matter what I've done.
No matter how many times you do it.
I got it.
Ok, it's time for your medicine.
What is it?
I told you it's time for your medicine.
I don't want it.
He is saying that he is going to be serious.
I will tell Tamura.
I was invited.
I was invited by Gunya.
I was invited and did it.
Let's open it.
What is this?
It's a medicine for your feelings.
I'm sorry.
What?
It's getting better.
Tr credibility
Didn't it feel better?
what about now?
I'm sorry.
It's getting better.
Do I have to do it again?
No.
I've done it once, twice, three times.
No, I don't want to.
I'm going to tell her that I was invited by Kurumiya.
Slowly, slowly...
Did you hear that?
Put your tongue out.
You look good.
Hey, did you really like it that much?
Put it in your hair.
What was that name again?
My head is hot.
Is it getting hot?
That's why I'm like this.
Why are you so nervous?
What are you doing??
Because of its sharpness
It is in combine
We don't have any chance
Give me!
OK
Where are you going?
I can't move.
Can't move?
You're going to take off your pants.
No, I don't want to.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
You're making me do something.
What's wrong?
Is it here?
No.
All of them?
It's all right, isn't it?
You're in a good mood, aren't you?
You can't, can you?
You're so excited.
It's obvious, isn't it?
You feel good?
What are you doing?
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Yonaru is amazing.
He's so cute.
Shun-chan.
It's okay
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Do you feel that way?
Are you crying?
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Do you feel it?
I don't feel it.
You're lying.
Why are you shivering?
I'm not shivering.
You're shivering.
Speak.
Don't be lazy.
Do you feel it?
Be careful.
I'm putting you under the bed.
I want you to sleep.
I'm scared.
You don't have to be scared.
You moved yourself.
What's the difference?
It's good
I like it
Are you okay?
Are you scared?
I'm sorry.
Go deeper.
Oh, I see.
Stop.
More.
It feels good.
What is this?
Help me.
Something's wrong with my body.
I'm not sure.
It's weird.
Is it weird?
Really?
Ah!
This?
Oh.......
You're Armenia
Did you go?
Why are you being told?
It's strange that my stomach is hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm sorry.
That's fine.
You'll get even more crazy.
Got it?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
You're really relaxed.
You're smiling.
Are you feeling good?
Feeling good?
Feeling good.
I see.
You're feeling good.
Why did you do that?
Because I saw you cry.
Can't you admit that you made that today?
But you can't say any more.
So, you think I'm better?
What?
You're trying to cry, aren't you?
Come on.
You're crying so much.
You're trying to cry, aren't you?
Come on, come on.
It's okay.
I'll take care of you.
I'm going to get you some medicine.
Open your mouth.
I can't do it anymore.
This is real sex.
Do you understand?
You can't say anything?
Hey.
It feels good.
It's already in there.
Don't cry.
I'm glad you didn't say you didn't want to.
I'm glad.
You've decided too much, haven't you?
I'm sorry.
You were treated for a second time at that time.
How was it in the second time?
To be honest, I didn't want to do it, but I felt like I had to do it.
I see. I'm sorry, it's a little hard to hear, but that means it felt good.
It's embarrassing, but yes.
Excuse me, do you usually have sex with your fiancé?
I did.
Do you think it's different than that?
Yes, it's the first time I've felt that way.
Did you end your relationship with Murase?
No, even in the middle of the night, his love didn't end.
It's not over yet?
Yes.
Hey, wash your body.
Hold your breath.
It's getting bigger and bigger, isn't it?
See?
Your arms are different when you use your boobs.
Relax, relax, relax.
Ah...
Chinako, your shoulders.
Yes.
You can see the shoulders, right?
Ah...
Do you want to put it on your cheekbone?
Put it on your cheekbone.
Put it on your lower jaw.
That's it.
It feels so good.
Put it on your cheekbone.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling good.
You don't have to be so nervous.
OK?
OK.
Good.
I'm sorry that my family is very sick.
I'm sorry that I didn't help you.
I'm sorry that I couldn't help you.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
Do you like it?
Are you okay?
Ah...
I just imagined it.
Are you okay?
Ah...
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
I want to go to sleep.
Use your hands.
No, no, no, no, no, no...
始めよう
怖い
You feel good, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Please turn on the lights.
I feel so good.
It feels good.
I feel like I'm going to die.
yam.
He starts to squirm around
G According to the
Yes.
I'm glad you were able to see Zanami's face.
I'm glad.
Did you put it on the table?
No, I didn't.
That's terrible.
And then?
It didn't end until morning.
I think he made me feel even more strange.
Even more?
Yes.
I was conscious that I shouldn't do it.
But my body didn't listen to me.
It's hard to hear.
Did you think about your fiancé during the process?
I didn't have time to think about him.
It's getting brighter outside.
Open your mouth.
Do you want it?
Oh, medicine.
You're getting better.
Do you feel good?
You don't need this, do you?
Shall we play again?
Put your hands in front of you.
Ah...
Chica, beep beep beep
Hey
What's wrong?
Chica, you're crying
Ah...
I'm going to stop.
Hey.
Yeah.
Open your eyes.
I'm going to play with you.
I'll play with you.
You haven't come in yet.
Are you looking forward to it?
Are you excited?
I'm sorry.
What?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Ah!
I'm going to die.
What's wrong with you?
It's okay, isn't it?
No, no, no.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You are not sick?
I'm fine.
How are you doing?
You are not sick?
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I don't want to do it.
I want you to do it more.
This is the place you really want me to do it.
It's been a long time, isn't it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What is this?
Ai-chan, ai-chan, ai-chan
More, more, more
It's going to be strange
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
It's so hot in here, isn't it?
I can't hear you at all.
It's not like that.
Karashima...
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You look sad.
Are you nervous?
I don't know unless you tell me.
I'm sorry.
You have a boyfriend?
I can't help it.
Are you making a phone call with your grandmother?
Do you feel good?
You're doing your best.
You're so beautiful.
Good boy.
You're doing great.
Oh, my God, I'm so tired.
Tofu feels good.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Please put it in.
Where is it?
It's in the corner of my eye.
It's not just a corner, is it?
Do you want it?
It's from behind.
Come here.
You have to come here.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It goes away so quickly.
You're doing it on your own, aren't you?
It just goes away when I put it in.
Okay, breathe.
No, Ichan!
Go, go, go!
I'm sorry.
You don't remember.
Don't move.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
You've been sleeping like a dog all this time.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Oh, it really hurts.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I'm so worried.
Can you hear me?
I can't do it anymore.
Go! Go! Go!
You're the only one who can do it.
Huh?
I'm fine.
Ugh...
Ouch.
Bad guy...
Then why are you 1,000 puedenst?
Ouch!
Help me!
More, more, more.
It's okay.
I'm not sure if it's because I'm not used to it, but I'm sure I can do it.
I thought I had done something wrong.
I have a fiance, but I've been threatened by Murase.
But I couldn't consult anyone, so I came here.
I see. You've done a terrible thing.
I appreciate it.
It's painful as an emotion.
Yes, it's hard.
Didn't you tell anyone about this?
No, I didn't.
Your fiancee?
Yes.
Your company?
No, I didn't.
Other than that, your family and friends?
No, I didn't tell anyone.
You can't tell anyone, right?
Yes.
So this is the first time I've heard about this?
Yes, this is the first time.
Well, if I tell you this, you'll be in trouble, won't you?
Of course.
You're a woman who won't turn a blind eye to anything.
I recorded this.
Yes.
Do you know what it means?
What?
You came here because you couldn't say no to anyone, right?
Yes.
If this goes on, you'll have to quit your job, right?
I'm in trouble.
You'll have to cancel your engagement, right?
Yes.
Do you know what it means?
What?
You still don't understand?
Women get hurt when they're kind.
Do you remember this?
Hey, Kurimiya-san.
Yes?
Let's drink this and go to Murase.