It was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It's been a while since we went
to the aquarium. How was it?
It's been a long time.
Don't you want to go to the zoo next time?
I want to go.
Let's go.
But you're going to be
an intern from tomorrow.
Are you looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Because I can meet Ryoji Yamada,
who I've always wanted to meet.
The world-famous Ryoji Yamada.
Yes.
I can finally meet him.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I see.
I feel like you're going
to be far away from me.
I'm not going to leave you.
Don't cheat on me.
I won't.
Really?
I won't cheat on you.
Well, I believe in that.
Yes.
You can trust me.
But you know what?
Yes.
The reason I wanted to be a designer
was because I saw your design.
Yes.
I can't believe I can work
for someone I respect.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm happy to see you, too.
Please support me.
I'll do my best.
Good luck.
Let's go on a lot of dates.
Yes, let's do that.
Do you think we'll be able to meet?
Yes, we will.
It's a promise.
This is a promise, too.
A pinky promise.
What if I lie?
It's our first time to
make a pinky promise.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
Yes, let's do our best.
Everyone, please look at me.
She is Meisa Kawakita, who is going to work
as an intern at our company for a week.
Say hello to her.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Meisa Kawakita.
I'm honored to work at your company.
I'll do my best, so please support me.
Ryoji Yamada.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
What?
Ryoji Yamada isn't here?
This is Ryoji Yamada.
Say hello to him.
Hello, I'm Ryoji Yamada.
I'm glad that you respect me.
What?
You look different from
what I saw in the magazine.
What?
I asked someone else to be my assistant.
I'm not interested in position and
reputation, so I don't want to be disturbed.
It affects my design.
I see.
You're very conscious.
Your seat is over there.
I've prepared your seat.
Why am I Ryoji Yamada?
Yamada was conscious, so we made him move.
He came here because he admires you.
Let him see you.
I see.
If you do that, you can do a lot of things.
Were you dead?
Do your best.
This is a sample of your design.
Have you ever seen such a tool?
Yes.
I've respected you for a long time.
Have you?
I'm glad to hear that.
I like your unique design.
My unique design?
I'm often told that.
You want me to teach you, don't you?
Yes.
It's different from what I imagined.
It's written there.
It's not what I imagined.
It's all imaginative.
It's a good idea, isn't it?
I came up with it.
Really?
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm here, so I don't care
about the atmosphere.
If the company is a little
dirty, it's my imagination.
It's my imagination.
Then, I'll make a park here.
Mr. Koizumi, do you have some time?
I don't have much time.
I got it.
I'll make it brighter.
I'd better use red here.
Here?
Contrast is important for design.
I see.
It's yellow here.
Here?
Yes.
I see.
I like it.
Really?
It's well done.
Thank you.
You have a good sense.
The gradation is good.
This one?
Yes.
I see.
I'll put it back.
I like it.
It's a good design.
Thank you.
It's well done.
I was particular about this part.
I see.
Mr. Koizumi.
You have a good sense.
Let me see.
I like it.
It's hard to get that color.
Really?
I'm glad.
No one can do this.
Thank you.
It's wonderful.
I like it.
I'll continue.
Okay.
I was taught by a designer whom I admire.
I've never been so happy.
I've never been like this.
You're doing great.
Thank you.
Can you bring me that one?
It's big.
It's great.
Really?
It's well done.
It's a good color.
I was particular about this hat.
Isn't it blue?
That's right.
I've changed the color.
It's good.
It's emerald green.
That's right.
I've unified this part.
Hello?
How was your first day of internship?
It was great.
It was the most fulfilling time in my life.
I'm glad to hear that.
Did you have fun?
Yes.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
I see.
Do your best.
Yes.
I'm glad to meet someone whom I admire.
He was a strange person.
Yes.
I'll finish it in five days.
Thank you.
I'll go out for a while.
Do your best.
It's great.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
Mr. Yamada.
Yes?
How was it?
No.
I don't want to talk to you.
What did you learn in college?
Hey.
It's not my hobby.
It's my job.
Do you understand?
What?
I can't believe it.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
You can't do it.
Don't tell me that you admire me.
I admire you.
I'm sorry.
Why did you make this?
You're exaggerating.
I just joined the company.
It doesn't matter.
I know.
Are you interested in designing companies?
Why did you make this?
It's a good label.
Do you like it?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to work.
You're too much.
I'm sure he's a good person.
He's a good person.
He's a good designer.
Do your best.
Okay?
Can I talk to you?
I have something to tell you.
Come with me.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I have something to tell you.
Okay.
You want to learn more
about design, don't you?
Yes.
Show me your motivation.
Motivation?
You admire me, don't you?
Yes.
I'll give you a lot of inspiration.
You want me to teach you, don't you?
I want you to teach me.
I'll teach you a lot of things.
You said you wanted to study design.
Don't do that.
You need this to get inspiration.
Akita.
Don't do that.
Relax.
You can't get inspiration by doing that.
I don't think so.
Why?
Don't do that.
You can't get inspiration by doing that.
No.
You said you wanted me
to teach you, didn't you?
This is strange.
This is an education.
Don't do that.
Relax.
Look at me.
I have a boyfriend.
You can't have a boyfriend.
You have to devote everything to art.
Does this have anything to do with art?
This is an education.
Don't do that.
Design starts with sex.
I'll teach you.
This is strange.
You said you wanted me
to teach you, didn't you?
You're wrong.
This is wrong.
I'll teach you the essence of design.
Look at me.
Yamada-San.
I'll teach you.
Don't do that.
Look at me.
This is wrong.
This is very beautiful.
This is very good.
Don't do that.
You can leave it to me.
This is strange.
I'm sorry.
Are you tired?
It's okay.
What's wrong?
This is how you do it.
You get inspired.
It's okay.
Don't do that.
You feel good, don't you?
This is strange.
Look at me.
What's wrong?
You feel good, don't you?
Don't do that.
Are you getting better?
I'm sorry.
You're getting better, aren't you?
This is the most important part.
You feel good, don't you?
Don't do that.
You're getting better.
What are you doing here?
Do you feel good here?
You get inspired.
You feel good here, don't you?
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
You feel good here, don't you?
You're getting better.
You like this place, don't you?
What's wrong?
Look at me.
I'm your imagination.
You have a misunderstanding, don't you?
Don't have a misunderstanding.
Don't do that.
I'll do it for you next time.
You admire this place, don't you?
You understand, don't you?
It hurts so much, doesn't it?
I'll do it for you.
Come here.
This is also an art house.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
Do you feel it?
Look at me.
Do what you want.
That's right.
You're getting better and better.
It feels good.
You understand art.
You understand art, don't you?
That's right.
If you lick a lot of gold bars,
you'll have a lot of imagination.
Lick it up.
That's right.
Do it harder.
You're getting better, don't you?
I'll do it for you.
Wait.
This is art.
This is the most important thing.
This is where art is born.
You understand, don't you?
This is art.
It's starting.
This is the best art.
You understand, don't you?
You understand what?
You're getting bigger and bigger.
I'll show you.
This is where it feels good.
What's wrong?
I don't want to do it anymore.
This is the most important thing.
You're getting better and better.
I don't want to do it anymore.
You're getting inspiration, aren't you?
Don't put it in here.
This is the best place.
This is the last one.
I'll give you this, too.
No, no, no.
Mr. Yamada, why?
This is education.
This is Ryoji Yamada.
Ryoji Yamada's real art is sex.
I thought I was fooled.
Change the design again.
It's about the material you ordered.
Is that so?
Two weeks later.
That's right.
If you do that, you'll be
able to meet the deadline.
I see.
I'll ask you again later.
Thank you.
It's been a week.
I'm going to cry.
What's wrong?
A client asked me to change the design.
That's what I'm talking about.
Really?
It's not just that we don't have time.
We don't have time.
I really don't know.
I heard that this is older.
That's right.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Mr. Yamada.
Please.
I've never seen this design before.
This color doesn't change at all.
Beautiful.
This is the best.
Everyone, look at this.
Take a look at this.
Did you draw this?
Look at this.
I've never seen this before.
How to use this color.
It's a good idea.
You can do this even though
you're an internship student?
That's amazing.
How did you come up with this?
This is similar to RYOJI Yamada.
I was conscious of it.
I see.
Can I give you the second RYOJI Yamada?
You have to be careful.
You can't lose.
That's amazing.
You can do this.
You can do this right away.
You look like you're alive.
You're alive.
That's amazing.
We can announce a new product.
This is a world-class product.
I'm sure of it.
I'm sure this will be popular this year.
You've created a new era.
That's good.
How do you feel?
I'm happy.
He's happy, so he's going to dance.
That's right.
This is RYOJI Yamada.
You can do this.
KAZUYA.
Yes.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
What is it?
I want to talk to you about the design.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
I had sex the other day,
so my design has improved.
AKITA.
I want you to talk to me.
Why?
It's necessary for design.
It's necessary to get inspiration.
I can't.
It doesn't matter.
There are many people who want to
be a designer because they admire me.
There are many people
who want to be a designer.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
It was your dream to join
this company, wasn't it?
Yes.
You understand, don't you?
Take this off.
Can't you do it?
You can't do it.
If you don't have
the attitude to devote
everything to art, you
can't stop being a designer.
Take this off.
You can do it, right?
That's right.
This too?
It's necessary for art.
Come on.
Show me your beautiful chest.
It's necessary for art.
You understand, don't you?
You want to be a top designer, don't you?
This is necessary.
It's a good bra.
It's a good design.
Why are you embarrassed?
You can't be a designer if
you don't be more active.
Yes.
You have a good taste.
It's a good design.
What's wrong?
This too?
Why are you embarrassed?
Can you stop being a short-tempered?
You can't be a top designer
if you don't be more active.
It's a good design.
Take this off.
Show me your nipples.
I'll introduce you to many people.
It's important to be
active in this industry.
You understand, don't you?
Yes.
There are many famous
designers in this city.
I'll introduce you to many people.
Show me your nipples.
You're hiding your nipples.
If you work hard, you
can be a top designer.
You want to be a top designer, don't you?
Everyone admires you.
I'm here.
Show me your nipples.
If you listen to me, I'll eat you.
What's wrong?
I'm here.
Don't do that.
I want to have sex.
Do you know Akezaki Aiba?
He's my apprentice.
All the girls I taught are top designers.
If you work hard, you
can be a top designer.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that.
You want to be a top designer, don't you?
It's enough.
What are you talking about?
Show me your nipples.
I can't.
If you work hard, you
can be a top designer.
I'll introduce you to many top designers.
Show me your nipples.
I don't want to.
Do you want me to introduce
you to many top designers?
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Are you a designer?
That's great. Thank you.
I'm really happy.
I worked really hard.
I'll introduce you to many top designers.
I'm a new employee.
That's right.
Thank you.
I'm really happy to get a job again.
Is the design old?
What are you talking about?
It's not old.
Are you doing well?
I want you to work hard.
I want you to work harder.
Do you understand me?
I feel good.
I want you to work harder.
I'll introduce you to many top designers.
You want a job as a designer, don't you?
Yes.
I'll evaluate you.
No.
You want a job as a designer, don't you?
I'll evaluate you.
That's a lot.
Do you feel good?
I'll evaluate you.
That's right.
That's good.
I'll evaluate you.
Do you feel good?
Don't take a break.
I'll suck you in.
That's good.
Do you feel good?
You can use your hands.
I'll get you out of here.
Yes.
Did your father teach you
the inspiration for Yamada?
Do you want me to tell you?
You came to my house for an internship.
I'll teach you a lot of things.
No.
I've been waiting for you.
I needed your help for
the inspiration for Yamada.
Help?
I'll help you.
You don't have to do this.
What are you doing?
I told you.
This is what you need.
That's right.
No.
This will give you a lot of colors.
This is the world of RYOJI Yamada.
Do you understand?
Your body is getting hotter.
RYOJI Yamada, I'll show you your world.
I'll show you your world.
This is the world that comes to mind.
Do you understand?
This is a design.
This is art.
This will give you a lot of ideas.
Do you understand?
That's right.
This will give you a lot of inspiration.
A new design will be decided.
This is art.
This will give you a lot of ideas.
This color is wonderful.
That's right.
This pink color is wonderful.
Let's look behind you.
Lean back.
That's right.
This will give you a lot of ideas.
This is beautiful.
That's right.
This is wonderful art.
This will give you a lot of ideas.
The next design is this round shape.
That's right.
This is important.
Can you follow me?
I'll show you the world of RYOJI.
This will give you a lot of ideas.
That's right.
Sound, color, and smell.
All of these come together to create art.
That's the world of RYOJI.
I'll show you.
This is colorful.
What does it mean?
This will give you a lot of ideas.
That's right.
You have a good voice.
By making that voice,
a new color will be born.
Sound, color, and harmony.
This is the world of RYOJI.
This is art.
That's right.
This will give you a lot of ideas.
This is art.
This is RYOJI.
This is blue.
This looks like blue.
Look at this.
What's going on now?
This looks like blue, doesn't it?
If you can't see it, you
don't understand art yet.
That's right.
This is art.
Here, too.
Look at this.
That's art.
There is art in this.
This is art.
What is this?
Take this off right now.
You don't need this.
You don't need this in art.
What you need in art is the way it is.
That's right.
That's the material.
The more you look at
what kind of material it
is, the more you will
be inspired by this state.
This is it.
That's right.
This will increase your sensitivity.
This is good.
Hold this.
That's right.
You can hold this.
Hold this.
That's right.
I'll show you how much you've grown.
This is Paris.
This is Japan.
And this is Japan.
In all countries, children are recognized.
You know that, right?
That's good.
That's right.
You've grown.
You haven't done it yet.
That's good.
What's wrong?
Please let me go.
I can't hear you.
If you want me to go, ask for more.
That's right.
You have to ask for it yourself.
That's good.
If this makes you feel good,
it's a proof that you're an artist.
You don't have to do it
yourself if you feel good.
That's right.
That's good.
You can't say that you're going.
Hold on.
That's right.
You have to change.
You have to be moved.
That's right.
You have to make art explode.
Let's make your art explode.
If you don't do it, you'll be moved.
Look back slowly.
That's right.
You can't say that you're going.
This forum is artistic, isn't it?
Isn't it?
That's right.
It's getting more and more artistic.
Let's make it explode more.
That's right.
It's getting more and more artistic.
Here?
That's right.
You have to change the
speed and depth of movement.
It's getting more and more artistic.
That's right.
Do you want more?
You can't say that you're going.
Look.
That's right.
Art is like an endless journey.
It's not over just because
you've been there once.
Do you understand?
Do you remember?
Art is something.
That's right.
It's not over yet.
You can't say that you're going.
Art is something beyond that.
That's right.
You can't say that you're going.
It's getting more and more artistic.
That's right.
Show your color.
You can't say that you're going.
It's beyond that.
That's right.
I think you got a new design.
I got a great inspiration.
It's all thanks to you.
That's right.
Thank you so much for today.
Hello?
I'm sorry I couldn't call you.
I've been busy with work lately.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Art is something.
That's right.
You can't say that you're going.
You're doing great.
That's right.
I'm doing great.
What's wrong?
Are you playing with your boyfriend?
That's right.
You've got a great inspiration.
You can't be a G4 designer.
Are you satisfied with
an ordinary designer?
That's right.
You can't be a G4 designer.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
That's right.
Kawakita worked at my company as an intern.
He left a great record.
I want you to work at my company.
Really?
In return, If you make everyone
here feel better, it's decided.
That's the condition.
What's wrong?
You admire Yamada, don't you?
What are you talking about?
This is what it's like to be in society.
That's right.
It's necessary to master art.
It's a must-have.
Please do your best.
That's right.
Let's get started.
There's another one up there.
That's right.
You have a great body.
It's artistic.
This hip line is amazing.
That's right.
It's artistic.
Your body is artistic.
I'm sure you'll be a first-class designer.
You have a great hip line.
You have a great body.
I want you to be
immersed in the world of art.
This is art.
You have a great hip line.
Mr. Kawakita.
That's right.
You have a great body.
You have a great hip line.
That's right.
That's not all you're good at.
You have a hidden talent.
Look.
This is great.
You have a great body.
That's right.
Raise your chest.
That's an artistic curve.
That's right.
That's great, Mr. Kawakita.
That's great.
Do whatever you want.
I'll take a look.
That's great.
You're so popular.
That's a great contrast.
That's great.
How does it taste today?
It's an artistic taste.
You haven't tasted it yet?
That's right.
I'll buy it for you.
That's great, Mr. Kawakita.
You have to show me a
lot of facial expressions.
That's great.
The sweat and tears of
art are falling from here.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
That's right.
That's great.
Look at me and sit down.
That's right.
Put your hands on your shoulders.
That's great.
You feel good, don't you?
Look at me.
Don't worry.
Don't cry.
That's great.
You're getting better.
Please bully me more.
Say more.
That's right.
I don't need this anymore.
Come on, I'll show you.
That's right.
What do you want me to do?
Look at me.
I'll show you.
I'll take this off, too.
That's right.
I'll show you everything beautifully.
I'll show you everything.
That's right.
You're beautiful.
You want me to bully you, don't you?
Please look at me more.
You want me to look at you, don't you?
That's a good reaction.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
When you feel good, you get a lot of ideas.
Don't you?
Don't cry.
Look at me.
You're beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
Your body is shining.
You're wonderful.
Look at me.
That's right.
You have a lot of ideas.
You're feeling better.
That's right.
You still have a lot of ideas.
I feel good.
Don't cry.
Look at me.
You're wonderful.
That's right.
When I look at you, I
want to look at your back.
You know what I mean, don't you?
That's right.
Stand up.
Put your hands here.
Lift your hips.
Can you see from below?
Can you see what's going on?
You're wonderful.
You're getting better and better.
You're getting better.
What's wrong with you?
You have to tell me clearly.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
Are you going to say this?
You haven't put your fingers in yet.
You're wonderful.
It's great to see you standing up.
Don't cry.
You haven't put your hands in yet.
If you can't stand up, ask me for help.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
What did you say?
This is good.
What's wrong with you?
Give me a kiss.
Do you want a kiss?
That's a good way to do it.
Give me a lot.
That's not enough.
There's a hand behind you.
Don't cry.
You're the best.
Let me rub your butt.
Slowly raise your butt.
Stick it out.
Stick it out more.
You're the best.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
I'll do it slowly.
Don't do that.
You're wonderful.
I'm licking you.
Stick it in here.
That's good.
That's good, isn't it?
There's a nasty sound
coming from over there.
How do you feel?
That's a good way to do it.
Let me see your face.
You're cold.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
I'll do it slowly.
This is my art.
You're excellent.
You can do it.
You're amazing.
This is my art.
You can't stop.
You're excellent.
I'll do it one more time.
You can do it.
This is my art.
I'll do it one more time.
You can do it.
Don't stop.
I'm sorry.
I'll look at you from below.
You feel good, don't you?
How do you feel?
That's good.
You feel good, don't you?
Let me see your back.
I feel good.
Please give me more.
You can do it.
That's a good voice.
I'll give you a lot more.
How do you feel?
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
Tell me you feel good.
Please give me more.
Can I tell you?
You feel good, don't you?
I'll do it.
You've had a lot of it.
If you want a pacifier, go to the pacifier.
Where is it?
Please give me a pacifier.
I'll make you feel better.
What are you doing?
You have to talk.
I want you to put it in the pacifier.
You put it in yourself, not the pacifier.
You can do it again.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good.
Can I give you a pacifier?
You feel good, don't you?
You put it in yourself, not the pacifier.
Your legs are moving.
I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
Your legs are moving.
The world of design is deep.
I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
You have to talk louder.
I'll give you a pacifier.
You feel good, don't you?
Your tongue is drooping.
You have to talk louder.
You feel good, don't you?
Your eyes are changing.
You're drooping.
You feel good, don't you?
I can't take it anymore.
You can't take it anymore, can you?
You can feel more.
You have to expose yourself more.
You have to expose yourself more, Kawakita.
The design is the same.
You feel good, don't you?
I'll put you in me.
Look at me.
You're drooping.
You feel good, don't you?
I can't take it anymore.
I'll put you in me.
I'll put you in me as a canvas.
This is art.
You're drooping.
How do you feel?
You feel good, don't you?
I'm sure you'll be the best.
I'll do my best at this company.
You're doing great.
You can do it.
That's the angle.
You're learning a lot.
You're doing great.
You're perfect.
You're a perfect canvas.
You're doing great.
Who is it?
Isn't it Kawakita?
Hello?
I'm at work.
Are you busy?
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
What?
I want to leave.
I'm sorry.
Please wait.
What's going on?
I don't know what's going on.
I'm sorry.
I feel great.
You're feeling great, aren't you?
You're doing great.
Please wait.
I can't wait.
It's decided.