This is the end of the last
month's Bon Odori report.
Since the number of participants
has increased since last year,
I am very happy as a mayor.
Next, Aoyama-san, please
read the accounting report.
Yes, I will read the accounting report.
I'm going to read the first
part of the letter to you.
High-heat bill for public buildings.
Execution fee.
Electricity 6,059 yen.
Gas.
3,260 yen.
I married my husband
and started living in this town.
It's been about three years.
Instead of my husband,
who was busy with work,
I was a member of the board of directors.
I used to be a warden.
I didn't really want to be a
warden because it was a hassle,
but I was asked to do it
because there were no
other people, and I
took it for a long time.
Well, now that we're
here, let's take a break.
That's right.
But, you know,
I found out after participating in the
board meeting that it costs a lot of money.
Well, it can't be helped.
The board doesn't take care of the details.
I see.
By the way, Mr. Aoyama,
Ms. Aoyama, have you got used to the
activities of the neighborhood association?
Yes, I have. I can't do anything, but
everyone is kind enough to teach me.
No, no. It is very helpful
for the neighborhood
association that Ms.
Aoyama has come.
She will handle the accounting properly.
Ms. Aoyama, do you have any qualifications?
Like a weapon?
Oh, well, it's just a second-class weapon.
Oh, that's amazing.
No, no, it's not that big of a deal.
Oh, Mr. Sugiura.
By the way, today is the
end of the month, isn't it?
What should I do?
The usual thing.
Oh, that's right.
It was the end of the month.
What's the matter?
I always have a drinking
party after the end of the month.
It's like a breather.
Oh, is it a drinking party?
Is that so?
Oh, that's right.
Ms. Aoyama, if you don't mind,
would you like to join
us after this? Oh, no, I.
..
I have some shopping to do.
Since we're here,
let's go for a ride once in a while.
Oh, of course,
we don't need money.
We'll pay for it.
I'd like you to have a drink
with me, even if it's just a little bit.
How about it?
Even if it's just one drink.
Well, just a little bit.
Well, Mr. Aoyama will join us today.
I'm not good at refusing, so
I decided to participate in a
drinking party with the members
of the neighborhood association.
Let's drink to the further development
of the neighborhood association!
Cheers!
Cheers! It's so good.
The alcohol after work is so special.
Yes, it is.
Aoyama-san, do you drink
alcohol often? Yes, I do.
My husband likes alcohol,
so I drink it sometimes.
I see.
But I envy your husband.
He can drink with such a beautiful wife.
No, it's not like that.
You're right, Chairman.
By the way, do you have any children?
No, I don't have any children yet.
Oh, I see.
If I were a beautiful wife like Aoyama-san,
I would do something like
making children every day.
Hey, hey, hey!
Ayame-san, that's a bad habit.
It's easy to drink.
No, no.
It's not good to drink at the table.
You said you could drink a
little, but you can drink a lot.
No, no.
Do you often drink like this?
Yes, at the end of the month.
At the end of the month, we always drink.
I see.
Let's drink together at
the end of the month.
Let's go together.
I want to go with you.
What do you like?
I like red wine the most.
I can drink anything.
How do you get
drunk? I don't know.
I am told that I don't change much.
I don't care.
You are strong.
It's a rare opportunity,
so let's have another toast.
Cheers!
Good, good, good.
It's a good drink.
Master, would you like a drink?
I haven't drunk it yet.
I'll treat you today.
I'm sorry.
But it's expensive,
isn't it? It's okay.
There is a deposit for that.
You don't have to worry about it.
Here you are.
One more time.
I can't drink anymore.
What?
Mr. Aoyama, you have a great style.
Did you do any sports?
No.
You have a great sense of fashion.
I want to do something about
my unyielding personality.
It's been a long time since I had a drink,
and I had a lot of fun, and I was drunk when I
noticed that I was drunk by the president of
the district who was good at making me drink.
But there was a problem.
I'm gonna win with 3-8.
3-7... I can't win with 3-8.
This weekend, I'm gonna win.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you win, please treat me.
Oh?
You fell asleep?
Aoyama-san, Aoyama-san.
What's up, Kaizo? I fell asleep.
What? Aoyama-san.
Aoyama-san, did you fall asleep?
The night is just beginning.
Aoyama-san, Aoyama-san.
Aoyama-san, I've been waiting for you.
Aoyama-san, please come in.
What's the matter?
He wants to go to the bathroom.
I've invited him to the bathroom.
Please let him in.
Have fun.
Aoyama-san, I'll take you to the bathroom.
Be careful.
Are you all right?
The bathroom is over there.
Are you all right, Aoyama-san?
I'll take you to the bathroom.
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
What are you doing? Don't worry.
I will release Aoyama-san.
Be quiet.
Don't do that.
It's okay. I'm going to release you.
Today, I'm going to show you
how to make a cute cat mask.
I'm going to show you how
to make a cute cat mask.
You are very wet, aren't you?
I'll take care of you.
Hey, Aoyama-san,
it's hard for you, isn't it?
Instead of your husband, you attend the
meeting of the neighborhood association.
But why are you so wet, Aoyama-san?
What are you doing?
Look, you are messy.
Maybe you have a lot of complaints.
Look.
I'll cool you down.
Aoyama-san
I'll make you feel good.
I can't.
I'm sorry, Mr. Chairman.
Don't worry.
I will heal you.
You have a nice butt.
I can't do it.
I'm so tired.
I'm going to die.
The movement of the waist is amazing.
Oh, it feels good.
I can feel the movement of my lower back.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Oh, it feels good.
I woke up from a drink and
was stunned to find that my
disordered self was covered
with a man's body fluid.
Cheers!
Cheers! It's delicious.
It's the best.
By the way, Kyo-chan, did
you watch soccer? Yes, I did.
That's great.
Yes, it is.
It's a big deal, isn't it?
Since then, drinking parties have
been held frequently in the district.
I should have known that
my husband was there,
but the sexual harassment of the district
chairmen has escalated more and more.
I wanted to reject it,
but when I drank alcohol,
I became sensitive and
my mind became pure white.
It's really fun today.
I've been in the
neighborhood for a long
time, but I'm happy to
drink with Ayama-san.
Hey, Sugino-san, what are you doing?
Where are you touching?
Are you touching anything?
No, I'm not touching anything.
It's just my imagination.
But you're touching it, Mr. Sugiyama.
It's not good.
It's a private bar, so it's okay.
I have to speak up.
And, Mr.
Aoyama, I like you very much.
No, you don't.
Please don't.
You were so hot the other day.
And you were shaking your hips.
I didn't do that.
I don't remember.
Don't lie to me.
I can't believe it.
She is so beautiful.
Mr. Sugiyama, it's terrible.
Did you have sex with Ms.
Aoyama? I had fun today, too.
Ms. Aoyama,
if you didn't, you wouldn't come
to the drinking party, would you?
You're already wet, aren't you?
Ms. Aoyama.
No, it can't be true.
You are going to sleep.
You have a lot of sleep today.
I can't sleep here.
If you make a sound, you will be eaten.
Let's enjoy today.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
You want to do it, don't
you? Let's have fun.
Are you okay? A little.
Are you okay? I'm fine.
Oh, my God.
I want you to laugh.
I'm nervous.
I'm fine.
What should I do if
you get angry? I'm fine.
If you don't make a sound,
no one will come, so be quiet.
Someone will come.
When you make a sound,
let's take this off.
If you take this off, you don't
want anyone to come, do you?
It's good, isn't it?
You are very wet.
You are easy to get wet.
You are wet.
Don't make a sound.
No, I'm not.
Are you sure?
Bye.
Please calm down.
What are you going to do?
You really want it, don't you?
Please put your hip here.
No, it's not good here.
Let's go.
It's in.
Nojima-san, you have to be quiet.
It's messy.
Drink some sake.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Nojima-san, how is it?
Let's have a lot of fun today.
Come on, get up here.
Come on, come on.
Your nipples are like this.
You like it, don't you?
You were shaking your
hips last time, weren't you?
It's OK to shake your hips.
Come here.
You don't have to be afraid.
It's OK, isn't it? Please go.
Nojima-san, it's not
fair to go ahead of me.
I'm sorry.
You want me, don't you?
Do you want me?
So, this is the process of making a shushi.
I don't think there is any particular
problem, but how about checking it out?
Yes, it is within the budget.
There is a reservation fee, but this fee is
the same as usual, so it's okay, isn't it?
Then, I would like
to tell you about this
in the interior of the
church, so thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Well, that's all for today's meeting.
Thank you for your hard work.
So, let's go to the usual bar after this.
Yes, let's go.
Aoyama-san, of course, you're going, right?
No, I'm going home.
I'm coming.
Can you go home? Aoyama-san.
Yes.
Are you going home already?
Aren't you going to the drinking party?
I was looking forward to it.
I can't go to the drinking party anymore.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I've heard a lot from the president.
I know you're doing something erotic.
What?
I'll keep it a secret from my husband,
so please keep it a secret from me, too.
In a place like this?
It's not good to do it here.
Just touch me with your hands.
Please.
It's me.
Are you gay? No, I'm not.
I'm fine, aren't I? Please.
Please stop.
What will you do if I come again?
I'll let you go right away.
Excuse me.
Do you know such a gay person?
I'm so excited because I'm gay.
It's wet.
I got it. I'll do it by hand.
Please don't.
Are you sure?
Is it OK? Someone will come.
Please wait a little longer.
Can I touch you directly?
I can't stand it.
It's just a little.
Thank you very much. I was very excited.
Would you like to have a mouth?
Someone will come.
Someone will come,
so if you do a little, it will
be over soon, so please
do it with your mouth.
It's just a little.
It's a prank.
You are very good.
Do you feel good?
I feel very good.
You are very good.
I'm nervous.
I'm going to make a lot of bread.
Bread is going to come out.
I'm sorry. Can I have my mouth out?
I'm afraid I'm going to spit it out.
An-san, please.
I couldn't refuse the invitation
from the neighborhood association.
I couldn't turn down the
invitation, so I went on a leisure trip.
It was good to come to the hot spring for a
night or two to express my daily gratitude,
but the old men were looking
at me with a round mind.
The hotel was facing me.
As soon as I arrived at the hotel,
the drinking party began again.
Cheers!
Mr. Aoyama, please try this.
It's a local delicacy.
The rice is delicious, too.
I want to come here often.
How is it? It's good.
That's good.
Aoyama-san, I heard it from Hiroo-san.
I heard you and Hiroo-san
did something erotic.
You seem to have done
a lot of things, don't you?
You are quite a person
who likes to do things.
Today, we came here to travel.
Let's have fun and get along with everyone.
You want to do it too,
don't you? Let's have fun.
Let's play the king game.
That's a good idea.
I can't see it.
But you know what it is, right?
Yes.
I'll let you draw first.
Okay.
Please hide the number.
You can draw as you like.
I'll start.
Let's do it with one hand.
Let's do it by hand.
Let's do this.
One, two, three.
Who is the king? Yes, it's me.
Why?
Why is it you?
Yay! I'm so happy.
What are you going to do?
I don't know what to do.
The number one person will kiss Osawa.
Number one, number three.
Number two.
I'm glad it's number three.
Number one.
Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss,
kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss... What? No? Oh, no.
..
What does the king say?
Absolutely!
Well, you're number one.
So, look, you'll be okay.
How many seconds?
How many seconds? I'm the king.
How about 10 seconds?
10 seconds is fine.
What does the king
say? Absolutely.
Please.
Look at Hiroo's eyes.
Look, what does the
king say? Absolutely.
May I?
The king will kiss you.
How many seconds? Ten seconds.
Oh, I didn't count.
It didn't come out.
Let's do it again.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8 I don't know.
I'm a little dizzy.
I haven't taken a tube yet.
Let's do it next time.
Yeah!
Who is the king?
What should I do?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm excited.
No.1 is...
No.2 is...
a Chikubiname.
Oh...
So, first of all... So,
first of all, who is No.
1? It's me!
As expected of the president.
Actually... No, it's not.
So, who is the second person?
Well, let's do it like this.
Well, I'm going to be rude to you.
You don't like it?
Let's do it, everyone.
One, two...
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
If you like it, please give us a high
rating and subscribe to our channel!
Please measure properly.
Let's go.
What's wrong? Great.
You're doing something erotic.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll do it now.
Who is the king? It's me.
Who is it?
The third person will be on
top of the second person's face.
First of all, the second person.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, then, the number
3 will be lying on the bed.
Number 3, huh? Well, then.
You are number 3!
Well, then, who is number 3?
Oh, what's the
number? Ah, ah, ah.
It's 3, isn't it?
So, I'm going to ask
you to cross your legs.
I can't do it. I'm embarrassed.
The king's word
is... Absolutely!
So, I'm going to ask
you to cross your legs.
Come on, Aoyama-san.
You are so cute.
Thank you.
Stand up.
Is it like this?
Is it OK?
Like this, right?
OK.
Stand up again.
It's difficult.
Come on! Good girl.
Come on.
It's difficult.
I'll support you.
Is this okay?
Well, where are you licking?
I'm not licking.
I can't help it.
Do you count this,
too? Ten seconds.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
You are so cute.
King James is over.
It's dangerous.
Because I'm not doing anything.
You don't have enough alcohol.
I'll taste it.
Please don't.
I want some sake, too.
Here you are.
How does it
taste? It's delicious.
There's no need to be so polite.
This is how you do it.
Is this how you do it?
Yeah, like this.
I won't disturb you.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh, here it comes.
You're wearing a tea bag today.
Why are you wearing such a vulgar panties?
Do you want to fight?
Do you always wear such vulgar panties?
You have a lot of enemies.
I'm sorry.
I'll take it off.
You want to put it on?
No.
Thank you very much.
You too.
I'm going to take it off.
Wow!
When I open it again,
It's wet again,
isn't it? No, it's not.
No, it's not.
Let's have fun today.
Yes.
I'm glad I was able to take care of Ayumu.
Ayumu is a very gentle cat.
I'm glad you like it.
You like this kind of thing, don't you?
I wanted you to put it in your friend.
It's Chico.
Let's have fun together.
I'll lick you.
You are so naughty.
Spread your legs.
Slowly.
Good.
You have a good look.
Open your eyes and show me.
No, I don't.
I'm embarrassed.
It is the custom of the Chōnai-kai to
show each other embarrassing moments.
Let's deepen our friendship.
I can't get enough of it.
It would be great to drink
alcohol while looking at this manko.
I want to drink sake.
Then, let's make it Wakame sake.
Sounds good.
Then, lie down.
Put your legs like this.
Who will drink Wakame sake?
Of course, it's me.
It can't be helped.
I'm going to give you a treat.
Let's go.
Uri
Uri Ah Oh Ah
Ah
Oh
Oh Oh Oh Oh
You don't have to go.
I want to go.
Let's play together.
I don't know what to do.
I'd like you to pet him.
He's young.
He's saying it himself.
I'm glad.
It's nice.
It feels good.
Come here.
Yabe-san, look at me.
I feel good.
I'll put you on my lap.
It's OK.
I'm going to sit on your lap.
OK, I'm going to sit on your lap.
It's good.
You look very happy.
Mr. Oyama.
There are more over here.
Mr. Oyama, you are grumbling.
Mr. Oyama, you are quite a M size.
Do you like this kind of thing?
Oh, great!
The skin got dirty.
Wow, great!
The mouth is also nice.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Ah, I got it, Dr. Hamayama.
Please let me stick it in, Dr. Hamayama.
He cannot do anything but move his mouth.
Come on!
Yes, a little bit.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm going to sleep.
I have a master.
Of course, I'll keep it a
secret from my master.
Well, well, well.
You haven't had enough
sake yet, have you? That's right.
Do you want me to give you a drink?
Thanks for watching this video.
Please feel free to ask questions yourself.
I'll try to answer as many as possible.
Please enjoy this video.
You're getting more and
more erotic, aren't you?
What's wrong with you?
I can't do it anymore.
I've been telling you
for a long time, haven't I?
I can't help it.
Do you want to change it?
What are you going to do?
Is it okay?
For the time being, once with this.
Oh, it's in.
I've always wanted to do this.
Look.
His nipples are sticking out.
His nipples are flat.
It's good, isn't it?
Ayumu-san, look.
Raise your elbow.
Get up a little.
Yes, yes.
Raise your elbow.
It's connected.
Look.
You can see it well.
Good.
You can't do that.
Look.
It's in there, isn't it?
How is it?
You seem to be getting along well.
It's not so cold.
I can't hear you.
It's cold.
Oh, it's tight.
You can't forget me.
The baby who was having a hard time
with the floor is now becoming a mother.
The baby is now 10 years old.
I have a futon for you.
Let's use the futon.
Come here.
Are you okay?
I'm going to take a bath.
Are you ready?
You have a good face.
You look good in anything.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Can I sit on your lap?
Your back is moving a lot.
Ayano, are you getting
serious? It feels good.
How do you feel?
It's the first time I've
been with so many people.
I'm going to go crazy.
You don't have to go crazy.
You're going to go crazy when you're born.
Your cheeks are blue.
You have a nasty waist.
You are so quiet.
You feel so good.
You are so good.
Are you thirsty? Look.
We'd like you to measure the number of toes
in the hand while sitting or standing up.
urinating We'd like to measure the number
of toes in the hand while standing up.
I'm going to give him a sedative.
Once in a while, I give him a sedative.
I'm not upset anymore.
I'm not angry anymore.
I'm not mad anymore.
I'm sorry.
May I look at your belly?
You have a lot of belly fat.
I can't take it anymore.
It's too strong.
I'm going crazy.
I will put the video link
on the description section.
Please enjoy the video.
Oh, it's so gross.
Oh, it's so painful.
Oh, if you hit me so hard...
I'm going to kill you.
This is how I became a butterfly.
I have become a comforter for
the old men in the neighborhood.
Every time I go around the neighborhood,
I am used to the cleanliness of the staff.
But in fact, I am secretly enjoying it.
Thank you for watching!