Hey, Aya-san.
Yes? Here you are.
I was going to send it by video,
but let's use the computer today.
OK.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I drank too much.
You've been drinking a lot lately.
That's good.
It's called team building.
Everyone is participating,
so you can't refuse, can you?
I don't like that kind of thing.
Where are you going after a long time?
I have an appointment
with the team tomorrow.
Until the day off?
Until the day of the competition?
They want to unite to improve
the team's performance.
I'm going to take a shower.
OK.
What time will you
be back? I don't know.
I'll call you later.
I see.
See you.
Employee trip.
It looks fun.
Team building.
Hey, everyone, take your luggage.
Let's go!
Look!
There is a person who is working hard.
Isn't it too early? I'm sorry.
What?
Are you shooting? Yes, I am.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a shortage of meat in the store.
Do you want me to get you a car?
Do you want to drink?
No, I don't want to.
I'll pay you later.
Really? Excuse me.
How much do you want to drink?
I'll drink a lot.
Have fun.
How much do you want to drink?
I'll drink a lot.
Why? Let's have fun.
Let's have fun.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Do you have anything to say?
I want to get along with
everyone in the morning.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Are you OK?
I'll close the car.
It seems to catch fire.
Where is the fire extinguisher?
It's in somewhere, isn't it?
Do you want to take it out?
The girls are having fun.
Do you want to take a picture?
Can I take a picture of you?
Let's take a picture together.
Say cheese!
Let's take another one.
Cheese!
Do you want to take
a picture? Yes, please.
Please check it.
Thank you.
Are you sure? Yes, I am.
I only have a meat brush.
You can't grill it raw.
I have to grill it well.
There is only meat and sake.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to take a video.
Isn't it cute?
It's cute, isn't it?
Is it okay if I take a video there?
I want to go in there.
You don't have to wear a swimsuit.
You can take it off.
I can't take it off.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Don't get angry.
We came here to get along with you.
Wow, you are back.
I'll have a drink.
Do you? I'll get ready.
You can drink it.
You want to drink it,
don't you? No, it's clean.
Anything is fine.
Strong at first?
I'm going to drink with my senior.
There is a bad guy.
There is a bad guy who
is trying to hurt his senior.
Who is it?
Look, look, look.
There are two bad guys.
How do you feel? It's cold.
Hello.
Girls, let's take a group photo.
Cheese.
Shall we send this to
everyone later? Yes, please.
Let's take a lot of SNS.
You look blank.
Smile.
We were chosen by the team of
the new project, but first of all, we
thought that we should know
each other, so we proposed this trip.
Please think that it is
not just an employee trip.
Team building, teamwork
improvement, communication.
We came here with a plan.
It's melting.
I don't know if it's good
to eat it with a side dish.
It's good to eat it with a side dish.
Let's enjoy today.
The meat is just right.
It's delicious.
It's good.
I think it's good.
Let's eat.
What do you use
for meat? Tongue.
Which one?
How about meat
tongue? That's good.
We don't have enough meat.
Did you work?
I'm busy to take a commemorative video.
I don't have a nose, so
I'll take a picture of this.
If you're going to take a picture,
it's better to take a picture of a girl.
What do you want to do today? Fireworks?
If it doesn't rain, fireworks are good.
I want to go to the pool.
Did you all bring your swimsuits?
I saw it earlier.
I want to see it.
I told you!
To communicate with everyone,
you need to be naked, right?
No, I'm not naked.
Your swimsuit is almost naked, too.
You need to wear a swimsuit because
you're dating a man and a woman.
I see, I see.
If you say you're naked,
I don't know what to say to the company.
I'll be in trouble.
Wow, wow, wow.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Oh, it looks really good.
They're talking.
I'm taking a picture of
you while you're eating.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
There's nothing in the camera.
I'll take a picture of you.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
A girl is eating meat.
I'll bring more later.
I'll put it here.
It's a bit late, so let's go.
1, 2, I'll get you some chopsticks.
They are working hard.
I'll get you some garbage.
Garbage of the bag.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's OK.
Let's eat.
Wow, the meat is amazing.
Awesome.
Yuzuru is cool.
Cool.
It's big!
Please eat first.
It's good! It's rare.
Isn't it rare?
Isn't it rare in this thickness?
It's okay because it's beef.
I'll take a picture of you
eating, so please eat deliciously.
Please report.
Let's eat.
It's so fatty.
Look at this.
It's like Jojoen.
Isn't it good? It's good.
It's good? That's good.
Next report, please.
Let's eat.
It's full of meat juice.
We are going to have a bite.
Is it good? Yes, it is.
It's good.
Is it good?
What is it? I don't know.
Is it good? Yes, it is.
By the way, your face is on the video.
It's on the video.
I'll edit it later.
Thank you for the meal.
Do you have salt?
Do I have salt, too?
Don't you do it? Yes, I do.
Thank you for the meal.
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
That's good.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm not good at it.
Which one is my sake? It's good.
This one?
I don't know what it is.
I don't know what kind of sake it is.
I'm hungry.
You are eating together.
It's good.
It's a good atmosphere.
Yuzuru is a professional cook.
He can do anything.
I wish I had a boyfriend like him.
Are you aiming at Yuzuru?
Yuzuru-san, you are being targeted.
What are you going to do?
Are you being targeted?
You are being targeted.
Don't do that. It's embarrassing.
What are you talking about?
Don't talk about me in such an erotic way.
You are talking about
me in such an erotic way.
Our company doesn't
want such communication.
It's not good to be erotic.
This is an indoor building.
That's right.
Oh!
Welcome!
You look great!
Can I take a picture with you?
Can I? I don't mind.
First, can you take a pose like a model?
Do you want to go over there?
Let's take a picture.
You can ride on the top.
What?
What did you do?
Yes.
It's hot.
It looks good on you.
Irita-san, don't you take
off your clothes? I don't.
I'll take off my clothes.
You can do it.
You look like a model.
Let's take a picture together.
Wow! Awesome!
Look at the boys. They are awesome.
Take a picture.
Wow, amazing!
It's really beautiful, isn't it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's too fast.
Wow, it's getting excited.
It's coming because I called it.
It's coming because you called it.
Don't say it's my fault.
It's nice, but it's amazing!
It suits you very much, Irita-san.
I'm sorry, but how can I
take a picture like a gravure?
I don't know at all.
You have to take a pose.
Like this.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a thing.
Wow!
It's moving!
Can I ride it? Yes, you can.
Wow! Thank you.
Can you show me your back? Sure.
I'll take care of all three of you.
Thank you.
A little more, a little more.
OK, OK, OK.
OK, three of you...
OK, three of you, please turn around.
Me? Oh, OK, OK.
I didn't notice anything.
Oh, good, good.
Wait a minute.
It's like a competition.
Don't fall.
It's a video, so don't fall.
It's a pool, so don't fall.
Erita, I'm sorry.
I wasn't wrong.
Is it the other way around?
I feel like I can see half of my butt.
What should I do? I don't know.
I don't know, either.
I don't know.
Girls, check it out.
Don't you see half of your butt?
I really want to see it.
I have to check it out now.
Is it right?
There may be a tag in front.
I can see half of it.
I'm a little bit confused.
I'm sure that there is a half-butt.
What's wrong? Wait a minute.
I'm not sure.
What's wrong? I'm not sure.
Don't lie.
Take a photo and show me.
I'm not sure.
I'm telling the truth.
You are telling
the truth? Don't lie.
I'm not sure.
You should check it.
You should worry about it.
I'm a little worried if I don't
take a picture, but I'm a
little worried if the crack in
the butt is a bit of a good day.
I'll take a picture of this only.
It may be such a design.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Which one is this?
But it looks good on you.
That's all for Rita's swimsuit question.
Thank you very much.
I'll give you money later.
Money?
Is it paid?
I'm a delivery man.
There's a lot of meat.
Please eat it with meat and sake.
I want an uwagi.
What's wrong with the uwagi?
The boy took the uwagi.
There are many fish here.
Yes, yes, yes, come here.
Oh, you are good.
You are the leader.
It's delicious.
Let's eat.
What? He ran away.
Is the wine ok?
Do you think you can
steal the wine? No, I don't.
Do you want to open the wine?
I'll give it to you.
Thank you.
What do you want to drink?
Do you want to drink wine?
Actually, we were
selected as a project team.
Really?
Are you still going? Stop it.
It's annoying.
Your way of speaking.
Is there something in it?
We are going to drink this.
Is it a bug?
I don't drink this.
I get drunk easily.
This is the most beautiful color.
It's easy to get drunk.
Champagne is also good.
I can't mix it.
I was surprised.
I'll drink it.
It's delicious.
It goes well with meat.
Are you communicating properly?
It's a rare opportunity.
It's very delicious.
You can eat the meat.
It's well-done.
You can eat it.
I have chopsticks.
You don't eat it?
Do you want to
eat it? Thank you.
It's well-done.
I'm pretty drunk.
I'm easy to get drunk.
Thank you for the meal.
We're going to play a team building
game to improve our teamwork.
I think.
The first one is a Shiri-moji
that Yuzuru-kun suggested.
We, the ladies, will
write Shiri-moji in order.
Please cooperate.
Then, Mami-san, please.
Me?
Yes.
Oh!
I'm so excited!
You look so cool!
Can you express your feelings with
the characters you want to convey?
The theme is your
feelings you want to convey.
Feelings I want to convey?
Do you know that?
If there are so many
characters, it's a bit... I see.
Please come this way.
Please show your butts to everyone.
How many
characters? I'm curious.
I'm curious.
No hint?
It's a number of characters.
Can I start with how
many characters? Sure.
I'll start with 4 characters.
4 characters.
I want you to raise
your hand a little more.
I can't see it.
You have to convey it properly.
It's easy to read.
I can't communicate with you.
I'll do it.
1 Wait a minute.
First stroke,
2nd stroke,
3rd stroke,
4th stroke,
5th stroke,
6th stroke,
and the last one,
5-5
Yes!
I got it!
Yuzuru-san?
Can I guess? Yes, you can.
Fun?
Correct!
Oh!
Can I give a reward to
the person who got it right?
That's not good.
But is it okay?
Yes, yes, yes!
What do you want to do?
What are you doing?
Stand up! Stand up! I'm scared.
How do you feel?
Amazing!
How was it?
Thank you very much.
Next, which one do you choose?
Is it a style to give up from juniors?
You guys are watching?
Yes.
It's like a team building, but it's
like you're watching the seniors.
It's like a team work.
Oh, it's a team work.
It's like team building.
Oh, yeah.
Let's look at the ones in the upper part.
You can read it.
Okay.
You're so cute.
I'm so shy.
I want to do this.
Yeah, you're so cute.
Why are you all dead?
I'm wondering if it's now or now.
Is it the same? It's the same.
In four letters.
Is it fun?
No.
Here we go.
The first letter.
Oh, I got it.
Can I try flying? No? Oh, wait.
I got it.
I think I got it, too.
I'll start.
The third character.
1, 2, 3.
I made a mistake.
Something is wrong.
The third character.
I'm a magician, so I don't know anything.
I'll start.
1, 2, 3.
Oh, you found out.
I don't know anything.
I don't know.
The fourth character.
The first one was
YASASHI-SAN? No, it wasn't.
Was it close?
The first letter was shorter.
Yes, it was.
It was the feeling of the moment.
It was 4 letters.
And the last one was SA, right?
I think it was the 3rd
letter that started with C.
And the first one was...
It wasn't the 3rd letter.
It was the feeling of the moment.
The 3rd letter was
supposed to end with 2
strokes, but you tried to write
3 strokes, right? Oh, I see.
That's right.
The order was wrong.
I'm sorry, but I can't say that.
Can I ask you to do it again?
Is it possible?
If you can unite, anything is fine.
Let's measure the unity.
How many characters do you want?
The first character is...
1, 2, 3, 4.
Can I say it?
The fourth character is...
1, 2, 3, 4.
I think I got it.
Did you get it?
Are you sure? Yes, I am.
I think it's happiness.
Correct!
Congratulations!
I didn't know it was happiness.
Well, what should I give you as a reward?
Should I bite you with my shoulders?
Can I have a drink with Asa-kun?
I can't drink it all of a sudden.
It's okay.
Because Ten's voice is
coming out, that's all I can do.
Can I have a drink with Asa-kun?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, over there.
Oh, he wants you to drink it.
He wants me to drink it?
He wants you to drink it.
It's the same as before, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come over here.
Please do it where everyone can see you.
Okay, here I go.
Here I go.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
What, what, what?
What are you doing?
Take a picture with the fish.
I want to take a picture.
I can do it.
You can do it.
You did it.
Thank you.
Yoshi, you are very energetic.
You did it.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
I was just grilling meat.
Next is Irita.
I want to see it.
No, Irita is fine.
Why?
I don't want to see it.
I want to see the cute two of you.
No, I don't want to see it.
Even as a senior, I can't close my eyes.
And as a team, it's
a little... It's amazing.
It's been a while since I've seen it.
This is for the team.
Dai-chan is drunk, so
please leave him alone.
He likes beer.
He is drunk, so he may forget it.
But he is a junior, so he wants
to see his senior's coolness.
I want to see it.
Here you go, Aoya.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Are you going to take off
your clothes? Wait a minute.
I want to see your butt.
I want to see it.
I couldn't see it.
OK.
Take off your clothes.
What are you doing? It's OK.
It's just my imagination.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait.
Your swimsuit is in a big trouble.
First of all, your round eyes are amazing.
My eyes are fine.
We have the same eyes.
Don't think this is Sekohara.
Your lower teeth are spilling a lot.
Let's fix it.
Kohara, are you going to shave your head?
I'm not sure if I'm going to shave my
head, but I'm going to shave my head.
You're a strong senpai.
It's okay, it's okay.
Yuzuru Hanyu, do you have any topic?
It's hard to answer now.
You'll be embarrassed.
You'll want to go home.
Thank you very much.
Let's start with the first character.
This is embarrassing.
No, no, no.
I feel like I'm getting really excited.
Here we go.
Here's the second character.
Oh, I got it.
That's amazing.
I got it.
That was fast.
Ok, let's start with the 3rd character.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Ok, the 4th character.
Ok, I got it.
Can I just listen to it?
If I say it, I'll be scolded.
I think it's a little bit difficult.
Yes, you are a leader.
Oh, I got it right.
What's the meaning of Mimiuchi?
I'm so glad I got it right.
You are so good at guessing.
If no one else could get it right, I
would have thought it was a good answer.
I know the 4th character,
but I don't know at all.
Let's all say it out loud.
What do you think the 1st character is?
The 1st character?
I know the 4th character.
What's the 4th letter?
Can I say it?
Yes.
I.
Correct!
I got it!
What?
Like, I want to drink.
Correct!
Wow!
How did you get it?
You stumbled on the 1st letter.
Dai-chan, give me a reward.
Come on, give me a drink.
What is it?
Give me a drink.
Oh, it's a bottle.
It's a bottle.
It's amazing.
Isn't it too much?
Come on, come on.
Go forward, go forward.
It's okay.
I'm fine.
Yes, yes, yes.
Stand sideways so that
everyone can see you.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Ah.
Do you want to do it at
a distance? That's right.
In the air.
That's right.
It's easy to understand
that you're drinking.
Look up and drink a little more.
It's going into my throat.
It's going into your throat?
It's good!
Do you want more? Yes, yes, yes.
Give it to him.
You shouldn't eat it in a weird way.
That's true.
I'm surprised.
I'm full.
I'm hungry.
It's delicious, but I'm getting sick of it.
Let's give a round of applause to
the women who played the game.
Let's get started.
What was the name of
the game? I don't know.
What's that?
I'll do my best.
Right hand, green.
At first, it's like that.
I can't do it.
Why?
Why are you coming
this way? I'm coming.
Do you cross suddenly?
Yui-san, Yui-san.
What?
Did you bring something extra?
Again? You're so hot.
You're so hot.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
I'm going to go here.
Left foot, blue.
It's far.
I'm the leader.
Are you okay?
You can choose your right foot freely.
Right foot, wide.
Wide? Oh, free.
It's not up to the person who does it.
No, I can decide.
I see.
It's difficult.
Isn't it small?
No, it's not that big.
Left hand, green.
Well, this is...
Oh, it's crossed.
It's getting closer and closer.
It's getting closer.
Left foot, red.
Right hand, blue.
You went to a bad place.
Left hand.
Left hand, blue.
Oh, it's over.
Good.
Hey, wait, look at me.
No, no, no.
Right foot.
Right foot? Right foot.
It's OK.
Are you OK?
The right hand, green.
Oh, you are right-handed.
Wait a minute.
Oh, great.
It's difficult to put it in.
The direction of the
face is very important.
The face is... I'm
a little mistaken.
The left hand, yellow.
Left foot, yellow.
Left hand, green.
Wow!
Did you do it?
Did you do it,
Irita-san? I did it.
You are experienced,
right? My experience.
You are so good at it.
It's not my experience.
You are playing with me.
No, no, no.
Next, please.
You are great.
Your left leg is yellow.
You are fast.
Your fins are different.
Your right hand is red.
My right hand is red?
Can you do it?
The left foot is also red.
Wait a minute.
It's on your butt.
It's quite close.
Are you OK?
You didn't do it on purpose,
did you? No, I didn't.
The left hand is red.
There are three reds.
The open red.
The open red?
It's the furthest.
This is it.
Can you kick it? No, you can't.
The leader has put it there.
This is the best one.
This is... No, give it to me.
He is kind.
Left foot, green.
This one.
Wow!
You look so cool!
Right foot, blue.
This is tough.
This is impossible.
Girito, this is impossible.
Right foot, right foot.
Right foot, blue.
Don't look at me.
Where is your hand?
Let's finish this.
I'm getting old.
Left hand, blue.
Left hand, left hand.
You have to get in a good position first!
Oh, great!
Wait a minute!
Hey!
You're going that way.
Are you okay?
I'm okay!
You're going that way.
Are you going to let me touch you?
Then, should I put my
hand over here? Oh, no.
Oh, no.
This is important.
This is better.
Here we go.
Left foot, blue.
This time, blue.
Ito-san, you are so strict.
Oh, no. Wait a minute.
Don't give up.
I won't.
I'm sorry.
Out.
Sorry.
So, the winner of this game is Rina.
I thought I couldn't win.
It was a fierce battle.
That was intense.
I feel like I can get a reward.
Of course, you can get a reward.
Then, I'll start with the view.
Oh, the view?
Then, do you want to drink?
Do you want to drink?
Do you want to share?
What do you mean by sharing?
Kissing is good,
isn't it? That's right.
Come on, kiss me.
I don't care about that kind of thing.
It has nothing to do with me.
It's a game.
Both of you are pilots, aren't you?
Then, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
It's all right.
What are you talking
about? It's all right.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking
about? It's all right.
It's a game.
If you want to see
it, you can see it.
If you want to see it, you can see it.
You can see it.
Let's have a meeting.
A meeting?
Which one is better?
I'd like to see her laughing.
It depends on the situation.
If it goes well,
there's no contact.
She drops it.
That's interesting.
She drops it?
Like the one before.
It's up, so if it's too
far away, it won't go in.
Do you want to do it again?
The container has changed.
The container is just a mouth.
Wait a minute.
You can't drink it all.
I want to drink it.
You can't.
You can't drink it all.
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you satisfied with the
game master? Yes, I am.
It was so manly.
You look like a poisonous tree.
I felt like I was getting a heart attack.
I'll do it again.
You need a tissue.
Tissue?
Is it over? It's not.
Tissue.
It was so much fun.
We are drinking again.
We are getting drunk.
We were drinking a lot.
We were drinking too much.
We were saying we wanted to drink.
Do you want to change?
I was thinking about it.
It's beautiful.
It's really thin.
What's wrong?
Both of you have big boobs.
Do you envy me?
What are you doing?
I'm glad to hear that.
That's good.
Three of us.
What are you talking about?
Let's change our clothes.
It's really beautiful,
isn't it? I'm jealous.
If you say so, it's hard to take it off.
Why? Please show me.
Is there a picture of me in the back?
You're a little aggressive, aren't you?
Do you always wear that kind of underwear?
Do you always wear it with your husband?
Are you doing it? Yes, I am.
You are quite straightforward.
I don't remember being so straightforward.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I think men will be happy.
Why are you hiding
it? Please show it.
There are only girls.
I see.
It's a little embarrassing.
And there are only two of us.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm already wearing it.
Oh, I see.
It's a flower from the bottom.
It was soft.
I'm going to sleep.
No, no, no.
I like you!
I like you the most!
I'm a Noble when I sleep.
Me, too.
I'm a Noble, too.
We are the same.
You can sleep well.
Your nails are cute.
Thank you.
It's summer.
I'm wearing clothes that
everyone wants to wear.
We got on the plane.
It's so hot.
It's hard.
I have to drink.
I'm at home.
What are you talking about?
It is said that there
is a possibility that all
of them will be able
to get a job in the future
It's not funny.
It's funny.
I'm not sure if it's the same.
I think she's married.
I think it's important to have a
body touch and a good relationship.
You're right.
I'm not sure if it's the same.
I'm doing this.
I can't do this.
I really like that face.
From behind.
I'm sorry.
Hello? Oh, yeah.
I got it.
Yeah.
This video is a derivative work of the
Tohoku Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
The video was shot in
the early morning of the last
day of the Tohoku Prefecture
Tourism Promotion Agency.
It's cold.
I'm the only one who doesn't have hair.
It's fun.
It's cold.
Wait a minute.
It's a hammer.
What's this? It's a globe.
It's a squid.
It's cold.
It's warm.
Be careful, don't spill water on girls.
It's scary.
I'm getting used to this water temperature.
I think so, too.
It's fun.
I want to do this.
I want to do it, but I can't.
Do you support it?
Me?
Come here, girls.
Let's have fun.
It's cool, isn't it? Yes, it is.
But it feels good.
The coolness of the pool
and the balance are good.
Oh, it's been in the water for a while.
Oh, it's a fish.
It's a fish.
It was a good fish.
It looks like a jellyfish.
Oh, it's embarrassing.
Oh, it's hot.
I got it.
But I can't get down.
I couldn't get down well.
I'm the only one who can't get down.
This is the balance.
Wow!
Eat it!
Tsubasa!
Do you want to get off?
Maya, you can get off.
Can you get off?
Can you get off? I'll get off.
Don't get off the boat now.
That was a good one.
You can get off from the high place.
Do you want to go from this side?
Are you OK?
Oh, there's a small one.
Oh, it's fun.
It matches well with Europe.
That's great.
This is the biggest one.
You can throw it away.
I'm drunk.
I can't run away anymore.
I was attacked.
Everyone is teasing me.
It's so bright.
It's so fun.
The water is so clear that you
can't see the bottom of the sea.
Don't you take a bath?
I'll give you a shoulder massage.
What? Take a bath.
I can't.
I'll be in the video.
Don't worry. I have a ring.
What do you mean?
Your husband doesn't
worry, does he? Don't worry.
No, no, no.
Don't worry.
I haven't told you in detail.
What if you have told me?
What if I had seen it
yesterday? Well, that's.
..
It's just a coincidence.
I left it out yesterday.
That's an accident.
No, no.
I'm accepting it.
Why are you laughing?
So I don't think it's a good idea.
What? Because you drank alcohol yesterday?
Yes.
I see.
It was an accident.
An accident.
Maya, you drank alcohol.
Is that okay?
If you drank alcohol
and you became like that,
take some pictures with this.
No, you don't have to
send it to my husband.
Oh, it's hot!
It's the latest trend.
Oh, can you hit it?
Oh, leader!
Leader!
Compliance!
Compliance doesn't matter!
【Yukiyuki】I'm going
to get a slap in the face!
【Yukiyuki】Maya, I heard that yesterday
you and Lee did something good.
【Maya】What?
【Lee】I heard that.
【Maya】Why? Why did you do that?
【Maya】I want to check that.
【Maya】Why did you do that?
【Yuki】I don't care about that.
【Yuki】I don't know what happened.
【Maya】What?
【Maya】I don't know.
【Yuki】What?
【Yuki】I don't know.
We're having so much fun today.
We came here to play.
Really?
Why? Did you take
a selfie? Yes, we did.
Why did you take a selfie?
We came here to play.
Let's play with everyone.
It's long.
It's getting dark.
It's funny.
What?
What? What? We are.
..
It's OK.
What?
Do you want to do this?
It's good to be a part of
the team building, isn't it, Mr.
Iita? This is called
team building.
I don't know what it is.
I think it's necessary to do
this to build a strong team.
It's very soft.
It's team building.
Let me see.
Wow!
Cool!
Who? Who?
It's the leader of the group.
It's the same, isn't it?
Leader?
I'll try it, too.
He said, let's play with everyone,
and we just came to call him.
Yes, yes, yes.
What?
What's wrong?
What? Wait a minute.
I don't want to be seen by everyone.
You don't want to be seen
by everyone? No, I don't.
You don't want to
be seen by everyone?
I don't want to be seen by everyone.
It's a battle.
We have to be chased.
We are the leaders.
We are the team.
It's discrimination.
I'm being watched.
It's too far.
Isn't it?
It's a great distance.
You look comfortable,
don't you? We are a team.
It's a communication.
What is the purpose of this time?
To keep silent? It's good.
But it's bad to be seen by
everyone, so it's just a little moving.
It's a very beautiful sound.
You have a very good boobs.
You are enjoying, aren't you?
You should enjoy together.
You can have a good memory.
It's been a while since I was drowning in
the pool. Do you know that? Yes, I know.
That's right.
I feel like I'm drowning.
I'm drowning.
But you can move it by yourself.
No, I can't.
No, you can't.
Then, I got it.
Did you get it? Yes, I did.
Let's go to a different place later.
A different place?
Can we go to a different place?
Yes, let's go to a different place.
Oh, that's a good idea.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go.
Yes.
He said no.
Tamae seems to be in a good mood.
It's a team building.
It's good, isn't it? It's good.
It's raining,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
It's going to be exciting.
It's no good.
Is it really no good?
It's not no good, is it?
Your back is getting stiff.
I feel so bad.
Your eyes are getting bigger.
It's embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing.
You look so great.
You look so energetic.
What?
Wow.
Wait a minute.
And you are holding it normally.
That's right.
I don't hate it at all.
I want you to hold my hand.
Of course.
If I say I want you to hold my
hand, you will hold my hand.
If I say I want you to hold my hand
directly, you will hold my hand directly.
Oh, is that so?
If I ask you to hold my
hand, you won't listen to me.
You are mean.
I don't know what's going on.
Is it OK? Yes, it's OK.
It's a little painful.
Is it because of the
temperature? Yes, it is.
It feels good.
You touch me a lot, don't you?
Aren't you happy that I touch you so much?
Are you happy?
Are you acting? No, I'm not.
I'm not happy.
I want you to kiss here, too.
Good boy.
Can I give you a treat?
Open your mouth.
Oh, my god.
You are so cute!
You are so gentle.
I want you to pet me.
You are getting more and more fun.
I want to pet you.
Do you like me?
Then, please pet me.
You are petting me.
I want you to lick me more.
Are you OK?
You are so soft.
I can put my hand here.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no, no, no.
You have a very good face.
I want to take a picture of you.
Soko-kun is looking at me.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a thing.
It's so cute.
Have you ever done this?
No.
No? Really?
Let's start with this one.
Here comes another one.
What is it?
If you don't know what to do, use number 3.
It's a big deal.
Don't look at it at once.
Don't look at it at once?
Can you do it? Here it comes.
Is it hard?
There is an order.
That is very caring.
She is a little bit
smaller than the others.
She is looking this way.
She is petting her.
She is so good.
She is petting in the middle.
She is lonely.
She is crying.
I can pet her three times at the same time.
It's like a real horse.
I'd be happy if you could look at me.
It's a horse.
I'll do it.
Next.
Next, I will change
the position of the face.
He is scratching his face.
He has a very good face.
He is enjoying it.
Let's enjoy it.
Oh, this height is... Oh, I see.
This height means... I see.
What do you mean? I mean.
..
I want you to attack here.
Wow, it's so soft.
I'll get stung.
Does it feel good to be rubbed here?
Yes.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't
it? That's right.
Here?
Yes.
――What kind of sandwich
do you eat? ――No I don't.
――I mean sandwich….
――not sandwich, I also need it.
No, no, no.
I'm going to do that, too.
It feels good.
What do I do? It's right.
Wow.
Let me brush my teeth.
I'm going to look at your teeth.
He does everything I ask him to do.
I know.
It's embarrassing.
Ah, it feels good.
Is this right? Yes, it is.
It feels good.
It feels good?
He looks like he's in a good mood.
It's embarrassing.
But he's excited.
I can't wait to see it.
Misaki is also looking forward to it.
Oh, no.
Let's switch.
What? Let's switch.
I'm sorry.
Like this.
You are learning a lot.
You are so excited,
aren't you? I am.
You are so excited.
Oh, I feel something from behind.
I'm going to take a picture of
the back of the baby's head.
The buttocks are soft and comfortable.
The buttocks are good, too.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
It feels good.
I want to have a massage, too.
Me, too.
Yes, equally.
What's this? Look at this.
It's so cute.
It's a skin scrub.
It smells good.
It's nostalgic.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It's cute.
It feels good.
It's the best.
Let's do it together here.
What?
Together? Yes, together.
I'm sleepy.
I don't know.
I don't care.
I'm a little scared.
Then, please lick me four times.
Rino's mother Mikan
Rino's father Tama
Rino's mother Tama
Rino's mother Mikan
I'm going to get a IV drip.
It's a good thing it's out.
Are you okay? It's out.
It was so good that it's out.
What are you
doing? It's so good.
How did it taste?
It's okay, it's okay.
Can I leave it to you?
No, I want to take a break.
Why?
You look like you're in a good mood.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, that's crazy.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
This is very delicious.
This is also delicious.
Oh, no.
It's about to come out.
It's too delicious.
Oh, no.
Oh, it's coming out.
Did it come out?
It came out very well.
Open your mouth.
Oh, it fell off.
Was it that bad?
It was really bad.
Because you ate a lot of meat.
It was bad.
I was shocked.
Everyone said they felt good.
The dirty building was a success.
It's a secret.
Team building? Yeah.
What?
I think it's better to keep it a secret.
No, no, no, that's not what I mean.
I didn't say that.
Does it feel good to be rubbed?
Yes, it feels good.
It feels good.
What?
Why?
I don't know why.
Let's build a building.
Yes, let's build a building.
Let's continue.
Is it okay to sit
here? Yes, it's okay.
It's like a real fortune.
I'm not used to it yet.
You are not used to it?
Do you want a shower?
I feel like a little while ago.
Are you not dirty?
I'm not dirty at all.
I have never seen you so dirty.
I've never seen it.
You are amazing.
What is this pot?
I want you to kiss me.
This is the information of my teammates.
Profile is important.
H cup.
What? It's a secret.
I've never heard of H cup.
I'll kiss you.
Wonderful.
He is kissing.
What are you touching?
You want to touch him.
I wanted to kiss you again, but is it okay?
Can I kiss you directly?
Is it okay if I do it right away?
You seem to like chocolate.
You said you were happy to
be surrounded by chocolate.
I'm happy.
You said you were happy.
I'm happy to hear that.
Really?
Yes.
Tamae's mother, Riki, is
the oldest Riki in the world.
Masachi-san, you are so strong.
I know.
Wow, you are shaking.
Your face is so smooth.
I'm scared.
There is no dirty place.
Have you ever been
here? No, I haven't.
You haven't? I'm glad.
She has a very good face.
Why are you looking this way?
No, no, no!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
It's going to be exposed.
What are you doing?
I want you to be quiet.
I won't speak.
Let's do it again.
It's okay if you feel better.
A little more.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Oh, it's so hot.
I'm going.
She can't hold her voice at all.
I'm sorry.
I want you to feel better.
I want you to look at this side.
Look at this side.
It's so cute.
Yes, yes, yes.
I want you to eat something you like.
What do you like?
Can you see it well?
Yes.
Oh, that's why.
It's a secret.
Can I follow the face of Tsukino?
Yes.
Can you look this way?
Can you lick this?
Yes, look at me.
Use your tongue a lot.
It's taken well.
What should I do with
this video? He is talking.
He likes to be licked.
He is licking with his fingers.
He hasn't eaten yet.
He has to be licked properly.
He is licking with his fingers.
He is licking his body.
I'll do my best.
Do your best.
This is also a test for the team.
You can hear her voice.
You can bear it if you add more.
Your eyes are getting bigger and bigger.
This is it.
That's it.
He is the oldest son of our family.
He often goes to the bathroom.
He is so sleepy.
He doesn't get up.
He didn't notice it.
I wanted you to do it.
Let's do it comfortably.
Look at the camera.
Here?
Eiku!
Let's go!
Tama Zoo, Chimpanzee I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Can you do this? It's painful.
Can you do this?
Can you? It's painful.
She has not been
able to sleep at all.
She is a good girl.
How is her posture?
She seems to have woken up.
She is asleep.
Let's check her posture.
I'm glad you've been
sleeping with me all the time.
I'll have you open the door.
Let's get on the bed.
It's really good.
Look this way.
I'm sorry, I can't make a voice.
Riki, who is the oldest, is the
first child of Riki and Fubuki.
I'm sorry.
You have to do that.
You can't run away.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
Come here.
You have a good face.
I'm sorry.
Fujita-san, you had a good face.
I couldn't stand your voice at all.
I couldn't stand it.
It hurts.
Can I wash my
hands? Yes, please.
Let's wash your hands.
OK.
Are you OK? Are you clean?
It's not so bad.
It's clean now.
It's clean now, so I'd
like to clean it up, too.
I'd like to clean it up, too.
She listens to me very well.
She's looking at the camera over there.
It may still be on.
This video is a derivative work of the
Tohoku Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
Learn more about Japan
at https://en.visitjapan.
jp Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
You look fine.
I'm about to throw up.
I'm going to throw up.
Let me see.
Wow.
You threw up again.
I did.
You have a nice mouth.
I have to wash my hands.
My mouth is so empty.
I am sorry I am so full.
Was it not bad? It was bad.
It was bad.
No way.
What?
Hello?
Honey,
I'm going to be late today,
so eat dinner first.
What are you doing?
I'm doing team building.
I'm busy, so I'll hang up.
Team building?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm on the phone.
When I'm doing it, I do it like this.
It's difficult.
Is this a swimsuit?
It looks good on you.
I don't know if anyone can wear this.
What are you talking about?
What's in the back?
I want to see it.
What's in the
back? It's a string.
Yes, it's a string.
It's a string.
It's embarrassing.
It's a waste if you don't see it.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no He is looking at me.
You have a lot of pimples.
You have a lot of
pimples on this side, too.
It's amazing.
The baby's posture has changed.
Look at him.
Good boy.
He's so naughty.
How do you feel?
You have a good expression.
Are you enjoying?
It's wonderful.
Are you OK?
How do you feel?
Are you OK? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
She is crying.
Please let her cry a little more.
Come here.
Where do you want me to pat you? Here?
Here?
You can do it!
Can you hold her hip?
What?
What is it?
When did you get here?
What happened?
Hey, Prince!
I love you.
I'm going to go.
She ran away.
If you don't attack her a
little, she will attack you soon.
Good girl.
Which one do you like better?
Tell me which one you like better.
You have a good expression.
Are you okay?
Hi-chan Hi-chan
Hi-chan
The two of them are
getting used to each other.
You can't do it anymore, can you?
What? It's hard.
I want you to look at my face.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I want you to look at my face.
It's very hard.
Look at my face.
Do you see that it's getting harder?
Yes.
This is the second day of
the cat's treatment, and I start
the treatment with a cat that
has been cured of his anemia.
I also treat a cat that has
been diagnosed with anemia.
Is it cold?
Cameramen are so nice.
They work even though
we don't say anything.
It's so quiet.
Is it our turn?
I am so happy to hear that
you are having a good time.
I feel so good.
May I hug you?
I'm going to give him a lot of food.
I want you to feed him a lot.
It's okay.
It's not over yet.
Keep feeding him.
Raise your hips.
Don't lick him.
I'm going to touch the back of his neck.
He's in the back of his neck.
I'll look at the back of his neck.
I'm going to have a bath.
Oh, my god.
Oh, you're licking my nose.
Kurita, do you feel
good? Yes, I do.
You have a very good voice.
I couldn't do it earlier,
so I'm going to do it now.
I'm so excited.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Was it amazing? Yes, it was.
What was amazing?
My grandpa was amazing.
Was he? He was amazing.
Was he? Yes, he was.
How was he?
He was like this.
He was breathing.
I'm so sorry.
She's moving a lot.
She's moving too much.
I'm sorry.
The baby is crying.
This is the first time I've
seen this kind of video.
I was surprised to see this video.
It's been a long time since
I've seen a video like this.
I'm glad I'm not alone.
I'm sorry.
Feel it.
I'm going to put the baby to sleep.
I put the baby to sleep.
I want to put it on your back.
On my back?
Yes.
It's really rubbing.
It's good.
Are you okay?
Does it feel good?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
What?
Are you okay? I'm okay.
Can I sit down?
It might be a little dirty.
It may be a little painful,
but it's a little dangerous.
I tried it and it was really painful.
Oh, don't suck so much.
It was really good.
I'm going to go. I'm going to go.
I'm home.
Give it to me.
It's so soft.
It's moving.
Are you more satisfied than
your husband? Of course.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You didn't touch my bag, did you?
No.
I'm going to take a shower.
Okay.