Was that...
Was that a dream?
No, it's not a dream.
There's still a trace of a kiss.
At the convenience store where I work,
two wives work at a bar.
Their names are Ono and Mino.
I don't know why they work in a
convenience store like this, but they are
so beautiful that I wonder why they
work in a convenience store like this.
In the free time of
their part-time jobs, they
complain about their
family and their husbands.
In addition, they complain about the
night, even about their sexless problems.
While I was listening to
them, they invited me to a hotel.
That's right. As it is, I
was ignored all night by
my wife, who was not
satisfied with her desires.
When I remember that time,
I get a cramp in my crotch.
But it's common for two adults
to have a one-night stand like that.
I'm sure everything will be fine, and I'll
be back to my normal part-time job life.
Oh, it's Yuzuru-kun. Good morning.
Oh, Ono-san, Mina-san.
Good morning. Are you taking a break?
Yeah, just a little.
That's all.
There are no customers at this time.
Don't you want to sit down?
I think it's better to sit down.
We want to sit next to you.
What's wrong?
Did you forget?
Did you do it?
What?
Even though you did it so many times?
No, I remember everything.
That's right.
You don't forget, do you?
Last week's night was amazing, wasn't it?
I guess it's because you're young.
You can do as much as you want.
I was really surprised.
Actually, I was going to break
up in one night, but I can't.
We can't forget Yuzuru's sex.
That's why we were talking about it.
Let's see who can make
Yuzuru-kun feel better.
The winner will have the right to
free Yuzuru-kun on the next Sunday.
Right?
I haven't heard anything
about the right to be free.
Don't tell me you don't like it?
Do you hate me?
No, I don't hate you.
You should be more honest.
That's right.
Well, let's get started.
Are you nervous? No, I'm not.
You really want me to do it, don't you?
Do you want me to do it here?
You can do it anywhere.
No, I don't want to.
You should do it when you want to.
Why are you wearing clothes?
Because I have to go out soon.
Look, there is still a kiss mark.
There is also a kiss mark on this side.
You are so perverted.
I like it.
Do you want to wear
more? No, I'm fine.
Yuzuru-kun, you like nipples,
don't you? Wait a minute.
There is no one in the store
now, so I have to go back.
It's okay.
This is more important than the store.
Wait a minute.
Right?
Are you okay?
Let me touch you a little more.
Your body is honest.
You are trembling.
You are so sensitive.
Your nipples are so hard.
You are so sexy.
Let me put you on my lap.
This is a kiss mark on the
same place again, isn't it?
No, it doesn't disappear.
Let's put a lot on it.
It's a sign of our love.
It's a mark.
Do you want to lick it?
I felt better the other day, didn't I?
I felt better, didn't I?
Hey, tell me which one felt better.
I don't know.
It's not fair for you to kiss me.
It's not fair.
I've only kissed you a little.
I like kissing you more.
You're getting bigger.
I can tell by your panties.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
I think it's great that you are young.
You are so big.
I want to touch you.
You were doing it yesterday.
Give me a kiss.
Do you know Yuzuru-kun's
weakness? Your ears.
No.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
The baby is crying.
Please listen to me more.
You have a great neck.
You are cheating.
How long have you been doing this?
You're feeling it more
than last week, aren't you?
You've been thinking about
it all this time, haven't you?
You have a nice body.
Hey!
What?
I'm going out of the store.
You can't go out.
No, you can't.
This one is better than that one, isn't it?
I don't like it.
Be honest with your body.
I'm not used to it.
What is it?
Today, there are no customers yet.
I wonder how it will be.
Yuko, you are always cheating.
It's okay.
Let's take it off.
There is no one here.
Look, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
It's more amazing than last week, isn't it?
You don't have to be honest.
It's okay.
You are a good boy.
You have a good body.
It's good to be young.
Your tail is flat.
Let me see your butt.
Are you going to take it off?
Wow!
What is this?
You are trembling.
Your butt is cute, too.
Yuko, you should attack from the front.
I attack from behind.
What do you mean, from behind?
Kenta, don't move.
Wow, Kenta, you are so chubby.
What is it?
I want to touch you, too.
No, you can't.
I'm licking you.
Let's share.
I'll do it, so you lick me.
I love you.
It's good to be with you.
You're me, aren't you? I'm you.
Go to the back, Chinki.
Wait a minute.
Go to the back.
This is the first time
I've had a baby, so I'm
a little nervous, but
I'm sure it'll be okay.
Wow, it's getting bigger than last week.
That's not fair. I want to do it, too.
This tube is the best.
It's getting smaller.
I want to lick my buttocks, too.
Do you want me to change it for you?
Look behind you.
I want you to give it to me.
You are shy, aren't you?
This is the first time
I've had a baby, so I'm
a little nervous, but
I'm sure it'll be fine.
No, you can't.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
I can't get up.
What?
Are you okay? I can't get up.
Let's sit together.
You can't get up, can you?
You wanted to sleep, didn't you?
You love boobs, don't you?
Look!
Hey, don't you want to see this?
You love boobs, don't you?
You have boobs on your back, too.
You are happy to be pinched
by my boobs, aren't you?
You don't want to come off, do you?
Come off, please.
It's like a cute baby.
It's still small.
Let's add more.
Yes, let's add more.
You are always standing on your tiptoes.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
It's the first time I've
ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
What's wrong with you, Mizuru-kun?
You like my boobies, don't you?
That's not fair.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
You have a cute face.
You have a really cute face.
It's not our fault, isn't it?
Why are you getting
so hot? I'm sorry.
Mr. Kono, you are so easygoing.
I know.
Do you feel good? My nipples.
You like my left nipple, don't you?
This one, right?
The left side feels good, doesn't it?
It's a little ticklish.
Oh, it's delicious.
I'll give you a kiss.
Oh, your tongue is soft.
Oh, it's delicious.
It's the best.
Young Uchiyuko is the best.
You are so full of kisses.
I want to exchange with you.
No, you can't.
Why?
I want to exchange with you.
You are my husband.
I can't help it.
I'm sure my Pera feels better.
I feel better.
Right, Yuzu-kun?
It's been a long time
since I ate it, isn't it?
I was imagining that we would
do something like this again, so
I was imagining it all the
time, but it was fixed, wasn't it?
I don't know what to do with this baby.
I'll lick you, too.
How long are you going to lick me, Yuko?
This is my baby.
You've been licking me all the time.
It's not fair.
I'll lick you, too.
I prefer this one.
It's mine.
Give me Tamatama, too.
It's not fair.
Tamatama is full.
It's mine.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
You feel good to be stroked, don't you?
I feel better, don't I?
You can even be stroked on the back.
My soft tongue feels good, doesn't it?
Let me stroke it.
No, you can't.
Don't lick me from the side.
It's my turn.
I'm a good boy, aren't I?
It's definitely me, isn't it?
Look, it's long.
Yuzuru, you like my breasts, don't you?
What are you doing?
You went back home last time, didn't you?
How do you feel?
It's softer than Yuko, isn't it?
Do you feel better in the wind?
You have a lot of pimples.
It's okay. It's been 20 minutes.
Next is me.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You feel better than
everyone else, don't you?
I'll give you a lot of this.
It's my tip.
I won't let go of this tip.
Let's switch places.
You're in a good place now.
Look at me.
You like my breasts, don't you?
You did it before.
You feel good, don't you?
You like this one, don't you?
You are so cute.
Touch me more.
You are so sleepy.
You are so cute.
Your neck is so warm.
Come here.
You love me, don't
you? Come here.
You feel good,
don't you? My boobs.
You feel good, don't you?
Then, I'll pinch your boobs together.
Oh, you pinched my boobs.
How do you feel?
You feel good, don't you?
It's the best, isn't it?
It's harder than before.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
I can see that the temperature is going up.
But you like me so
much, don't you? Come on.
You had a fever the other day because
of this, didn't you? It's all right.
Get well soon.
It's hot, isn't it?
Your neck feels good,
doesn't it? It's so hot.
My nipples are too hard.
It's my boobs, isn't it?
Your neck feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, it's coming out.
You're a pervert.
Do you want to take it out?
Do you want to take it out as it is?
I can't help it.
Oh, there's a lot of it.
Oh, it's gone.
It's gone, isn't it?
You've got a lot of it.
I've got a lot of it.
My boobs felt good, didn't they?
You've got a lot of it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll give you some, too.
You'll give me some, won't you?
You're such a good boy.
Wow.
It's not fair.
Hey, get out of the way.
I'm trying to take it.
What are you doing?
Hey, everyone, go over there.
Do you really put it in here?
I'll put it in here.
It's not fair.
I'll put it in.
It's not fair to put it in before me.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's painful.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, you shouldn't look at her body.
Don't run away.
It's not fair.
I feel sick.
Do you feel good?
You shouldn't do like that.
You have a good feeling.
You are leaning on me.
You are so cute.
You are good.
I want to take care of you.
What are you doing?
I want to feel good, too.
You are so cute.
I'm sorry.
You really want to do it, don't you?
You like standing up, don't you?
It's not fair to men.
You really like to play,
don't you? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Help me! Help me!
It's not fair! It's not fair!
Oh, it feels good!
Do you really like to squeeze?
Help me! Help me!
Wow, you're
sweating! I'm shaking.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cry.
Oh, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Oh, I miss you, Chibuko.
I miss you, too.
I miss you so much.
You can't do that.
Oh, no! She is crying.
Oh, no!
Oh, I feel good.
Don't cry so much.
Oh, I love all of them.
Oh, there are a lot of them.
Oh, no!
〈Refrain〉 It's bad that you
don't keep your hands together.
It feels painful.
It's not good.
I want you to do it from the back.
No, you can't.
You looked very comfortable just now.
Hey, don't do that.
Ayako-san, you did a lot.
What's going on?
What are you
doing? It's not fair.
Look at this.
It's not fair.
There, there.
Come closer.
It's dangerous there.
Go, go, go.
Oh, my God.
I'm so tired.
What are we going
to do? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
This guy is the best, isn't he?
I can't stop laughing at him.
It feels so good.
Mito, you are so cute!
Oh, no!
She is panting a lot.
She is panting.
My Mako is comfortable, isn't she?
She is comfortable, isn't she?
Isn't she? I'm so happy.
You don't have to do it anymore.
Put it in my bowl.
No, you've been doing it for a long time.
It's been a long time
since you came last time.
I'm so happy.
Please put it in my bag.
You are so cute.
You don't look like me.
You are amazing!
I feel good when you are happy.
Oh, no, no, no!
Yenko, you are an old girl.
Yen-ko, can I put you
in the bed? No, you can't.
Oh, it feels good.
Let's go.
Can I move
around? Oh, it's hard.
I cried.
Oh, great.
I just came out.
What's this? Great.
You were very curious.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy that you said it's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Hey, what are you doing?
I want to do it twice.
It's amazing that you want
to do it twice in a short time.
You can do it, can't
you? No, I can't.
It's hard? It's still hard.
A little more.
I'm tired.
You can still do it.
The customer has come.
I wanted to do a little more.
I'm glad to hear that.
We'll do it again next time.
What? It's 1,959 yen.
I'll pay by credit card.
Thank you very much.
Yuzuru-kun,
the number of customers
has decreased, hasn't it? I see.
If you kiss me now, you won't be found out.
What? I can't.
I have a guest.
You won't be found out if you kiss me.
That's not the problem.
I really can't.
Welcome.
What were you doing?
I was doing nothing.
Don't lie.
You were kissing without me, weren't you?
That's not fair.
Kiss me, too.
What?
What? No, I'm not.
You're fine now.
What? You're fine.
I see.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, Izuru-kun.
What?
You have a pimple.
No, no, no.
You have a pimple while you are working.
Yes, you are right.
You are a pervert.
It's because of you two.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing?
Hey, let's check it out.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm lining up in a line.
You're lining up in a line?
You'll be fine if you turn around.
I'll teach you when you wake up.
Yuzuru is bad at playing the piano.
What?
He has to play the piano.
I know.
His pants might be torn.
You were expecting it, weren't you?
It's not like that.
Look at this.
Yuko-san is looking at it.
What is this? It's clean.
It's from the top of the teapot.
What should we do? We are working.
It's because of you two.
We can't do anything.
That's right.
What should we
do? Let's wash it.
That's the best, isn't it?
What? I can't hear you.
What's this? Calm down.
It's all right.
It's already like this. Look.
It's more flat than before.
Yuzuru-kun, it's embarrassing to
make such a big penis on the toilet.
Why?
What are you going
to do? It's painful.
It's painful, isn't it?
You're making such a big
penis while saying no, no, no.
I'll be found out.
I don't know.
What will you do if someone comes?
I don't know what to do.
You get excited when you do
something you shouldn't do, don't you?
Oh, it's a nipple.
You don't like it here,
do you? No, I don't.
You don't like it
here? No, I don't.
I'll do it for you later.
What should I do?
It's coming out.
You are sleeping in such a place.
You are so shy.
You are a pervert.
What are you doing?
What?
You don't have to do anything.
You are a pervert.
What?
You are sleeping in such a place.
You are a naughty girl.
I can see your nipples.
Don't worry. I won't make you wet.
It's embarrassing to see you
wet in the convenience store.
Don't make a sound.
You can't do that.
Everyone will find out.
The manager will be mad at you.
It was great.
I'm glad you like it.
This is my nipple.
I like it.
It's true. It's full.
You've eaten a lot today, haven't you?
I wonder if you'll be able to
get out of the convenience store.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
How much is the bag? That's all.
Okay.
That'll be 450 yen.
That's all.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It's not fair to do that alone.
Why are you licking it?
I should do it first.
You kissed me just a while
ago, so let me kiss you, too.
No.
It's not fair.
I don't know.
Come here.
Hey, no one is here now.
Hey, let's do it over there.
It's narrow here, so come this way.
This is more open, isn't it?
If someone comes, I'll tell you.
Don't take it away.
I'll lick it.
It's not fair.
You've been doing it all the time.
I'm not following you.
You're so cute.
You're like my little girl.
You have a lot of hair.
If you get a hair loss at this
place, the product will be sold out.
So you have to put up with it.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
Please clean up.
Yes, I will.
I don't want to be found out.
Really?
Otherwise, I'll be fired.
Yes.
Do you understand? It's so easy.
she is getting used to
be watched by humans.
she is sticking up her neck.
She really loves to be looked at by humans.
She is perverted to be looked at by humans.
How do you like being licked here?
You are a pervert.
You are harder than before.
You are so hard.
Your neck is so hard.
I'm waiting for you.
I'll give you a hand.
You look comfortable.
It's embarrassing.
Do you want me to give you a stronger hand?
I'll give you a lot.
How do you feel?
You feel good, don't you?
It's getting hard.
Wow, wow, wow.
I can't move.
Wow, it's hard.
It's very hard.
I'm sorry.
You are so serious.
Look at the other side.
Look.
That's good.
Don't worry about it.
I'm so sorry.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's too hot.
I'm so sleepy.
Do you want to sleep?
Wow! Wow! It's hot.
Wow! Look at this.
It's a mess.
Hey, what are you going to do? Are
you going to wipe it off? That's right.
Thank you for cleaning up.
Thank you, too.
Please make it clean.
Me, too.
Minocchi-san.
Yuzuru-kun.
We're finally alone.
No, we can't.
We have to go back to the store.
There is Yuko-san in
the store, so it's okay.
But...
It's a secret to Yuko-san.
What?
We're finally alone.
This is a place no one has seen.
Don't you think you can
do a lot of erotic things?
What?
Right?
You were not excited at
all, weren't you? Oh, well.
..
I couldn't calm down, either.
You can do it here, can't you?
I want more and more of Isuru-kun's dick.
Is it really okay?
So it's a secret to Yuko-san.
It's delicious.
Yuzuru-kun, you wanted to be with me
more than Yuko-san, didn't you? That's.
..
Tell me the truth.
I don't know...
You're an honest and good boy.
Oh, you really like this body.
Do you want to put a kiss
mark again? No, I don't.
It's good because no one is watching.
Touch my boobs.
I've always wanted to do this with you two.
I'm so happy, Isuru-kun.
You're reacting to me.
You love my breasts, don't you?
I'm so happy that you're being so active.
My body is shaking. I can't stand it.
It's amazing that you are young.
You are always big.
Now I can do this by myself.
I'm so happy.
I feel so good.
You can lock your
sensitive nipples by yourself.
It's the best.
It feels so good.
You can be more honest.
It's hot.
No one is watching you here.
Yes.
You're so swollen.
You're amazing, Izuru.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want a kiss from you, Izuru-kun.
You want it, don't you? Please.
Put it in my pussy.
Put it in here.
Can I?
I can't stand it anymore.
Look, if it's here, you
can do anything, right?
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
Can I put my foot in?
Yes.
I feel so good.
Oh, that's a nice hand.
Feels good.
Oh, that's amazing.
I can't breathe.
Why am I so good at licking a young man?
I was about to die.
I want it.
Oh, my jaw skin is disgusting!
I want to kill my jaw skin.
Let me kiss you.
It feels good.
I feel so good.
Oh, my God!
Your kiss is the best!
It feels so good!
Is it better than mine?
Oh, my God!
Give me more!
Make me feel better!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels great.
Oh, my God.
More, more, more.
Hey, what are you two doing?
What are you talking about?
Hey, what are you
doing in a place like this?
What are you talking about?
Yuko-san, you just kissed him.
Kissing and hedging are totally different.
Come on.
Stop it.
It's my turn now.
Go back to the store.
Yuko-san, it's your turn.
No, it's not.
You've done a lot already.
I can hear you.
Hurry up.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
You looked so round.
Did I?
Did you get jealous?
You looked so happy.
But I was told I wouldn't be found out.
That's not fair. I want to do it, too.
It's okay, right?
Which one do you like better?
It's me, isn't it? Let me see.
You are so obedient.
Let me see your tongue.
Oh, it's delicious.
You love my kiss,
don't you? Yes, I do.
You still want more, don't you?
I'll empty it for you.
You're so mean.
Wow! It's getting better and better.
Wow!
Oh, no! I can't do it here.
If you make a sound, it will be broken.
I know.
But I can't do it.
Be gentle.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my!
I can't stop shivering!
My back is about to bend!
Oh, no!
Oh, my!
It's so ticklish.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I can't do it.
Oh, it feels good.
Do it directly.
Did you do the same thing to Mr.
Suzume? Yes, I did.
Did you do this, too?
Yes.
It's not good to do such a terrible thing.
Since when did I become
so good at this? I can't do it.
Oh, no.
I'm going to sweat.
It feels so good.
I feel like my skin is going to break.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's so good.
I want you to do it one more time.
Oh, no!
I can't go any further.
Just a little bit more.
I'm going.
Ouch!
Oh, it's hard!
Oh, great!
I can see the shape of my grandpa.
It feels good!
Oh my god!
Yuzuru-kun, you are strong.
You are so strong.
Hold on.
Does it feel good?
Oh my god!
I love you!
My head is really comfortable.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
I feel so bad.
One more time.
Oh, I'm shaking.
I feel so bad.
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
Sex is the best.
I'm so happy.
Really?
Yes.
I feel so good.
I'm so happy.
Don't cry.
It's time for me to cry, too.
Yuko, go to the store.
OK?
OK.
Yuzuru-kun.
Yes?
Give me more blood.
OK.
I'm sorry.
You'll come back, won't you?
I couldn't wait any longer.
I'm going to disinfect your mouth.
Yes, please.
Please be careful.
It feels good.
It's more intense than before.
Give me a kiss.
Oh my god!
My hips are getting stiff.
Oh my god! It's OK.
I told her that I would
disinfect you every day.
It's OK.
I'm going to sleep.
Yes, yes.
I'm going to sleep, too.
Oh, no.
I'm sleepy.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! My arm hurts.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I'm scared.
It's scary.
Do as you like.
It's creepy.
Do more.
Really?
You can do more.
Are you okay? I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Yuka, it's not your fault.
It's not your fault.
Get away from me.
But I can't get away from you.
Which do you feel better?
I can't get away from you.
I feel better.
I'm better than you, aren't I?
Oh, it's coming off.
Hey, me too, me too, me too.
Hey, Yuko, don't worry.
It's just an order.
Hey, Suru-kun.
I'm better than you, aren't I?
I have to disinfect this tape.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's been a long time since
I've had a baby, so I'm a little
nervous, but I'm going to do
my best to take good care of her.
I'm going to do my best
to take good care of her.
I'm sorry.
I love you so much. Don't leave me alone.
I can see the house from here.
It's so warm.
I want to be with you, too.
I want to be with you.
I feel good.
Oh, my God.
I feel like I'm getting a pimple.
I'm getting a pimple on my clitoris.
I can't stand up straight.
It's so hot.
It's so comfortable to rub my body.
I feel so good when I rub my belly.
What did you do?
Why did you do such a bad thing?
You should have changed.
It's not fair.
I'm sorry.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
I feel like I'm going to puke, too.
Me, too.
Yuko-san, please put on a diaper.
I can't see anything.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, I feel like I'm going to fall.
Yoripi-kun, you have a lot of muscle.
You have a lot of muscle.
Ah, it feels so good.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my waist is moving.
Oh, I'm going to die.
I'm so scared.
Did you cry? Yes, I did.
You're the best.
I want to kiss you again.
I want to kiss you, too.
How long are you going to be like this?
I'm going to give you an antibiotic.
Open your mouth.
Here you are.
No, it's not good.
Then Ibis tentacle
tofu I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
I am happy to see you.
I'm so happy to see you.
Are you happy?
You're happy, aren't
you? You are happy.
I'll give you a candy.
You're so cute.
I'm going to burn your blood.
Your head is full of blood.
I can see your life and death.
I'm sweating a lot.
BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
BAM BAM BAM PARK It's so delicious!
Now my face will be puffy, right?
Yes, you will be puffed up.
And you look very good.
Yes, you look younger.
I'm going to make a lot of steamed rice.
I have a lot of eggs.
I don't want to be hungry.
I'm always hungry.
Do you want me to hold your boobies?
You are so naughty.
Then, I'll shake your boobies next to you.
It feels good to be held by your boobies.
You are so naughty.
You are going to leave soon.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to leave?
You feel good, don't you?
You are going to leave.
You are so soft.
It's amazing.
I've never seen anything like this.
There are so many.
How many times have
you done it today? It's scary.
It's amazing.
It's like a young warrior.
It's the best,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
Isuru-kun, you left again.
But it's not over yet, is it?
What?
I have plenty of time until my
husband comes back today.
Let's go to the hotel after this.
I'm glad you've become so honest
with me, even if it's just a part-time job.
You don't have to worry about me today.
I have an hour until my husband comes back.
Let's have fun together until then.
That's right.
Today, Yuzuru-kun can feel much better.
You can do whatever you like.
Oh, it's getting hard.
It's true.
I'm going to show you
how to take care of Chikkun.
Chikkun, you're amazing.
Chikkun, you're amazing, too.
You're so sensitive.
Kiss me, too, Yuzuru-kun.
Look at your nipple. It's so swollen.
Your left nipple feels better, doesn't it?
Do you want me to put it on your face?
What do you want to do?
Do you want to feel better?
Are you okay?
Are you okay? It's me.
Which nipple do you
feel good? I feel good.
You feel good.
It's a luxury.
Oh, Mie-chan, you've grown up so much.
You've always been pretty since
you were in the convenience store.
You're right.
You're such a good girl.
But you don't have to
put up with it anymore.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
I'm glad you said it feels good.
You've got a lot of hair on your neck.
Let's take care of your neck.
I'll put some on this side, too.
I'll take care of your neck.
Are you nervous?
You are in my way.
Do you want me to take it off?
I'm so happy to see you again.
I'm jealous. Me, too.
I'm so jealous.
I love this friend.
What's wrong? No, not yet.
Look, I'm going to tickle you a lot.
It tickles, doesn't
it? It's hot.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm going to sleep.
I want to sleep.
It's amazing.
How many times have you done it today?
How many times?
5th?
You've done it 5 times already.
It's amazing.
I've never done it so many times.
You're so sexy, Izuru.
But you can still do it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
We don't have enough food at all.
We still have a long way to go.
We still have a lot of time.
Come here.
You can still do it,
can't you? Still, still.
You can still do it, can't you?
You are so cute.
You are my friend.
You feel good, don't you?
Both of us feel good.
You finally become honest.
Oh, I'm going to brush your teeth.
Oh, your nipples.
You like this, don't
you? Yes, I do.
You have the best face I've ever seen.
Really? You have a cute face.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Rina.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Do you want me to give
you a massage? More.
Give me your whole body.
Wow, your neck is so soft.
I'm going to give you a
massage on your chin.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You have a very open face.
It feels good.
It's better to go to bed early, isn't it?
It's better to go to bed slowly.
I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
It's really good.
I'm glad to hear that.
You feel good, don't you?
Show me your face.
How do you feel? You two can play together.
It's great, isn't
it? I'm so hungry.
I'm so hungry.
Everything is delicious.
Don't be so grumpy.
It feels so good.
You are wearing such a cute dress.
You are so cute.
Mom, I want to lick your tongue.
What are you going to do?
You always lick my tongue.
I want to lick your tongue, too.
The first day I met
him, he was a little boy.
He was a little boy.
Wow, I'm so happy to see you.
Wow, I feel so good.
Your legs are so fluffy.
You're on fire.
It's uncomfortable, Ichigo.
No, no, no.
Go away!
Get out of my
way! You shouldn't.
You shouldn't.
I've never touched you.
No, you haven't.
You're not fair, Yuko-san.
She says she's lonely, too.
You're so nice.
I'm going to cry, too.
Yuzuru, my breasts feel good, don't they?
Feel it with your nipples.
I love you so much.
Let me give you a kiss.
I'm sorry to make you so quiet.
I'm going to rub your nipples.
My nipples are tingling.
I'm in pain.
Wow, you have a big boob.
It feels good.
It feels good to feel your boobs
with your whole body, doesn't it?
What do you want
to do next? Chin-chin.
You can see your bottom well.
Let's lick together.
You can do it, Ieko.
It's all round.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I'll touch your buttocks.
I'm so happy to see you.
I feel good even though I love you.
It's all a mess.
I can't play with other people.
That's right.
What should we do?
We are the only ones
who can't play with them.
I want to play, too.
Wow, it's in your mouth.
Are you okay,
Yuzuru-kun? I feel sick.
You feel sick and it's
going to be weird, isn't it?
Then, let's make it four times this time.
Four times? Come here.
I'm going to love you more and more.
I'm going to take care
of you, so lick my breast.
I'm going to sit on your lap.
That's nice.
It feels so good, Susume-san.
The other side, too.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's so hot!
Your skin is so hard.
Let me touch your skin.
You're right.
You are more energetic than before.
You are so energetic, Yuzuru-kun.
Let's do everything you want to do.
You are licking me, aren't you?
You can do it, it's all right.
I'll make you feel better.
Yuzu's tongue is dangerous.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Oh, it feels good.
How do you feel, Suzumi?
【Mari】Mari, you're a sweet girl.
【Mari】Wow, you're a masquerade.
【Mari】Oh, my god.
【Mari】You're a masquerade.
How do you feel? She's gone.
She's gone.
She's becoming very stiff.
She's becoming very
stiff while licking her.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm falling in love with you.
Chibu, I want you.
You've fallen in love with me, right?
Right? Yuko, you
want me, right? I do.
You want me, right?
Yes...
I feel so good.
You, Kumi, it feels so good, doesn't it?
It's the best!
I want to be a little more comfortable.
I want to touch you.
Look over there.
The place where we are touching.
It feels good.
Hey, put it in.
I can't do it.
Put it in.
Which one should
I put it in? It's me.
It's me, isn't it, Maki?
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Why isn't it me? I feel so good.
I want it, too.
I feel so good.
Don't cry.
Oh, no.
I feel so good.
It's my turn next, isn't it?
No, it's not my turn yet.
I'm going to do it.
I can't sleep.
I feel so good.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me!
Go, go, go!
Hey, you want to go back
home, right? No, I don't.
You don't, right?
It's time for me to go back.
You are greedy, Yuko-san.
I want to give it to you.
Look, Toshi-chan.
Do you feel good?
Wow, he is going, going, going.
He is going, going, going.
Wow.
It's my turn.
I can't stand it.
What's wrong with you?
Of course, I'm fine.
How long are you going to struggle?
I can finally sleep in peace.
I'll look after you.
No, look after me.
I feel so good.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
It's the best!
It's not enough yet.
I'm so happy to see you.
You are looking at me.
You look so comfortable.
Can you see me?
You two are looking at me.
You are so naughty.
You are so cute.
Let me see.
I feel so good.
You are the best.
Let me see.
Oh, no, I'm going to be late again.
I'm going to be late.
I'm so scared.
Oh, no, I'm going to be late again.
I'm going to be late again.
I want you to be late, too.
I understand. I'll be late.
You know, just like you did to Yuko.
What?
You did it to me, too.
Good boy.
You are a good boy, aren't you?
You are a good boy.
Look at me from behind.
Look at me.
You are so cute.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
Hey, hey, hey.
I was almost done.
I can't take it anymore.
You're so mean.
Are you still going to do it?
I want to be alone forever.
I can't have sex with my husband anymore.
I don't want to see your face.
Let me see your face.
It feels so good.
How do you feel?
I can see your pores.
It feels so good.
Did you feel good?
Oh, my God!
You are so cute!
You are as cute as Tsume-san.
Your back is so cute!
I'm so happy to see you.
Can I look at you? Yes, you can.
Oh, wow.
I'm so happy.
You are so cute.
Oh, wow.
It feels good.
When I was in the hospital, my
daughter's sister Kikki came to see me.
Kikki was the only child
in my family who was sick.
I'm sorry.
We've been spoiled by Yuzuru's grumbling.
Oh, no.
Are you going to
fall down? Oh, no.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Oh, no.
I'm going to fall down.
I'm going to slip and fall down.
I feel like I'm going
to have a heart attack.
This is the second-day
child of mom and dad.
Today is the first day of
the day when I get tired.
I was so into playing with Mom's
daughter, but I couldn't do it.
I am in a very good mood today!
I'm in a very good mood today!
What is it?
Do you want me to join you?
It's good!
It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels so good.
I can't get up.
Mom, I feel sick.
I feel dizzy.
Wait a minute.
Mom, I feel sick.
I feel dizzy.
Me, too.
I'm so happy to see you.
I want to be in the video, too.
Do you want to be in the video, too?
Are you satisfied with the video?
I'm not satisfied yet.
Do you want to be in the
video, too? It feels good.
It's great.
Are you all right?
You feel like you're at home.
I feel good.
I feel great.
I'm glad to hear that you're feeling well.
I feel really great.
I feel great.
I'm waiting for you.
My waist is moving.
Oh, no!
Ma-kun, you're blushing.
Oh, no! Let's go.
He's gone.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Why do you feel so bad?
We are watching you.
Can you see it?
My weak spot is here.
Let me stroke your back.
You are so naughty.
Oh dear, Oh dear,
Oh dear... Tell me...
Tell me...
Do you feel good?
You are drooling.
Do you feel good? Let's go.
Let's go.
Where did you learn such a technique?
I want to do it, too.
Oh, it feels good.
It's great to be in the bath.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Mom, I'm sorry.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Oh, it's great.
It's comfortable.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's terrible.
I feel great.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Oh, it's terrible.
I'm at my limit. I'm going to throw up.
Do you want to
throw up? Yes, I do.
It can't be helped.
I'm going to make you feel better.
I'm going to throw up.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! I'm so tired.
Oh, my God.
Hello, Suzuki.
You've had a lot of babies.
It's amazing that you're so young.
It's amazing how many times it comes out.
I don't know how many times it came out.
You're right.
Hey, do you want to try
how many times it comes out?
That sounds fun.
Wait a minute.
My husband said he would come back.
You don't have to worry about that.
But... Even if it's a
little late, it's okay.
We still want to be Yuzuru-kun.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to push you down.
Because, look.
Your nipples are getting hard again.
It's okay, isn't it? Look.
I can't help it.