Tanaka, come here.
Thank you.
Please sit down.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
Tanaka.
Yes.
You know, right?
Chief, even if you say you
know, I can't hide it anymore.
Why? If you do something,
the company won't find out.
Even if you say so, I already
have more than 20 million yen.
Tanaka.
Yes.
Who are you
talking to? I'm sorry.
I'm the one who made you a manager
and made you successful, right?
That's right, but it's difficult.
Listen up.
This time,
I need 5 million yen
for my cute young wife.
I'm counting on you until tomorrow.
Until tomorrow?
I'm not going to take it.
I'm counting on you.
That's not what I meant.
It's the company's money.
Even if you say that,
the money is mine.
I understand.
Please let this be the last time.
The last time?
If you give me the same amount
of money every month, I'll quit.
Money is.
..
impossible.
Or...
Can I make you satisfied with this?
What?
What are you talking
about? Tanaka-san.
Yes? What I like is.
..
Yes? Money.
And... Don't forget.
I'm the wife of the chief,
who has a great power.
That's it.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Momo.
I'm back.
Are you okay, chief? I'm fine.
Get me out of here.
Hey!
Oh, you're back early.
Chief, I've been drinking all day.
I'm drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I'm the chief.
You bring the money, so I
don't have to do anything.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to bed.
Bring me some water.
Wake me up when you're done.
Yes, Tanaka.
Hey, Tanaka.
Yes?
Where's the money?
What? I'm sorry.
I'm not ready yet.
Hurry up and bring it.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Tomorrow,
That person is not in Baroque,
Be sure to bring it.
Then go home early.
Sato.
What's up?
I can't do it anymore.
What? I'm fired.
What do you mean?
Do you know?
It's about the manager's pay.
Oh, that.
Yeah.
I can't do it anymore.
So, how much is it
this time? 5 million yen.
5 million yen? Yeah.
And my wife asked me to do it.
I can't help it anymore.
So you're giving up on it?
Clean-out? That's right.
I've prepared so much.
I can't do it anymore.
I have no choice but to be hungry.
Are you sure you don't need a manager?
It can't be helped.
I was promoted thanks to the manager.
I can't do it anymore.
Hey, Tanaka.
I have a good idea.
What's the matter? It's this.
What's this?
I'm going to make my wife drink this.
What's this powder? Is it okay?
It's a beauty serum.
Beauty serum?
What's beauty serum?
If you drink this, you'll feel better.
Are you sure it's okay?
If you drink this, you'll get erotic.
Are you sure it's
okay? It's okay.
It's a little erotic.
It's no problem compared to Oryo.
Is that so?
I'll make you drink this and pay you back.
Are you sure it's okay?
I'll find a way to make you drink it.
Oh.
When the day comes to
get married, I'll go with you.
Please contact me.
I got it.
I believe in you.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'll leave it to you.
Yeah.
That's right.
I'll leave it to you.
Yeah.
Yes.
Excuse me.
It's hot.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Please give it to me quickly.
Please wait a minute.
It was very hot today.
Please give me a cup of tea.
Is this okay?
How is it?
Please give it to me quickly.
Well, well, well.
Don't be in such a hurry.
I've got it ready.
Oh,
I don't have the 5 million
yen envelope I prepared.
What? Oh, right.
I put it in the post just now.
Why did you put it in the post?
Can you take a look at it?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I didn't see it in the post.
I'm sorry, Miss.
It was in the bag.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Is this okay?
By the way,
this tea tastes really weird.
What?
It's really bad.
What are you talking about?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Is it delicious?
A little more?
What is the effect?
Mrs.
Are you okay?
Hey, what is this?
It's a nice view, isn't it?
You did a good job.
Oh, Sato.
Hey, what are you guys
doing? Hey, let me go.
I'm your husband.
I work with Tanaka.
Do you think you can
get away with this? I know.
I'm going to arrest the
wife of the worst manager.
I'm going to do it now.
Don't make noise.
Don't touch me.
If you do this, you'll be fired.
I'm already fired.
By your worst husband.
But if I have this
video, you'll be targeted.
From other employees.
Don't touch me.
Nanaka, I'll talk to your chest.
Hey, Sato.
Stop it.
Don't touch me.
Hey, stop it.
Stop it.
What's wrong with
you? Hey, stop it.
Are you drunk? No, I'm not.
What?
Hey.
Honey, it's medicine.
What?
It's medicine for you.
What? Stop it.
You don't look well.
Stop it.
I made you drink it
because you didn't feel well.
Stop it.
Do you want me to stop?
You don't look like you don't like it.
No, I don't want to stop.
What's that voice?
Are you listening
to me? No, I'm not.
Don't touch me.
Let's see how much you're listening to me.
Stop it.
Don't touch me any more.
I can't leave you alone.
Stop it.
Please calm down.
I'll make you feel better.
Please stop.
You're wearing such a dirty thing.
Is this the reaction of a person
who really wants to quit? I can't do it.
Do you really want to quit?
I don't want to.
You're reacting a lot.
This is proof that it's working.
I feel weird.
I can't do it.
What's going on?
You're feeling better
because of the medicine.
No, I'm not.
I'll give you a lot of medicine.
Is this better?
If you feel so good,
What's wrong with you?
What's going on here?
Why can't I touch you?
Are you in a bad mood?
Your clothes are very wet.
Why?
Don't you hate it?
What's wrong with
you? You are so wet.
Can you hear this sound?
You are more nervous than before.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter with you?
You look a little sick.
Did you get sick?
You've never felt so good.
I've never seen a cat like this before.
I told you, didn't I?
Do you wear such an
erotic costume every day?
What are you doing?
I'm just touching your butt.
Why are you moving your body like that?
I don't feel good just by doing this.
Do you want me to lick you again?
Good morning, Su-yong.
You seem to be in a good mood.
What's wrong with you?
You don't resist at all.
You don't have enough strength.
You are going crazy.
Oh, you got loose.
You can run away.
You got loose.
You don't want to run away?
Do you want to continue?
What's wrong with you?
Do you want this? Come closer.
What's wrong?
Do you want this?
Aoi's owner says, Aoi has
a problem with her stomach,
and that's why she's
having a hard time eating.
I'm going to give her a medicine,
but I'm going to take care of
her, and I'm going to feed her.
I never thought I'd be able to do this.
Pfft.
Urgh.
You look more delicious.
Pfft.
Urgh.
Ah, ah.
Pfft.
Urgh.
You look so hungry.
Do you want to eat only your mouth?
You don't want to eat, do you?
Where do you want to eat?
It's good, isn't it?
It looks like it's going to go in a lot.
I want you to put it in.
I'm going to enter the cat room.
Are you okay?
You are not okay, aren't you?
You are doing something bad.
You are getting fatter
and fatter, aren't you?
I'll leave this video for you.
You are getting fatter
and fatter, aren't you?
Please feel it more.
You are getting fatter
and fatter, aren't you?
She is about to cry.
I think it's getting more
and more effective.
What are you going to do?
You don't know how you feel, do you?
You've gone completely crazy.
What's wrong with you?
Where did your first foot go?
Look, it's swollen.
You're doing such a terrible thing.
My son's going to sleep a little longer.
He's moving his body.
He's moving his body again.
You want to sleep comfortably, don't you?
This video is a video of
a baby who Just woke up.
I made a video of the
baby's bedding andarent.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and I've
never seen a cat like this
before, so I'm a little worried.
I'm worried about the cat's health.
Oh, it's so hot today.
What have you been
doing? It's so funny.
I am going to sleep.
Please forgive me.
Riki, I came here to see you.
Where do you want to sleep?
Do you want this?
Do you want to go to school?
I want to live a normal life.
I don't want to go to school.
You are a good actress.
Sato, you did a good job.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
This is the best.
I can't hold this.
Hayako.
What?
Hayako, come here.
I don't want to. I'm tired.
Hayako.
I brought a pencil case.
I brought it for you.
Is it good? Yes, it is.
Make yourself comfortable.
It's good.
Lick it.
There's a lot left.
It's soft.
It's good.
Can I touch your stomach?
My stomach hurts.
Does it hurt? I'm tired.
Does it hurt?
Put your hand in.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
Now you can put your hand in.
It's uncomfortable.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
I'm done!
Are you OK?
I'll give you more.
There you go.
How do you feel?
Can you break
an egg? Yes, I can.
Ugh...
Ah...
Ummm...
I want to sleep...
I want to fall asleep...
Ahhh...
Oh, that feeling...
You are very good at it.
Look this way.
You have a good smile.
The day before yesterday,
I had a hard time with him.
So I'm going to take a break from his hair.
At first, I thought that it would
be hard to get used to the hair.
But I was able to get used to it.
This?
It's good!
Do you know it's getting hard?
It's getting hard.
I want to eat it quickly.
You will be sucked in soon.
Oh, you are very ticklish.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Today, I will show you
how to make Tuna Katsu.
Tuna Katsu is a food made with
tuna, which is a low-carb food.
I will cut it in half with
a knife and cut it into 4.
Oh, it's hot.
Chinchin is getting hard.
Oh, it's dirty.
I'm sorry.
I want to go to bed.
You are talking with a surprised face.
Let's sleep.
The stomach is getting bigger.
That's great.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
It's been a long time since I've seen
I'm sleepy.
Do you like the pillow?
I like the pillow.
I want to sleep more.
Keep doing it.
My stomach is growling.
It's very hard.
Touch the ball.
The ball?
Yes.
Harder.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
I hope you get a lot of hair.
I think I can get a lot of hair.
Really?
Can I? Yes, you can.
I can get a lot of hair.
It's so hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
I think you'll forget how you look
when you get a hair transplant.
I'm going to take a shower.
I came here as I promised.
Please delete that video.
It's not that easy.
That video is a gift from Tanaka.
Tanaka did a good job.
But I feel sorry for him.
I was hanged and fired
by the head of the club.
We will avenge you by
following Mr. Tanaka's will.
Then you should blame him.
I have nothing to do with it.
You have.
You are the wife of the head of the club.
I think you have a lot of money.
I hate that kind of person, too.
I just want to be with him for money.
You have a good mind.
Then, let's get excited about
things that you don't like.
Let's get excited with such a thing.
Please drink it today.
Don't you want it?
You drank it yesterday,
didn't you? Drink it.
You want to fly, don't you?
You've been waiting for
a long time, haven't you?
Ochi-san
Let's wait until he comes to you.
Yes
Ochi-san
You've been on a little trip.
It's about time you let go of your eyes.
Yes
You are amazing.
By the way, this is very effective.
What do you want?
What will happen if the chief sees this?
Do you want so
much? I'm so sleepy.
You're so sleepy.
You can't concentrate.
I want to do it right now.
Please.
How about this? I'm so sleepy.
You're shivering.
What are you going to do?
You must be excited to hear the sound.
You are very sensitive.
It's still too early to make progress.
Hey, let's have more fun.
No.
Do you want to be more comfortable?
Please take it off.
Take it off and show me.
Hurry up.
Show me your disgusting body.
Show me your bra.
What's wrong
with you? I'm tired.
You have a bad body.
I can't stand it.
Look at this.
Do you like Chikurin that much?
Your neck is swollen.
I'll give you a stronger massage.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Did you feel it only on your nipples?
Hey.
Do you feel it only on your nipples?
Come here.
What will happen if I press here?
Where do you want me to press?
I want you to put it on my belly.
I don't know if you have a lot of hair.
Please put it on my belly.
Your belly.
Here.
It's so comfortable.
Please put it on my belly.
Did you put it on?
Please put it on.
You did a good job.
You are amazing.
I can't show you to the manager.
I can't show you to such a strong wife.
Do you want me to do it directly?
Mr.Oshiro,
Yes?
Please let me lie down directly.
I'll put you on the bed.
Okay?
You have to lie down firmly.
I can't move my hips.
I'm scared.
I'll put you on the bed.
It hurts.
You are too fat.
I'm sorry.
You're getting crazy.
You're crazy enough.
I can't show you to the manager.
I want you to be stronger.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
You are still in a coma.
It's wet, it's wet.
It's wet.
Do you want to get out?
I don't want to.
Honey, hang in there.
I want you to do it.
if come on
toward me come on
toward me
hold on If you don't want to
do it, you have to do it properly.
I want to go home.
I want to go home, but I want to go home.
Do you want to
feel good? I can't.
I'm hungry.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I thought I was a little bit nervous.
I was so scared that I
couldn't move my legs.
I'm so sorry.
I was so scared.
Oh, Oh, Oh!
You've had enough.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah, Ah, I am sorry.
Ah, Ah, Ah, Ah...
Ah...
Are you pushing yourself into the bed?
Yusuke is all over the bed.
Yusuke is playing with Goma.
Yusuke, you are another kind of
dog that doesn't care about Goma.
What will happen if Kuritori-san does this?
Please help me!
What? Do you want it?
Kuritori-san!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm getting more and more depressed.
You're getting more and more depressed.
Good morning.
Please help me.
Mom, I can't get out of the room.
I'm scared.
I can't get out of the room.
Open it and show it to me.
Give me everything.
Hurry up.
I want it.
Show it to me.
Hurry up.
Put it in.
You like this,
don't you? I can't.
I'm going to put you in a box.
I can't stand it anymore.
What the hell is
this guy? I'm so tired.
I'm so tired.
Hurry up.
I want you to hurry up.
Wife, how many times
have you been doing it?
What?
I want you to hurry up.
Do you want this
again? I want that.
You want to take more, don't you?
I want you to let me go.
Give me more.
You'll feel better.
What do you want?
I want to go to the bathroom.
To the bathroom?
I want to go to heaven.
Good morning.
It doesn't have to be in such a hurry.
I want to do a lot.
It's so pleasant.
I want to sleep more.
I'm sorry.
Oh...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I didn't be good to you.
I feel so good...
It feels so good.
My body feels so good.
Just by licking it.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
I want a tail.
I'm sorry.
I'm not done yet.
I want you to bully me more.
Then, you should do it quickly.
I'm not done yet.
Hurry up and put me in the car.
Please help me.
I can't get in the car.
My daughter is crying
because her face is hurt.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I'm sorry.
My husband and I have been living in this house for a long time
What's wrong? I want a bath.
You want a bath?
I'm sorry, I can't do it anymore.
I want a bath.
I want to breathe deeply.
I want you to sleep.
You grew up.
You are amazing.
I was able to get a good night's sleep.
I was able to sleep well.
I don't know why, but
she's not eating the food.
I'm sure she wants to eat it all.
I'm not sure if it's because
she's a little hungry.
I'm sure she's trying to
eat it, but she's not eating it.
You did a good job.
I want to go home ASAP.
There is a lot of Tsingtao.
The cat is exhausted from a long trip.
The cat is crying because
the owner broke the door.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll give you a little more.
I'm sorry.
Quickly please..
Please help me.
Please... Please
help me quickly.
I'll hit you with a stick.
Let me have a look at your left leg.
Please hurry.
Let me have a look.
It hurts so much.
I can't walk.
What's this?
Oh, my God!
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm so sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't get up.
The night of August 14th, 2020
I was worried about the
movement of the baby.
Mom!
Oh, you're drooling.
I feel sick.
You're drooling from your mouth.
I don't know what to do.
You're drooling.
I can't move.
I'm scared.
Ouch!
His leg is broken!
I can't swallow it.
not at all.
I can't.
I can't swallow.
Put more milt on the butt.
I can't.
You have to spread it.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to break it.
Can I break it?
More, more, more.
I can't do it.
No, I don't want to go.
Mokko, come here.
Come here.
Stand up.
Stand up and put your butt out.
I'll carry you, Chimpo.
I don't want to go.
This morning, my husband and I woke up.
The sleepiness of waking
up at night made us very hot.
Thank God it's
gone soon! I'm sorry.
I want you to do it more.
a family outpouring
lanzolas of sunshine rain
on their family to
rent tents and live in.
I know, but suddenly it didn't look good.
I want you to give me a lot of it.
Oh, it's painful.
It's still there.
I'm going to bed.
I think it's time for the
director to come home.
I'm going home.
Mom, I'm home.
I'm home.
Mom, are you coming?
Hey, what's with this
school? It's the worst.
What's wrong?
All your grudges are against me.
What?
You're going to be fired early tomorrow.
That's enough.
What are you doing? Break up.
You son of a bitch.