How was it?
It was good, wasn't it?
Himawari is that place, right?
Yes.
It's like a tent to the other side.
The place where the bandits live.
Borders are like that.
It's so scary.
At that time, I thought
that I was like a master.
Kii-chan, come in!
What happened?
What? What? What?
I was surprised.
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
What were you looking at?
Did you hear it? No, no, no.
Today is the day to win!
Congratulations!
What?
I don't think it's going to work.
It was amazing.
It was really good to play it four times.
Really?
Where do you
remember? It was amazing.
I think so, too.
I saw a lot of things.
I moved a little.
You usually sleep in a different place.
I want you to tell me that.
I want to see it.
Do you want to see it?
Let's go to the next one.
It's dangerous.
It's true.
It's amazing.
You can still go.
The golden egg is still big.
Is it big?
Yes.
I haven't eaten yet.
I know. You ate a lot and came
here today, didn't you? No way.
How much did you eat?
That's a lot, isn't it?
Then you'll get a gallbladder.
That's right.
Or is it just a daily
routine? Daily routine.
But it doesn't feel like it.
I want to play more.
Let's eat.
Hello.
Let me kiss you.
Hey, you're getting bigger.
Wow! That's amazing.
I just kissed you.
Wow, it's amazing!
It's the best!
It's so much fun!
The kisses are getting bigger and bigger.
It's true.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
The tip of the nose is so sharp.
It's getting brighter.
It's really getting brighter.
Wow.
Did you just touch
something? I did.
I did.
It's been a long time since I've had a meal like this, so I'm not sure if I'll be able to eat it all at once
I want to sleep a little longer.
Emotional Wow,
there are so many.
That's amazing.
Isn't that amazing?
I don't want to go here at all.
Wow, there are so many, no matter how many.
We've got such good bonds.
It's so good.
I'm so tired.
Do you want me to do it again?
You want me to do it, don't you?
Do you want me to
do it again? It hurts.
It hurts.
Yes.
I want to eat it.
I ate it.
Oh, no.
I'm so sleepy.
I want to eat more.
It's so hard.
What's going on? It's crazy.
It's really crazy.
It's true.
It feels good.
It's so hard.
!!
Oh, did you send me a text message?
It's really nice to live a life of a girl.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I'm living a life of a girl.
I think I'll fall.
Where are you going?
You guys are so erotic.
It's not good to look at it from here.
I know.
Are you still going to sleep?
Are you going to sleep?
I want to see how much you sleep.
Wow!
It's like a facial expression.
It's not a facial expression,
but it's quite painful.
That's right.
It's hard to understand facial expressions.
It's simple and easy to understand.
It's easy to understand.
Oh, it's really hard.
This is a muscle.
Wow!
It's a little hard.
It's hard.
Oh, my God!
Is this hair okay?
It's not good for your body.
You should take it out.
It's heavy, isn't it?
How heavy is it?
Look, it's fine.
It's going to come out.
Really?
Already? It's amazing.
Is it coming out?
What? Is it coming out?
It's coming out!
Why are you getting
embarrassed? I don't know.
It's coming out.
Wait, wait. It's still coming out.
Wow!
Isn't it great?
It's not that bad.
It's not that strong.
Isn't it great?
It smells like tea.
I think it's getting stronger.
Wow!
Why are you laughing?
It's really the best.
It's the best.
I heard it for the first time today.
Thank you for watching!