How do you feel? I was bullied.
Is it your first time to come here?
It's your first time.
Are you nervous? Don't bully me.
Do you drink alcohol?
Have you drunk?
I want you to bully me.
I'm so shy.
You are shy, aren't you?
Surprisingly, they are normal.
I'm normal, too.
Are you excited?
Do you want to kiss?
Let's have a lot of fun today.
What kind of things do
you like? You came again.
I'm so tired.
I'm fine.
I feel dizzy.
Can I take it out?
Can you open the white one?
Can you open it?
This is a serious situation.
Stretch your arms.
Yesterday? You did a lot.
I'm scared.
What does it feel like to have a dream?
That's what it feels like.
Does it feel good because it hurts?
It doesn't hurt, does
it? No, it doesn't.
It's funny, though.
How about this?
It's funny, isn't it?
I'm taking a lot today.
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
It's funny, isn't it?
Wait, wait, wait.
Kojo is a pervert,
isn't he? It hurts.
It hurts, doesn't it?
It's better to be touched.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
The baby's crying is so cute.
Let me know when you
want me to pet your boobies.
I don't like it.
You don't like it, do you?
You don't like it,
do you? I'm sorry.
I can see a lot.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
What should I do?
Please don't change.
That's right. I have no choice
but to change. I have to do my best.
Do I have to do my best?
Yes.
It's disgusting.
I wonder if I can touch it.
I'm going to do my best.
You are so kind.
I'm a pervert.
I got a key.
I'm going.
Oh, my!
Wow!
What is this? I can't do it.
Oh, my!
Great! It's so fast.
It's on the screen.
Hey, hey.
Are you recording already?
Isn't it fast? Hey, it's fast.
Hey, stop it.
I'm sorry.
I'm greedy.
It's very hard.
I want to sleep there, but I can't.
Can you sleep there?
She is sleeping.
She looks sleepy.
I'm scared.
I'm not good at this.
I can't do it.
Crying
Crying Crying Crying Crying I have to
go somewhere, but I can't go anywhere.
I love you.
I love you so much.
I'm so tired.
Do it from behind.
It's dangerous.
I'm so tired.
Did you do it again?
Did you take a
shower? Yes, I did.
Did you feel refreshed?
Yes.