It felt so good.
What?
It was so close.
Did you get wet? Yes, I did.
Where should I
go next? This way.
It's so good.
It looks fun.
I'm going to take a bath.
Wow!
It's so beautiful.
It's great.
It's great, isn't it?
It was really good.
What was good? The shower.
Really?
It was the best.
It was so refreshing.
No way! It was so soft.
But you were panting a lot.
You did it! It's good.
It's good? It's good.
What?
Maybe it's because it's a hammock,
so it's still a bit out of tune.
It's still out of tune?
Can you still do it?
You did it a lot earlier.
What?
Wow!
You did it!
You did it! It's good.
Yes.
Okay, here we go.
I'm not good at it.
Oh, no. I'm not good at it.
Are you a newbie?
Are you enjoying it?
Oh, well, it's going to be a lot better.
What? Wait a minute.
What? Did you just kiss me and
you're so excited? That's crazy.
You look like you're having a lot of fun.
I'm going to sleep.
What?
It's difficult to go back there.
Hello.
I'm here.
Hi.
What? You look too happy.
What are we doing here?
I heard you guys were doing great.
Yeah, we were.
How many times did you
release the album? Just once.
Just once?
But you guys were so good.
Yeah, I was so sleepy just a
while ago because I took a nap.
Chogito, what are you doing?
Why? I don't care.
What are you
doing? Don't do that.
Chikubi, do you like it?
Oh, something is coming.
What?
Oh, what?
Oh, a lot of people are here.
We're back.
Hi, Tomo.
What happened to you?
You look like a humanoid.
Wow, Ichikun is also very big.
I can't do it.
Show me your neck.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm weak to damage.
I feel good.
I'm sleepy.
I want to sleep a lot.
I want to play with Koichi.
I wonder if he is sleeping.
This is a video of a child
who was doing a handstand.
I'm sorry.
What? Can't you bear it?
I want to get angry soon.
It's fun, isn't it? Let's do it.
Wait a minute.
I thought I was going to die.
I'm going to touch your mouth.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
I'll touch your mouth.
Oh, it feels good.
Come on, kiss me.
Yes, it is.
Oh, you can touch the side.
No, I can't.
Oh, you can't.
What are you doing?
What are you
doing? Oh, you can't.
Oh, you can't.
I remember a lot.
This and this.
Do you like mine?
What are you doing?
What a mess! I feel so good.
You feel so good?
I feel so good.
I don't like her.
Let's have a break.
Let's go.
Come here.