I heard that today's guests are a
couple and three female friends.
I wonder what will happen.
There are not many places
where three people can massage.
That's right.
I just opened it, but I hope it goes well.
You guys enjoy it, too.
Come on, put more beauty in it.
Do you want more?
More?
You can put more, can't you?
If you put more, it
will be more fun, right?
I made a reservation.
Yes.
Would you like to have a meal?
Yes, I'm listening. Please wait a moment.
Here she comes.
Nice to meet you.
This place looks very expensive.
Is it okay?
But this is the place which
Ruka introduced to me.
It's totally fine.
Really?
I looked at the website,
and it seems like
the three of us will be
able to take the test.
It seems like we have to renew it.
I see.
It's new.
So, only the new ones
are beautiful? I think so.
Wow, but it's a high-class place.
I'm so excited.
It's been a long time since
we took the test, right?
How was it? No, no, no.
No, no, no.
You should sleep after you get home.
That's right.
Did we go on a trip the
other day? Yes, we did.
It was in Korea,
wasn't it? Yes, it was.
It was fun, wasn't
it? Yes, it was.
I want to go again.
The essay at that time was good, too.
Yes, it felt good.
Yes, it was fun.
I'm getting more and more excited.
Let's go together next time.
If we go together next
time, what will happen to me?
Let's go together again.
No, no. Don't you feel lonely?
You know I don't have
a boyfriend, don't you?
Why don't you make one?
What's that?
You're flirting there.
No, no, no.
I envy you.
You should give me this baby.
What's that? What do you mean?
No?
It's me, isn't it?
Really?
You're a little lost,
aren't you? I'm thinking.
You're thinking, aren't
you? Think about it.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I'll do it when I get home.
That's right.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's my second year as a member of society.
Even though it's in front of God, stop it.
Don't do that.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I don't know when customers will come.
Please don't do that.
Let's get rid of our tiredness
for the second year in a row.
Excuse me.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for coming today.
We will serve you.
This is a welcome drink herb tea.
Thank you.
Please drink a lot.
Let's drink.
Please.
Thank you.
It smells good.
It's good.
Is it good?
Is this lemon? Yes, it is.
It also contains lemon grass.
It is very effective for the neck.
Is that so?
We also blend lavender, which
is good for sleep, in our own way.
That's great.
Please drink a lot.
Thank you.
Please.
Nice to meet you.
Are you her boyfriend?
Which one? Yes, I am.
He is my ex-boyfriend.
What? Really?
Are you kidding me? No, I'm not.
I believe you.
Are you kidding me? Stop it.
You three get along well.
We've been friends since we were students.
I see.
I think today's course is perfect for you.
Actually, we are going to have a
fun massage with friends today.
But you may be confused
because you have just started.
So, we are going to have a
half-price massage. How do you like it?
I saw it on a page.
Please do it.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm looking forward to it.
There are two types of course,
dry course and course using oil.
Is it okay for you
to use oil? It's okay.
I think it's better for you.
I can get rid of tiredness.
Please tell me where you are tired.
Can you tell me what you are good at?
I am good at shoulder work.
Is it around here?
There are quite a lot of shoulders.
Then, let's focus on the shoulders.
Here are the shoulders.
Thank you, everyone.
Also, in this exhibition, the male audience
will be massaged by the female audience,
and the female audience will be massaged
by the male audience. Is that okay?
Is that so?
Is there a reason for that?
In fact, the female audience
tends to prefer a stronger
massage, and the male
audience tends to feel pain.
I see.
It may be because they
like strong massages.
I see.
Interesting.
Are you okay?
Please drink more tea.
I'm sorry.
You can relax.
Please drink a lot.
Thank you.
It will warm your body.
Please drink more.
Please sit down.
I drank it all.
It was delicious.
It was good.
Thank you for the meal.
The room will be ready
soon, so please wait.
Yes.
Have you changed
your clothes? It's early.
I'm changing my clothes now.
Aren't the pants too small?
I wonder if it's okay.
Hey, are the men's pants too small?
I wonder if it's really okay.
I've changed my clothes,
so let's take a look.
Oh, really? Can you take a look?
The one next to it?
Yes.
It's small, isn't it?
It looks small to me, too.
What do you mean? Like this.
Oh, I see.
It's easier for people
who use oil to apply.
I see. That's why it's smaller.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
You were watching it, weren't you?
I don't mind watching it.
By the way, you are quite muscular.
You have a nice body.
I'm a woman.
How do I look?
I don't look like Rika.
Hey, Sana.
Are you doing
something? No, I'm not.
I'm just chatting.
Chatting?
Yes.
What do you mean
by chatting? Well.
..
If you tease me, I'll
stop being your friend.
You don't have to do that.
I'm nervous.
But I'm looking forward to it.
After this, let's go to
have a meal together.
Thank you.
Let's get started.
I'll start from your shoulders.
You have a lot of hair.
I don't think there are many
people who have this much hair.
Do you have a lot of work to do?
Oh, you work on the outside.
I see. Then you can use your body a lot.
It's a little far away, so may
I excuse you? Excuse me.
Here we go.
Are you all right?
This side is easier to operate.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right around here?
You have a lot of hair.
Did you do any sports? I see.
When you were in college?
There are a lot of questions.
What kind of relationship do you have?
A friend in college?
Do you think it's Rika?
What do you think,
Kana-chan? Ah, Kana-chan.
That's it.
Kana-chan seems to have been
added to make her body warm.
I'm sure she was looking forward to it.
Did you have a relationship?
Did you have a friend?
I didn't know that.
Your boyfriend seems to be very popular.
He is definitely popular, isn't he?
If I say such a thing,
Rika-san will scold me.
Hey, I'm glad you came. Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Where are you working? I see.
By the way, you said you came here
with your boyfriend. Do you know who he is?
Yes, I do.
Oh, really?
He is a Samaritan.
Oh, I see.
He is a man who does his best.
I see.
That's nice.
Can we have a massage together?
I want to see you after a long time.
I wonder if there are many
old people in this crowd.
What's the matter?
I'll get some oil.
Excuse me.
I'll use the oil to remove the blood.
It's very hot.
Rika-san, you make a strange sound.
Are you feeling
better? It's hot.
Your friend looks very comfortable.
Can you hear it?
Please raise your hand.
Are you all right?
I'm just massaging your lower back.
Your breath is getting heavier.
What's wrong?
Did you hear that?
I think the tip of your
ears are very sensitive.
You feel good, don't you?
You don't have to look at me so much.
I entrusted you to a person
who is good at massaging.
Are you nervous?
Please do something.
You are using a hot water
bath, so your body will be warm.
Excuse me.
How are you?
I'm a little hot, too.
Rika-san and her friends
are enjoying the massage.
Are you curious?
Are you okay?
What's wrong? Excuse me.
It seems that the
massage was a little strong.
Are you okay?
Then I will massage your legs.
How long has it been
since you last saw Rika-san?
Two weeks?
You have a lot of things to
look forward to tonight, don't you?
Rika-san is so small, but
she has a good personality.
She is a very proud girl.
Sit down.
Wow, your legs are full.
You are working hard.
I want to be firm.
May I be excused? Excuse me.
You don't have to worry
so much about your mother.
More than that, you are
worried about me, aren't you?
I'm drawing on your face.
I'm going to massage you.
Are you Rika-san?
Rika-san is just getting
a massage, so it's okay.
Don't worry too much.
Just focus on my massage.
What's wrong?
Are you surprised?
I can see you from this side,
but not from the other side.
I can't see anything, so it's okay.
This is a special massage for you.
You were surprised, weren't you?
How do you feel?
You are massaging your friend.
Did you get scared?
How do you feel?
You know,
when you see such a big boob,
you get nervous,
don't you? Look.
Even though Mika-chan is here,
you got nervous because of your friend's
appearance and massage on me, right?
Rika-san's massage is a
hip-up massage for women.
It's okay.
That is also a hip-up massage.
Don't worry.
That is also a massage.
Riko-san, you seem to be in a good mood.
Are you feeling dizzy?
I'll give you a good massage.
Let's do it.
A lot.
She is next to you.
Do you hate her?
Are you okay?
You both drank a lot of tea, so I
guess your blood flow is getting better.
You seem to be able to get a good massage.
How about here?
Can you hear me?
There are a lot of nerves here.
Excuse me.
I'll do my best.
Rika-san and Saba-san,
This is a massage for women.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Excuse me.
Do you feel good?
Oh, no!
It's a virus!
Do you hate this kind of thing?
You don't hate it, do you?
Why?
Because it's so serious.
It's OK.
I'm not the only one next to you.
It's been two weeks since
we last saw each other.
I think you should have sex.
You'll feel better tonight.
Are you okay?
Is it dangerous?
What's dangerous? I'm not alone.
It's okay.
Riko-san, you look very comfortable.
I'm glad you enjoyed my massage.
Are you glad to see me?
What's the matter?
Are you lonely because of your friend?
Are you excited to see him?
Or, Morika-san?
But,
You get excited when
you see him, don't you?
Actually, your friend is aiming
at your boyfriend, isn't she?
I saw you two talking a while ago.
Did you see it?
I'm sure the dog is aiming at you.
You want to do it, don't you?
This is a special massage.
Chikabe's wink is so cute, isn't it?
You haven't taken a
shower for a week, have you?
How do you like my big boobies?
Do you like it?
It's bigger than Rika-san, isn't it?
Look, it's so wobbly.
It's hard here again.
Chinchin.
Can't I do more than this?
I can't, can I? Look.
It feels good.
Are you having a meal because it's so cold?
Or do you feel good
to be teased? It's hot.
Is it dangerous only for you?
You are not alone, so it's okay.
Do you feel good?
You don't want to go
to bed directly, do you?
Can you see it? Here.
Can you see the boobies here?
Sutan-san, you are twitching a lot.
Oh, you got even more
tired after seeing the boobies.
Sutan-san.
Are you all right?
What are you going to do?
You have a lot of hair.
Are you all right?
This is a mirror.
It is effective to do it while
looking at yourself in the mirror.
Ah!
Mika-san, you're in a lot of trouble.
Can you see? It's all right.
You can't see from the other side.
It's a magic mirror.
Ah!
That's also a surgery.
Fufu.
She seems to be in a good mood.
You can't eat so soon.
She is being teased.
You have grown up again.
You are so beautiful.
She is in a very bad mood.
Riko-san is also in a bad mood.
Are you all right?
You are in a bad mood.
Why are you so excited?
Do you want to play more?
Rika-san, you are so excited.
You look so comfortable.
You look so happy.
You are so cute.
Look down.
Why do you look so happy?
You are so cool.
Are you excited to see Rika-san?
Are you excited to see Sana-san?
Are you excited to see me?
Please be honest with me.
You are amazing.
You are full of energy.
How is it?
Do you feel good?
You don't have to do your best.
Look at her.
She looks comfortable.
She is getting bigger and bigger.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
It's chilly.
I'm getting sleepy.
Actually,
there was a medicine
in the tea I just made.
Look at Riku's face.
She looks comfortable.
Oh, you can't do it anymore.
Don't look at me.
Don't move.
You have a ring on your finger, don't you?
Imagine that you have
a ring on your finger.
Or I'll take it away with my hand.
It's OK.
Are you okay?
You are still holding it.
It's all right.
I'm not going to bite you.
Come on, listen.
You are making a lot of noise.
You are so stubborn.
What are you going to do?
Rika-san has gone.
What?
Do you think you are
different from your wife?
Hey, you can go by yourself.
You have a strong sense of justice.
You are so cute.
You are sleeping so slowly.
You look sleepy.
How do you feel now?
Do you feel good? Look at me.
How do you feel?
Ufufu, umfufu,
umfufu,
ughh,
amazing!
Ufufu, I will be a
magical monster,
oh?
It feels good when you do it like this.
But you can't do it anymore, can you?
How is it?
Are you really patient?
I'm sure you've got a lot of hair.
I was surprised.
It's easier to see than before, isn't it?
I was surprised to see you.
You were surprised, too,
weren't you? Don't worry.
I can only see you from here.
Here you are.
You can't stand it, can you?
You've been doing this for a long time.
For a long time.
It's OK.
You may fall asleep
even if I hold you like this.
Hey, girlfriend.
You are amazing.
You have been patient for a long time.
But I want to massage your back.
Then I will lick your back.
Do you want to play?
Why?
She is waiting for you.
You will be left alone.
Or do you want to play with me?
I've been watching you
for a long time, haven't I?
Ah!
I knew you were having a romance.
I knew you like boobs.
Look at me closely.
Look at my hand.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
Other girls are also pulling my hair.
It's annoying, isn't it?
How is your hand?
Do you want to touch it?
Do you want to
touch it? That's good.
Look, it's getting warm again.
Try touching it.
It's getting warm.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to make you feel
better, so please look down at me.
Okay?
I don't know why Rika-san
is in such a good mood.
Look at your brother's figure.
Can you touch here?
Did you do it yourself?
You did it yourself, didn't you?
Are you sleeping?
Do you want me to show you your face?
Do you want me to touch you?
I can't stop it anymore.
It feels good.
I'm going to cry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm going to be a nurse.
I'm sorry that I have to put up with you.
You can't put up with me
anymore, can you? 「I'm so tired.
」 「I'm so tired.
」 「I'm getting
bigger and bigger.
」 「Brother.
」 「I'm getting
bigger and bigger.
」 Don't worry. You won't
hear the sound of a massager.
You'll feel much better.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Do you like it?
You are amazing.
You are so big.
So big.
Rika-san, you can't bear to
go in front of Ada, can you?
You can't bear it, can you?
I can't bear it anymore.
【The sound of a baby crying】
Are you a baby?
【The sound of a baby
crying】 Oh, you are gone.
You are gone.
〔Coughing and sneezing〕
What's wrong?
You don't have to bear it.
You don't mind, do you?
You are so kind.
What's the matter?
You are my friend.
I'm going to start eating now.
Can you hear a lot of happy sounds?
Do you feel like you are
loved by your mom and me?
Do you feel good?
You are making a great noise.
I will make a noise, too.
Do you want me to do something great?
You do, don't you?
Look!
You got something on your face.
I'm going to take it off.
Wow!
Oh!
How do you feel at home?
You have a cold.
I can't bear it.
Why do you bear it?
Let's bear it, too.
You can't sleep, can you?
Are you going to sleep?
Wow!
You put the water in your mouth.
Are you a sweet girl?
Do you like to drink water?
Do you feel good? I did my best.
Please do your best.
I feel good, too.
I want you to feel good.
This is a heart massage.
You are moving by yourself.
You are very energetic.
It's OK.
Let's do it again.
I can hear your happiness.
I can hear your happiness, too.
I can hear your heart beating.
We can't lose to you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Wow! It's amazing!
I was saved!
I'm so happy!
Can you touch my butt?
Do you want to touch my butt?
You are so cute.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Let's make our eyes sparkle.
Can you see me?
Please look at me.
Please look at me carefully.
I feel great.
I'm nervous.
Are you tired?
How do you feel? I'm here.
How do you feel?
I feel like she is next to me.
Please be rather careful.
Please recover your consciousness.
It feels good.
Please fall into me without hesitation.
Please, please fall into me.
Please fall into me more.
Please fall into me more intensely.
I hope you will feel better
when you catch up with me.
I feel so good.
Please be patient.
I've come this far.
Let's feel better.
Let's get to know each other.
This is a massage that
can only be started in a hotel.
Come closer.
If you feel so great,
let's have a meal together.
It feels so good.
I'll go first.
It's so intense.
What's going on? Sano-san.
Sano-san, you are very tired.
What are you doing?
You are being pushed inside.
You are being pushed inside, aren't you?
You want more, don't you?
I want you to feel better.
Okuma-chan.
I stopped breathing.
Maybe... Rika-san...
Rika-san's voice is coming out.
Hey, isn't it good that
her voice is coming out?
I've been holding it in for a
long time, but it's limitless, isn't it?
Please put a lot of
Nishikondometoxin in me.
Please put it out.
Wow!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Oh, you came earlier than me.
How was it?
You felt good, didn't you?
Your face is not red at all.
It was really good, wasn't it?
I really liked it, but...
If you don't mind...
When Rika is busy...
Would you like to come with me?
I'll keep it a secret from Rika.
You won't come, will you?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What were you talking about?
I was talking about how comfortable it was.
Massage?
How was it?
It was very comfortable.
My shoulders and body became lighter.
My whole body became refreshed.
I was talking about coming again.
Yes, I do. I want to come here again.
It's hot.
Yes, it is.
Excuse me.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
How was it?
Yes, it was good.
Thank you.
Thank you very much. Kare-san, how did
you feel when you were in charge of me?
Did you feel good?
Thank you very much.
How about you two? I'm fine.
How about you? Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm fine, too.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
We are looking forward to seeing you again.
Please come and see us again,
whether you are alone or with your friends.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for today.