Are you coming here?
Why did you come here again?
I'm worried about you.
Let's sleep.
I'm kissing you.
You're in the way.
【I'm so sleepy】 【I'm so sleepy】
It's so hard for me to sleep.
【I'm so sleepy】 How many times did I sleep?
【I'm so sleepy】 【I'm so
sleepy】 【I'm so sleepy】
【I'm so sleepy】
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Pim-chan.
I want to sleep.
I want to sleep for a while.
I'm sleepy.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
Hey, you.
You're looking at me.
I'm jealous.
I'll look at you, too.
Why?
Wow.
What?
You're licking that part?
Don't lick that part.
You're licking the same part.
I'm watching you from
a very close distance.
Oh, your butt?
Hey, what are you doing?
I thought you wouldn't notice.
I didn't notice.
Since she was a baby, she has been
sniffling and licking Poco-chan's lips.
I brought a video of my cats
eating the cat food I prepared.
It was a video that I
took a long time ago, but I
wanted to make a video of
my cats eating the cat food.
I'm sorry if it's a video
that you're worried about.
I try to give them a snack.
Momoka is very interested in the snack.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How many times have you done it?
Did you finish eating?
Let's brush your teeth.
Let's go out of my way.
You're in a good place now.
Are you in a good place?
Yes.
Do you want to do the other way around?
This is the first time I've ever seen a
baby crying like this, and it's so cute.
The baby's crying is so
cute that I can't help but cry.
Thank you very much.
I want to sleep soon.
Can I put it in like
this? Oh, it's hard.
Did you put it in
again? I put it in.
I'll put this in, too.
Don't get angry.
Why?
Oh!
It's a cheat!
Today is the 10th day
since my daughter was born.
The daughter is crying
with tears in her eyes.
Kyaa!
I can't see well...
Wow! I can see very well!
I'm doing my best.
Oh, my butt.
I put banana in it.
Do you feel good?
Do you want to see a lot?
Let's see a lot.
Wow! Wow! I forgot.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God!
Did you get the best
one? It's amazing.
Did you get the best one?
You got the best one.
Oh, it's so cold.
This team is too amazing.
Don't do that.
What do you want?
Don't make a face like you want me, too.
Are you tired?
You did it three times.
Don't you want to do it with me?
You can do it if you do it one
more time, right? Let's do it.
I know you guys are watching my video.
It's been a while since I last saw my cats.
They are so cute!
I had a hard time getting used to this.
They make me feel good.
I'm happy.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's been
a long time since I've seen a
cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm worried because I've
never seen a cat like this before.
Oh, my God.
Which one do you like?
Which one do you
like? It's too much.
It's a picture of a man.
I thought it was a picture of a man.
Oh, I see.
It's a picture of a woman.
I had a baby in the country side.
I'm going to take a video of a
baby in the countryside today.
As I'm filming a video in the countryside,
I feel that I'm going to get angry and cry.
I had a baby in the country side.
What are you doing?
Do you want me to do it for you?
Are you happy to be brushed?
I'm going to show you what
happens when I take a bath.
I'm going to take a bath.
This is a video that I took when I was in elementary school
It's too hard.
I'm sorry.
It's getting bigger.
It's amazing.
I did it three times,
but it became like this.
It's amazing.
I wonder if I can do it
as many times as I want.
How many times do you think you can do it?
What? What?
What's this?
Are you okay?
It's different, isn't it?
It's moving, isn't it?
This feels good, too.
I'm so happy.
I saw the movie so many times.
I wanna watch the movie a lot.
It feels good.
I love you.
I don't want to die.
Oh, no.
Ah! Oh, no.
Did you see that?
Did I do it?
Ah!
I did it again! Oh, no.
It's terrible.
It's still going to come out, isn't it?
No?
No way!
It's going to come out, isn't it?
Noe-chan, you did it just now.
What?
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't do it!
I'm going to do it again.
Let's do it with me.
Why?
I want to do it again.
Why do you want to do it again?