Le Yu Sports Sponsored by Paris
Saint-Germain, Chelsea, Mubappé, Neymar.
Play safe, play safe, Le Yu reminding
you, under 18, please do not watch.
Little brother, do you want
to chat with your sister?
Sister, I'm a little lonely tonight.
Come to Taiwan and chat with your sister.
Let's talk about the sky together.
There are many lonely
sisters here at night.
You can talk about anything
you want to each other.
Let's talk about the
sky with a voice video.
You can do whatever you want to do.
If you dare to make a
video, I dare to take a video.
There are 90,000 young
women in the country in Taiwan.
There are many types of Yuyu,
Lamei, Yujie, Loli, Heisei, and
Xueshoumei in Taiwan, and you
can always use the type you like.
There are secret registration
services in different cities around
the country, so maybe we can make
an appointment in the same place.
No one knows anyone here, sincere
friendship, not involved in friendship.
Taiwan Yuyu provides
privacy protection, so
you don't have to worry
about privacy leaks.
There are also many good gifts to
be sent to these registration platforms.
I'm going to show you
the inside of the room.
It's amazing.
Is it like this?
Can you see it?
Yes, I can.
It's so big that I can't get in.
How far can you get in?
Hey!
Thank you for coming all the way here.
You're welcome.
I heard you applied on our website.
That's right.
Could you introduce yourself first?
My name is Kenta.
I'm 27 years old.
Do you have a job?
If I don't use the umbrella too much.
I'm a salaried man and I run a business.
I see.
Is the color of your hair okay?
It's barely safe.
I've heard that there's
a special reason for that.
I guess it's a special reason.
I've always had a desire to
be popular on the Internet.
I'd like to see a scene where a black
person gets beat up by a tall person.
That's a lot of requests.
It's boring if you're Japanese.
I see.
So you are married, right?
Yes, I am.
How long have you been married?
It's been 3 years.
Is it still hot?
Well, we go out and take pictures together.
I don't know if I can ask you,
but how is your marital life?
What do you think?
I don't think I've done it yet.
It's not enough.
It's about to be my third year,
so I'd like to have an accent.
By the way, do you have
any experience in bed?
No, I don't.
I think it's the first
time for a black man.
Why?
You're flying today.
By the way, can I have
a look at your photos?
Sure.
I'm personally interested in them.
Can I take a selfie of you?
Is that allowed?
Selfie?
People send me photos of their clothes.
Cute.
Can I look at other photos?
Sure.
If you do it like this, it's okay.
It's like a different
pattern of the same selfie.
What's this?
It's a couple's thing.
I see.
By the way, is it possible
to set up a camera at home?
At home?
At home, it's a little...
It's an apartment.
It's a little... That's right.
That's not good.
There's a hotel we're staying at.
We can film there.
I'll set up the camera.
I'll give you the camera.
You'll film yourself?
Yes, I'll cover my eyes.
The black guy will be on standby.
So you'll cover your
eyes and take the camera?
Yes.
I see.
That's a problem.
I understand.
I'd like to contact you in detail.
I have a question for you.
Is it okay if I use your company's
phone number and email address?
No problem.
I'm going to have a
meeting with a foreigner.
Thank you very much for today.
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
It's spacious.
It's a nice place.
There's a lot of space in the back.
Isn't it spacious?
It's a Japanese-style room.
Let's get in.
It's so spacious in the back.
I didn't think it would be this big.
Let's take a break.
I'm tired.
It's a good time to
celebrate the anniversary.
That's right.
Is it the third year?
You remember it.
I remember it, too.
It's been a long time.
It's been three years.
You are so fast.
You got a job at the same company.
Yes, I got a job at the same company.
How many years have you been dating?
How many years have I been dating?
Half a year.
How long have you been married?
2 years.
You remember it well.
I remember it well.
I miss working with you.
I feel nostalgic.
I was a little annoying senpai.
You were.
What are you doing now?
I was sent to another place.
Really?
Yes.
I didn't know.
There was something.
There was something like a crime.
That's right.
That's a little... I'm glad.
I'm glad I met you.
If it wasn't for that senior, I
wouldn't have had a bad relationship.
And then I got married.
Surprised?
Surprised.
Did you have a marriage proposal?
Well, as long as there was a good person.
I see.
How was it?
I already had it.
Did you have it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes. I think I got married
at the same age as my ideal.
I think so, too.
It was 3 years ago, so I
was about 25 years old.
24 years old.
Isn't it ideal?
I thought that was good.
I was ideal.
I wanted to get married
when I was about 25 years old.
That's what I thought.
You came here on your 27th birthday.
It's been a while since I came here.
I'm looking forward to the hot spring.
I heard it's nice here.
Is that so?
I want to go in.
Let's go in.
Let's take a bath.
It smells good.
It's a little cold, but it's pretty cold.
It's still cold.
But it's still cold.
I'm sure you're nervous.
I'm not nervous.
More?
More.
I've only been to the Shinkansen once.
That's right.
Yes, that's right.
We didn't have time to
get along with each other.
That's right.
I was busy with work.
It felt good.
Yes.
Do you feel relaxed?
Yes, I feel relaxed.
I feel relaxed.
That's right.
I'm glad to hear that.
You're a sexy shot.
Do you want to have a child soon?
I want to have a child.
Do you like children?
My child is cute.
I agree.
What do you want?
I want two children.
Do you want a boy or a girl?
Which one do you prefer?
I don't care.
You don't care?
I like them both.
If I'm alone,
I might want siblings.
You might be lonely.
I might be lonely.
If we're alone, we can hang out together.
That's right.
Is that okay?
I don't know if it's a good
thing or a bad thing, but
I think it's a good thing to
have a son or a daughter.
I like the countryside.
It's relaxing.
It's far from the hustle
and bustle of the city.
I like the sea.
I like the sea, too.
I can see the sea.
Do your best.
I'll do my best.
I heard you use sake.
Yes.
Japanese sake?
What do you think?
Yes.
Let's make a toast to the 3rd anniversary.
Cheers?
Is it in?
Thank you.
Please follow me.
Go ahead.
I'm going to get drunk.
It's okay.
It's just a tip.
Wow.
It's hot.
That's how warm it is.
You don't usually drink, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't drink at home.
I'm not good at drinking anymore.
You don't drink, do you?
No.
Are you tired?
No, I'm not.
But it was a good time.
I was healed.
I'm glad.
Where should we go?
Do you want to go for a walk?
I wonder if there is a tourist attraction.
I heard that monkeys are famous.
Are you going to see monkeys?
I have never seen a monkey.
Be careful not to be caught.
I'm scared.
I'm tired, so I'll massage you.
Are you serious?
What's up?
I wear the same clothes every day.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I want to meet him.
Do you want to meet him?
Is it here?
How is it?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Wow, it's sticking out.
Around here?
It's thin.
What are you talking about?
Is it?
Like a stone.
A stone?
It doesn't go as far as a stone.
I wonder what it is.
It's like a gori.
It's like Gori Gori.
It feels good.
I'll give you back.
Really?
Sleep.
Do you want me to crush it?
I'm going to massage your face.
What?
I saw a video on TV the other day.
What is it?
If you massage your face while covering
your eyes, it will be very effective.
Really?
Do you want to try it?
I don't know.
I'm tired.
I have it.
Do you have it?
I was thinking of giving you a massage.
Is that so?
It's a coincidence.
Where is it?
Did you forget?
No, I still have it.
It's a mess.
What is it?
I don't know what it is.
I found it.
I put it next to me.
Please put this on.
Can you put this on?
Is it like this?
That's good.
Can't you see it?
I can't see it at all.
You can't see it at all.
I can't see anything.
Then...
Wait a minute.
I'll give you a finger massage.
Really?
I don't need it.
I can't see anything.
Really?
Wait a minute.
Can't you see it?
I'll put my hand in front of the massage.
I don't need it.
Can't you see it?
Okay.
First, the shoulder.
It feels good.
It's stiff, isn't it?
It's really stiff.
Let's do the other side.
It feels really good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Let's massage the lower part as well.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's soft.
You look younger than before.
Really?
The other side.
I can't see anything.
I feel something strange.
What do you feel?
I don't know.
I feel something strange
when my vision is taken away.
Is it different from usual?
Yes, it is.
What's wrong with you?
I'm getting angry.
How about a massage?
I'll leave it as it is.
What?
As it is?
Oh, really?
You're good at it.
You've always wanted
to do that, haven't you?
Well, I guess so.
Can I play hide-and-seek with you?
What?
Are you interested in me?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You are excited.
I'm always different.
Because you are different from usual.
This is the end.
Is that dangerous?
It is dangerous.
Well, both are a bit of a foul.
You're more sensitive than usual.
What?
Your legs are shaking.
It's difficult.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It tickles.
Okay, roll over.
Stretch your legs.
Huh?
What?
What's wrong?
I forgot this.
You forgot?
I didn't think you were a no-brainer.
Let's do a special course.
Special course?
I'm sleepy.
How do you feel?
What's wrong?
I feel sick.
Open your legs by yourself.
You're so cute.
Do you want me to pet your face?
Yes, please.
It feels good.
It's good, isn't it?
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, it looks painful.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, it feels good!
I'm so happy.
It feels good.
Good morning.
You look like a four-leaf clover.
Your butt is like a four-leaf clover.
Turn your face to the right.
Oh, it's cute.
It's a little embarrassing.
Yes.
I don't want to see it.
I'll massage your butt.
What's that?
Hehehehe.
He's sensitive there.
How do you feel now?
I don't know How do I feel?
I'm a little nervous.
Hehehe
I can't see it.
It feels good.
Can I take it off?
No way.
I can't help it.
What is it?
I don't know what you're fishing.
It's a normal fish.
Oh, is it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
You are getting more and more messy...
Moles grow so easily?
Yes.
Oh, oh... Oh, my...
It feels so good.
Ah...
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, it feels so good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's so good.
It feels good.
I want you to feel good, too.
I don't know where it is.
Let's go this way.
This way?
Here?
Why are you laughing?
There it is.
Here?
Good.
What's wrong?
Was it this big?
You are more excited than usual.
It's heavy.
It's 30% bigger than usual.
The atmosphere?
Yes.
Hmm.
How does it feel to lick
while hiding your eyes?
What?
I felt so good that I almost said it.
Why?
Yuin, let's do it again.
Until when did you do it?
You're amazing, I'm
going to sleep a little more.
Yes, you sleep by yourself.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wait, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Isn't it big?
It's about 1.5 times this time.
It's big.
Wait a minute!
You're drooling more than usual.
I'm drooling.
It doesn't fit in my mouth.
How far can you put it in your mouth?
What are you talking about?
Show me your tongue.
Like this?
You are so cute.
Really?
Can you give me a kiss?
I have a heart, too.
Wait a minute.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm going to sit here.
Give me a kiss.
Are you cute?
I'm so nervous.
Is he playing with me?
I don't know.
He is playing with me.
Can I stand up?
I think I should raise
my legs a little more.
I've never done this
before, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right.
It's going well.
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
Let me brush your teeth.
Are you used to it?
Are you ready?
Why are you making a weird sound?
I don't know.
If you keep doing that, I
won't be able to bear it.
What?
No, you can't.
Wait a minute.
Can you go upstairs?
Upstairs?
Upstairs.
Here.
It's here.
Here?
What's wrong?
My heart is pounding.
I'm more excited than usual.
I think she likes it.
You are always mean.
It feels good.
Oh, it's not good.
She said she was going to go.
It feels good!
Does it feel so good?
Is that so?
I feel like I'll be a father soon, yes.
Really?
Can you stand there for a second.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I was about to go.
I'm going to sleep.
Here?
I want you to move your hips.
Like this?
That's good.
It's good.
It feels good.
Let's wash your hands.
Hold this.
Open your legs.
That's right.
Oh, my back hurts.
Oh, it feels good.
I love you so much!
I feel so good.
I got a voice mail.
I love you so much!
Who are you?
Why are you taking a video of me?
Wait, I can't.
Wait a minute.
Did you feel good?
I felt good.
Who are you?
We are friends, aren't we?
I love you, Ken-CHAN!
Hello!
Who are you?
Why are you taking a video of me?
Wait! I can't take a video of you!
Wait!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Who is she?
She is my friend.
Wait a minute.
Do you have a friend like her?
Yes, I do.
She was my friend when
I was studying abroad.
Are you kidding me?
I thought you were Ken-chan.
At first, I was Ken-chan.
At first?
The first one?
Yeah, the first one.
After that, it was him.
Him?
That's crazy.
That's amazing.
I won.
She's feeling good.
Feeling good? Oh, nice.
Yay!
Me too.
I think he can do it again.
Can you do it again?
Are you looking at me?
I'm looking at the camera.
It's a little embarrassing.
Can I do it?
Yes, you can.
Why are you looking at me?
It feels so good!
Let's go!
Oh my god!
It feels so good!
What?
I'm so happy.
Ah~~~~illy~~~~.
It hurts... It hurts...!
Oh, you're drooling a lot.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Do you want to do it again?
Can I do it again?
Yes.
Now, turn your hips and do it again.
Lay down.
I'm sorry.
I've never seen you so fast.
You're amazing.
Stop it!
Hey!
Open your eyes!
See, I'veollowed her.
It was bad, good for you.
selfish Let's go go go go.
You have to do it.
This is a very good sound.
Ah, I'm going to fall.
I'm going to fall.
It's in, it's in.
Oh no.
I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going to fall, I'm going to fall.
Arigatou gozaimasu.
What?
How was it?
What do you mean?
I don't know what you mean.
I wanted to see you with a black man.
Are you really my friend?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
I feel good.
You reacted better than I did.
I was surprised, too.
Did the person next to me hear it?
I heard her voice.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you.
I heard that you applied on the website.
Yes.
I heard that you have
a special personality.
I don't know if it's special.
I have a wife who has
been married for half a year.
I have a wife who is a bit older than
me, and I wanted to see her sleeping.
Have you had such an experience?
I've seen it in manga and doujinshi,
but it was my first time getting married.
I've been with my girlfriend
for a lifetime, but I can't keep
up with her anymore, so I'm
looking for her on the website.
So you're looking for her all the time.
I see.
I don't have a big camera,
so I'm wondering what kind
of face I'll make when
I'm satisfied with the size.
I'm a little interested.
I see.
There is a hotel in this area.
I'll set up a camera there.
I'll take a video of you.
I'll cooperate with you.
Is it OK?
By the way,
should I contact the address
and phone number you sent me?
I see.
I'll contact you later.
I'll contact you about it.
I got it.
It's wide.
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
I'll put a scissor here.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'll put a lot of energy into it.
Thank you.
You are in a very good mood, aren't you?
I'm in a good mood, so I'm
going to take a break for a while.
I'm tired.
It was a little far, wasn't it?
No, but it was a good exercise.
I'm tired.
My legs hurt a lot.
I haven't seen you for a long time
It's been a long time since
we came to the onsen.
It's been a long time.
I'm sorry I've been busy all the time.
I haven't done anything.
I'm sorry I'm glad to be able to meet
you for the first time in a long time.
It's like a hot spring.
I'm looking forward to it
It's been a long time
since I had a day off.
That's right.
I'm looking for a job.
It's been 7 months since I got married.
That's right.
I'm always at home and
Kyoko is always outside.
I'm sorry.
why?
I've been alone all the time.
I can't go out to play.
I have a bad boss.
I have a lot of work to
do, so I'm sorry for that.
It's okay.
You'll be 30 years old soon.
That's right.
What should I do?
I don't think anything will change.
It won't change.
I've been the same since I turned 30.
It's been three years
since I was in my 20s.
On my birthday, I want to
go to the hot spring again.
I hope I can go.
How about having a baby?
That's right.
It's hard to have a baby when you're young.
It's better to have a
baby before you're born.
I don't know.
It's hard to have a baby
when you're pregnant.
I've never been pregnant, so I
don't know if it's going to be hard.
But I want you to get pregnant soon.
I've been thinking
about it for a long time.
Do you think so?
I think so, but when I'm at work, I
just go home, eat, and go to bed.
When I come to a place
like this, I sometimes say,
Let's do our best.
What?
Let's do our best sometimes.
My body is about to break.
Why?
I'm tired.
It's almost 10 o'clock overseas.
It's early in the morning.
Today,
let's use the hot spring slowly.
Let's eat delicious food.
Let's relax.
Let's do our best.
Yeah, it's relaxing.
Okay.
Let's do that.
It feels good.
Good, good.
The hot spring was the best.
It was really good.
It was like this.
It was great.
It's been a while since we went in slowly.
Yeah, we went in slowly.
There were no people at all.
Really?
Yeah.
I was so hungry.
That's great.
I saw a lot of them.
It can't be helped.
Women's baths are called long baths.
I think so.
I didn't go to many baths at home.
The size of the bath
is completely different.
I agree.
It's a big deal to have a bath at home.
It's a big deal.
I agree.
Because I was sitting there.
That's right.
I'm glad you like it.
I had a great meal.
It's been a while since I ate like that.
I see.
I always go home and
sleep with a full stomach.
I see.
I'm glad.
I drank beer after a long time.
It was a good day.
I'm glad.
Can I hug you?
Will you stick to me?
What?
I'm not that kind of person.
Oh, really?
I'm sticking to you.
That's right.
Can I stick to you?
No.
I don't want to do that.
Hey.
Today is a special day.
It's a special day.
It's a good trip.
Kyouko-chan, can you
do something different?
What is it?
I want you to cover your eyes.
What? You want me to do that?
I heard from my co-worker that if you cover
your eyes, it will make you feel better.
Really?
It's easier to get pregnant.
I don't know if it's true or not.
Is it physically effective?
It's physically effective.
Really?
Yes.
What do you think?
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
Really?
I came to this place.
That's right.
I bought this at a 100
yen shop the other day.
What is this?
This is an eye mask.
Is this normal?
This is a normal eye mask.
This is on your head.
This is to prevent your
hair from crumbling.
Please hold this for a moment.
Really?
Please pull this.
Is this the correct way to do it?
This is wrong.
Please pull this.
This doesn't hurt, does it?
What do you think?
Is it weird?
No, it's not weird at all.
What is it?
It's just my hair.
It's fixed.
I can't see anything.
Don't you feel pain?
I'm fine.
I can't see anything.
Even if you hide your eyes,
you're still cute.
That's amazing.
What's that?
Your skin is so beautiful.
I can't live without your eyes.
I'm not happy with that.
It's a new discovery.
It's amazing.
I feel strange.
It's pitch black.
Is there a gap under your eyes?
I can't see anything.
It's pitch black here.
What is it?
Can you give me a hug?
What?
Where are you?
I'm here.
It's been a long time since I gave
you a hug It's been a long time.
Oh!
It's warm It's warm.
This is the best I
want to hug you.
Kissing is the best, isn't it?
That's right.
Let's kiss.
It's been a while.
It's your turn.
Wow, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I can't see anything.
But you're touching her shoulder.
Do you want to kiss her again?
Yes.
I'm going to give you a kiss I'm
going to give you a kiss on your boob.
Oh, it's so big.
You always touch it.
It's been a while
since I touched it, so it's
different Are you excited
because it's been a while?
I'm excited.
Do you want me to take it off?
Yes, please take off the string.
Oh, it's already out of the frame.
I took it off.
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Your hands are cold.
A little more.
It's so soft.
Really? I've been holding it in.
Really?
It's heavy.
It's so soft.
It feels good.
Can I touch your neck?
I was surprised that Asa was surprised.
It feels good.
Is it hot?
I wonder if there is Asa on the right side.
Let's see.
Wow, he is standing up
He is standing up
Do you want to be carried?
I don't want to.
Do you want me to throw it away?
No, I don't want to.
I don't feel good.
It's so hot!
It feels so good!
Your hair is so nice today, isn't it?
I've been taking care of my hair.
Oh, really?
It feels so good!
Ah!
You're sweating a lot.
It feels good.
Did you sweat?
You're sweating a lot.
You're sweating the most.
Eh?
Ah, it feels good.
Ah!
It feels good.
Oh, no!
Don't worry, I'm here.
It feels so good.
Did you hold it in?
Yes.
It feels so good.
It's really good, isn't it?
Let's lie down, Kyoko-chan.
Should I lie down?
Yes.
The pillow is over there.
Is it here?
Yes.
Thank you.
Open your mouth.
I'm going to touch your belly button.
You are sleeping soundly.
It's uncomfortable.
How do you feel?
I'm going to touch your
neck and belly button.
How do you feel?
I'm going to cry.
Are you going to cry?
Ah!
Oh, you're sweating a lot.
It feels good!
Ah!
Is it hot?
It feels good!
Wow!
It's amazing!
It's like I'm in a sauna.
Ah!
Oh no!
This feels good!
Ah!
Oh, wow!
Your back is floating.
Ah!
Ah, it feels good.
Is it hot?
It's hot.
Your lower back must be hurting.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Ah, you're sweating.
I want you to touch the surface again.
I want you to touch the Chestnut.
The Chestnut?
Yes.
I'll touch the Chestnut.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot.
Oh!
Feels good!
It feels good!
Does it feel good?
Oh!
Is it a little wet?
It's wet!
Oh!
Here?
Ah, it feels good.
It's almost there.
I love you.
I'm going to go.
Go.
I'm going.
Ouch!
Can you make me feel better?
Sure.
Can you do that?
Yes.
Ouch!
Where are you?
I just hit you.
I'm sorry.
You are better than usual.
The ice cream is super hard.
I'm excited.
It's been a while, so it becomes hard.
I want you to breath.
Wait a minute.
I'll wait.
Can I take a picture of you?
Yes, sure.
This is me.
What was I doing?
I was on your left leg.
Here?
Yes, that's right.
Let's do it again.
Is it right?
Yes, it is.
Did you get better than before?
Yes, I did.
I don't think so.
I think it's because it's a trip.
It's hot, so you're cold, right?
Yes.
I can't see it.
It's very beautiful.
My feet are itchy.
It's okay.
Yes, yes, yes.
Keep going.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I like it.
Ah, you're going all the way to the back.
Oh, it's the biggest one I've ever seen.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's very intense.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, it feels good.
It's getting really hard.
I feel like I've gotten really big today.
Can I have you pinch me with your boobs?
Sure.
It's my turn.
Hang in there.
Wow, it's so hard.
It's hard today.
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It's the best feeling I've ever had.
Really?
Kyo-Kyo-Ko-Chan is so erotic.
I'm getting excited.
You are so cute.
It's so hard.
It's bigger than usual.
Really?
Maybe it's because your face is swollen.
Why is my face swollen?
Because you are in a good mood today.
What are you talking about?
You are in a good mood.
Oh, my God.
Are you in a bad mood?
What's wrong?
Do you want me to put it in?
Yes.
I'll put it in.
I'll put it away from you.
Put it in.
You might be able to have a baby.
Please put it in.
I feel so good.
Oh, so slippery.
You're so slippery.
Oh, no.
It's completely different
from when you were alive.
Oh, no, dad.
Can I squeeze your arm?
Yes, please.
Oh, it's so nice.
I feel great.
Don't you feel like you're getting bigger?
I ate a lot of rice earlier.
Did you eat food?
Yes, I ate a lot of food.
I feel like I'm getting bigger.
I feel great.
I'm so happy.
I'm gonna come!
Hi there.
Nice to meet you.
My name is David.
It's a pleasure.
Hi there.
Nice to meet you.
My name is David.
It's a pleasure.
I'm not a suspicious person.
Who are you?
We used to go to a bar
together at the company's bar.
We got along with each other.
Did you get along with each other?
You are a very good person.
what?
You are a good person.
You're a good person.
Don't be scared.
Instead of that...
What do you mean?
On the website...
On the website?
Why?
There's someone who takes care of me.
I really like Kyoko-chan.
I really like Kyoko-chan, but...
I want to see Kyoko-chan
being taken care of.
So I applied for it.
Wait, wait, what do you mean?
I really like Kyoko-chan, but... I want
to confirm my love for Kyoko-chan.
I think I can like Kyoko-chan more.
I thought he was a nice guy.
What?
He was a really nice guy.
He was really nice.
If he wasn't, I wouldn't have asked you.
Is that so?
Yes, yes, yes.
What?
He was really nice, wasn't he?
His reaction was totally
different from mine.
I thought he was a nice guy.
I was watching him.
I was like, what?
What?
I'm so used to it.
I think it was amazing.
I was surprised.
It was really good.
A lot.
It was a lot.
In English.
Now?
Yes.
I speak American.
I'm sorry.
I can't help but laugh.
Thank you.
When did you start?
At first... I sat here and blindfolded
myself for about 30 seconds.
I can't count, so I don't know.
Really?
I had three fingers.
There were three of them.
There were?
Really?
I don't know.
I felt a little uncomfortable.
There are no humans.
But I don't think there
are three of them here.
I don't think so.
One more.
What?
What is it?
Are you serious?
Are you kidding me?
I'm scared.
Ah!
How do you feel?
It's so big!
Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
It's so bad!
Ah... Ah... Ah...
I'm so tired I'm sleepy.
Do you think you can do it?
Yes.
You think you can do it?
I think you can do it.
Oh.
Oh Oh Oh Oh my God.
Oh no.
Oh my God.
oh my god let's look inside.
did you find anything?
wow, you have a lot
You can see a lot of blood.
Foreigners have a lot of blood.
She is very good.
A lot of blood came out.
How did you feel?
Your face is swollen.
Can you move down a little?
Kiyoko, you're good at moving.
Can I put it in?
You can put it in.
If you put it in from
below, it will go deeper.
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous? It looks dangerous.
That's right.
That's great.
You're breathing slowly.
You're breathing so gently.
No.
Are you scared?
She's trying to help you.
She's helping you.
Big!
If you put it up, you can pick it up.
You're picking it up a lot.
Un...
Water's in it a lot.
Oh!
Your favorite towel.
Un... oh oh.
oh i'm gonna come to you.
oh oh god.
oh.
oh oh !
Ah!
Now it's out... Mugyere is out.
Oh, is it out again?
How many times do you put it out?
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah.
It's coming out a lot.
How many times has it come out?
Oh no.
It's coming out.
It's okay.
Great.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I'm good. Very good.
Thank you.
See you again.
I'm not going home.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Pyo-San, say bye-bye.
It was amazing.
I was surprised.
How was it?
It wasn't surprising.
Right?
It was crazy!
Wasn't it crazy?
Crazy, crazy, crazy It came
out a lot It came out a lot.
But it felt good, didn't it?
Well, that's true.
I'm glad I didn't know you
had such a desire I see.
Yes, I think so.
Really?
So, I think I did a great job. Thank you.
I'm glad that you're happy.
I heard that you have a special talent.
To be honest, I have a desire
to be popular on the Internet.
I can't find such a person.
I applied for this time because I saw the
website and I was able to sleep a little.
Who do you want to sleep with?
I'm a little embarrassed, but I'm a virgin.
I have a small penis, so I would
be happy if I could have a big penis.
I see.
You have a wife, right?
Yes, I do.
Can I see your picture?
Sure.
I've been married for 6 years.
It's about a year old.
Isn't it cute?
I'm proud of it.
Is this the one you took today?
Are you going to send me a selfie?
That's right.
You're taking a lot of selfies.
I see.
I live a normal life on my days off.
That's why I'm taking a lot of selfies.
By the way, is it possible
to set up a camera at home?
Is it possible to rent a house?
A house?
A house is a little...
My mother-in-law lives there.
Oh, your mother-in-law.
That's right.
I see.
It may be a little
difficult to rent a house.
You can't live without a house.
That's right.
I have a lot of things to do at home.
I see.
Then, there is a hotel that
we have prepared for you.
Can you take a trip
there and bring it to us?
If you don't mind, I can give you
a place to stay for a cheap price.
Is there such a place?
I'll give you a place to stay.
Really?
I'll contact you later.
I'd be happy if you could do it there.
Is the address and phone number okay?
No problem.
I see.
I'll let you know when
the details are decided.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for today.
You're welcome.
Thank you very much.
Please come in.
It's very spacious.
It's spacious and beautiful.
The room is big.
It's nice.
It's nice to have an atmosphere here.
It's pretty big.
This is enough for two people.
I couldn't make a reservation at this inn.
Is that so?
I've met a senior at the company, Suzuki.
I've met him a few times.
He made a reservation for me.
Oh, really? That's amazing.
You told me that you can't
go on a vacation with me.
Oh, really? I should thank you.
It's been 6 years since you got married.
Yes, it's been 6 years.
Time flies.
Yes, it does.
We don't really travel much.
Yes, we did only when we first got married.
I was busy too.
It's been a while since I've been here.
It's nice.
It reminds me of the old days.
It's great.
I usually go shopping, but I
haven't been to such a place.
Me neither.
I'm looking forward to it.
I heard that there are
many hot Springs here.
Really?
I want to go to various hot Springs.
I want to take a rest.
You always leave all the housework to me.
I want you to take a rest.
I want to take a rest.
I know.
But, if you have a baby,
you can't take a rest.
I know.
You can't take a rest.
What should I do if I have a baby?
How many children do you want?
Well, first of all, I want
to have one person.
I think you'll get a job soon.
I think you'll be able to
cooperate with your wife.
How many people do you want?
About three people.
That many?
That's a lot of work.
You don't know that, do you?
I don't.
But, you are cute, aren't you?
I'm sure I'll be cute when I'm born.
You are cute today, too.
Thank you.
You don't say that all the time.
I don't.
By the way, I heard that
the hair salon is spacious.
Let's go inside.
Let's go.
My hair salon is very spacious.
It's wide!
It's quite wide, isn't it?
It's really high.
I didn't know it was this wide.
It's said that it has a
skin-cleansing effect.
This?
I'm sure.
It's even more refreshing.
What is it?
I've been thinking about dry skin lately.
It's a white skin.
I'm not used to it.
It's so hot.
It's not my fault.
It's your fault.
It feels so good.
Yeah, it feels good.
I'm glad we came here.
I'm really glad.
The bath was really good.
Yeah, it was good.
It was really warm.
Yeah, it was good that it
was like a hot spring town.
Yeah.
I want to go to a place
like that again tomorrow.
Yeah.
Let's go together.
Where did you buy it?
I don't know.
I heard you can eat here, so I like it.
What do they have here?
I don't know what they have, but if I
ask a hotel staff, they might tell me.
I see.
Do they have ramen?
I think so.
I want to eat it.
What flavor do you like?
If there is a famous restaurant
here, I want to go there.
I see.
It's a local restaurant.
It looks delicious.
Let's go there tomorrow.
The crab I ate earlier
was also very delicious.
I'm glad.
I don't eat crab.
You don't eat crab.
It's a high-grade food.
Sashimi was also good.
It was good.
It was delicious.
I ate too much.
I'm glad I could come with you.
Yeah, it's fun.
It's nice to be with you.
I want to go to a lot of places tomorrow.
Yeah.
Is there a zoo?
Maybe there is.
Like a aquarium or a zoo.
We haven't been there recently.
A place like a date.
That's nice.
We haven't been there.
I'm excited.
I can go anywhere with Hitomi.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Really?
Yes.
I was able to come here thanks to you.
I think I need a chance like this.
Yes.
You're right.
We were busy all the time.
It's like an expression of love.
Yes.
We come here every year.
Yeah, I want to cherish those memories.
Yeah.
It's nice.
The yukata is very erotic.
Erotic?
It's sexy.
Really?
I don't see it often.
You don't wear it, do you?
I don't think I've ever
worn it in front of you.
Maybe.
A proper yukata.
It's erotic to be naked.
You look like you're wearing a skirt.
Isn't it like that?
Like that?
Is this right?
It's been a while since I
wore something like this.
It's really nice.
Stretch your legs.
Like this?
Isn't it too tight?
Too tight?
No.
Because you have a big chest.
It's a yukata, so it
doesn't look tight, does it?
Does it look tight?
Have you grown up?
No, I haven't.
I haven't changed.
Really?
Let me touch you.
It's good.
Have I changed?
Do I look like I'm taking a bath?
You look so slender.
Do I look slender?
You look so tired.
I didn't have a good sleep last night.
I'm so nervous.
We don't live together at home.
You're right.
I always sleep when I'm tired.
You look so bad.
It doesn't hurt at all, does it?
It doesn't hurt at all.
It's very smooth.
It has the effect of moisturizing.
It's smoother than usual.
I have a play I want to try.
Play?
What do you mean?
I want to hide my eyes.
Covering your eyes?
Yes.
Are you going to do it?
I want to do something exciting.
I don't mind.
But you've never done it, right?
Let's do it.
I'm curious.
I can't do it at home.
Did you bring it?
Just in case.
If it doesn't work, I can't do it.
I don't mind.
Really?
Yeah.
Hold on a second.
Okay.
I like this kind of static play.
Yeah, I agree.
It's good to do something
you don't usually do.
This is it.
Oh, yeah.
Should I put it on?
Yeah.
Like this?
I can't see anything.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Like this?
It's a little tight.
What should I do?
Is it like this?
If you shake it too
much... Will it come off?
I mean, you can see it.
Oh, I see.
Like this?
Yeah.
If it's too tight, it's fine.
I don't know.
If you can't see it, get excited.
It's not like that.
I don't know yet.
I don't know.
Wait for me until I get there.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Nothing?
How do you feel?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
Good girl.
Do you want more?
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or
not, but I'm going to give it a try.
Do you want to eat it?
Is this okay?
I'm a little embarrassed.
Can't I look at this?
No.
Not a good sign.
Come here.
Nope.
I'm scared.
You don't want to?
No, thanks.
What? Did you hit something?
No, it's just my imagination.
It's just your imagination?
You're hitting something, aren't you?
I know I'm hitting something.
I feel like something
is rubbing against me.
Isn't it wet?
Is it wet?
I think it's wet.
It's better to wear this, right?
Yes.
What are you looking at?
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
It's so hard to open this.
Really?
Yeah.
Ah!
It's so hard to open this.
Yeah.
I'm going to take this off.
I'm scared, I'm scared,
I'm scared, I'm scared.
I'm going to do it.
Are you?
Yes.
保育用のアイテムを使っています。
多分、私はそれを使うことが大好きです。.
だから、私はスポーツに入っているスポーツのインタビューをすることが好きです。.
私はもう一度、スポーツをとるので
今はもう少し球を見ていますね。.
そして、私の新しいスペースが治ったので、
私は今はもう少しスペースをとります。.
私は空腹に入ったがため息をしながら、 健康を取るように、.
何かが分かるように、
How do you feel?
Your feet hurt?
I cut your toenails.
You cut my toenails?
You cut my toenails.
It's so painful.
Mom, what's wrong?
You look like you're in pain.
I'm not in pain.
What?
What's wrong?
Hello.
Who are you?
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
I'm in pain.
Mom, what's wrong?
I don't know what to do.
Don't do that.
What?
Hello.
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
What?
I called someone who has a big penis.
I called you.
Really?
What?
You don't come back to my house.
Really?
Why did you call me?
I wanted to record you.
I don't understand you at all.
Who is he?
He is my friend.
What?
A friend?
What's this?
This is quite big.
Chinko, you were talking a lot.
I was talking all the time?
Yes.
Thank you.
How is it?
What's going on?
What? What do you mean?
You know, I'm always like this.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to stab you.
Thanks.
I'm so happy.
I will do my best from now on.
Thank you.
Yua-kun, what are you doing?
Yes, that's what I'm doing.
It's a little late, so let's go over there.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Oh, a little?
What?
Is that so?
Ok, let's eat!
You said you felt good, didn't you?
But it's not me, It's him
It's cold, isn't it?
Is it cold all the time?
Yes.
Is it cold?
I'm sorry.
I don't mind if you feel better.
I want to see you panting.
Please play with him.
Do you want me to play with him?
Do you want to see it?
Yes, I want to see it.
You want to see it, don't you?
It's my wish.
I don't have a chance like this.
I'll think about it.
Like this?
Yes.
I want you to do it for me.
I want to ask you
something, so I'll do it for you.
What?
Here?
Yes, yes, yes.
You have a lot of hair.
Around here?
It's a little different from Yuka.
But the difference between
black and white is obvious.
You get excited when you see this.
Yes.
Is that so?
It's so delicious.
It's good.
Can you give me more?
It's bigger than mine, isn't it?
It's big.
I think it's a little thick.
Is this okay?
It's fine.
It's very weak.
Rub more.
Rub?
I want to see that.
This is really good.
I can't help but look at this.
That's a lot.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
What?
You can't do that.
Your mouth is 10 times bigger than mine.
It's not that big.
Can you put it in your mouth?
I want to see you feel it.
I want you to put it in your mouth.
What do you want me to do?
Get on the bed and sleep on it.
Do I sleep on it?
Yes.
What about the rubber?
Rubber?
There is no rubber here.
Can I sleep on it?
Yes, you can sleep on it.
Really?
Yes.
Can I sleep on it?
It's bigger than the yukata.
Yes, it is.
Oh, wow.
Oh, no.
It's in.
Oh, it's in.
Wow.
It's really in.
Yes.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
How is it?
It's totally different, isn't it?
Is it bigger than mine?
No, it's not.
It's bigger than mine.
It's not good.
Move more.
I can't move.
I want to see where you are going.
It's good.
It's really good.
Oh, my God.
There's a lot in there.
Oh, no.
I'm going to go.
Show me where you're going.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
You don't usually go that fast.
I'm going again.
Can I?
Yes.
Oh, my.
I want to drink more.
I have to drink it.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry.
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Uh huh.
Oh.
Oh Oh Oh Oh...
Oh... Ah!
Ah!
No... No, no, no, no, no!
Kosei, no... No,
no, no, no, no, no!
Yuka!
Ah!
Fuuuu... Oh!
Oh...
Uhh... Eh?
Ooh... Eh?
Eh, Eh?
Hm... Is it hot?
Yeah, yeah.
Can't tell if you're sweating, right?
Ooh... Hm... Show me... Hmmm...
I did my best.
It's okay.
It's okay?
But... It's too dark.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I want to see you feel
it at a different level.
You've become four-legged.
Four-legged?
You can still do it.
I can't do it at all if I do it once.
Do you still do it?
Yes.
Turn this way.
This way?
Yes.
Really?
Ah!
How do you feel?
It's not good.
Not good?
Yes.
It's totally different from me.
I know.
I'm going to take a bath.
Ah!
I'm sorry. I feel sick.
No.
Ah!
ah.
ah ah ah.
The smell is so strong
I can't breathe ah.
ah.
Ah ah.
Look at me ah ah.
ah.
ah ah.
ah ah You have a lot of
blood in your mouth ah.
I can't do this.
It's so hot!
A little bit more, and you are going
to make it, I know you can do it!
There you go.
I made it?
Yes, you did.
Look at you, you are going
to make it much easier.
I'm not going to make it.
Here it comes.
There you go.
Okay, lift.
Breathe.
Oh, my God.
Damn, that's good, right there.
It's so hot.
Oh, my God.
Let me touch you.
Let me see your face.
I have a lot of pimples.
I'm happy.
Do you still have pimples?
You still have pimples.
Oh, it's hot.
It's really hot.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
Oops!
Oooh!
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
Here it comes.
It's coming.
Good girl.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
You are so big.
I feel so happy.
I'm so happy.
See you.
I'm glad to see you.
How was it?
It was very good.
I see.
I'm glad to see you.
It was very good.