This video is a derivative work of
the Touhou Project. It has no relation
to the original work, and is a
derivative work of the Touhou Project.
I haven't seen you in a long time.
You haven't seen me in a long time?
Then you don't have to hold back.
Okay.
You're not feeling better than usual.
I'm going to hang up.
I'm going to ring the bell.
Wait.
Keep the door open.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Did you go in?
Yes.
Have you ever had sex?
No.
I don't know.
I'm glad.
I just drank it.
Is it different from usual?
I don't know yet.
You'll find out soon.
I'm sure it's going to be
completely different from usual.
You'll feel better if I do this.
No.
Is it different from usual?
Yes.
My body is getting a little hot.
I'll give you a full body massage.
I'll give you a massage
that you can't always attack.
Can I bite you?
Do you like this place?
Yes.
You can sleep well.
I'll give you a full body massage.
It may be different from usual.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to touch me.
Don't you like it?
I don't like it.
You do this at home, don't you?
Please touch me.
Hold your legs so that you can touch me.
I'll give you a massage that you like.
Open your legs.
Pull your legs so that you can see me.
I don't like it.
It's different from usual, isn't it?
You like thick things, don't you?
I like thick things.
What kind of things do you like?
I like big and thick things.
Do you like thick things to the end?
Yes.
It tickles.
I'm nervous.
Do you like thick things?
I don't like it.
It's different from usual, isn't it?
Do you want me to massage you hard?
I'm nervous.
What kind of massage do you like?
It's hard.
Do you like big things?
Do you like this kind of thing?
I like it.
Do you want it or not?
I want it.
I want to talk to you.
I'm nervous.
Do you like thick things?
I like thick things.
I want to talk to you.
Put your mouth back in.
Do you like big things?
Do you like this kind of thing?
I like it.
That's big, too.
It tickles.
I want to talk to you.
Do you want to talk to me?
I don't want to talk to you.
What kind of thick things do you like?
I want to talk to you.
Do you want to talk to me more?
What kind of thick things do you like?
My body is getting weird.
It's hot.
I'll massage you hard.
My body is getting hot.
You're sweating a lot.
Please put it in.
I'm sweating a lot.
Are you looking at me?
Are you thirsty?
I'm thirsty.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
Let me put it in my mouth.
Where did you put it?
I put it in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
Are you thirsty?
Do you like big things?
I like big things.
Do you like it?
It feels good.
Please hit me.
Talk to me.
It feels good.
Are you thirsty?
I'm sorry.
I'm thirsty.
Please do it well.
Do you want me to do it?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do it?
Please do it well.
Did you hear me?
Can I put this in your mouth?
Can I?
This is the medicine I gave you.
Please soak it in.
I'll put it in your butthole.
It's different from usual.
Do you want me to put it in your butthole?
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to put it in your butthole?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Are you still okay?
I'm sorry.
Do you like me?
I'm going to put this in your butthole.
I like you.
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'll put this in your butthole.
I'm sorry.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Everyone is waiting for you.
I'll put a lot in your butthole.
Is it hard?
I'll make your butthole clean.
It suits everyone.
Your butthole is clean.
Marimo.
I'm going to put a lot in your butthole.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Do you want me to
put this in your butthole?
I want you to put it in my butthole.
Please speak louder.
Please put a lot in my butthole.
Please do it louder.
Can I make everyone feel better?
It's okay.
I'll touch you.
Can I touch you?
Please touch me.
I'll touch you a lot.
Do you want me to do
something you can't see?
I'll touch you a lot.
Do you want me to scratch you?
I'll tickle you more.
Do you want me to do
something you can't see?
Do you want me to give
you a lot of medicine?
What's going on with the dog?
Tell me what's going on.
I'll tickle you more.
I'm scared.
You don't have to be scared.
I'll do it for you.
I'll soak you in my body.
How about this?
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good.
I'll tickle you a lot.
I'm scared.
Do you want me to tickle you more?
I'll tickle you a lot.
How about this?
I'm scared.
I'll tickle you a lot.
Look around you.
I'm scared.
I'll tickle you a lot.
Do you want me to tickle you?
I'm scared.
I'll tickle you a lot.
Do you feel good?
I'm scared.
I'll tickle you a lot.
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good.
I'm scared.
Do you want me to tickle you?
I want you to tickle me.
I'll tickle you a lot.
I don't feel good.
I'm scared.
Do you feel good?
I'll tickle you a lot.
I'm scared.