Well then, cheers!
It's the best!
This hot spring feels good.
It's the best with delicious sake.
Hey, listen.
It seems that my
husband is still infertile.
I don't know what to do.
So we have a good style and it's
amazing that we can open up to that.
I don't know.
What do you think?
How do you think from a man's
point of view? That's strange.
Are you listening?
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm listening.
That's weird.
I wonder if we don't have any charm.
Do you think so?
Don't you think so? We are not attractive?
I don't think so.
Right?
Because we have been together so far.
Hey, aren't you really
happy to be played by us?
Look, she is happy.
I'm glad you're having fun like this.
You look happy.
You've been following me all
this time, haven't you? Hey, hey.
Huh?
Are you listening to us?
Have you been listening to us for a while?
Are you standing up?
Did you feel your nipples being touched?
Let's do it again.
You like to be done quickly.
Your nipples are standing up.
What's wrong?
Hey, you're reacting a little, aren't you?
What's this? What's this?
It's getting spicy.
You're reacting, aren't
you? You're excited.
But that's how much
we're attractive, isn't it?
Yeah, I guess so.
Why don't my husbands
treat me? I wonder why.
We have no choice but to
pretend, don't we? That's right.
Do you have a partner
like that? No, I don't.
You don't.
You have to find one.
That's right.
That's why I'm right here.
That's good.
I was right here.
You can play with each other.
I brought you here.
But I was happy to follow you.
That's true.
What's wrong?
Are you excited?
It's the first time for three
of us to go to a hot spring.
Are you excited to see our bodies?
I'll show you up close.
How is it?
You stood up when you saw this, didn't you?
You like it a lot.
It's cute.
It's nice, isn't it?
Look at me more.
You can look at me up close.
She's excited.
You like my boobs, don't you?
What do you think? Are they attractive?
Hey, why do you think we
don't treat you like a husband?
Hey, what do you think?
Come on, tell me why.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Your eyes are twitching.
You're excited.
But you like not only your
chest, but also your butt, right?
How is it?
Uchiro, you don't want
to touch my butt, do you?
You want to touch it, don't you?
Your hands are shaking.
Is it okay to just look at it?
Oh, you're holding back.
You can't say anything to me, can you?
Chiran, you are a good girl.
When I see your butt in front of me,
you get excited again,
don't you? Let me see.
You are very excited.
It's full of love.
Oh, so you're saying you're going
to bully them, aren't you? That's right.
You know, we don't want to do that.
We don't want to be treated like that.
You're going to play with us, aren't you?
That's why you're
here, aren't you? Yeah.
Wow, look, you're being attacked so much.
What's wrong? Do you like people?
She says she likes you.
You're a bad girl, too.
You want to have more fun, don't you?
Do you want to have more fun?
You're honest, aren't you? Yeah.
I want to see you a little
closer, so go up here.
Come on.
Look at this.
Oh, it's coming out.
Wow, it's full.
It's amazing.
Wow, you are standing up.
You are so excited.
Did you fall in love with me?
You have a cute face.
What do you want to do with me?
Do you want to go with me?
If you don't tell me...
I'm cute.
You like here, don't you?
Oh, you have a runny nose.
You have a big runny nose.
Come on, stick out your tongue.
You like ears, don't you?
What's wrong?
Um, um, um, um, um, um,
um, um, um, um, um, um, um...
Hey, you said you like
to be carefully licked.
Oh, ok, I'll lick you
as well! Don't do that.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You can feel it, can't you?
Your ears are getting hot.
It's getting hot.
I think it's going to be just in your ears.
You were so excited.
Hey, touch our boobs, too.
Touch it.
You've always wanted
to touch it, haven't you?
Can't you touch it?
Okay, I'll put it in your mouth.
Please lick my neck.
Please put it down more.
I'll put it down.
It feels good.
You have a lot of boobies, don't you?
And the other side.
I'll lick this side, too.
This song is a lullaby.
It's a lullaby for the cat.
I am a cat, so I like lullabies.
I can't lie down, so I'm
going to sleep next to the cat.
Oh!
I got a cramp in my neck.
Hey, if you like boobs so much,
I'll fill your face with our boobs.
Oh! That's nice.
How is it?
It's powerful, isn't it?
You're excited,
aren't you? Yeah.
Look, look, look.
Look, it's all over your face.
You can't breathe,
can you? That's true.
Are you able to breathe?
This is happiness.
This is the best!
Look at this!
Wow, it's a lot!
Coco, you wanted to
touch it, didn't you? It's slimy.
Do you want me to lick you?
You want me to lick you, don't you?
Let's lick together.
Wow!
You have a cute face.
Do you feel it?
You are happy to be
attacked by a bird, aren't you?
You really like this.
You are the best.
Mom, you are so cute today.
You have a lot of hair.
Do you have a lot of hair on your back?
Did you cut your hair?
We're just kidding!
I'll squeeze it for you.
Hmm, it's good.
Amazing.
I'll look at you again.
She is making a sound of a water bottle.
She is trying to say
something to her brother.
It's been a long time
since I've had a bath,
so I'm going to show
you how to take a bath.
I'm going to show
you how to take a bath,
so I'm going to show
you how to take a bath.
I know, right?
We're getting hot, too.
How is it?
Do you like it when I do it hard?
Or do you like it when I do it slowly?
It's so hot in here.
It's so hot.
I want you to stay here.
Why don't you touch me?
What are you doing
alone? I'm sorry.
Come on.
You finally touched me.
It feels good.
Hey, touch mine, too.
This is a video of me touching
Chimpanzee Mom's belly.
I'm sorry if you feel uncomfortable.
You feel good, don't you?
Ah! No!
My tummy!
Oh, I can't stop.
Oh, it feels so good.
I might be drunk.
Thank you for making me feel better.
Oh, it feels so good.
Hey, don't you want to be here?
Hey, it's okay, isn't it?
We're already at our limit.
You want to be here, don't you?
Hey, you!
You are so fluffy!
Hey, please!
It's good to be wet, isn't it?
Oh, you can't resist it.
Alright!
It's been a while since
I had a bath like this.
It's really nice.
Touch me more.
We're getting excited.
You're excited, too, aren't you?
How do you feel?
I'll massage your face more.
You feel good, don't
you? That's great.
I'm getting tired.
I want to put it in my body, but I can't.
I want to put it in my body, too.
It's okay if I put it in my body, right?
This is the first time I've ever seen
Poco-chan kiss me on the cheek, so I'm
not sure if it's a good thing or a bad
thing, but I'm sure it's a good thing.
I haven't kissed you at all, Poco-chan.
Are you going to throw up?
Because this part of my body is already...
Look, it's reflected, it's reflected.
Wow! It's wet.
Let me put it in your nose.
It's so wet.
This is my favorite.
It's good.
It's going in.
It looks so good.
It's the best.
It's been a long time since
I've had a bath, and it's the best!
Show me where it's in.
Wow!
I'll do it all the way in.
Let's go in.
It feels good.
This is the first time I've
ever had a baby, so I'm a little
nervous, but I'm sure it's
going to be a great experience.
I'm sure it's going to
be a great experience.
I'm so happy.
I love this water pressure.
I feel so good.
I'm so happy.
Oh, it's the best.
I feel my whole body is very sensitive.
Hey, look at what I'm doing.
It feels good.
It's really the best.
Ahh...
I can't...
OK.
It's too hot.
Ah... I can't, I can't.
You have a cute face.
You have a cute face, too.
I'm going to licks your ears.
The smell is getting everywhere.
I'll put the licks in your ears.
It feels good, right?
You are the best!
You have a really cute face.
I want to eat you.
Your face is wet because of our bath.
Are you happy?
Because we licked your face.
I'll make your face wet more.
I'm going to touch you a lot.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Oh, it feels good.
Please keep touching me like this.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
I think I can do it.
No, I can't.
It's the best.
Well, next is...
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm so happy to see a cat like this.
You don't have any
sunglasses, do you? Yes, you do.
How do you feel? I feel so good.
I feel so good.
I'm so happy.
I haven't had sex with
Karate-chan for a long time.
I feel so good.
Ahh, no, no.
I can't do it.
It's uncomfortable, I can't stop it.
Do you want me too?
I'm just kidding.
I feel good.
I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood,
and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood,
and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a
good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and
I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good
mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, and I'm in a good mood, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Next is me.
Are you ready?
Then I'll be in the back.
I'll go in.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
I feel sick...
I feel sick... I'm sick...
Oh, my god, I feel sick...
I'm sick...
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
I feel good.
How do you feel in the first microphone?
Oh, it feels good.
You are the luckiest person in the world.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Oh, you're sweating, aren't you?
You are weak, aren't you?
You've lost a lot of weight.
You've become so plump.
I'm in a trance.
You're so cute that I want to eat you.
I'm not enough yet.
You still want to be with
me, don't you? I can feel you.
You are so cute.
I can't stop smiling.
I'm so sorry for my voice.
You look like you're suffering.
You're getting really full.
You're about to cry.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
If I let you out, Let me out.
Oh, I'm surprised.
It's very hot.
Oh, it's inside.
Oh, it's hot.
It's thick.
It's out.
But it's not enough yet.
Are you going to
kill me? Come on.
Let's do it more and more.
Come on.