Hey, you can still do it, can't you?
Hurry up and stand up.
Come on.
I'll give you a lot of
strength in your weak spot.
Look, here.
You like it, don't you?
I can feel it, Coco.
I can feel it again.
Are you alive?
Do you feel good to be petted?
Do you like to be licked?
I'll give you a lot here.
Because I love you.
You like to be petted, don't you?
I'll pet you here, too.
It's been a long time, hasn't it, Kako?
Haven't you had enough yet?
Did you miss me?
We still have a long way to go.
Let's do it today.
Can I lick this one too?
Which one do you feel better?
Which one do you like better?
Do you like it?
It's getting harder and harder.
I'll make you feel better and better.
Do you like neck?
It's good, isn't it?
You drank a lot.
Ah!
I'll make your ears wet.
It's easier to put it in, isn't it?
Oh, it sounds so good.
Oh, it's getting hot here.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this,
so I'm a little nervous,
but I'm sure it'll be fine.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Look at me.
I'm going to cry again.
I feel good.
Oh, it's terrible.
I really hate it.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, my legs are going to stop.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
How do you feel? It's cold.
How do you feel? I'm cold.
Let's go.
I can see you well.
It's the best!
Ah, it feels so good!
Your heartbeat is the best!
I'm going crazy.
My stomach feels good.
What are you doing?
It seems that the signal
has reached the threshold.
It's going to the end of the world.
It's strange.
Oh, this is good.
I'm going to go again.
I can't. I'm going to go.
How do you feel?
I can't see where the water is.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Can I just take one step ahead?
Let's go this way.
Oh, this place feels good.
Just one step ahead?
I think it's too narrow.
Don't you think so?
Ah!
Look! I'm still open.
I'm going to go.
Ah!
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hang in there.
Please.
No, I can't let you go yet.
You've been patient.
That means it's about time for me to go.
I put it in my throat, so you
can put it in my stomach, too.
It's okay. Don't be patient.
Put it in my stomach.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, you're out.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you're kissing me.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm not sure if it's because I've
never seen a cat like this before,
but I think it's because I've
never seen a cat like this before.
Now, let's move on to the next one.
I want to eat a little bit.
I'm going to do a little bit of a massage.
Please forgive me cuz I can't do
any harm to the kitten in this video.
Does the kitten feel good?
It's so much fun watching you.
I'm glad you like it.
I'll be always happy to hear that.
I love you.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I'm very happy
to see a cat like this.
I'm glad to see a cat like this.
Ah
I feel good
You have woken up
Oh, you touched my hips I
feel good You touched my hips
I'm sorry You touched my neck
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll make your ears wet.
I'll make your ears even wetter.
Look at the inside of your ears.
You can see it, right?
It's great, isn't it?
Oh, it feels so good.
I feel so good.
Look at her face.
It's so good, isn't it?
I think it's almost the limit.
I'll do it more intensely.
She's still sleeping.
You're going to sleep a lot.
Wow!
You have a lot of hair.
You can still do it,
right? Let's do more.
Yes.
Do more.
You can still do it, can't you?
This time, I'll make you
move and make you feel good.
I'll give you a lot of kisses.
It's intense.
I can't get up.
I can see a lot of your body parts.
Young men are good.
You are very energetic.
You have a lot of muscles.
You have a lot of physical strength.
We can do this.
We still have a long way to go.
Give me more.
I want you to follow me more.
Wait for me.
It's intense.
I'm sorry.
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... More... More... More... More...
Oh, it feels good.
Put your tongue out.
Give me a kiss.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm getting stiff.
I can't open my mouth.
Let me go.
Hey, are you going to go again?
You can't go yet. Hang in there.
Oh, my turn is left.
I'm a fan of your channel, so I'm
going to put a video of me kissing you.
Oh, it's disgusting.
Oh, it's still not enough.
I hope you'll be fine.
Oh, it's dirty.
Oh, it hurts so much.
I'm so sad.
I feel so good.
I'm so happy.
I'm so lonely.
You may fall asleep.
I want to forget.
Oh, it's the best.
I can't do it yet.
Oh, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I can't do it yet.
Does it feel good?
Oh, this is the best.
This is the best sleep
I've ever had in my life.
I'm so sleepy.
This is the best sleep
I've ever had in my life.
Are you hungry? Come here.
Let's sleep together.
It felt good, didn't it?
By the way, you like boobs, don't you?
There is a bubble over there.
Let's use that bubble
and put it on your boobs.
Would you like to touch your boobs again?
Would you like to have more fun?
Is it okay?
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm glad I didn't touch it.
You like it, don't you?
Both of you have a lot of breasts.
How is it?
Which one do you like?
Are your boobs soft?
Which one? You know well.
Come on, look closer.
How is it?
Look at me carefully.
It's so powerful, isn't it?
Put your hand here.
I'm going to give you a massage,
so I'm going to pinch you.
You're getting excited again, aren't you?
Does your hand feel good?
You can feel a lot better.
I'm going to bed now.
I can't sleep.
You look so happy.
You like to drink.
You drink a lot.
It's good, isn't it?
How do you like it?
It's soft, isn't it?
You don't get tired of
it, do you? No, I don't.
Then, why don't you try to
drink each person's boobies?
It's good, isn't it?
Look at me closely.
How is it?
It's soft, isn't
it? It's amazing.
I can feel it.
How is it?
Do you like this boob?
It's getting warm.
It's getting warm, isn't it?
I want to play with you a lot today.
Look at me closer.
How do you feel?
If I crush your face,
you'll stay like that.
You can't breathe, can you?
Well, this time...
Come on.
Wait a minute.
Do you like my boobs?
Are you okay?
You're sucking a lot.
It's soft, isn't it?
You can suck a lot.
You look happy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm going to get closer to you.
I'm going to press your face like this.
I'm glad.
You look so happy.
Your boobs are kissing me.
How do you feel? I'm so happy.
I can't breathe.
But you're excited, aren't you?
You're so energetic.
You are happy, aren't you?
You are excited because
I touched your boob.
Look, you are so fluffy.
You are standing up again.
No matter how much I touch
you, you are still so fluffy.
Does that mean you can still stand up?
You are so energetic.
You are so cute.
We have to cheer up more and more.
You are still quiet.
Are you still quiet?
We have to take everything out.
Hey, sis.
Oh, you don't have to touch my butt?
You don't care about
my butt? Touch it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
My butt is big, isn't it?
My butt is good, isn't it?
I want you to touch my butt a lot.
We will also rub your butt.
Don't go yet.
I have to save a lot.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
You're rubbing a lot.
This will make you feel good.
Do you feel our boobs?
I'll rub a lot for you.
I'm going to play with a cat.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Please enjoy it as much as you can.
Wow, it's wrapped up.
How is it? Does it feel good?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
This is good, too.
You're going to sleep,
aren't you? That's great.
You're getting better.
You like my boobies, don't you?
You like my boobies,
don't you? Yes, I do.
I can feel that you like my boobies.
Let's take a break.
You're going to be out of the bed.
No, I'm still going to be in bed.
Your waist is moving.
I was about to be out of bed.
There's one more person,
right? Hang in there.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
I have to make you sleepy.
Wow!
How is it?
Can you feel the softness?
Wow! It feels good!
I'm going to make it quick.
Oh, you're twitching.
Great.
You're holding back a lot.
How are you feeling?
Do you feel better?
I feel much better.
My boobs feel better.
I feel good.
Wow.
It's getting harder.
Today my husband is playing
with me and I am excited.
The baby is trembling.
I'm getting more and more excited.
It looks so delicious.
I'm going to show you how to get
rid of dead skin cells in your boobs.
It's been a long time since I've had a cat,
so I'm not sure if it's a cat or a cat.
I see.
But it felt good, didn't it?
It felt good for us, too.
I'm glad the three of us were able to come.
Let's come again.
I want to come again.
The three of us again.
I mean, it would be nice if
we didn't have a husband.
It's nice.
I can enjoy it.
I'm glad you don't have a husband, Shiro.
You can have a lot of fun.
Let's continue to be together.