The day of the first meeting
This is a very nice store.
Where do you work? I'm a clerk.
You are very smart.
You haven't changed.
I haven't changed.
Long time no see.
It's been a long time.
This shop is so old.
Long time no see.
It's been a while since I've seen you.
I'm so nervous.
Let's hang out next time.
If you come here, I'll
take you to eat ramen.
I'm fat, too.
No, you're not.
Ramen is for hanging out.
It's not just ramen.
You're drinking, aren't you?
I'm eating good food and
drinking good food, aren't I?
You can't stand it.
Long time no see.
You're still wearing it?
Yes.
Really?
What's going on?
It's Shun, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Seriously, why didn't you tell me?
It's Shun, isn't it?
Really?
Since before?
You guys knew it, didn't you?
Why didn't you tell me?
I finally knew it when I got a call today.
Really.
Is anyone else coming?
Tanaka?
Tanaka can't come today because of work.
And then, Yoshino
couldn't get in touch with us.
And then, Himori is coming.
He is going back to Tokyo.
Well, everyone, let's order
a drink and have a toast.
Oh, beer.
Himori was a little late.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers!
This is delicious.
It's been a long time,
but we're drinking again.
Cheers! I'm sorry.
Don't overdo it.
No, no, I won't.
I'll keep going.
Don't choke on it.
Don't overdo it.
How is it? It hurts.
It hurts a lot.
You drank a lot, didn't you?
Well, it's been only two years
since we graduated from DOSO.
That's right.
I met Nishino yesterday.
It's been a long time.
Who came up with the idea of this video?
I met him at the spirit ceremony.
We talked about meeting again.
I see.
Thank you.
Let's have fun.
It's good.
Don't push yourself too much.
I'm fine.
Let's order something else.
I'm 20 years old now.
Thank you.
Do you want to
challenge? Sounds good.
So, when did you start dating?
I'm going to ask that.
You didn't have a girlfriend
in high school, did you?
You didn't have one, did you?
I've had one since I graduated.
Oh, I see.
I see.
I knew it.
You knew it? Yes, I knew it.
Why?
You didn't know him,
did you? No, I told him.
Right?
I didn't know that either.
Did you know him? I knew him.
Why didn't you tell me that you knew him?
You knew him, didn't
you? I knew him.
I'm the only one
who didn't know him?
You knew him?
Did you know Kanda?
Where did you hear it from?
I heard it from the camera.
You heard it from the
camera? Why? I'm sorry.
I was wondering where to go.
Are you taking a break from high fever?
But... But...
I've been on a break
from the reunion today.
Yes.
What? Really?
Really?
Yes.
I don't have enough people to come.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Well, let's drink again soon.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you when I get there.
Okay.
I'll call you.
Take care.
Thank you.
See you later.
Good luck.
I'll call you.
Thank you.
Bye.
Cheers!
Let's get excited for them!
I think this is a book of Sumi Shogi.
It's like a book of Nantezumi.
How many Nantezumi do you have?
Wax? No, there are thousands of them.
Really?
It's really wax.
It's really difficult.
It's like the one you sell
becomes a painting in the end?
Yes.
It's like a beautiful accumulation.
Masamushi? You're late.
Where are you?
Turn right there.
There it is, right? Yes, there.
Wait.
I feel like I'm
in love with you.
Who is it? Himori.
He's coming soon.
Himori.
Himori is coming soon.
I heard he's coming.
I didn't know him.
It's been 2 years.
I don't know him.
I don't know anyone.
Where is he from?
University?
He's not from here.
It's hard to recognize his name.
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Oh, you're here.
Long time no see.
You're late.
That's right.
You haven't changed much.
Can I go to the bathroom?
You can go to the bathroom.
There's still some food left, so go ahead.
Long time no see.
It's good.
This is my favorite.
That's good.
It looks delicious.
It's almost gone.
It's been a long time.
It's true.
You don't contact me at all.
I'm sorry.
I'm quite busy studying.
Are you self-taught?
No, I'm not self-taught.
Did you go to university
today? Yes, I did.
It's a big school.
It's amazing.
It's a souvenir of Kyoto.
What about tea sweets?
Tea sweets?
I wanted a matcha donut.
It's a fat trigger.
It's a fat trigger of Kyoto.
It's like a candy.
I've never been to Kyoto.
Really?
Did you go to middle school?
Middle school?
Where did you go? Kamakura.
Really?
I was surprised.
Kamakura is good.
Long time no see.
How have you been?
Himori-kun seems to be
working hard at university.
Well, it's not just that the
Department of Law is attending a
lecture, but it's not good if the
score of the exam is not high.
I see.
It seems that you are dating Sekine.
Well, we just started dating.
I see.
I wish I could meet you, Sekine.
I know.
You don't have a girlfriend,
do you? No, I don't.
I'm not in the right place at the moment.
I don't think so.
You've changed.
Have I?
For example? For example.
..
I don't know.
I don't know what I'm good at.
By the way,
your face is red.
Did you already do that?
Really?
I wonder if it's easy to do.
You look embarrassed.
It's embarrassing.
Hey, let's take a picture together.
What?
Let's take a picture.
Really?
Yes.
We are going to start the game.
Oh!
Yeah!
Did you get it?
OK!
One, two, three!
Yeah!
Please be more serious, everyone.
You look like you are having fun.
I want to get it too.
You are the one who is responsible.
Kanta, take it properly.
Take it, you.
Don't shake it.
Timing.
Are you really taking it?
Kanta, you're shaking a lot.
You're shaking a lot.
Iketani, you look cool.
Turn it around.
Turn it into a group.
I'm going to send this to the group.
You can take a break.
What's that?
It's really pink.
This is sour.
I have to drink all.
You left a little.
Don't look at me.
Are you OK?
You are shaking.
Your face is red, too.
Let's have a break.
Let's wrap it up.
Let's go.
Don't push yourself too hard.
It's the last day.
Can we go home? Yes, we can.
Who will go with us? Be careful.
Hey, Hibiki.
Hibiki, are you leaving?
Come back soon.
What about you, Himari?
Me?
I want to show my face to my family.
So, I'll go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there.
I'll go to Kyoto next time.
We are going to Tokyo University.
OK, then, let's go to the second floor.
See you.
Are you OK? I'm OK.
Thank you.
Are you OK?
How about everyone?
Everyone?
We are going to the second floor.
I see.
I don't have to go to Himari-kun's house.
I don't want to go.
I see.
Yes.
By the way,
I'll send you home.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
My last train...
Oh, I don't have a last train.
I see.
Your house is in Oizumi, isn't it?
Hmm... What should I do?
I think I should go to the bathroom.
I don't know what to do.
Get a grip.
I'm going to lose my train of thought.
I see.
I don't have any time to enjoy myself.
I don't have any money for my family.
What should I do?
Should I stay at a hotel?
What?
I heard that the hotel in front
of the station is quite cheap.
Hibiki, do you want to stay there?
No, I don't have that much money.
I don't want to stay there.
It's OK.
I have enough money for two rooms.
Oh.
Why is there only one room?
Well, it's the weekend,
so it's good to have a room.
That's true.
It's impossible to take a taxi from here.
Here, drink some water.
Hirori-kun, aren't you drunk?
What? I'm drunk, but you're over it.
That's true.
What? What? Nothing.
So?
What are you going to do?
Do you want me to explain
the situation to you? No, no.
It's not good.
I don't want to be misunderstood.
I'm your ex-boyfriend.
I'm going to sleep here.
Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry.
I usually sleep on the sofa.
Don't worry about me.
You look like you're sick.
Hey, Himori.
You can use half of the bed.
You don't have to use it.
But...
It's really bad.
I'll give you half of it.
Thank you for your hard work.
You really helped me.
You can give birth today.
Oh, really? OK, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
You're welcome.
You don't have to answer the phone.
I'll call you later.
He's not answering.
I guess he's already gone.
Hey, Morimoto.
Are you done with work?
It's 2 o'clock now.
You should come too.
Yeah.
Oh, is Ren there?
Huh?
I think he went home for the anniversary.
Oh, and Himori went home too.
What?
Just the two of you?
Kizu? I don't know.
I didn't notice you.
By the way, Ron is here. Come on.
Hey.
You said...
I've changed.
In what way?
Were you worried about me?
I wasn't calm before.
I feel calm now.
I didn't feel so calm.
Is that the reason why we broke up?
That's another story.
When I was with you,
I had a lot of fun.
Also, you were so sexy.
I wanted to have a normal date.
You said you didn't want
to because you like me.
I didn't want to make you do it.
Thank you for telling me.
I'm still in love with you, so I can't help it
I can't stand it.
Hibiki, lend me your hand.
It's difficult.
I won't do it like I did before.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Don't you throw up?
It's been a long time, so I'll throw up.
I'll throw up.
Of course, I'll definitely
keep it a secret.
I'll throw up.
I can't do it.
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
I'm going to take a bath.
It's okay.
It was very pleasant.
Really?
It was very pleasant, wasn't it?
You are not good at it.
Did you change your mind?
I don't know yet.
I want to make you feel good.
I really like you.
I love you.
You are so beautiful.
I was petting him all the
time, but he didn't bite me.
He became more beautiful.
May I bite you? Here you are.
I put a lot of food on your face.
You are a cat with a big belly.
You put a lot of food on your face.
Do I?
Yes.
I think it's a good idea to do that.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
You want it so much, don't you?
It's cold, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I put my tongue out.
I put my tongue out here.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to
put it in? Massage.
It's hard, isn't it?
It's not the same as before.
It's much stronger than before.
This one is too strong.
No, no, no! Oh, it's sour.
If you keep breathing
like that, it will come out.
I didn't force you.
Stop breathing. It will come out.
No, it will come out.
This video was taken in August 2020.
Don't shake your hips.
I'm sorry.
Would you like to read this?
You read this? Wait, wait.
What is this? Wait, wait.
Ah! Ah, ah.
Ah, ah.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't feel good.
I was able to get a lot of sleep.
I was able to sleep well.
I had been sick for a few days.
But when I got back
to my room, I felt better.
I'm glad to see you're doing well.
I hope you'll do well.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was drunk and fell asleep.
I'm at home.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Good morning.
Hibiki...
Why did you choose me?
Why...
I have to go home.
It's delicious, isn't it?
This is a video of me when I
was pregnant with my first child.
I was pregnant with my first child.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Don't you want to do it?
I want to do it,
but... Then, you do it.
It's a bit gross.
That's not good.
It's gross.
It hurts.
I can't breathe.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Hibiki, it's nothing.
Good luck in college.
Len.
Sukine-kun.