Master, I beg you.
Please make it messy again today.
What do you want me to do? Tell me.
Master, I want you to put in a lot of mud.
It's enough with your fingers.
I can't believe I'm
doing this to myself.
Ah!
This is the third time.
It feels good.
Let's stretch it tomorrow, huh.
Okay.
what are you doing?
Let me see your face.
Look, something is coming out.
Don't let it out.
What is this?
I don't want to do it anymore
Why are you doing this?
It's strange, isn't it?
Your hands are dirty.
You just rub it
No, you shouldn't.
You are funny.
Stop it.
I told you that you are wet.
Hey.
Your hair is wet.
I can't believe I'm doing this...
what's your name?
my name is Tomo.
my name is Muneo.
oh my god what's your name?
my name is Takashi
Don't be angry.
I'm going to put it on your feet.
I'm going to make you beautiful.
What should I do?
You rubbed your own feelings, didn't you?
You're doing it with your feet, right?
It's a little hard.
Come on.
It feels good.
It's warm.
It's time for you to go to bed.
You're a good girl today.
Do you want some?
Yes, I do.
Excuse me.
...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Let me do it.
I told you to lick me!
I told you, didn't I?
You didn't lick me enough.
I'm sorry.
Lick me.
Lick my head, too.
I told you, didn't I?
Lick from head to toe.
Use your whole tongue.
How many times do I have to do it?
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
Yes, is it okay if I put it in your mouth?
Yes, it's okay.
Don't chew on your own.
Look at the camera and talk.
Take a deep breath and stop there.
There's still this much left.
Drink all of it.
Don't you know what it is?
Give me more.
It doesn't feel good at all.
Is it painful?
Are you tired?
Do you understand?
Do you understand, Oku?
I don't want to stop you.
Oku.
Look at the back, can you see?
Who told you to spit?
I don't know.
Keep going.
I didn't tell you to spit.
I told you to look at the back.
I'll help you.
Look at the camera.
I'm filming.
Don't cry.
You're not crying, are you?
Suck it.
You have to wash your hands.
It doesn't feel good
if you don't go this far.
Don't put your teeth up.
What's wrong?
You have a wound on your nose.
It's not good.
You have a wide nose.
It's painful?
You have a lot of vomit here.
You have to go down.
You have no place to put your foot.
Go down.
I'm going to give him a treat.
What's wrong with you?
Your throat is getting wider.
You should spit it out.
You can take it out.
What's wrong?
It's in the bowl.
Let's continue.
I can't help but feel that I'm sick.
I'm sick.
It's so good.
Oh, my God.
Ugh... It doesn't
look like it's working.
I don't know.
It's hard to breathe.
I can't feel my breath.
I don't know who you
are, where are you from?
I'm a Japanese.
Ahhhhhhhhhhh Haaa haa haa
haa haa haaa haa haa What's inside?
haa haa ahh My cosmetic skin.
What is inside?
Foundation.
Inside.
R Moly?
Really inside
ARRRGHHHH AHHHHHHHHHH.
HAaaa haa
HAa Ha.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
oh, oh, oh.
You're here to say good morning.
You're a low-class.
Oh, it feels good.
I don't want to go back
to the old man's house.
Put your butt in.
Open it and put the mannequin in.
I'm so happy!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Ah...
This is raw Chimpo, right?
Was it delicious?
Yes, it was.
I'm in the camera of happiness.
It was delicious.
Raw Chimpo was in it.
I'm happy.
You are so cute.
You are so big.
You are wet.
Can I dry your belly?
Your belly.
You are amazing.
What's wrong with you?
Do you want to go out?
Let's go.
How much did you get?
I got a lot.
There was a lot in the manga.
A guest has come.
Kano.
Yes.
A stranger has come.
What?
It's your new friend.
Is that so?
Be nice to him.
Okay.
Can I call him?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'll clean up and get ready.
Okay.
Do I look good today?
Of course, I'm ready for it.
I have a good reputation, so I
can introduce myself to any guy.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm at the level you can expect.
Really?
What?
Not yet?
He said he'd get ready.
He's taking a shower.
You don't have to take a shower.
He's honest.
It's okay.
It's long.
It's good.
Do you want me to push you?
It's good, isn't it?
Do you want to take a shower?
No, I don't want to.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's all.
I'll take a shower.
Today, I'm going to use you as my pet.
I'm going to let you have a lot of fun.
Are you ready?
Good boy.
Kano.
Please entertain the guests.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to use the toilet.
I'm so sorry I couldn't protect you.
Good boy.
I'm going to massage you.
Do you feel good?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
Let's try to get up.
I'm getting up Nice to meet you.
Daddy is trying to calm her down
Have you been doing your best lately?
What?
What are you doing in the shower?
I think she is still awake
What the hell is this?
You are so dirty.
I'm sorry.
Urgent call from the doctor.
I have a stomachache.
I'm horrible.
You did that on
purpose Don't do that.
I don't want to do that.
What's wrong with you?
Don't do that.
Don't make me angry.
Okay.
You are walking with a limp.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Don't lie to me.
Okay.
Don't cry.
I'm moving my head while I'm licking it.
Yes, that's right.
I move from top to bottom.
I move my head.
I want to be licked.
Yes.
I want to go home.
You have to tell me.
Let me go home.
You don't seem to be in a good mood.
I'm not in a good mood.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I can't help but laugh
when I see him like this.
I'm sorry.
It's not over yet.
The next day.
I'm scared.
You are so beautiful.
Please don't do this.
Please.
I'm begging you.
You don't feel anything inside?
No, I don't feel anything inside.
What's wrong? Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I'm going to take it off.
Take a deep breath
and hold it for a moment.
Oh, my God.
It's alright, honey.
I'll be fine.
Oh, my God.
Why don't you take a break?
I'll be fine.
Oh, my God.
There's so much water.
I'm behind you!
Stop hearing these things on TV.
Wait, there's another bowl here.
Here, wash your face.
I am waiting for the baby to come home.
The baby is crying like a child.
I am trying to calm down the baby.
You don't eat this?
You said so, didn't you?
I did say so.
Don't cry.
What are you doing?
I'm not crying.
What's wrong?
Good girl.
He jumped to the tub.
Good job!
Can you see the burp?
Are you burping?
Look at this.
Aren't you burping?
Easy! Don't worry, it's not that bad!
So you don't have to
worry about your scalp.
I'm still warming it.
I don't want to drink it.
It's hot.
You are so good.
I'm gonna get you some water.
You've run a lot of errands, haven't you?
You are still wetting your pants.
Hey, don't wet your pants.
You have a lot of errands to run.
It's hot.
I can't do it anymore.
I told you not to use it.
You can't run away from me.
Open your eyes.
You should look at the audience.
Oh, it's hot.
Something came out.
You should take a bath.
You want to take a bath?
Good boy.
But, you are not taking a bath.
You are not taking a bath.
I'm sorry.
Oh, wow.
Oh, you're coming out.
You don't need to pee, do you?
Don't you need to pee?
No, I don't I can't
hear you I want to pee.
Do you want to pee?
I want to pee No,
I'll give you more.
Do you want me to give you more?
Look, here.
Look over there.
Lift your chin up.
I'm going to take the urinal out.
I think I can do it.
OK.
Don't grab it so hard.
Do you feel pain in your bones?
Hey, you.
What's wrong? Why are you so relaxed?
I'm doing my best.
I'll give you a lot of milk.
I want to use it more.
Go on Walk slowly.
Panting.
Panting Go on the bed Pant your butt Panting
Panting Panting Panting Panting Panting.
If you want to sleep, you have
to stretch your buttocks more.
You want to stretch your
buttocks, so you close your buttocks.
And then, look.
Behind us.
Not yet.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
I can't put it in your mouth.
I've been doing it over and over
again, but I can't stand it anymore.
I don't know if I can
do it if I try it myself.
I don't know.
I'm tired.
Let's try to move.
Can you move?
It's good to be able to do it like this.
Does your tail feel good?
I feel good.
Does your stomach hurt?
It hurts.
I'm glad.
I feel great.
Wow, wow, wow...
hahahahahaha I'm really sorry!
I let you down wow wow wow.
Why are you doing this to me?
hey, hey, don't do that.
You push the back of
the head with your back.
Okay.
And push the belly.
Oh!
I'm so tired!
Don't push.
Oh!
Push in.
And you use the hole.
You can stand up.
I don't feel good.
It's not good because you're young.
I'm going to put a bandage on you.
Waaaaaaaaa!
I accidentally swallowed
the meat... Waaaaa!
A... Oh oh oh oh!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Stand up!
Aaaaaaaaaa!
Aaaaaaaaaaa!
A- Aaaa...
I'm sorry.
You are crazy.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ahh, ahh, ahhh, it's all ticklish.
Ahh, it tickles.
I can't do it anymore.
You fell down, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Let's go home.
Look at me.
Look at this.
I'm taking a picture of you.
What's in your nose?
I have a pimple in my nose.
That's good.
Yes.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It doesn't matter whose pimple it is.
No, it doesn't.
It doesn't matter.
Who are you?
I'm scared.
Are you scared?
Are you happy?
Yes, I'm happy.
You are fine now.
You are coming out from
your mouth You are so cute
You're spitting out the semen
you just took out, aren't you?
I took it out.
Don't waste it.
You can do it.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Move over.
Hurry up.
Move.
I need to ask you.
How do you feel?
How do I feel?
This is not good.
You should do like this.
Ahhhh.
Let's go up to feed her.
Hurry up.
Go up.
Are you okay?
I told you I was going
to feed you, didn't I?
Look.
What's wrong with you?
Look at me.
Open your eyes.
You're so cute.
You're shaking all over.
I'm sorry.
You have a sore throat,
so I'll give you this next time.
Is this okay?
Yes, please.
I'm going to take it out of your throat.
Please don't wet me.
You are going to be a waste of your life.
So, please don't wet me.
Please help me.
He went out.
I put a blue one in there, but it came out.
Thank you.
It's a relief.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't help it. I want something from you.
Why do you want something
from me all of a sudden?
I can't help it, either.
What do you mean?
It doesn't feel good at all.
I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
You've been cute all this time.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm going to take off my panties.
I'm going to take a nap.
You're awake.
You're going to be eaten.
You can't be like this.
You didn't want to push me, did you?
I've got two other people.
We prepared it for you.
Thank you so much.
You have to chew properly
You have to swallow it I'm sorry.
I'm going to pour you some water.
I'm so glad that we are all together.
To the right, to the left, to
the right, to the left, to the left.
I'm sorry.
Can I do anything?
Yes.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious.
Don't cry.
I'm going to rub you
from the front to the back.
Are you happy now?
Let's do something more fun.
You can't see him, can you?
No, I can't see him.
What? What's that sound?
He is groaning.
I want to see him
more He is groaning.
What's so scary about it?
It's just like that.
It's scary, isn't it?
Don't go on your own.
Can you bear it?
I can't.
I'm going to die.
You just got out.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to die.
Oh, you got dirty with water
on your own, didn't you?
Do you want to go over there?
Let's go this way.
Let's do something fun.
There's a bed in front of you.
Come to me while doing this.
Good boy.
You listen to me, don't you?
Can you listen to me?
Can you?
Are you okay?
I can't get up.
Let's get up.
Are you scared?
You want to sleep comfortably, don't you?
Let's take a look.
There are so many people.
Look at everyone's faces.
Look over here.
A lot of people have gathered.
Look at the people around you.
Can't you see?
Why?
Why are you crying?
Are you embarrassed?
We've done a lot of fun
things today, haven't we?
I've prepared something even
more interesting for the end.
Everyone's here for Canon.
You have to say hello here.
I'm Renki Mikuru.
I'm a butcher.
Please let me clean your stomach.
Can you hear me?
I'm a butcher.
Please let me clean your stomach.
You guys did a good job.
Did you do as you promised?
Yes.
Please let me sleep in your arms.
Well,
I'll take care of my Canon.
The baby's crying is so cute.
Give it to him.
Wow.
Everyone, give it to him.
Here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh I would
like you to lick everyone more.
Let's take it off.
It's better, isn't it?
Let's take it off together.
Are you happy?
You're happy, aren't you?
Yes, I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
You're happy, aren't you?
Yes, I'm happy.
I'm going to show you how to drink it.
Do you want to drink it?
No, I don't.
Do you want me to drink it?
Wow, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's a miracle, isn't it?
Both hands are free, aren't they?
It's free, isn't it?
Put your hands together.
Don't play with it.
It's a problem, isn't it?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Come, come, come.
Show me your face.
Yes.
Squeeze more.
Hey, hey.
You are so messy.
I'll let you go.
It's so sweet.
Amazing.
Beautiful.
It's a good thing.
Show me your butt.
This way.
Great.
What's he going to do?
He's going to throw up.
Look here.
Maybe he should throw up in order.
Look at his blood vessels.
Show your blood vessels.
What's going on?
He has a strong immune system.
Show your blood vessels.
He's opening his mouth.
Open it! Open it!
What's in your belly?
My butt is in there.
Where's your butt?
It's in my belly button.
Is it twisted?
Yes.
That's good.
Let's feed you.
Oh, he's feeding!!
They are feeding their babies!!
You guys are really nice!!
Only the ants can eat them.
This shop has a hole that the
ants can open by themselves.
Show it to me!!
This is a mist fan?
Look!!
The ants can open the hole by themselves.
I think that's a good idea!!
Wow, it's round.
Let the ants to approach here, please!!
It's beautiful.
Oh, no.
Lift the chair.
Look this way.
Stick out the chair.
She is drinking milk.
She is holding a milk in her mouth.
Do you want to drink milk?
Yes, please.
She drinks milk.
She is very weak.
It's amazing.
The dog is very careful.
He drank it.
He is going to drink it again.
Turn your face this way.
Look, there's a lot of them.
There's a lot of them.
Look, look, look.
Look at this.
Wow, that's amazing.
Can you move your hand?
Look, look, look.
Look over here.
There's a lot of them, right?
How do you feel?
I'm weak.
Are you happy?
This side, too.
Open your mouth.
To the back.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Look at me.
Look at the camera.
I'm slacking off.
You are a big guy.
I'm sorry.
Let's move that.
Do you want to go in?
That's right.
Good.
He licks at the same time.
That's great.
It's very efficient.
Great!
You have two of them.
Hurry up!
I'll give you a bath.
Look down.
Yes, yes, yes.
Take a breath.
Come closer.
Do like this.
Move your head.
I'm so happy.
Open your eyes.
I'm going to do it while
looking at everyone's nipples.
I'm going to do it from here.
There is a change.
You don't have much experience, do you?
Is it okay to just shovel?
No, I don't want to.
Do you want to do it?
I don't want to go inside.
I can't hear you.
Where do you want the electricity to go?
I don't want to go inside.
Good boy.
I'll give you a treat.
You did a good job.
Don't you need a treat?
Here you are.
Look at the top.
Wow.
It's good up to the eyes.
It's beautiful.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes.
Wow.
It feels good.
Look over there. Look over there.
Look at her.
Everyone is looking.
I'll give you a massage.
I want to be a Butler.
Let's have a massage.
Here you are.
I'll give you a massage.
Oh, it's great.
How do you feel?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's done.
Let me see your belly.
It's warm.
I'm so scared.
It's not over yet.
I'm glad you let her breathe.
I'm going to inject her.
How do you feel?
I feel great.
I'll let you go.
Let's go.
Look at the camera.
Take a good look at her.
I think she has a lot to say.
Thank you very much.
It's not over yet, is it?
There's more to come.
It's painful.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You're great.
I'll put you in the box.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Here you are.
I'm so sorry.
Let's get you out of here.
Get in there.
Let's go.
Lie down.
Put your legs up.
Thank you.
I'll help you.
I'll do my best.
You're doing great.
It's overflowing.
Thank you very much.
Can you keep calm?
Please go back to sleep.
You can keep calm.
I want to go out.
Please go back to sleep.
Tears are coming out... I could
hardly breathe, I was in such a state.
Oh, it's hard.
Are you okay?
No, no, no.
It's okay.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm going to give you a bath.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Raise your hips.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
I will leave the rest to you.
I am sure that the doctor
is going to be happy.
Next, we are going to check the
respiratory condition of Yu-chan.
Ahhh.
Ohhhhhhhhhhh.
Ok, ok.
You're doing great.
I'm sorry.
Kano, how does it taste?
It's good.
Do you like it?
Yes.
You look like you want to spit it out.
Kano, do you want to spit it out?
Yes.
You must be thirsty.
It's true, isn't it?
Yes.
Then, everyone, please.
Please let me out.
More.
Okay.
Let's go.
No more.
I'll leave it here.
It's not enough, is it?
I'll give you more.
Ahhhhh Ahhhhh.
Two more people OK.
Open your mouth.
You have to drink a lot.
This is enough for you to vomit.
Try to vomit.
OK.
You have to drink a lot.
Are you going to vomit?
Drink at the same time as you go.
It's cold.
How was it?
It was delicious.
That's good.
There are still a lot of
people who want to stay here.
I'll take her out.
I'm going to take her out.
Let's go.
Look at this.
Peek in to see if you can see.
Ok, I'm going to put you in the room.
You have a lot of feces.
I'm going to put you in the room.
Do you feel good?
I'm sorry.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Please prepare a warm
towel and make a fire alone.
After warming the fire,
we pull out the firewood...
...and prepare it to cook rice
and dish stock for 4 people.
This is the last stage, which refers
to a point whereblood isughing-alive.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
I don't know.
It hurts.
It hurts!
Ouch ouch ouch It hurts.
That hurts Oh my god
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah.
me I want to see you
move in by yourself.
I can't breathe.
Oh!
Look at the next one.
We're waiting for you.
Turn your face this way.
Come on, hurry up.
We're waiting for you.
Oh, my God!
Put your hips up more and look at it.
Look at it.
Look at the place where it comes out.
You are still turning around.
I'm going to take you out.
It's still too early to get out of bed.
I'm afraid I can't help
it if I have to sleep.
There are still people who want to go in.
I'm sure there are
people who want to go in.
I'll line them up.
Open your legs.
It's getting brighter and brighter.
Thank you very much.
The labor is getting harder and harder,
the pain is getting worse and worse.
There's still a lot of
people who want to go in.
It's too bad.
Oh, no.
Oh, no...
I think my turn is over.
How do you feel?
It feels good.
I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Your back feels good.
Yeah the back feels good.
I'm scared.
I'm going to put it in.
Spread the blanket.
I'm going to die.
I'm so tired.
I'm already in this.
I'm hungry.
Put all the rice in the bowl.
You have to suck it all in.
I gave you a lot.
What's wrong?
The baby is crying.
In addition, a lot of blood
is coming out of this baby.
The baby is suffering from a lot of blood.
The baby is crying.
I'm sorry.
You want it, don't you?
You're shaking, but you're not moving.
Ouch!
You're so annoying.
I'm sorry.
Don't be so stiff.
I don't have it.
Give it to me.
Thank you so much for taking care of me.
I'm so happy that I was able
to give birth to so many babies.
Thank you so much.
Raise your head.