I'm back.
What did you come to do today?
Today?
What did I come to do?
I think I came to have sex.
What do you mean by sex?
Is it okay to have a normal sex?
No.
I want you to take it off.
What?
I'm going to take it off.
Can I take it off normally?
No.
You called me because you
had a purpose, didn't you?
Well... Normally...
I don't want to take it off normally.
It's not normal.
It's not normal, Echi.
What is not normal, Echi?
What does that mean?
I want to be messed up.
Why are you blushing?
You want to be messed up?
Do you want to be loved?
You don't like normal love?
I want to say a lot of
different words than usual.
Can't you do something unusual?
You have a lot of boyfriends, don't you?
People think I'm a pervert.
Can't I say that?
Are you okay with an old man this old?
I think I can do a lot of things.
I see.
What were you thinking when you came here?
Well...
Were you imagining a lot of erotic things?
Well... Well...
I don't think so.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why, but I can't
help but cry when I think about it.
I'm so happy to see you.
You look funny.
Have you ever had a hair cut?
I'm sure you have.
I'll take a video of you.
Do it like you always do.
Like a woman.
Turn to the other side.
Show me your left side.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
You dropped it.
Did you get a shock?
Are you okay with just your fingers?
What are you touching?
I want this.
I want to put it in my mouth.
Can you make it bigger?
Look this way.
I'm filming you.
I wanted to eat it so badly
I wanted to eat it so
badly You kept eating it.
You can eat up to the point
where you want me to feed you.
What are you staring at?
Is it bad, Chinko?
It's delicious.
I want you to give me more.
I want you to give me more bread.
Give me more.
It's strange, isn't it? You can do it more.
Do it as usual.
It's almost there.
You can't eat it, can you?
Stand up.
You have to keep it in your mouth.
You'll spit it out soon.
I'm sorry.
I'll keep it.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Baby, when are you going to grow up?
I don't know.
I'm sure that you'll grow up well if
you get to know more about the world.
I hope that you'll stay active more.
You'll know better that you'll
notice new things as time passes.
Today's video was about a video
I was wondering if I should do.
If you're curious about what happens
next, please watch the next video.
I'll put the link in the description.
Thank you for watching until the end.
I hope you have a nice day today.
I love you.
Bye bye.
Ah a it Ah.
goo.
I can't This is me.
Thank you I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
He is trying to get up.
You are about to jump.
Are you excited?
Are you very excited?
Do you like it?
It's hot.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
What should I do with this?
Well...
You feel good.
I don't want you to show your face.
I'm going to finish it today.
I'm going to finish it.
What?
I don't want to do it.
I want you to hug me.
The baby is crying.
I want to hold her.
Does it feel different?
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
How are you feeling?
Put on something comfortable for you.
There?
Don't step on my waist.
Put it on yourself.
There?
I'll put it on you.
She is so cute.
Can you do that?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
I'm going to put a blanket on you.
I'm going to take a bath now.
I'm going to take a bath.
Can I drink it?
Do you want to drink it all at once?
What does it taste like?
It's a strange taste.
A strange taste?
It's a mixed taste.
What is mixed?
The juice in me and the juice in you.
Do you want to know what it smells like?
It smells like something mixed.
Is it mixed?
You look happy.
Are you satisfied?
Are you going to sleep?
It's hot.
Are you done?
What's that face?
You can't take it anymore, can you?
Hide your eyes.
Can you see?
I can't see.
Maybe this side is lower.
Like this.
Can you see?
I can't see.
Let's play a little more.
You can't see it, but it's fun, isn't it?
This is a fun game.
When you cover your eyes,
your sensitivity will increase, right?
Let's go to the vet.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You don't need a rubber band today, right?
No, she is fine.
She is a baby She is grumbling
You are doing a good job.
Do you want to be massaged?
Yes, I want to be massaged.
You can use as much as you want.
It's very sweet.
I want to give you a massage.
Please give me a massage.
I'm sorry.
It's a bit cold.
You're sweating a lot.
I want you to get used to it.
I can't do it anymore.
You don't have to worry about it.
Don't do it on your own.
I like this sound.
It sounds good.
More, more...
You are tightening it well.
Tighten it more.
I'm sorry.
Are you ready?
Are you okay?
You really wanted to drink, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Don't go without permission.
You haven't gone yet, have you?
Don't go.
What are you trying to do now?
Don't be selfish.
What?
Don't let go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh!
What?
Please help me again.
No, no, no, I won't.
Ah!
I'm glad you are happy.
I know you want to go to the vet.
You don't like it at all.
I'm scared.
I told you not to touch it.
I'll wash your body.
You don't like it at all.
I was able to wash her face clean.
At that time, I thought that she was going
to the bathroom, but I did not notice it.
I washed her body clean
and put her on the floor.
I was surprised that she didn't move.
I'm going to wash my
daughter's face with hot
water, but I can't do
it because it's too hot.
I'm going to wash my
daughter's face with hot
water, but I can't do
it because it's too hot.
I'm going to wash my
daughter's face with hot
water, but I can't do
it because it's too hot.
I'm going to wash my
daughter's face with hot
water, but I can't do
it because it's too hot.
I'm going to wash my
daughter's face with hot
water, but I can't do
it because it's too hot.
In the meantime, in the next video...
I will show you the part
where I will slip on the floor.
In the next video, I will show you the part
where I will get wet in the next video.
Why did you make it so clean?
Why did you make it smell so bad?
There's more over there.
I'll clean it up.
Give me a kiss.
Don't lick my hand.
I feel good.
You can lick my feet, Fubuki.
You can lick my feet.
You can lick my fingers, Fubuki.
I can't do it.
You can do it if you're a
little more concentrated.
I can't do it.
I can't do it I can't
do it I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Look, lick my finger properly.
Use your tongue.
Lick between my fingers.
I can't do it.
You lick me.
What are you doing?
I can't do it.
I told you to lick it cleanly, didn't I?
You can't eat it now.
I can't eat it.
Lick it cleanly.
You have to lick it well.
You want to go to the bathroom?
What are you talking about when
you were just about to be eaten?
You said you wanted to be eaten, but you're
the one who wants to be eaten, right?
Eat it all the way to the end.
I wanted to put it in your mouth.
Eat it all the way.
It's hard, isn't it?
Open your mouth.
You can do it!
The day has come.
He seems to be in a good mood.
Good boy.
Do you feel so good?
I don't want to do it.
I'm going to spread your legs.
You're annoying.
I don't want to do it.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you want me to call the doctor?
I can't do it at all.
I'm fine.
What's wrong?
I think you're a little dirty.
Do you want a new diaper?
I don't want it at all.
Please, dad.
I'm gonna open your legs.
What's this?
Give me your hand.
Don't lie down.
You can't move at all.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
It means that he is about to give birth.
He seems to have a lot of problems.
The baby is crying.
What do you want?
Please give me something to drink.
Where do you want me to put it?
Where do you want it?
Put it in my stomach.
You can do it.
Spread your legs.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
I'm sorry.
You don't have time to rest.
Good boy.
I'm so sorry, I'm such a bad boy.
I'm sorry I don't know
how to be a good boy.
You didn't know how to be a good boy.
You don't know how to be a good boy.
Mama, you love playing
with your neck, don't you?
You're amazing.
You love playing with your neck, don't you?
It feels good.
What's in there?
Mama, it's Chin-chin.
Why are you whining?
Who are you?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You don't know that I'm whining?
You are dead.
Who do you want to be?
Who do you want to be if you are alive?
No, I don't want to be anyone.
You don't want to be anyone, do you?
You are dead.
It's time to take a bath.
You've got a lot of bubbles.
You have a lot of bubbles.
I'm going to give you a new one.
I'm going to get rid of all the bubbles.
What's wrong?
What do you want?
I'm sorry.
You don't know me.
Do you want a seat?
Are you OK?
I'm sorry.
It's so hot.
I'm going to take a shower.
Do you understand?
It's foaming.
It's like cream.
It looks like a flower.
What does it smell like?
It smells like a flower has bloomed.
It doesn't smell.
Let me taste it.
It's sour.
Is it the taste of sage?
It tastes like sage.
I wonder if it's good. It's mixed
too much, so it's a different taste.
It's already out, so push it in properly.
I put it in.
I went to the shower.
How was it?
Did you enjoy it?
Are you happy now?
I'm happy.
As you wish?
Yes.
Don't you want to be happier?
Do you still have more?
I want to be happier.
Then, follow me.
You look good in it.
I don't want to.
I'm hungry.
Put your hand on it.
Turn around.
You don't like it.
Why?
Let's add more people.
I want to add more people.
Okay.
I'll call a lot of people.
How many people?
I don't know.
How many people do you want?
How many children do you have?
Five?
Six.
That's a lot.
Well, it's good to have a lot.
Greed.
It's greed.
You have to prepare for it.
Do you know what preparation is?
You have to stretch.
A lot of things are coming.
You want me to use the
bungee cord, don't you?
Yes.
Then, you have to loosen the bungee cord.
I can't.
You can't?
Then, let's do it.
You look great.
Can you move?
You can't move.
You don't like it?
Ok, let me massage your belly.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm going to take a nap.
He is pulling the string.
His tail is moving on its own.
Do you understand?
He is moving on its own.
What?
I'm sick.
Say it.
Why?
It's hot.
It's going to come out.
I'm sure you feel a tingling
sensation in your stomach.
Say, switch on.
I can't hear you.
Switch on.
Louder.
He's turning around.
Were you sleeping?
Yes, I was.
Did he come?
Did the man come?
Yes, he did.
Did he come?
He woke up.
What's wrong?
Why are you so happy?
Why did you call me?
Because I was waiting for you.
I see.
You haven't finished your exercise.
It's perfect, isn't it?
It's perfect.
Can I call a man?
I won't stand up.
I'll greet you here.
Come in.
You look great.
You're so cool.
What are you doing?
You're showing your boobs.
What do you want to do?
This?
What's wrong?
I want you to put it in.
Do you want me to do it properly?
I want you to put it inside.
Inside?
What do you mean by that?
You want me to put it inside?
I want you to put it inside.
If you do it well,
I'll put it inside.
But you're three, so
I'll let you stay here.
I'll get you in there for you.
I can't get in there.
You can't get in there.
It's still there.
It's still in there.
I thought you were in a bad mood.
You can't get in there.
Don't put it in your mouth.
I want to put it in my mouth.
You can't put it in your mouth yet.
It's not a mouth.
You put it in your mouth.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of hair.
I have a lot of hair on this side, too.
I wonder if it's delicious.
It's getting delicious.
Have a good sleep!
Wǒ!
Er!
It's good, isn't it?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm done.
Nnn!.
Nn-!!
Nnn-!!
It's already over?
You don't look like you're in a good mood.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
What's wrong?
Ouch!
Manko?
You're in there.
What are you saying?
It's Manko Kuchi.
I'm glad you're in there.
You're in the way.
There's more, right?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are big, aren't you?
I want you to eat more.
This is the end of today's video!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's so hot.
The baby is in pain.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Prank!
I'm going to eat it all.
It's painful, isn't it?
I put it in your belly, didn't I?
Why do you put it in
your belly with your hand?
Tie it up.
I can't do it anymore.
Let me go!
He is in a good mood.
How do you feel?
Tell me.
You wanted to be licked, didn't you?
You are being licked.
It's hot.
I'm gonna throw up.
Don't spit it out.
Show me the water in your mouth.
Is there any water left in your mouth?
Do you still have some in your mouth?
Do you want to drink?
Do you want to drink water?
You have a wide mouth.
Now you can eat everything.
What's wrong with you?
Don't overdo it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry It's hot.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Haa... Haa... Haa... Uu... Ah!
Ah!
Haa... Haa... Haa... Haa...
Haa... Haa... I'm sorry.
Ahhhhh.
Ahhhh Derek.
Ahhhh
Ahhhhh.
She is having a mental breakdown.
Is it good?
It's bitter.
What? Is it bitter?
Do you want more?
Yes.
Oh!
Oh!!
Ah!
Urgh!
Oh!
Look over here.
Look at his face, he has a big one
in his mouth Let me see your face.
What's wrong with you?
Come on, give it back, it's a waste.
I'm going to give you this
big one for the last time.
Take it with your belly. Can you do it?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh I'm hungry, I'm hungry.
Show me your mouth.
You can't do it because
you have a weak body.
You have a scar.
It's coming out.
Clean it up.
I don't know why I'm doing this.
He is still a baby.
He is in a bad mood.
I miss him.
I don't want to.
I'm glad.
I'm glad you put it in the bowl.
I don't want to.
You have to say it.
Give me the bowl.
If you don't say it, he won't put it in.
Good evening.
No, no, no, no.
Why?
Look.
You are eating too much.
I ate all.
What?
You ate all.
You are enjoying today.
You are a cute cosplayer.
It suits you.
It suits me.
What's this?
Is this a bra?
It's a bra.
Is it?
Yes, it is.
There's a pocket here, so I
don't know what's in there.
What?
It's not a bra.
It's a bra?
It looks like it's going
to hurt your chest.
Yeah, it looks like it's
going to hurt your chest.
How big is it?
It's big.
It's small.
Everyone is caught up in this cosplay.
Yeah.
You're wearing weird pants.
Is this how you usually dress?
How do you usually do it?
Usually?
When I'm at home, I
don't put it on my tongue.
I don't put it on my brain.
Brain?
Brain bread?
Brain bread.
It's a strange word.
Let me hear it.
What do you want to do?
Ferris wheel Ferris wheel?
In the Ferris wheel?
In the Ferris wheel And?
Where?
Everything.
Everything?
Do you want to do everything?
You don't have much time It's
only about 10 minutes, isn't it?
But you still did it.
I stopped at the top.
It's the top, so I can't see it
because the side is a little down.
You were in a situation
where you wanted me to do it.
Yes.
Where is the thing that comes out?
I hid it.
At that time, I didn't have
tissues, so I had to use my mouth.
You had to use your mouth.
So that's how you made the mistake.
Is there any place other
than the Ferris wheel?
Other than the Ferris wheel...
There's nothing but school.
There's nothing but school?
You're making a mistake in Japanese.
Stairs?
Stairs.
The top floor.
The top floor is not used.
This is the top floor.
You like the top floor.
That's right.
If you go to the top floor,
you will want to do it.
I will be free.
It's not the top floor now.
You don't want to do it?
No.
I'm not the top, but I'm a little worried.
You're the only one.
I'm always worried about the side.
What do you want to do?
I want to be with a lot of people.
What do you want to
do with a lot of people?
I want to get along with them.
So I want to ask them for help.
So you want to stay here.
That's good.
How many do you have? 4 or 5?
As many as I can.
As many as you can?
Don't worry, everyone is getting better.
Look at this.
I'm going to give you a peck.
You're getting better.
Let's have everyone out.
Nana, how are you?
I called you a lot today.
I have a lot.
You did your best.
It's a reward.
How many boys do you have?
Four.
I have one.
That's good.
Do you want to lick it?
OK.
Look at this.
If you lick it a lot,
it will get better.
What are you going to do?
Do you want to put it on the table?
You want to put it in your mouth?
I want to put it in my mouth.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
You want to put it in your mouth?
It's too early.
I have it.
You were happy when I put it in your mouth.
You have a lot of it.
You have it.
You are good at it.
You are comparing the taste.
Everything is good.
Which one do you like more?
Which one?
You have a good face.
Hold this for a moment.
No, I don't want it.
You don't want it?
Be careful, be careful, be careful.
I'll put it in front of your eyes.
Do you want it?
I don't want it.
I'm going to give it a try.
Are you tasting it?
I have to taste it.
It's raw.
It's very slimy.
Do you know it's raw?
I'm scared.
You can't be so serious
because you're still tasting it.
You can't be so serious.
Do you want to taste another one?
Yes.
It's a taste.
I want to taste this one too.
How is it?
It's good.
What?
Let's go to the next one.
This one is good too.
Let's go.
Next.
It feels good.
It's not Ajin's face, but
isn't it really Ajin's face?
One more.
It's amazing that Ajin's legs are so open.
It hurts.
You are being turned around.
I wanted to be turned around.
As you can see, everyone is
doing the same thing to you.
Don't do that.
You shouldn't do that.
You are Ajimi.
I'm just giving you a drink.
Everyone is in such a small room.
There are so many kids in the room.
It's so small.
I know.
Let's go to the other side.
You should wear
blindfolds at the same time.
OK.
Wait a minute.
I can't see.
Let's go to the large room.
Sit down.
Everyone wears the hands of the head.
You can wear the hands of the head.
It's dangerous.
Do you want to go inside?
Do you want to go in slowly?
Yes, slowly.
Push him out.
Let's sit here.
What's inside?
Which one was the first one?
Do you know?
The first one.
Oh, you know.
Let's sit here.
Where?
Where is it?
You can sit on this
bed if you don't like it.
I can't see it.
It's okay. You can't see it
because you cover your eyes.
Your sensitivity will increase, right?
He likes to be petted.
You have very wide legs.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
You wanted to poop a lot, didn't you?
How do you feel?
You don't have to hold your pee?
It's like...
What's wrong?
Everyone... You're
doing your best.
It's like...
What's wrong?
I feel like there are a lot of dogs.
It's like... It's like... It's
like... I don't want to do it.
How is it? Are you having fun?
I'm having fun.
I'm having more fun than before.
You're doing your best.
No, I'm not.
I'm going to lick your butt.
I'm going to lick you.
Where do you want me to lick you?
Where?
I want you to lick where I say.
I'm going to lick you.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Please lick me gently.
Four boys are licking you.
What's wrong?
Please lick my necklace.
Everyone is licking your necklace.
I feel like my hands are full.
What?
Let me see.
Let me take your blindfold off.
He's sleeping.
I was surprised.
It's better to have a lot of babies.
I was surprised because
I had too many babies.
Kizu, are you surprised?
I think some of you are
meeting him for the first time.
Come here.
You have to say hello to everyone.
You have to say hello.
What's your name?
My name is Nana.
This is my mom.
She is so cute.
What did you come here to eat today?
I came here because I wanted to eat a lot.
What do you want to eat?
Tell me.
I want to be turned around by a lot of men.
You want to be turned around?
And?
Mama's poo.
Mama's poo?
What are you going to do with it?
I want you to put it in.
Where do you want to put it?
What do you want?
I want you to put it in my mouth.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to put it in your mouth.
If you say it once, I won't
put it in your mouth later.
You can take it out.
You don't need a rubber band?
No rubber band.
You all got it.
You can use it raw.
I like it raw.
You can get a lot.
You like it raw.
I like it raw.
I want to touch it.
Do you want to be messed up?
Say it to everyone.
Please mess me up.
Do you understand?
Is this enough?
Please mess up Uchiyo and Nagao.
Let's play a game together
because there are a lot of people.
I don't want to do it anymore.
You don't need a skirt anymore, do you?
It looks good on you.
You look really good without a skirt.
I'll give you a gift.
Do you want me to lift you up?
Yes, yes, yes….
He is licking his baby's belly.
It's good, isn't it?
He is enjoying it, isn't he?
Look!
He is licking his baby's belly.
There are still many people
who want to lick their belly, right?
He is licking.
Let me lick your belly.
I'm going to lick your neck.
Show me your neck.
Do you want to lick your buttocks?
She loves her buttocks.
Let me see your buttocks.
Your butt is also... No!
No!
You were in a high place
a while ago, weren't you?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I'll pick it up.
I'll screw it in.
It's so close.
Good boy.
He is very energetic.
Look at his buttocks.
Where are you being licked?
On my butt.
There are many people who
want to be licked, so let's take turns.
What's wrong with your butt?
You want more, don't you?
You want to eat more, don't you?
I'm here!
You're here!
There are so many.
Look at her face.
She is standing on a man's leg.
It feels so good.
There are so many.
There are so many, so let's take turns.
Let's lick all of them.
I'll lick all of them.
It's good.
Is it good?
I'm going to cry.
There are a lot of them.
It feels good.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm hungry.
Let me taste it.
Who is going to eat it?
Hold it.
It's going to get cold.
I'm sorry.
I want you to eat this.
This and this.
Your face is covered with chimpanzees.
Look at the side camera.
How do you feel?
How do you feel with a lot of chimpanzees?
What do you think?
Are you happy?
Yes.
That's good.
Talk to me.
It's broken.
Oh, it's wrinkled.
Oh, it feels good.
I've never made you eat so much at once.
Taste it.
It feels good.
I'm sleepy.
You are sleepy.
I want to go to bed.
I'm sleepy.
Have you finished drinking water?
It's delicious.
It feels good.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with your face?
You're getting bigger.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Where's the sofa?
Look, look, look.
Who wants to drink?
Can I drink?
Let's do it.
Open your mouth.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Look, look.
Please do it one by one.
Oh, great!
I'm glad that you drink it.
Wow, you are pulling the string.
Wow, it's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
There's a better one than your finger.
Do you want it?
Do you want this?
It's raw.
It's good.
I'll put it on.
Can I go in?
It's a bear.
I'm going.
I'll take it out.
Help me.
You are still breathing.
He is coming out.
He is still breathing.
The dog is showing its face.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
Yes, it is.
Did you want me to do more?
More?
It's not enough yet.
It's cold.
I'm so embarrassed.
You're so embarrassed.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
You want more and more, don't you?
Here it comes.
We don't have any toys for you.
You don't need toys, do you?
No, I don't.
You don't need toys?
What's wrong?
There is something wrong with your butt.
Please try again.
Pull your butt a little more.
Hold your butt in.
Did you say it?
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, he's gone.
He's gone.
He's shaking.
He's mixed up.
He's tired.
He's got a pain in his butt.
He's a little more up.
You can finally see the inside of the room.
It feels good.
The next person is waiting for you.
Come in.
This is a penguin.
Wow!
You've grown a lot.
You're going to the hospital?
Thank you.
She's out of the hospital.
She's going to get out.
Oh, ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Ah, it's warm.
Oh, it feels good.
I'll put a lot inside.
Uh, Mom, please put this in.
I'll put it inside.
Inside.
Oh, it's going.
Aah.
They are taking
stretches to reduce fatigue.
It's too hot.
It feels good.
It's slippery.
I'm massaging her hip joints.
I'll massage the back of her neck.
You are back!
How do you feel?
Do you feel like you
are being carried around?
It's the best!
You are being carried around, aren't you?
I'm just going to sleep.
You can't sleep
You are a good girl.
It's good to put a lot of
sauce in the dumpling, isn't it?
I'll try to make it a big dumpling.
Feels good, right?
Ah!
I'll try to tighten your belly.
You're having a hard time.
Ah!
Does it taste good?
Are you enjoy?
Yes!
Are you enjoying?
Can you see it?
Can you see it from below?
You can see it in full view.
Wow!
It's amazing.
Oh, you can see it well when you zoom in.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Don't do that.
You want something in
your mouth, don't you?
You're thirsty, aren't you?
Do you want me to give
you something to drink?
What do you want?
Juice.
You want juice?
Then I'll give it to you.
Please give me juice.
Give him a treat.
Don't open your mouth.
I can see you have a lot of it.
You can't drink it yet.
You are too energetic.
Open your mouth.
Don't spill it.
I wonder if there's
anyone else who can do it.
You want to fill your mouth, don't you?
Don't spill it.
I'm going to go in a little more.
Let's go.
Come forward.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Can't you let it out?
Okay.
Drink it in your mouth at
the same time as you go.
Okay.
It will follow you from below.
Oh, it's hot.
How does it taste?
It's fishy.
It's fishy and delicious.
It was good, wasn't it?
I'm glad I can take care of him.
He's still a baby, so I
have to take care of him.
I'm going to put him in the room.
It's a little hard, but I don't mind.
I found a lot of hair on the floor.
It's also a little hard,
but I'm glad I use it.
I'm trying to make it look like a baby.
I'm going to take it off.
It hurts.
Put your hand on the back.
I'm going to take it off.
Oh, you want to go down, don't you?
There's more.
Oh, you're so fluffy.
Oh no, you're going to slip.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
You are licking him.
You have a lot of sebum on your face.
Sometimes, you see, you
have a lot of sebum on your face.
Let's go.
Look down.
Look, there is a pee.
Do you like it?
Are you happy?
What is she saying?
What are you doing?
It's okay.
What's wrong?
The cat is very happy
to be able to see its mom.
I'm worried about her.
The cat has a lump on her face.
Wow, amazing.
I'm going to put her back.
The cats are lined up.
Let's go to the back.
You can't go there.
Let me open the door for you.
It's hot, isn't it?
Let me close the door for you.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot.
It's overflowing.
Let's go.
I'll show you.
Look at this.
Wow.
Oh, I see.
It's about to leak.
What?
I'm sorry.
Is it leaking?
It's leaking.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels so good.
It's leaking.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a look at this.
Look back.
What's this?
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
It feels so good.
Ah!
Aik!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
20 seconds left.
Ah, feels good.
My nose feels really good.
Ah!
Aik, that's enough.
Let's go.
Can you see it?
It's amazing.
Now, you can close the lid.
Don't let the water out.
Let's check how much
seeds are in the earth.
Don't let the water out.
No, no, no, no.
A little more.
I can see it now.
I think it's a little higher.
I'll put it in this hole.
There are people who squeak all day, right?
You can see it around you, right?
They say they want to put it out.
I'll put it out.
Please add more water.
Where do you want it to be?
In this hole.
In this hole, right?
Close your eyes and put it in.
Please close your eyes and put it in.
It looks like it's going to spill.
Did it spill?
It's been a while since I've had a bath, so
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
How many baths did you have?
I had three baths.
You look like a healthy brother.
I'll cut your hair.
It's coming off.
It's not coming off at all.
I don't think it's coming off.
You can push it.
Try it.
It's coming out.
It's a lump.
It's like a lump.
This is the last one.
It's coming out.
Wow, amazing.
One more time.
Pull yourself together.
Wow, amazing.
It's coming out and in.
It's a surface tension.
Wow, amazing.
If you laugh, it will come out.
Oh, it's spilling.
It's heavy.
Touch it now.
You can touch him now.
He comes to me when I laugh.
He is trying to hide his face.
It's been a long time.
He is getting smaller.
Don't spill it.
How was it today?
How was it?
I'm happy.
You wanted to do it with
a lot of people, didn't you?
I'm happy that my dream came true.
Yes.
You wanted to be loved by everyone.
You wanted to be loved, didn't you?
I'm glad your dream came true.
Yes.
Tomorrow again?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
You have to get more people tomorrow.
Yes.
You're greedy.
Thank you so much for giving
me a lot of energy and love.