I'm going to buy a new camera.
Hey, I've been waiting for you.
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting for you.
What's this?
Oh, I know what this is.
I bought this.
Did you buy a new one?
Yeah.
It's this small.
It's so small.
It's already taken.
How much can you take?
Do you want to see it?
I want to see it.
Wow, it's pretty good.
Wow!
It's like a vlog.
What are we doing today?
Since we bought this,
we are going to take a walk.
A walk?
OK.
You look sexy today.
Don't I look cute today?
You look cute.
Can you see my shoulders?
Yes.
We are not going to take a walk.
It's like going to a club, isn't it?
That's right.
I feel like a party person.
Have you been playing recently?
I've been playing a lot recently.
What kind of play have
you been doing recently?
I drink at a club and play with everyone.
I'm taking it home.
Taking it home.
It's the opposite.
My rank is going down.
Are you okay?
Because you didn't meet me.
I'm busy.
Didn't you forget about me?
No, I didn't.
That's good.
Let's go.
Let's walk to the hotel.
I see.
Do you want to do it?
I want to do it.
Just like this.
Just like this?
Here?
Now?
Did you do anything good recently?
Anything interesting?
What do you mean?
Something funny?
Something erotic?
Something like a romantic monster?
Do you do something about it?
I don't do anything about it.
On the other hand,
I don't come here often,
so I go from here.
I have a lot of space in
the strike zone, It's so big.
I think it's okay for anyone.
I think it's tough if you don't
have a strong desire to win.
Even if I drink alcohol,
I feel like I'm full.
Do you still go to izakayas?
I go to izakayas.
I drink a bottle of beer.
Don't you drink raw beer?
Why don't you drink beer?
I like beer, but I don't like fresh beer.
I like the freshness of beer.
You'll be thirsty when you're done.
I'll be thirsty.
Let's drink around here.
I want to drink.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Don't you need to go to the bathroom?
You peed, didn't you?
I want to do it.
Let me take it off.
Do you want to put this in?
Do it hard.
It's painful.
That's all.
How do you feel?
Strong.
Sweet.
Look at her.
You look like a baby with a stomachache.
It's hard to walk, isn't it?
Are you okay?
It's better to walk normally.
Let's stop it once.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Did you stop?
Do you hate this?
I don't hate it.
But I was nervous.
You look serious.
I thought you were relaxed.
No, I'm not relaxed at all.
Look at this.
It's cute.
There are a lot of people.
I can't.
No, no.
No.
You can go while people are watching.
No, no.
Look, people are watching.
You can go.
You can say, Happy
Maru's crotch is full of vibes.
No, no.
Say it.
Say, my dog has vibes.
You can say that.
No.
You don't say it?
Show me your face.
Why are you so naked?
It's hot.
What?
I'm thirsty.
You're thirsty?
I told you to drink something.
What's wrong?
I see.
Look up.
You were there, weren't you?
I'm stuck.
Can I stop you?
What?
No.
Why?
Why are you behind me?
What's wrong?
I'm stuck behind you.
It's wet.
Is it wet?
Underpants?
Yes.
I can't do it.
I'll leave it.
I have to wash it properly.
I'm desperate.
Don't push me.
No.
I thought you would push me.
I thought you were going to bite me.
Don't bite me.
You are cute.
I took a good picture of you.
It's difficult.
Wait a minute.
I can't do this.
Did it stop?
It stopped.
Didn't it stop?
Did it stop?
No?
What?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
No, it stopped, didn't it?
No, it didn't.
Did it break?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
It stopped.
Did it stop?
That's good.
It was good.
This is...
It's my own, isn't it?
I can't hear you.
Here we go.
You must be tired.
Yes, I am.
How was it today?
I was so nervous.
Were you?
Yes, I was.
But...
I think there was something missing.
What was it?
What about you?
I had to be quiet, so I
couldn't do anything intense.
I wish I knew.
What?
It would be bad if someone came.
I'm relieved.
Let's do this.
It's done.
It's awesome.
I was surprised because
you took it out suddenly.
I was surprised.
You may be sweating a lot.
You're right.
I still have a little taste left.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You can finally make a sound.
I don't know why, but I feel like
I'm going to die if I keep doing this.
You are a good boy You are
a good boy Give me your paw.
Good boy Give me your paw You
are a good boy You are so clingy.
You make a weird sound.
Happy Marunee-zuki is so good.
It's better than putting it in a manko.
Really?
This is good enough.
No?
I don't want to.
Add some more.
Let me drink a lot That's right.
Oh, oh, oh.
It was painful, wasn't it?
You were terribly muddy, weren't you?
I was muddy, wasn't I?
Look, look,
Why don't you be my friend?
After this,
we will go to Sanpichi.
I want to do it.
You want to do it, right?
Let's call her.
She might be around.
Really?
Can you call her right away?
I think so.
Let's call her.
I'll call her.
Hello?
Hello? Can you hear me?
It's me. Hello? It's me.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
About that...
What's up?
I got a girl's permission.
Where are you now?
Shinjuku?
Do you know where the usual hotel is?
Call me when you get there.
Call me.
The woman wants to change.
Hello?
Brother?
Do you want to play with me?
Let's play!
Yes.
Hello?
Can I come in?
Come quickly!
Let's play!
What do you think he is doing now?
I don't know.
Hello?
Hurry up and come.
I'm sleepy.
I'm still cold.
What am I doing now?
Uh... Uh...
Mr.Taniguchi, let's do it.
I'm waiting.
No.
Bye-bye.
Ah… Ufufu.
Ah….
Ah, feels good Ah!
Ah… Ah….
Ah….
Ah, it's so nice to be able
to sleep in my own bed.
Ah, I'm getting bigger and bigger.
Ah, it feels so good.
Awesome.
This is terrible.
I feel sick.
Wow.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Pant... pant... Pant...
Your waist won't stop, right?
It won't stop.
What?
Pant... pant...
Pant... pant... Pant...
Pant... It's uncomfortable.
I'll give you my hip pads.
Pant, pant, pant...
You can use them a lot.
You can use it a lot.
Can I use it a lot?
Yes, you can.
You are scared, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
He is still in a bad mood
He was in a bad mood a while ago.
He is in a bad mood.
He is in a bad mood
He is in a good mood.
Is he your friend?
Really?
I think she's coming.
I think she's over there.
Really?
Should I call her?
I'll call her.
Just like this?
When is she coming?
She's coming.
Here you are.
Me?
Go, go.
Nice to meet you.
This is my friend.
Say hello.
I want you to do a lot of things for me.
Can I do it?
Yes.
Yes, you can.
Can I?
I've been waiting for you.
I'm scared.
I can't help you.
You smell like sweat.
You didn't think so, did you?
I love the smell of sweat.
I'm going to sleep.
You can do it.
I want to sleep.
Happy, you are the brother of the phone.
Oh, it's very intense.
Oh, it's close.
How did you feel when you heard the
voice on the phone and saw the video?
It was a little different.
What kind of image was it?
I thought he was a little kind.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was excited because
you suddenly hit me hard.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
You can't eat it.
Great.
Chin Chin.
Treasure found.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Ouch!
Who said it's okay?
It's not okay.
Really?
No?
No.
I told you no.
I'll use this.
You don't mind, do you?
Ouch...
Oh my god...
Good girl.
I feel good.
I feel like I've been in heaven.
I can't.
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
I can't believe I'm doing this to you.
I'm doing this to you.
I feel good.
I feel good because I'm doing this to you.
It hurts.
What's wrong?
what's up?
What's up?
No, I'm fine.
Do you want me to stay this way?
You want me to stay like this, right?
Open your eyes wide and show me your face.
Do you want to sleep?
I want to sleep.
I told you to sleep.
Give me a kiss.
Hi hi Ah ah ah ah eh.
Ah yeah ah.
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Hahaha Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, it is not good.
No!
I'm going!
Good boy.
You are a good boy.
Happy, look at the camera.
What are you doing?
Tell me.
What are you doing in
the middle of the night?
I'm taking a shinko.
What kind of shinko?
Shinko.
Whose shinko?
My friend's shinko.
Oh, your friend's shinko.
Is it your first time seeing him today?
Yes, it is.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I'm not feeling good.
It hurts! It hurts!
I'm a little tired, so let's go to bed.
Where am I?
I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
You can use it right away, right?
Yes.
Oh!
It's not wet.
No.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Wow.
I'm going to put your favorite
chimpanzee in your mouth.
You have to clean your mouth like this.
Yes.
You have to stand up straight.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
If you do it properly, you can
put the chimpanzee in your mouth.
I understand.
I'm going to sleep.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
I'm going to put the
medicine, so be careful.
Don't cry.
I'm going home.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
I'm going to sleep.
What's wrong?
What do you want to do?
You're saying it's okay to say it?
You're going to leave it to me?
Let's just say it.
I'm sorry.
She is crying.
I'm going to sleep.
I put the bed in the back.
Great.
Good boy.
You are a good boy.
This is the best!
Why am I so happy!
Wow!
You have a pimple again.
You are fluttering!
Here we go!
You are great!
You're a good boy, my friend.
You've got a lot of hair.
I was surprised.
Were you surprised?
I had a lot of hair, too.
You were happy, weren't you?
I was very happy.
That's good.
You don't have enough hair, do you?
Did you take it off?
No.
Are you going to break up with me today?
Are you sure?
You said you wanted to play with me.
Yes, I did.
Then, will you come with me?
Really?
You are free today, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Yes, I will.
Then, I will gather a lot of people.
What?
OK, I will follow you.
OK, follow me.
Don't stay there. Let's go.
Already?
Let's go.
I don't have time.
I can't.
You can't.
Stand up.
I can't.
I will leave you here.
No way.
I can't.
Nyan, nyan.
It's cute.
Is it a cat?
Hyo?
It's a cat like Hyo.
Mehyo?
Mehyo.
I thought it would be happy.
Who would be happy?
A lot of people will
come after this, right?
A lot of people.
How many people will come?
Do you care about that?
Of course I do.
Do you care about the number?
Yes, I do. How many?
So far, I've got 4 or 5 replies.
What?
What do you mean?
I want a little more.
That's a luxury.
That's right.
I want 7 or 8 more.
What did you say?
You are a luxurious woman.
I want more.
You want more?
OK.
I'll call you a little more.
You can take a break until they come.
Take a break?
Even though I changed my clothes?
It'll take about an hour.
It's itching.
It's itching?
What should we do?
What should we do with Nabu?
How about a warm-up exercise?
How about a warm-up exercise with Manko?
A warm-up exercise.
Do you want to do it normally?
Yes.
So that many men can accept it.
Let's do a warm-up exercise.
Let's take a look at your face.
You have a cute face.
It's embarrassing.
Do you know what kind of face you have?
I don't know.
You have a cute face.
Do you want to see your face?
Do you want to see it?
It's cute, isn't it?
No, it's not cute at all.
Look at it properly.
I don't want to.
I saw it.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's leaking, isn't it?
It's leaking.
It's not leaking.
I can't take it off.
Can you take it off?
What is this?
It's very vibrating, isn't it?
Amazing.
What's that?
It's a dentist!
Look at the camera.
It's leaking.
No, it's not.
Let me clean your nose.
My nose is itchy
It's itchy, isn't it?
It's itchy.
It hurts.
Ouch!
It's time to go to the vet.
Do you feel good?
You should feel good.
Don't go to the vet without permission.
You can't go to the vet without permission.
It's getting harder.
He's purring.
Do you feel the difference
between right and left?
I want to go to the left.
Left? This way?
It's not a big deal.
I want to go to the left.
It feels so good.
Which way?
This way?
Right?
Ouch!
I'm going to turn it over.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm sorry.
You are wet.
You are naughty.
What are you going to do? You are wet.
Let me see.
Let me see your belly.
Let's put this in.
It's leaking.
Don't let it leak.
Good boy.
I'm glad you are in good health.
I also wish you good health from now on.
I'm glad I made your wish.
Today's dinner is a cold Ume-soba.
I'm going to put the switch on.
I can't hear you.
You are very excited.
It's dangerous, so don't do it on your own.
I'll pull it out slowly.
I'll pull it out harder.
Oh my gosh!
Are you OK?
You're sweating a lot.
What's this?
What's that?
Sweat?
Salt?
Is salt this much?
It's too much.
Don't make my house dirty.
Please don't.
Yay.
It's cute. Stand up.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's a modern JK.
I don't like it.
Can you sit like this?
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Look at this.
It looks good on you.
You look like you are in
front of a convenience store.
Tamuro?
Yes, Tamuro.
There are many gyaru like you.
Really?
By the way, what are you doing?
Are you waiting for someone?
Didn't you call me?
I was waiting for you.
You were waiting for me?
Yes, I did.
I stretched my legs.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Did you call me?
Yes, I did.
Why are you so excited?
I called you.
I called you because you said
there were not many people.
I did it!
I think you did a good job.
Play with me.
Call me.
I'm here.
What should I call you?
How about come on?
Welcome.
I'm in trouble.
What do you mean?
How about come on?
You want to be here, don't you?
You don't mind, do you?
How about come in?
Can you say something like, please come in?
Yes, I can.
Please come in.
Can you say something like, please come in.
There are so many.
Here you are.
Thank you so much.
I called you as you requested.
Look around you.
It's amazing.
Everything is solid.
It's getting better, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Why don't we listen to what
they have to say and move on?
What?
They are kind. They are my friends.
Friends?
That's right.
Let's talk. I can't look at you.
Hello.
I want you to touch him.
He has a lot of dung.
Dung.
What's wrong with him?
I want to put him in.
Where do you want to put him?
I want to put him in Manko.
I want to put it here.
You are good at it.
Let's take a look.
Let's take a look at your ears.
Touch it.
I'm so happy.
Are you happy?
You've never been surrounded
like this before, have you?
No, I haven't.
Let's get started.
Can I touch you?
It feels good.
Good boy.
How is it?
Please observe him.
He is big.
He has a small mouth.
You're so small.
You're so big.
Everyone is big.
I like big ones.
I think it'll feel good if
you put this in a manko.
It looks good.
You want me to put it in a manko, right?
I have to tell everyone.
Put it in a manko.
Next.
Do you want to put in this little one?
I want to put it in.
What should I do?
How about this one?
The line is made Great I
want to put in this little one.
I want to put all the mangoes in it.
Everyone is big, isn't it?
Everyone is big.
I'm going to eat it.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
Don't take a break.
You have a nice face.
You eat a lot.
Look at the back.
How is it?
Do you want to open it?
Look at the back.
It's so tight I'm scared.
Where should I put it?
Tell your brother where you want to put it
I think he'll put it in for you I
want you to put it in the mango.
The mango?
We like mangoes, but we also like
to put it in the back of our throats.
Really?
I'll put a lot of mangoes
in the back of our throats.
Really?
I'll make you do it.
I'll do my best.
Really?
Yes.
I'll do my best.
Good boy.
He's scratching his head.
What is this?
No, no, no.
What did you eat?
I'm embarrassed.
You're embarrassed, but you're eating it.
Don't you need Chinchin?
You don't need Chinchin?
I want it.
I'll do it for you as much as I put in.
Good boy.
Oh, he's gone He's gone.
Don't try so hard by yourself.
You're not coming in at all.
Wow, that's amazing.
You've come this far.
You're not coming in at all.
Oh, you're out again.
There's nothing in there.
I told you to put it in the box.
Wow.
There's a lot of water.
There's a lot of water on the futon.
You've got something on your face.
Get out of the futon.
It's amazing.
Do you smell?
What did you eat?
I'm tired of waiting.
Make it big.
You want to put it in, don't you?
Manko, you don't have to go that far.
You want me to put it
all the way in, don't you?
It won't stop. It's all wet.
See?
Your uniform is all wet.
You don't drink it, do you?
I think I'm going to throw up.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to throw up.
You're drooling a lot.
Good boy.
I'm sorry.
You are strong.
Is it painful?
How is it?
It's painful.
What's wrong?
I'll put you on the other side.
Look at me.
Look at the camera.
You can do it!
I'm going to have a hard time.
I feel sick.
Can I take out a lot of this?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Don't drink it on your own.
Show me your mouth.
Open your big mouth.
Show me your small eyes.
Do you have a little bit?
You have a little bit.
It's not a big deal.
You've been eating for about a week.
How much did you eat?
I dropped it on the floor.
Did you drop it on the floor?
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
I didn't tell you to drink it.
I'm sorry.
Don't drink it next time.
It's hot.
Here you are.
Oh, it's hot.
Here he comes.
You did it.
Suck it.
You can do it.
That's right.
I'll give you some poison.
It's coming out.
That's right.
Don't run away.
Let's put it in your mouth.
It's still coming out.
Show me what's in your mouth.
Show me your face.
This is a sperm, isn't it?
Around your mouth.
You have to take it.
You can't let go of it.
Gather all the sperm.
Taste it.
How does it taste?
It's good.
It's good? That's good.
There's still more.
You can't do that.
You'll get angry if you do that.
You can't move, can you?
I'll make it impossible for you to move.
OK?
You can't move?
You can't move either.
You can't drink it all.
Look at me, Pimma.
Look at the camera.
You're not going to eat it?
Look at this camera, he is filming You
are so energetic Look at the camera.
He is looking at the camera all the time.
Oh, it's scary.
Oh, it's creepy.
What is this place?
Oh, I'm going to get in.
I'm still going to put it in.
You shouldn't complain.
Look at me.
You have to keep looking at me.
I'm sorry.
I'm done.
Please get up.
Heh, heh, heh.
I think I will make
it What should I do.
Show me the inside of your mouth.
It's good that you're
looking the other way.
There's a little bit left.
Taste it and drink it.
Did you taste it and drink it?
How does it taste?
It's good.
Really? Is it good?
Yes.
That's good.
You can do it if you don't rampage.
I'll take it off for you.
Just don't rampage.
OK.
Don't rampage.
OK? If you rampage, I'll put it back on.
OK.
I'll wipe your mouth.
Wipe your mouth.
Can I screw this all the way in?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
I'm going to give you a treat.
I'm sorry.
You're breathing in and out.
kin-chan I'm not good
at coping with cuteness.
I'm not good at coping with cuteness.
Well, in that case,
Let's see.
That's true.
I'm sorry, I don't
understand the situation.
Did you get a good rest?
Did you drink a lot?
Don't drink too much.
Hey, let's play more.
Here.
Put it here.
You're going in there.
How do you feel now?
You feel good now, don't you?
I'm listening.
I feel good.
Let me hold you.
Then I'll make you feel better.
Do you understand?
Do you want to eat?
I'll give it to you now.
If you do your best,
I'll give it to you later.
Here we go.
One, two.
You have a lot of fur.
Are you okay?
You have a runny nose and a cough.
You shouldn't have sneezed.
I'm sorry.
Did you say, you're sorry?
Where did you go?
What are you doing?
It's not over yet.
Are you still there?
Why are you lying on the bed?
You're lying on the bed.
Raise your butt.
Look at your brother's face.
You're a human, aren't you?
It's a strange behavior.
I don't know what it is.
He's drooling.
Good boy.
Do you feel good?
Look at you, Ochinchi.
Is it long?
It's big, right?
I can't stop drinking.
It's not over yet.
Look at his face.
What do you want?
You feel good, don't you?
Chinchin Chinchin,
you feel good, don't you?
You feel good, don't you?
I'll play with you.
He is still in pain.
Show me your mouth.
Did you drink it all?
You didn't drink it all, did you?
Puff, puff!
Why are you coughing?
Get it under control.
Cough!
Here we go.
Alice also seems to be a little better
Did you finish?
Have you finished eating?
I'm glad you put it in the manko.
It was good, wasn't it?
Manko is a throat manko, though.
It was a man.
I'm a serious gay.
Really?
If you notice it, you'll be a fan.
I'm glad you're a fan.
Can I look inside?
Yes.
How old were you when you
saw your boobs for the first time?
I haven't seen my boobs.
I don't think I'm interested in freeing.
I'm not interested in freeing.
Are you?
I'm not interested in people.
What kind of people
are you not interested in?
For example, when I was
a student, I was a teacher.
Oh, I see.
So that's what happened.
Yes.
You didn't actually do it.
You were a teacher
and... Teacher.
And... You were a class teacher.
I was a class teacher.
That's dangerous.
Did you go to the
classroom with your teacher?
Yes, I did.
What?
You didn't go to the gym, did you?
No, I didn't have a gym.
I didn't have time to do that.
There is a mat in the gym,
so you can use it as a bed.
Oh, I see.
Are you experienced?
No, I'm just delusional.
What did you do just now?
What is it?
Didn't you go to the bathroom
when you woke up drunk?
I do that every day.
Every day?
I have sex every day.
Really?
Do you have a lot of sexual intercourse?
I have a lot of sexual intercourse.
I have sex with five people now.
It's hard for 5 people to fly
a robot every day, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
What's this?
This is the police.
I'm going to arrest you.
The police are behind us.
I don't like this part.
Oh, no.
I'm tired of it.
I want to adjust this part.
Let's adjust this part.
I can't find the balance.
Please adjust this part.
I'll adjust this part.
Is this OK?
I think this is not good.
Isn't it great?
It's so smooth.
It's not coming in, but it's okay.
It's hard, so you can take it off.
I'll give you a little.
It's embarrassing.
Yeah.
Here you are, my baby.
She's doing great.
The inside of her mouth is warm.
Can I lick this?
It's been a long time since I had a baby,
so I was worried that I wouldn't be able to
eat well, but I was able to eat a lot of
delicious food because I had a baby in my arms.
I'm so happy that I can eat
delicious food with my baby.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Okay, okay.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
You should lick the other part of the head.
Look.
I'm hungry.
It's a butt.
You like it?
Yes, I do.
It's embarrassing.
Give me a kiss.
Do you want me to drink it?
Do you want to drink it?
I'll drink it.
It's good, isn't it?
If you want to drink
beer, there is a better way.
If you pour it here.
Pour it here?
Yes.
Oh, it's very hard.
Is this a hindrance?
Is this better?
Do you like it?
Do you want more beer?
No, this is enough.
The cat was slimy.
Sorry, sir.
I'll take this one.
You have to put it in your mouth.
Put it in your mouth.
You eat a lot.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
Do you want me to lick you more?
You are so heavy.
Let's put you to rest.
It's so heavy... It's as
heavy as you are in milk.
You might fall down.
Wow... Your tail
is not helping you.
Look.
Let's put you to rest.
You need to kiss me.
Can I put it in my mouth?
Can I?
Yes.
Wow.
Can you see it?
I want to catch this, too.
Wow.
This is good.
I want to taste a lot of things.
Wow!
Puma-chan, Puma-chan!
Put this chip in here!
Let's look at it from a close distance.
Wow!
Ah, it's in there, it's in there.
Look, it's in there.
Ah, amazing.
There's still time.
It's really dangerous.
This is going to work.
Eh, it's fast.
But here, it's a little
hard to do, isn't it?
Is it over there?
Over there?
Yeah.
And one more thing.
I want you to be more like me.
Like this.
What?
If you cover your eyes.
Cover my eyes?
I think it's more comfortable.
But if you cover your eyes
and guess whose dick it is.
Oh, it's like Mickey's dick?
Yeah.
Raise your bangs.
Can you raise your bangs?
I can't see anything.
Let's fix the axis.
Let's do it.
Let's do it slowly.
Is it okay?
You have to hold here.
Okay.
I'll support you with both hands.
I'm tired.
Let's take a break here for a while.
I feel sick.
I'm sick.
Lie down in front of me.
Let me see your feet.
We will do our best
to make you feel better.
We will touch you a lot.
You don't know who is touching you, do you?
I don't know.
Yes, that's right.
It's good for you to feel better.
You can move freely.
Sit here.
You have a lot of hands.
Raise your hands.
I'm going to give you a snack.
What is this?
I'm going to touch you a lot.
I'll give you some more, okay?
I can't see where you are.
We're doing a great job.
You don't know whose hand it is, do you?
You're doing your best.
You have the power to cover your eyes.
You have a lot of hair.
How do you feel?
What's going on?
All four of us are doing
our best, aren't we?
Aren't we four?
Why are you turning around?
Why are you saying that we are not four?
Why?
I know why.
Do you want to take a blindfold?
What?
Take a blindfold.
Can you take it yourself?
Yes, I can.
He's so cute.
Who is that?
Hello.
He's so cute.
Are you going to stand up?
He's drunk.
He drank too much.
No, no.
He's definitely drunk.
Happy, look around.
I can't.
Can you look around?
Yes, I can.
It looks fun.
There are four people.
I can't.
You asked me to do something.
Did I?
What was it?
Did you forget?
I'm sorry.
Congratulations!
Please invite a lot of people.
I did.
I invited a lot of people.
Please say hello.
How about me?
You can't introduce me.
What's your name?
I'm Apemaru.
What did you do today?
I went to have sex.
I went to the bathroom.
I wanted to have sex with everyone.
What about the rubber band?
I don't think I can wear a rubber band.
You can wear it in the middle of the night.
I want to have sex with everyone.
Did you hear that?
Did you get it?
Yes.
Then, let's take care of
my Tapimaru together.
You wanted to eat this, didn't you?
I'm sorry.
Good boy.
How is it?
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
It's good, isn't it?
Everyone is looking at
Manko, but her skin is beautiful.
What are you doing?
Daddy, let me see your butt.
Show me your butt.
What's in your butt?
I don't know.
Do you like it?
Oh, great.
Your butt is great.
What's in your butt?
My butt is great.
There is a person who loves my butt.
Are you being licked?
About 2 or 3 people.
I'm being licked.
I love your butt so much.
I want more.
You are licking Manko's butt.
He wants to be hugged.
He is still in a coma.
Wow!
Hurry up!
Good boy!
Can I have some?
It's good, isn't it?
It's so good.
Yummy.
Everyone likes to eat with salt.
She is drowning.
You're going to break it.
Sit down and lie down.
I'm going to make you a lot harder.
Look at me.
Here, too.
There's a lot.
Just your mouth.
Eat this, too.
How do you feel?
You have a lot of gums.
I have a lot of gums.
How do you feel?
Are you having fun?
Are you happy?
Look at your happy face.
There's still more.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
I have a sore throat.
You have a lot of mouth.
Does it feel good?
Is it still coming out?
You have a lot of salt.
Imari-chan, more and
more chinchin is coming.
New chinchin is coming.
I'm waiting for chinchin.
I'm waiting for you.
Look at the camera.
I'll lower your head a little bit.
Oh, my God.
You're drinking too much.
Kikuchi, you are being licked.
Kikuchi, can I have a doggy?
Yes.
Sit here.
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going to put it in raw.
You wanted me to put it in raw.
I'll leave it here.
What should I do?
I can't stand it anymore.
It's okay to take it out
in the middle, isn't it?
It's a little too much, isn't it?
It's too much.
How long have you been silent?
3 days.
Can I make you cry more?
Are you happy?
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Here we go.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
I'm going to take you to the bathroom.
Take it out I'll take it out.
Can you see it?
I took it out It feels good.
Let's take it out.
It feels so good.
It's falling.
I'm scared.
Ahhhhhhh.
Ahhhh Ahhhh.
Ah, that feels so good.
Ah Ah, that feels so good
Oh, that feels so good.
Ah.
Ah, I'm tired.
I'm tired.
Ah.
Ah Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Uehhh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wow, wow.
Wow!
It's in there.
Uehhh.
He's shredding the snow.
Uehh.
He's shedding.
This is a little disappointing.
Ahh.
That's the end.
You are doing great.
Look at her.
You are pulling her.
Do you want to hold her mouth?
You are good.
I can't do it.
Show me your face.
You have a beautiful body.
Take off your bra.
It's so hot.
Let's turn on the air conditioner.
I'll turn on the air conditioner.
I'm glad you're happy.
I think I'm going to throw up.
Don't you have to pee?
Put a lot of kimchi on it.
Is this kimchi?
Kimchi.
There are a lot of things to do.
Put kimchi on it.
Be careful.
What's going on?
Haki, look at the camera.
Don't you forget the camera?
I don't forget.
You have to say it when you are breathing.
I'm so tired.
You're tired, aren't you?
You're thirsty, aren't you?
Aki-chan, you're thirsty, aren't you?
Open your mouth and have a drink.
Breathe in, breathe in.
It's still coming out.
Keep it in your mouth.
Don't spill it, don't spill it.
It's still coming out.
Don't spill it.
Keep it in your mouth.
Don't drink it.
Get up, get up.
You can do it.
Open your mouth.
You're eating a lot.
Don't spill it.
Drink it at the same time as you go.
Ah... Hmm...
Hmm... Hmm...
How do you feel, Sesshi?
What does it taste like?
It tastes like something I've eaten before.
Do you like the smell?
You like the smell, don't you?
That's good.
Good girl.
Do you want to sit on the chair?
Let's go.
Put your hand on the chair.
Let's go inside.
Your breath is coming
out from the back, isn't it?
It feels good to be a gyaru-no-man.
Because you've been sighing a lot.
Here we go.
I'm going to push you.
I'm going to cry.
You're so weak.
I'm so tired.
I'm sorry.
Wow.
It's amazing.
I've never seen such a thing.
You should look at it as it is.
Don't cry.
I'm going to sleep now.
Everyone is sleeping there.
Everyone is sleeping.
You can do it.
This time... You
can take it off.
What?
You can take it off.
Let's go.
It's warm.
How do you feel now?
Good boy
Show me your face.
Are you alright?
Give me your urine Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Breathe in.
Oh, my God.
You are going to have a baby.
I'll take a look at you.
I'm so happy.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
I can't take it anymore.
Wow, you are amazing.
Chibi-chan, open your bowl.
You got a lot of food.
I got a lot of food.
It seems that there are some
people who haven't got food yet.
Give it to Haki-maru's bowl.
I won't touch you.
Wow, you are so warm.
Yes.
Let's put it all in the bag.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's clean up.
Help me.
It's okay, it's okay.
I don't know what to do.
Have a seat.
You're so beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Please leave me alone.
You must be exhausted.
What did you think of when you were killed?
I was thinking about my family.
Did you taste each one of them?
Yes.
I see.
But you had a good life.
Yes, I did.
Do you want to take it home?
I want to.
You do?
Yes.
Good.
Really?
Yes.
If we exchange our contact information.
It's fun to have more followers.
I wonder if I'll increase it.
This kind of stimulation is good, isn't it?
It was the best!
You wanted to play, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Do you want to play again?
Yes, I want to play again.
Then, let's play more.
No, I don't want to.
Anyway, you are full today.
See you next time.
Good night.
Bye bye.