It was delicious, wasn't it?
Yes, it was really delicious.
Can I join you? Yes, you can.
Don't worry about it.
Really? I joined you the other day, too.
It's OK.
By the way, do you have time after this?
Yes, if I make it in
time for the last train.
Oh, then let's go to my favorite bar.
Bar?
Yes.
I've never been there.
Really?
Yes.
Let's go.
This way.
The entrance is very suspicious.
No, it's normal.
Is it a bar? It's not a bar.
I got a call from a bar.
It was crowded.
So I changed my mind.
I see.
Let's go in.
It's not suspicious.
It's like a grocery store.
LOL
What's wrong with you?
Are you drunk?
Are you OK?
I'm looking forward to it.
Good job.
Are you drunk?
Are you drunk? I was drunk.
Oh, really?
You can drink there.
What's that? We're friends.
Let's drink together.
It's fun to drink together, isn't it?
Are you guys drinking?
Of course we are.
Isn't it not enough?
Can I drink all of it?
Cheers!
Do you want to drink something?
What do you want to drink?
Do you want to drink
URAHAI? I'll bring it.
Where did you find this?
Cheers!
You guys are nervous.
I'll make you relax with a funny gag.
3,2,1
I did it!
You're laughing.
You're not drinking enough.
Why?
You are drinking a lot.
You are always looking at me.
What do you mean?
You are not good enough.
Stop it.
I think I drank a lot.
You are like a takoyaki.
It will get cold.
I'm going to go.
I have to go to the last train.
You have to go to the last train?
Really?
I'm going to the last train.
I see.
Let's drink a lot at the end.
I'm pretty drunk today.
Let's have a drink.
There is a very delicious drink.
I'll make it.
Wait a minute.
Let's have a drink.
A very delicious drink?
Are you going to make
that drink? Let's do it.
It's a special drink.
Let's do it.
Wait a minute.
Welcome.
It's very delicious.
What's wrong with you?
He is good at it.
His drinking skill is really good.
Really.
He is good at it.
He is good at it too.
What does it mean?
Why do you throw it away?
Why do you throw
it away? He is scary.
What's wrong with you today?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you for waiting.
Look at the color.
Isn't the color cute?
This is the usual one.
This is a gimmick.
This is a really good
one made by Shun, who likes sake.
I was thinking of developing a product.
Let's have a drink to celebrate the first
anniversary of Chiharu-chan's debut.
To meet Chiharu-chan,
Cheers!
Chiharu, drink it all.
Drink it all!
At first, it might be
a strong attack, but once
you get used to it,
you'll be able to drink it.
Is the camera okay over there?
Is it rolling?
Yeah, it's rolling perfectly.
Okay.
I've already drunk too much.
It's not okay.
You look like you're not satisfied.
You are so cute.
What's wrong? Did you get drunk?
You got drunk, didn't you?
Are you okay? Are you conscious?
I want to go home.
Do you want to go home?
Can you see it?
Why?
Welcome home!
Why is there a cat here?
What's wrong?
Chaco, why?
Why?
There is a cat here, too.
Here, too.
Here is a new cat.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's a new cat.
Yes.
Let's taste it properly
and see if you can open your mouth.
Pass, pass, pass.
She is eating very well.
She is still hungry.
She is eating well.
She is eating very well.
She is moving her tongue.
Is she moving?
Yes.
She is licking her tongue.
She is a bitch.
Is she a bitch? She is a bitch.
Is she so cute?
Is she a bitch?
Did she do it
on purpose? Good girl.
This way.
No, no, no.
No, it's not like that.
Are you going to take a bath?
It feels really good.
I'm going to go to the back of the room.
Did you want to go home by last train?
Or did you want to go to the lab with me?
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Which one do you want to go to?
I think everyone is looking forward to it.
I think so, too.
It's better to play with everyone.
It may not be a play.
I think so, too.
Let's drink it carefully to the end.
Slowly Oh, it feels good.
I'm going to put a towel on his neck.
He is in pain.
Open your mouth You
are about to throw up
Open your mouth and move
Now, let's go to the
back Do you feel good?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're so wet.
Come here.
You're so rough.
You are eating everything.
Can I sit here?
You can sit here.
Let's make you grown up.
Now Hiragao is getting ugly.
What a waste.
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
I'm going to put him in the box.
Wow, you are so cute.
Good boy.
Here, here.
Is it a execution ground?
You are gonna puke.
Good boy.
You can't run away, can you?
It doesn't matter if
you don't die, does it? Let's have fun.
How are you?
Pon-kichi, this way.
Let me take your tongue out.
You are a good boy, Pon-kichi.
You are a good boy.
Open your mouth.
Do you eat this? Yes, I do.
Do you eat this?
Open your mouth.
Give me a lot of food.
Don't spill it.
You can't.
Yummy.
Open your mouth.
I'm going to give you a treat.
Don't spit it out.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
You have a bad breath, so you have
to be careful.
Open your eyes.
You are a good boy.
You are too nervous.
Go, go.
Love-chan, do you think you can go?
You did it, you did it.
Is it OK? I'll hold you.
You'll feel good.
Go, go, go.
Look.
Look, you can go further.
Oh, no.
You have a sore throat.
I will lift your chin.
And this side.
It was so good.
You are getting better.
Please put your head down.
Head?
Please open your mouth.
Yes, yes.
You are breathing well.
How do you feel?
How do you feel? Tell me.
I don't know if you are drunk or not.
Oh, you feel good.
You are drinking a lot.
Don't let go.
I'm going to let you out of the cage.
I'm going to let you go.
Let go of me.
You've got so much.
I've put out a lot.
You've put out a lot.
Awesome.
Cheers.
It seems like Jiharu can't do it.
Jiharu, let's drink.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it? It's hot.
Are you OK?
I'm taking it off for you.
Is this a string? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm going to give you a drink.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I like this.
You know this.
You're so dirty, you son of a bitch!
Don't get cocky!
You're so dirty.
I'm going to go wash up.
You're all sweaty.
We have to drink again.
Yeah, we have to.
Open your mouth.
We have to reset it.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Do you feel good
now? Let's have fun.
You don't want to take it off, do you?
It's so much fun.
I'm going to throw it away.
This one?
It's hot, isn't it?
Your buttocks are big.
Big buttocks.
Your buttocks are erotic.
I'll massage your buttocks.
What's the matter?
It's been a month.
Give me your tongue.
I'll kiss you.
I'll be popular.
I'm more popular than you.
It's more fun if we do
it together, isn't it?
Do you feel good?
Do you want me to take your boobs off?
What do you mean by that?
I mean the back of your head.
What are you talking about?
Cheers!
You have a lot of pus.
What's wrong?
Cheers!
You have a lot of pus.
You are getting sensitive.
Do you feel good?
Do you like it?
You're getting stronger.
You're becoming stiff.
Open your mouth.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm sure.
You're gonna be fine.
Hold her tight.
Is it comfortable?
It's uncomfortable.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
I want to go home.
I don't think so.
This is our house.
You can stay here whenever you want.
We won't let you go out.
I don't have a guide.
Listen to me in English.
It's dangerous.
Look at his butt.
He's going to the back.
He's looking this way.
Don't spit it out again.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Put your tongue out.
Put your tongue out more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You are enjoying it, aren't you?
You have a good face.
You are grumbling.
You are doing your best.
Good.
Are you OK?
Do you need help?
Yes.
Good.
You can do it yourself.
Hold her legs.
What are you doing? Oh, I see.
She is trying to spread
her legs by herself.
She is so kind.
Hold her legs.
No, I don't like it.
You are very wet.
Wow, you are so wet.
Wow, you are right.
You are so nice.
Do you feel good?
You have a lot of fur on your body.
You are so cute.
You are getting so hot.
OK, you can turn your back to me.
Turn your back to me.
Stick out your tongue.
Yes, that's right.
Are you going to take
it off? You are so big.
You are amazing
Let's open your buttocks
You have
a low buttock hole Does it feel good?
Wow, what's up? Do you feel good?
Are you moving by yourself?
You are moving by yourself, aren't you?
You're moving by yourself,
aren't you? Like this.
You're moving by yourself, aren't you?
Open your mouth.
Let's drink this.
Hold it tight.
I can't do it anymore.
Look, look, come on.
What's going on?
I'm going to give you a massage.
Oh, my.
I'm going to put you on my back.
Open your legs.
Yes, yes.
Let's support her.
Yes, support her.
Why are you
trembling? It's a candy.
You eat it deliciously.
What is this?
What is this? It's amazing.
Is it clean? Oh, it's gone.
Something came out.
Don't scratch my face.
No, no, no.
Stop it!
You bastard!
Hey, you!
Don't mess with me.
She's running away.
She's not a human.
Do it properly.
Wait a minute.
You forgot it.
Do it to the end.
Don't spit it out.
You want me to spit it out, don't you?
Spit it out.
Good boy.
You can go far,
can't you? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You don't want to join us?
You're not in the mood.
You like to be surprised, don't you?
You like to be stroked
like this, don't you?
You are such a pervert
Good boy
I feel you
You are being
stroked Good morning.
Don't let go of my hand.
Get up.
Give me your paw.
Come here.
Come here
Good boy Can you look this way?
Good morning
You feel good, don't you?
You feel it, don't you?
Every time you get
eaten by Oku, you feel it, don't you?
You feel it, don't you?
I'm doing it with all my heart.
That's the way you are.
You're a man, and you're a happy creature.
That's right.
Like this, like this, like this.
What are you doing?
The cat is in a good mood.
The cat is full of energy.
The cat seems to be in a good mood
thanks to the food.
The cat is full of energy.
The cat is in a good mood.
You can do it.
Be gentle.
Already?
What? You are fast.
Be gentle.
Good boy.
You can change the position.
When she got old, she was so scared
of people that she could hardly move.
She was scared of
people and couldn't go outside.
She was so
scared that she couldn't go outside.
Look at me.
Look at my shoulder.
You can kiss me.
Be careful.
It's dangerous.
Kiss me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
I was surprised.
You were surprised? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everyone.
You were too drunk.
I didn't know you were so drunk.
What are you doing?
Nanao, why are you so shy?
You look so scared.
I can see your love-sabre.
Look at Nanao.
Show me.
Let's go, let's go.
Can you move up a little?
Move up? I'm tired.
Let me raise your shoulders.
Let's do it.
Ready, go.
Go up.
Go.
Oh, you are shaking.
Your back
is shaking when you are in the bed.
Oh, my.
You are holding her.
Yes, I am.
Let her move.
Up and down.
Oh, my.
You are going to fall down.
Let's go.
I'm going up.
Get up, please.
Shizu-chan, you don't
want to go forward? She's groaning.
Does she feel
good? She likes it.
I think it's about time.
It's dangerous.
Come here.
You must be tired.
You have a big waist.
It's time to go.
Take it off.
Slowly.
Give it to him slowly.
You want to put it in?
You're gonna take
it, aren't you? Yes, I am.
I'm gonna take it.
Give it back to him.
You always do something.
He has a lot of influence on him.
He is always like this.
Wow, you are strong.
Are you sad?
Open your mouth.
Wow, you are strong.
You have a strong mouth.
I'm going to close my mouth.
He closes his mouth a lot.
I'm surprised.
What's going on?
He was about to bite you.
You don't like it, do you?
Finally, you're going to win.
Get up.
Don't make me do it.
I'm not a tooth.
Good night.
Isn't it great? Good night.
He reacts so well.
He reacts so well when
I put him in the bag.
When I went to the back, I was surprised.
You wanted to have sex, didn't you?
It's better to have a lot of sex.
It's the best.
It's good, isn't it?
Mikan and Tamae are now at the same age.
Oh, it's disgusting.
Help me.
Thank you for helping me.
Thank you.
Oh, that's right.
You are amazing.
It's the right answer to enter this circle.
Are you having fun?
You are having fun.
Do you want to kiss me so much?
You are so pure.
It's good to hold hands like this.
You are so lonely.
You are so pure.
It's good to hold hands like this.
Give me a hand.
Give me a kiss.
Nao, what's wrong?
You say, no, no, no!
Is it a matrimonial?
It's not a matrimonial.
Show me a real kiss.
This is a real kiss.
I'll show you a real kiss.
I'll show you love.
This is how you kiss.
The cat reacted to the kiss on the lips.
Stop it!
It hurts, doesn't it? I'm sorry.
I'm trying to get the cat out of the cage.
So you're going to
have sex for the rest of your life?
No!
Huh?
It's fine, right?
It's good, right?
What are you doing?
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's bitter, isn't it?
Did you go to the vet?
Here is your medicine.
Let's go to the vet.
You drank the medicine.
What are you
doing? Don't push me.
I don't like you.
Don't push me.
I'll put you on my back.
Don't help me.
I hope they get along well.
She is so cute.
It was really comfortable.
What is it?
I have no vocabulary.
It's the best to do it in Sour.
It's really the best.
That's right.
Don't say it.
I'm going to take a picture.
Like always.
Let's take a picture.
I'm going to take a picture.
Please take a picture.
This is a commemorative photo.
Let's make a peace sign.
Put your index finger
and middle finger like this.
Smile.
I have to smile.
Peace.
Young, young.
Young.
He is Hai.
They are good friends.
Let's take a picture together.
He is Wakai.
He is Machiharu.
They have reconciled.
Good for you.
Don't lose him.
Take care of him.
After that, I was used as
a bait in the videos and photos they took.
Not only my parents, but also my friends.
I couldn't
talk to them about what I was doing.
I spent my days feeling fear and anxiety.
Mitsuha-san! Mitsuha-san!
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Please stop it!
No, no, it's not like that.
Mitsuha-san, I'm not your enemy.
It's not my fault. I couldn't
stop them because I was afraid of them.
Shun-kun and Kyu-kun
were so scary that I couldn't do anything.
That's why I was so nervous. I'm so sorry.
They seduce girls like Misa-san every day.
It's the worst.
It's the worst, right?
That's why I want you
to deliver the victim.
But...
But?
I think it's hard for
you to say that in such a bright mood.
But I can't bear
to see a girl in such a bad condition.
Please.
Um...
If they come, I'll be in trouble.
I'll go.
Take care of the damage.
Please.
See you.
You!
What are you hiding?
What are you going
to do with such a lifesaver? Hey, you.
What are you
going to do if we lose our friendship?
Our fun campus life will be ruined.
Hey.
Don't do anything weird.
I have a video of you moving around.
If you tell
anyone, I'll spread it in the dormitory.
Don't do anything that doesn't make sense.
You should drink this.
Drink it.
Hurry up.
Please.
Don't you drink it? It's boring. Hurry up.
Drink it.
You can drink more.
Go, go, go. Hurry up.
It feels good to drink
a lot, doesn't it? It's good.
I think I'm back to my old self.
Let me touch you.
Look at me.
I'm a big boy.
Let me touch you.
Do you feel good? I know you do.
It's getting
hot, isn't it? Yeah.
My body is getting really hot.
It's hot here too,
isn't it? Let him sleep.
Let him sleep.
It's a little hot.
That's right.
Come on, come on.
Come on, touch it, touch it, touch it.
Touch it.
How is it? That's right.
How's your hand?
How is it? It's hard.
How about the
right paw? Here, here.
I will let you take a bath.
Take a bath.
Oh, good.
Good boy.
Let me lick you more gently.
Do you feel good?
Oh, you feel good.
Nao-chan,
Are you trying to let this girl go?
You are a bad boy.
How do you feel?
Big.
Big?
Let me give you a treat.
You can do it by yourself.
You do it well.
You can do
it well, right? I see.
You are so good.
You are getting better.
You are becoming a great man.
You are a good husband.
You are so good.
You are eating very well.
You have been doing
this since you were a baby, haven't you?
You are very good at it.
How is it? Is it good?
You are not energetic enough.
You should stick your tongue out.
Here you are.
You can eat up to the back.
You like the back, don't you?
Don't hit me.
Rin chan, come here.
You can see the other
person's face clearly.
You have a very good expression.
Open your eyes.
Look at your eyes.
You have a lot of swelling.
What are you doing?
You are not good at this.
Do you understand?
Why
are you so grumpy? Say something.
Stop it.
We are having fun.
Do you feel good?
You feel good, don't you?
You feel good because
you were scared just now, don't you?
I'll do it by hand.
I'll show you how to do it.
Show me how to do it.
Show me.
Yes, yes.
Use your tongue.
Yes.
Lick it.
Lick, lick, lick.
Use your tongue.
Make more sound.
Yes.
Yes, that's good.
That's a good sound.
It's okay.
I'll give you some more.
Hey, Nano-kun.
Look at my erotic ferret.
Look at it.
Say it.
Look at my dirty hair.
You did a good job.
I'll give you a reward.
Do it by yourself.
Hold his waist.
Yes.
Look at his dirty hair.
I'll lick it from the bottom.
You are looking at the other person's face.
Yes, that's right.
Do you want me to massage your back?
You have a lot of hair on this side, too.
You have a lot of hair on your back.
I'm sorry.
You should hold your chin properly.
Yes, yes, yes.
Show me your favorite woman.
Your favorite person.
Nana, are you watching?
Nana, are you
watching? No, I'm not.
No?
You're not?
Show me your chin.
Wow, it's so sweet.
Swallow the bullet.
Swallow the bullet
and put it from the bottom to the top.
Swallow.
Boom.
That's right.
Swallow a lot of bullets.
While moving your waist.
Hey, you became erotic.
You have a funny face.
OK, lick your butthole.
Turn around.
Your butthole.
You can do it, can't you?
You can lick your butthole, can't you?
Lick your butthole.
Make it clean.
Let's take a look at your back.
You have a wide back.
Wow, you have a wide back.
Here is your head.
He is licking your back.
You can see it clearly.
You have to lick your belly, Bara-chan.
Pull your belly button, Bella-chan.
Pull your belly button like a tail.
Yes, like this.
Yes, that's good.
You are so gentle today.
You lick your belly
button from your butt to your butthole.
You can do it,
right? Yes, you can.
You are a good boy.
You have a very erotic expression.
You are the best.
You know it.
You like erotic things, don't you?
Don't you? That's right.
Look at me.
Look at me, Bardo.
You want to be licked.
I'll lick you.
It hurts.
You lick everyone's buttocks.
You are a pervert.
You are strange.
You are gross.
Nanao, you have a bad breath.
You have a bad breath.
Make more noise.
Nanao, you have a bad breath.
I don't have a bad breath.
Nanao, take a bath.
If you don't take a
bath, I'll leave you here.
Wait a minute.
Nanao, you have a bad breath.
Really?
Everyone, touch Nanao.
Touch my dick.
You are serious.
You are so serious.
You are a pervert.
Do it.
You are so nice.
You are a liar.
Wow, Tenko, you're so honest.
No, I'm not.
Drink some water.
What? Wait a minute.
What's that
voice? It's pathetic.
Are you a totem
pole? Go to sleep.
If you do that.
..
I'm sorry.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, my God.
As you saw
earlier, I'm going to lick you from here.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to lick you a lot.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
From the bottom to the top.
I'm going to make you drool.
I'm going to lick you a little bit.
Why don't you drink
it first? No, no, no.
That's the back of the head.
That's not good.
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good.
What are you talking about?
Why are you so grumpy?
I'll give it to you.
I'll give it to you while
looking at your nose.
It's annoying, right? Oh, I see.
Do you like it
there? No, I don't.
You're pathetic.
Why do you look like that?
It's fine, isn't it?
Do it more violently.
What?
Do it more softly.
No, I don't.
I'm done.
You're so stingy.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
Oh no! Let me do it.
Let me do it.
No, no, no.
No, no.
I'm not sure if you can do it.
If you can do it, please tell me.
No, no, no.
You are a good boy.
It's fun to be licked
by a lot of Kenpo, isn't it?
You have a happy face, don't you?
You have found it well, Kiyo-chan.
It's a company with
my skirt, isn't it? It's the best.
You are getting better and better.
How are you doing?
Look at the person who is licking.
Does it feel good?
Yes, yes, yes.
Ask him.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Please put a lot of food in your mouth.
Do you want a treat?
You want a treat, don't
you? It looks good.
You are feeling good, right?
Oh, it feels good
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, you are going to go.
You are amazing.
Utsu-san, you can't go home today, can you?
Take care of him.
Oh, it feels good.
I'll clean you up.
Thank you.
You look fashionable.
Next.
It suits you.
Look at me.
Lean on me.
Stay close to me.
Give me your hand.
You don't have to say it.
You have a bad breath.
You have to stop breathing.
You have to clean your body.
You have a lot of mental problems.
You have a bad breath.
You look good in this.
You're a smelly woman.
I'm going to beat you up.
Do you want to take a picture?
Let's take a picture.
Let's get together.
Sit down.
You're a big fan, aren't you?
Let's take a picture.
Look at the camera.
Stand up.
Smile.
Since that
day, I was imprisoned by these men.
Almost every day,
I was forced to prostitute.
Love has been escalating day by day, and
my own body and heart have been worn out.
Bye bye, Yari Yari!
Cheers!
That's a good drink, Emi-san.
Do you want more?
Cheers!
It's a good drink.
It's good.
Haru-chan,
you've been around for a long time.
Maybe you've fallen in love with her.
Maybe so.
You've been drinking alone lately.
Right? Oh, right.
Hey, Tano.
Be my friend today.
I see.
You haven't asked me out yet, have you?
Don't be a friend, not an acquaintance.
That's right.
You want to be a friend, don't you?
That's not what I'm saying.
Can't you listen to
me? Like this.
Like this.
If you don't be
a friend, you'll be taken by Gyu-chan.
Are you sure? I'll take you.
He is a very good boy.
You want to get
a cat's nail as a present, don't you?
You are always like this.
You are so cute.
You are wet.
You too.
You are all wet.
Kiku-chan, you are going to take it all.
I'll do it for you.
Chihara will lead you.
You're already drooling.
I'll show you.
You want to do it, don't you?
You're using your body.
Please give my mother a kiss.
How do you want to be kissed?
How do you want to be petted?
Do you want to be petted hard?
I'll pet you more.
You don't want to be petted hard, do you?
Do you want to be petted hard?
Does it feel good?
You have a bad breath.
You have a nosebleed.
You have a breast in front of you.
Look! Here it is.
It's a boob.
What are you going to do?
If you don't
come, you'll be eaten by Gyo-chan.
Look!
What are you going to do?
What are you gonna do?
You wanna be attacked, right?
Yes.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
You're getting a lot of kisses.
Let's have sex.
I'll give you a kiss.
Don't push me.
Finally, you are here.
Look at me.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Good boy.
How do you feel? It feels good.
It feels good.
That's good.
You're going to fall.
Drink water.
Give me a kiss.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I can't do anything, so I'll do my best.
I'll take off Nanao's clothes.
I'll do my best.
You have a good sense of smell.
I'll rub your belly.
You rub your belly, don't you?
You are aggressive.
Does it feel good?
You are rubbing your belly.
Let's go to bed.
Oh, you went to bed.
You are weird.
You have a lot of hair.
Do you feel good?
How do you feel? I don't know.
What are you doing?
You have grown up.
You are so fluffy.
Do you feel good? I feel good.
You are feeling good?
Here?
Do you want here?
You want me to touch you, don't you?
You are moving your waist a lot.
You have become very skinny.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to touch you?
You are moving a lot.
You are moving a
lot, aren't you? Ok, look at me.
Where do you want to go?
Spread your legs.
Nana, hold her legs.
Don't squirm.
Hold her legs.
What do you want to do?
Do you want me to touch you?
Where?
Here?
I'm going to tuck you in.
Please do.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to touch me directly.
Directly?
Where do you want
me to touch you? Here.
I don't know where
you want me to touch you.
Where is here?
What is here?
Cleatress
Cleatress is good, isn't it?
Your cleatress is wet, isn't it?
Do like this
Here
You have a hard time
Do you feel good?
Yes
What are you doing?
Open your mouth.
Show me your chest.
Here.
This is your favorite place.
You've gone.
Wait, wait, I haven't put anything in it.
Oh, good.
You've put something in it.
You've put two in it.
Do you feel ticklish here?
Does it feel good?
What do you want me to do?
What do you want
me to do? You are wet.
Clean your body.
Clean my body.
Let's clean your face.
You've got a lot on your face, Kiyo-chan.
What do you want?
Do you feel good?
Do you like it?
It's good, isn't it?
What are you doing, Nanako?
You've been staring at it.
No, I haven't.
You haven't, have you?
You've been staring at it.
Do you want more?
Do you want more? Do you feel good?
You can eat more by yourself.
You can surprise yourself.
Do you feel good?
Do you want more?
How about your throat?
Do you feel good?
Do you want more?
OK.
Look at me.
Bring me a drink.
Open your mouth.
Drink.
Good boy.
You are drinking tea
together? No, I am not.
I am not.
You are drinking tea together.
OK, open your mouth.
You have a lot of saliva.
I'm going to put it down.
You want it, don't you?
You're the first one to eat it.
Does it feel good?
She is the
most likely to eat in the children's cave.
She pushed the baby.
She is going to the baby.
Did you go?
Do you feel good?
You feel good, don't you?
Let's get together.
If you have any
questions, please leave a comment.
Don't open your mouth.
You like to bite, don't
you? You bite, too.
You feel good, don't you?
Oh, there you are.
You are so strong.
I'll lick you next time.
I'll ask you to lick me.
Lick me.
He is in a good mood today.
No, No, I want you to let him go.
I want you to let him go.
What's up?
You are going to the vet?
Come here
Do you want to go to the vet?
You lick him
Are you having fun?
You like sex, don't you?
I'll give you a lot of pills.
I told you.
You lick me, don't you?
Don't make a sexy face.
You lick my head, too.
Look at me.
You have a place to lick more, don't you?
You have a lot of tongue sticking out.
I'm going to take care of
my cats for a while, but I can't help it.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you feel good? I feel good.
Good boy.
Do you want to sleep?
Do you want to sleep, Aokuma?
You are so excited.
You have a lot of saliva.
You feel good, don't you?
Here, let me take care of you.
I remove the chair.
I pull out the chair.
What is this?
I love it!
Teach me!
This is a battery.
A battery?
And then?
Do you want
to go in? Please go in.
Please go in.
OK, I'll let you in.
It's like this as soon as you get in.
You love sex, don't you?
Are you feeling good?
You are not moving.
Are you saying that you are not moving?
Oh, you felt it too much.
You are saying that you are
feeling good because of your own squeaking.
What do you mean?
You are not moving yet.
You are not moving.
You are just opening your mouth.
What do you want to do?
Do you want me to put you down?
Are you surprised?
Oh, you are strong.
You are strong
because you want me to put you down.
Do you feel good?
I was able to make it.
It's a baby.
It's not a baby.
You'd better hold it.
Lie down.
It's a baby.
Spread your belly.
Give me your hand.
You have to put it in.
How are you?
Do you want me to do it?
Ok Ok, do it more.
Do it more.
Ok, ok.
Ok.
You can move as you like.
Don't kiss me too much.
Do you feel good?
They are very close to each other.
They are clinging to each other.
No, I can't.
I can't.
Good boy.
You are a big boy.
Stand up.
What's wrong with you, Misa?
Did you find
something? I found it.
Let's decide it.
Ready, set, go.
He seems to be in a good mood.
He is in a good mood.
Good boy.
He is a good boy.
He is good at controlling himself.
Lift your leg.
Lift your leg again.
Look at me.
Can you see where I put my hand?
You guys are so cheap.
What?
Can you see?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Oh, you drank it yourself.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
Let's take a bath.
This way, this way.
Do you like it?
Do you feel good?
I'll put you on the bed.
Poco is a little nervous.
You're feeling good enough to run.
Turn your head this way.
You are in a good mood, so I will put
you on the bed.
Please raise your body up.
You look like you want to be hugged.
You are surprised.
You are great.
Please hold this.
Do you want me to
put your legs down? Get up.
I'll put you on my nipples.
Move more.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Mura-chan, Mura-chan.
Raise one leg.
The other leg is behind you.
Look at me.
Look at the mirror from here.
Good boy, yes.
Mura-chan, you are too much.
Hold him.
Let's take his legs.
Let's take a bath
Good morning
Do you feel good?
Do you want to take a bath more deeply?
Today, I'm going to show you a video
of my cat, Yo-rai, who is in a good mood.
Yo-rai, who is in a
good mood, seems to be in a good mood.
You have the
cutest face when you are having sex.
Do you feel good?
I want you to open your mouth.
Can I open your mouth?
You want me to open your mouth, don't you?
Let's go to the vet.
You are sleepy.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you feel good?
Please get up.
Someone came.
Did someone call you? I'll go.
No.
Atma?
Higashiko?
No.
I'm sorry, Kibu-chan.
I'm sorry.
We'll search her for a crime of adultery.
Search.