Have you ever been in contact
with people from around the world?
No, I haven't.
You haven't?
No.
Is this your first time?
It's my first time.
Your first time?
Eh?
In private?
No, I haven't.
You haven't?
No, no, no.
Let's leave it at that.
You can tell me the truth.
No, no.
I'm worried about communication.
Ah, I see.
Yes.
Yeah, you're right.
There are some people who
can't speak Japanese well.
Konnichiwa.
Oh, you can say Konnichiwa.
Let me introduce you again.
This is Elena.
She is the actress Kitayama-chan.
I'm Kitayama.
Kitayama-chan.
Yes, Kitayama-chan, OK.
So, Elna-San,
today,
the shooting has already started.
Yes.
So,
today's shooting is a
one-day date with him.
OK.
What is your first impression of him?
He looks a bit like a Hong Konger.
Eh?
Compliment?
Is this a compliment?
It's a feeling of closeness
It's a feeling of closeness.
But it has a special feeling
Because it's a feeling
of love It feels different
It's a feeling of
closeness But it's exciting.
Exciting.
Exciting, I'm excited
too What's exciting?
It's very common
Yes, I'm excited.
So, today's plan is not just a date.
Actually, there is one more thing.
But, actually, I have a passport.
Yes.
During the date, I will send
you various instructions on LINE.
Yes, I see.
And you must follow these instructions.
I've never done this before.
I'm very nervous, but I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
I'll leave the phone number to you.
Please take it.
We're going home.
From here?
From here.
Please take care of me.
Nice to meet you.
I'm nervous.
Right?
Right.
It's amazing.
Let's go.
It's hot outside.
It's hot.
You are cute.
Thank you.
So cute.
Kitayama-chan.
Kitayama-chan Kitayama-kun
Kitayama-kun Let's go Let's go.
Lady first.
Nice.
Fashionable Fashionable
Fashionable Beautiful Beautiful Beautiful.
Do you like date?
Date?
Ok, ok.
Oh, I see what is this?
couple couple?
sex.
that's funny that's erotic
that's funny stay stay sit.
you're cute.
cute thank you.
so you understand kawaii
kawaii cute yes yes cute.
well that's good
ok ok.
let's go.
I don't know what to say
in English at a time like this.
I love Japan.
What do you like about Japan?
Everything.
I like everything.
I like the culture, the
food, and the people.
Japanese.
What food do you like?
Everything.
Sushi.
Sashimi.
Sushi. Sashimi.
Hot pot.
Yes, hot pot.
Sukiya.
Sukiyaki.
Sukiya The name of the
restaurant is Sukiya Sukiya.
Ok Let's go It's interesting.
Ok Let's go.
Cute Cute.
Okay, let's go.
Seat belt okay?
Okay.
It's okay.
You're good at Japanese.
I can speak English.
That's great.
Because I love Japan.
Let's go.
Okay.
From now on...
Where should we go?
Let's see... Date.
Date.
Leave it to me.
Leave it to me?
How much do you study Japanese?
Japanese... Study.
Study?
How long have you been studying Japanese?
How long?
It's embarrassing.
2 years?
But I take classes once a week.
But you're good at it.
I don't have the confidence
to speak Japanese.
That's not true.
You've been speaking Japanese for 2 years.
But you're good at it.
I'm not good at it.
Really?
What's your hobby?
What are your hobbies?
Chogin Chogin?
Chogin and.
Sexy.
Sexy?
Hobbies Sexy.
Eat.
Eat?
Yes, I do.
What's your favorite food?
My favorite food is... It doesn't
have to be Japanese food.
Uh...
buffet.
Buffet?
Yeah.
And...
all-you-can-eat.
Oh!
All-you-can-eat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Delicious, delicious.
All-you-can-eat, huh?
Yes.
I... Yes, because you
can eat a lot of food.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ah!
Yes?
The order has arrived.
The order.
The order?
Yeah. The order has arrived.
From the director.
Okay. From the director.
Um... Yes? Um...
Open the dashboard...
This one.
Wait a minute.
This...
What is this?
I heard that.
I have to give this to Elena.
What is it?
It's a present.
I'll give it to you.
Thank you.
What is this?
Oh!
Yes.
Do you know that?
I know.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Japanese...
Tobiko.
Tobiko. Tamago.
Tabiko Chinchin It's not
Chinchin It's not Chinchin.
This is...
How do you... Oh, yeah, yeah,
yeah If you push this Did it move?
It moved, it moved Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah This...
Like this In a place like this.
Your voice is a bit erotic.
Did it stop?
Yes.
Have you ever used it?
I don't think so.
Start?
Yes.
Do you know it?
I know it.
You can put it here like this.
Wow, you're so curious.
You're so curious.
Is it fun?
It's fun.
Is it correct?
It's correct.
Do you want to do it?
There's a new e-mail.
Wait a minute.
Do you want to press it?
Here we go.
It moved.
Wow.
Feels good?
4C4?
Did it stop?
No, no, no.
You have to enjoy it like this.
Fun.
Yeah, it's fun.
Since we're here, let's put it in here.
Right?
Let's leave it like this.
So sexy.
Sexy.
Sexy?
Yeah.
That's amazing.
Sexy, sexy.
But... Using this...
Don't go.
Don't go? OK.
You're not allowed to go.
That's the message from the director.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You have to be patient.
Patience.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
No, no.
No?
No, no, no, no, no.
Elena, you are so bold.
Yeah, I am.
Are you ready?
Are you?
Do you feel good?
You are so sexy.
Well, let's go to Odaiba.
Odaiba?
Odaiba.
Yes.
Wait a minute. I'll go there.
No, no, no.
Really, I'll go there.
I said no.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
You said it.
You have to be patient.
Patience.
I can't be patient.
You can't be patient?
Isn't this already clear?
We got the topic.
Right?
Let's wait for the next order.
Let's wait for it to come.
Take a picture of this.
Oh, it's wet.
What?
Wow.
It's in here.
Elena, you've been patient.
You've been patient.
How do you feel about me?
Eroic.
No, you're the one who's eroic!
You're the one who's eroic.
Eroic?
Yeah.
It's easy to be eroic.
I love it.
I'm glad to hear that.
We're here.
We're here!
Yay!
Sex!
It's not sex!
So erotic.
We're here!
Yay!
That's cute!
Yes.
What is that?
My face.
Anime.
Oh!
Wow!
Wow, wow, wow!
Cute!
Thank you.
It suits you.
So,
Now,
From the director again,
Yes.
A new message has arrived.
Here,
the two of us are on a date.
This is a date.
and you can use that.
Japanese Tobiko that you got
Japanese Tobiko you can use it.
and go on a date with it Ok?
I have this here.
You're so cute.
Thank you.
I'm sure you'll get it right.
Did you get it right?
I did.
You're good.
Wow, that's amazing.
No, no, no.
No, you can't.
Well, let's walk a little.
Did you stop?
Are you moving?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Let's go this way.
Let's go.
You have to be patient.
Be patient.
You have to open it by yourself.
No, no, no.
You will be exposed.
What?
It's amazing here.
Let's stop for a bit.
Did you stop?
Yeah.
I stopped.
Scenery?
Yeah, nice scenery.
Nice scenery.
Do you want to eat something?
Yes.
Do you want to eat ice cream?
Ice cream?
Yeah.
Right?
Right.
Nice.
Okay.
Hey!
Wow!
You're doing that again.
No, no, no.
Is it good?
It's good.
Did you eat it?
We're waiting for the rain to stop.
Let's wait and go to the hotel.
It's still raining.
Yes, it's raining.
Do you understand?
I'm sleepy.
Please take me to the
hotel as soon as possible.
OK. Let's go.
Let's go.
We have arrived.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
Look at this.
Isn't it beautiful?
The scenery is beautiful.
The scenery is beautiful?
Yes.
Look at this.
Don't do that.
I'm going to take a picture
of you, not the scenery.
No?
No, no, no.
Why not?
I got a new order from the director.
Yes.
When we get to the hotel,
we will have sex.
Yes.
But you already touched it
before the command came.
Yes.
No, no, no.
I got it, I got it. Wait a minute.
Shall we do it?
Etch.
Etch?
Sex.
Shall we do it?
Let's do it.
Oh, my God.
It's fast.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's not cold, so it's okay.
It's amazing.
That's crazy.
What's that?
That fast?
Oh my god.
I can't do it anymore
Oh, it's cold.
Wow Oh my god.
No.
It feels good.
I'm so hungry.
It's soft, isn't it?
I'm a little bit tired.
Oh, really?
What did you do?
I just did some stretching.
I'm not tired.
I feel really good.
I'm feeling good.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh,
my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my
God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh,
my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my Ah...
Ah... It's funny...
You're amazing...
Ah... It's amazing here...
Heang-Dee needs more
care to get album covers.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't believe I'm doing this to myself.
I can't stand up anymore.
I'm going to the bathroom.
It's so cold.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Wow, amazing.
Sit down.
Yes.
Open your legs.
Hmm...
Look at the camera Look at me.
Can I put it in?
Here... Ah... That's right...
Your elbow is on it.
That's right.
And...
Ah... Ah...
It's still there...
Doesn't it hurt?
It feels good!
Brutal... I can't
breathe at all.
I can't breathe.
I'm so happy... I'm so
happy... I'm so happy...
I'm so happy...
I can't do this.
I can't do this anymore...
I'm going to die...
Why?
I can't believe it.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
...
... ... ... ... ...
... ... ... ...
... ...
...
I can't do this... I can't
do this... 【The sound of
breathing】 Your voice is so
great 【The sound of breathing】.
I finally heard it.
【The sound of breathing】.
【The sound of breathing】
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah To the buttocks To the buttocks?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes Wow, amazing.
Now, put your hand here
Yes, yes, yes.
Wow, amazing.
Ah, it's so comfortable.
It's so comfortable.
I can't believe I'm doing this to myself.
Oh my god so hot...
Woah!!!
Tch?
Ah... Ah... Ah... Oh my
god... Oh... Ah... Hmm?
Ah... Ah... Ah...
I'm so scared!
My neck is f**king heavy cannot be
pushed I got a big one I'm so sleepy...
Wake up.
Wake up!
I'm sleepy...
I'm comfortable.
I'm so sleepy...
Ahhhh Ohhhh.
Ohhhhh Ohhhhh Ahhhhhh.
Ohhhh.
so comfortable.
so comfortable i can't make it.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
Can I put it out here?
ah.
shit ah I'm sorry I'm
sorry I want you ah ah.
ah ah ah ah ah.
Oh, my God.
I have a lot of breasts.
The baby is coming.
Let's take a bath together.
Do you like the bath?
I like it.
Let's take a bath slowly.
Let's take a bath together.
Let's take off the part
where the hair is sticking out.
Take it off.
Is it warm?
Yes, it's warm.
That's right.
What's that?
It's hot, isn't it?
It's cold.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Ah...
Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... Here...
You can...
you can pinch it.
Pinch?
Like this?
Yes, like this.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes.
I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Come on, Lala.
Ah...
Mm.
Mm... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Mmm.
Mm... Slurping...
You can do it, you can do it!
You can do it!
I'm going to get you!
Ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah.
The bell is ringing.
That's right.
Ah, ah.
Well, let's have a toast.
Yes, cheers.
Yes.
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
From the director again.
I see.
Do you know?
I know.
I'm scared.
It's time to do it.
You can use this to attack Elena.
Attack?
Which one do you want to start with?
Which one?
Do you want to start with this?
Do you know? Have you ever used it?
Yes, I know.
I've used it before.
You've used it before?
What?
But I don't have it.
Have you ever done it?
Yes.
I have.
I don't have it.
I see.
Let's start from here.
Let's go over there.
This way.
Since we are here,
look at the mirror and stand up.
Ecchi Ecchi.
You are Ecchi.
Yes yes yes.
Let's try this
Like this.
Oh.
You can see it.
Hehehe.
This is amazing Good girl.
You can say a lot.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm scared...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I can't breathe.
Uuu, uuu, uuuu
uu, uuu, uuuuuuu, uuu, uuu,
Aaaa...
That's amazing...
Aaaa... Zzz... I
can't take it anymore.
I can't take it anymore.
Take a deep breath.
Urgh!
Urgh Oh!
Urgh Urgh Urgh Here you are.
Show me your face.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, oh.
Okay, okay, okay.
You can go a lot
Like you did before.
I can't do it anymore.
How do you feel?
Good.
I feel good.
Good?
Yes.
It's hard but I feel good.
The director is calling you again.
I have a message for you.
Wait a minute.
I see.
You should use an eye
mask and do something erotic.
OK.
Can you do it?
Can I do it?
Yes.
Can you do it by yourself?
OK.
You can't see it, can you?
I'll put it here.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You have a lot of blood.
You are very wet.
Do you get excited when you can't see?
Yes, I do.
You're so wet.
I want to go home.
I can't believe I'm doing this to myself.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Wow, amazing.
Nina, do you want me to put this in?
What is it?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Do you want it?
I want more
I want more more?
what do you want?
I want more.
I want more I
like it I want more.
It's so heavy.
I'm so tired.
Don't do that.
What?
More.
More?
I'm so tired.
Take it off.
I'm sorry.
I feel so much pain
Try to move like this.
Yes yes Like this.
Oh, my god!
I'm so tired.
I feel like I'm suffocating.
I know.
What should I do?
Do you want me to do it?
Yes!
I can't do it.
Can I do it?
I can't take it anymore.
How do you feel?
It's so hot It's
so hot It's so hot.
It's so hot I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's go.
Give me your tongue.
How was your day today?
It was so comfortable. I was so relaxed.
Are there any Japanese
men you want to date?
I want to date a Japanese man.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Because they are
really good at doing it It's
really comfortable Giving
me another experience.
But in terms of Japanese,
I have to work harder.
Thank you for today Thank you.
See you!