The next day
Good morning!
Yes!
I'm sorry to
interrupt, but... Yes!
Could you bring the tea for
the customers to the tea room?
Yes!
It was really good.
Really? Look, look.
Look, isn't the level high?
Wow, it's so dark.
By the way, are you doing this?
Yes, look at this.
I can't see anything.
This is the first time I've ever met such a cute girl
Make an appointment? It's open.
It's open on the weekend.
60 minutes?
You can do it in 120 minutes.
It's long.
You can do it.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Mr.Matsuda and Mr.Kato are
talking about something strange again.
I'm in a bad mood.
Is that so?
Ms.Nene, can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
I know that you came here today.
The company's order is not very good.
So I have to make a quick decision.
I have to cut my hair.
It's not right away, but I'm going
to cut my hair for half a year.
I think they're pretty
beautiful at any time.
I think I can make
money by working at night.
That's right.
Can I leave it to you?
Yes, please leave it to me.
That's what I'm talking about.
You came when I was coming.
It was comfortable.
What should I do if he cuts my hair?
I have to go home.
Yoshitaka, Honda, can I
talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
I have something to tell you, but
it'll be over in about 10 minutes.
Yes.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Then, let's meet in the conference room.
Yes.
Is it the same as before?
Isn't it too early?
Mr. Matsuda, you are quick to judge.
It's dangerous.
Don't worry.
I have a good idea.
Really?
Don't make such a serious face.
Don't do that.
How are you doing
these days? As usual.
Me, too.
As usual?
As usual is the best, isn't it?
Don't you think so?
What?
You thought I was going
to eat you, didn't you?
You didn't think so, did you?
Then, I'll go straight to the point.
I'll terminate the contract
with you this month.
Well, I'm heartbroken, too.
I see. However, considering the company's
situation, I had no choice but to do this.
Well, from my point of view,
you two have been doing well.
Taking advantage of the company's experience,
I will do my best for the next step.
What is it?
Mr. Matsuda, I fully understand.
What?
The company is in a bad situation, and we
have no choice but to cancel the delivery.
But I don't understand.
Why is it full this month?
Can't we get a little more?
I'm thinking about the company's situation.
I told you we could wait a little longer.
I had no choice but to do
this to keep the company safe.
Don't say that. You're a virgin.
I'm not a virgin.
You are.
No, I'm not.
I heard what Kato-san said.
Momo-chan.
What is it?
You're a virgin, aren't you?
I'm a virgin, so what is it?
You know, don't you?
I heard what Kato-san said.
I've heard that you're a virgin.
So, what is it?
You're a virgin.
I'm going to expose you to the public.
Please don't do that.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
To be exposed as a virgin.
No, it's not embarrassing.
If you don't want to be exposed, If you
don't like it, please take back what I said.
If you do, I'll do the best thing for you.
What?
The best thing?
You can't invite a girl
because you're old, right?
That's not true.
You're cute.
We'll teach you how to be a woman.
What's going on?
Mr. Matsuda.
It's your first time to be
naked in front of a girl, isn't it?
Is it my first
time? No, it's not.
Please show me your virginity.
Please show me.
Please don't.
Mom, let's take off your clothes first.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
I'll take off your clothes.
Please be quiet.
Mom, wait a minute.
What is it? I'll touch you.
Wait a minute.
You have a weak neck.
Do you have a
fever? No, I don't.
Do you feel good?
Just a little bit.
Be more honest.
Be a good boy.
Your necktie is about to fall off.
Let's take it off.
Let's take your head off, too.
No, that's...
No, wait a minute.
It's okay.
Show me how you hold your head.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
I'm not a monster.
Don't worry.
You're really happy to hear
that, aren't you? No, I'm not.
You have a big neck.
It's so soft.
Stop it.
You're so cute, aren't
you? No, I'm not.
What are you doing, Yoshitaka-san?
Your body is so shiny.
Do you feel it? No, I don't.
I don't feel anything.
You said such a thing.
You have a very pleasant face.
You have a voice.
No, I don't.
Do you want me to
lick you? No, I don't.
Let's lick together.
You licked me.
Look at me.
Matsuda-san, you are so cute.
No, I'm not.
You are annoying.
You are cute.
What's the matter with
you two? I'm having fun.
It's been a long time since I've
had a baby, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm not pregnant.
You're a pervert, aren't you?
Be honest with me.
I'm sorry.
Komomo-chan.
Yes?
Do you want me to take it off?
Yes.
Please don't do that.
I'm sorry.
How long have you been standing?
I haven't been standing.
You haven't been standing.
You have been standing.
Matsuda-san.
You haven't been standing.
I'm not standing up.
Is your belly
bulging? No, it's not.
Let me see your belly.
I'm not standing up.
Let me see.
Show me your face.
You have a cute face.
What do you want me to do?
Show me your face.
I don't want you to do anything.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it if you tell me.
Please be more honest.
We'll go home.
Is that okay?
That's a little...
You look like you feel good.
It's getting harder and harder.
How do you feel
now? It's a little.
..
Both of you...
It's a little...
I didn't know there was a place like this.
It's very erotic.
You're laughing,
aren't you? No, I'm not.
Then why are you standing
like this? No, I'm not.
I'm not standing.
You're not standing, are you?
No way.
You're standing a lot.
I'm not standing.
You are a pervert, aren't
you, Katsura-san? No, I'm not.
Katsura-san, please follow me.
How do you feel? I feel good.
Please don't move.
How do you feel when you
are touched by someone?
I'll touch you a lot.
Please stop.
Your voice is coming out.
Can you make it louder?
What are you doing?
Your lower teeth are coming out.
Do you like to be patted on the butt?
I don't like it.
I'll make you feel better.
How do you feel?
I don't feel anything.
You are making a voice.
You are shaking a lot.
Your nipples are very hard.
You are getting more and more beautiful.
You are so cute.
I can't touch you.
You have grown up a lot.
Momo-chan, try to touch you.
I want to touch you.
You are right.
You are amazing.
Why did you grow up so much?
Do you feel good?
I haven't grown up.
I'm not strong.
You are strong.
You are stronger than before.
Don't show your face.
No, I won't.
You look very patient.
No, I'm not.
Don't pretend to be strong.
What are you
doing? I'm not strong.
I'm going to tickle you a lot.
Isn't it hard to stand
up? It's very hard.
It's amazing here.
I'm going to tickle you a lot.
How do you feel?
What did you do at
first? It's very hard.
It looks painful.
It's getting harder and harder.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this,
and it's been a long time
since I've seen a cat like this.
I'm not sure if it's because it's been
a long time since I've seen a cat like
this, or if it's because it's been a
long time since I've seen a cat like this.
I'm not sure if it's because it's been
a long time since I've seen a cat like
this, or if it's because it's been a
long time since I've seen a cat like this.
I'm not sure if it's because it's been
a long time since I've seen a cat like
this, or if it's because it's been a
long time since I've seen a cat like this.
It's been a long time
since I've had a baby, so
I'm a little nervous, but
I'm going to do my best.
You look like you can't take it anymore.
Do you want to
go out? No, I don't.
Do you think you can
I see.
I'll touch here.
Tama-chan, how do
you feel? I feel great.
I'm impressed.
I'm glad to see you doing
such a wonderful thing.
It's our first time, right?
If you make a loud
noise, they can hear you.
I'm sorry.
You like to be licked by me.
You have a lot of favorite places.
You can't stand it
anymore, can you? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's so hard.
Let's do it together.
How is it? It's great.
Don't get up.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
You look cute.
Show me more.
You're slimy.
You're so slimy.
You're sticky.
Atsumi-san, I'm going
to protect you tomorrow.
Or, do your best to improve your grades.
If you do your best, I'll do
something nice for you again.
She's gone.
What did the manager say?
I'll leave it all to you.
I won't forgive you if your grades drop.
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
Let's do our best together.
What's wrong with your face?
What's wrong?
Are you worried about your face?
Or are you expecting
something? You are cute.
I'm expecting something.
You are honest.
You have a good face.
You promised me.
Let's do something sexy.
What do you want us
to do? Please answer.
What do you want us to do?
I want you to kiss me.
Kiss you?
Please answer.
If you don't answer, I won't kiss you.
Please kiss me.
Look into my eyes and say it.
Show me your tongue.
I'll lick your ears.
You like it, don't you, Chikurin?
Please let me lick you more.
I'm happy to be licked by you two.
That's right.
I'm very nervous.
Hey, take off your necktie
by yourself this time.
I got it.
I'm going to kiss you.
Mr.Orikoro.
So, next, take off your clothes.
Take off your button.
You want to kiss, don't you?
I want to kiss you.
Oh, great!
Ouch!
Utsuha-san is twitching.
Cute!
You want me to touch you
directly, don't you? Don't be shy.
You have a round neck.
I'm going to touch you.
Do you like to be touched?
You really have a round neck.
I'm nervous every time I touch you.
Are you trying to
lick me? No, I'm not.
Be honest.
I'm not.
Make a wish.
Make a wish with a voice you can hear.
I'm going to give you a massage.
You look so good.
Can you hear me if I speak too loud?
Your nipples are very hard,
aren't they? It's very hard.
It's hard.
It's cute.
Your nipples are really weak, aren't they?
They are sensitive.
Shall I pinch your
nipples? Yes, please.
Your nipples are twitching the most.
You like to be patted on the neck
while being licked on the ears, don't you?
Are you nervous? No, I'm not.
You're sweating a lot.
You're right.
Please stop.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do next?
Please take off your jacket.
You can take it off, right?
Yes.
Do you want to take it off by yourself?
I didn't expect you to get
bigger just by doing this.
What?
I'm getting bigger.
You haven't touched it yet?
You're so sensitive.
What do you want
me to do? Look at me.
Please touch me.
Say it again.
Is that so?
What should I do? I can't hear you.
Please touch me.
I'm going to listen to your wish.
It's very hard.
Wow, it's big.
I'm going to give you both.
You are sticky.
Your body is twitching.
If you move like this, I can't touch you.
Your lips are wrinkled.
Please take off your panties by yourself.
Okay.
Please take off your panties.
Hariko.
Do you want me to touch you directly?
Do you want me to touch you?
Please touch me directly.
You have a lot of pimples.
You're still a virgin, aren't you?
A virgin?
What should I do?
Mimmy is good at touching.
Do you want to touch it?
I want to touch it.
You don't want to
touch it? Wow, amazing.
It's hard.
I'm going to give you a snack.
Do you want to eat it?
Look at me when I'm licking you.
Look at me.
Your penis is hard.
I don't think it's going to work.
It's getting bigger.
Don't do that.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to do this?
You are so kind.
Do you feel good?
It's your first time, isn't it?
I'm going to take a bath.
You are taking a bath.
Oh, are you Nami? You are mean.
You are Nami.
Wow!
Do you feel good?
It's your first time, isn't it?
Wow!
I should have learned this.
Great.
You look tired.
What's wrong?
Where?
Do you feel pain? Yes, I do.
Let me see.
I want to touch you more.
You are really greedy.
I want to touch you.
Do you want to touch me?
What should I do? Do me a favor.
Do me a favor.
I want to touch you.
I couldn't hear you.
Let me touch your boobs.
It can't be helped.
You are so stubborn.
You will be found out.
I'm sorry.
What should I do? Be gentle.
Please tell me.
This is how you touch.
Lie on your back.
Be gentle.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Good.
What kind of face is that?
You look like you want something.
What's wrong?
You can't help it.
I'll take it off, too.
It's impossible.
Do you want to see
the inside? Yes, I do.
What should I do?
What should I do? Please.
Please show me more.
Please show me.
I want to see your boobs in person.
You're greedy, aren't you?
You're getting more and more honest.
It's getting hot,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
Do you want to see my boobs?
Yes.
Look at them carefully.
Look at this side, too.
Can I touch them?
Look at them carefully.
You can't stand it?
You look like you want to touch it.
I want to touch it.
You are a good boy, Matsuda-san.
Be gentle.
You are getting better than before.
Let's take a bath.
You can touch me.
You look like you want to touch me.
You don't have to.
I want to lick you.
Do you want to lick me?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
Did you brush your teeth properly?
I want to lick your boobs.
Can you do it one more time?
It's cute, so I'll forgive you.
Can you lick from this side?
Can you do it gently?
You look like a baby.
Let me touch your nipple.
You look so comfortable.
You are so cute.
Let me touch your nipple.
Does it feel good?
You have a lot of hair.
Both of you?
Are you really a
virgin? One to three.
Have you always wanted to do this?
You are a happy person, aren't you?
It's the first time for three of us.
That's good.
Next time, I want to look down more.
Do you want to look down?
Yes.
Can't you be satisfied with just this?
Are you really greedy?
I want to look well.
Look carefully.
Look at me.
Look at me, too.
You're thinking about
something, aren't you? Look at me.
I want to lick you.
Do you want to be licked?
Yes.
It's your first time
to be licked, isn't it?
You can lick me as you like.
You don't have to be shy. Be gentle.
There.
Yes, gentle.
You look shy in this outfit.
You look like a doggy.
I did it.
You look comfortable.
It feels good.
You are good at it.
Do you feel your
nipples? It feels good.
It feels so good.
You are good at licking.
Are you licking me gently?
It feels so good.
You are good at licking.
Don't you stop?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You look like a prince.
You don't have to do that.
Let's go back.
Are we going back?
Do you feel
uncomfortable? No, I don't.
Aren't you going to do it?
Do what?
I mean, if you come all the way
here... Because I've become like this?
Do you want me to steal your virginity?
Yes.
What are you
going to do? Please.
Yes.
Then, let's start with me.
Please.
May I?
I'm glad you said it was your first time.
I'm happy.
Then, lie down there.
Yes.
Are you nervous?
I'm going to massage your back.
I can feel it.
I can see your whole body.
I feel good.
You have a good temper.
You are growling.
You don't go out right
away, do you? No, you don't.
You should be careful when you go out.
Do you like to be petted?
Please wait a moment.
How do you feel inside me?
You look very comfortable.
Take a deep breath.
You are panting.
You are panting a lot.
You have a cute voice.
I know what you are thinking now.
You want to lick my teeth, don't you?
Do you want to lick my teeth?
You have grown up in love.
Did you want to kiss me?
Do you want me to kiss you?
This is the first time for me
to see a baby who is crying.
He is a genius.
I can't do it anymore.
How does it feel to be hugged
by two people? It feels good.
I'll give you a lot.
This is the first time I've ever seen a
baby crying like this, and I'm very happy.
I'm so happy that I can't help but cry.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm glad I was able to film this video.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I was surprised to see
a baby crying like this.
I'm so nervous.
You are still in a good mood.
Can you still bear it?
You shouldn't do it yet.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
Look at me.
Do you feel ticklish?
I feel ticklish.
Do you feel good?
You like my ears, don't you?
I can't believe that I'm
going to be a mother.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to go to bed.
I'm going to bed.
I'm so sleepy.
You're a good girl.
You're growling a lot.
I'm going to bed.
It's been a long time.
Say it properly.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's right.
I was really surprised.
She's holding back.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
I'm going to give you a massage.
You seem to be in a good mood.
What's wrong with you?
I want to do it too.
It's like I've been stuck
in here for a long time.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, over there.
Ouch!
I'm going to cry.
I'm glad you like it.
Nini-san, how do you feel
about Matsuda-san's kiss?
It's annoying, but it was
better than I expected.
That's good.
Then, I'll do it next time.
Excuse me.
I'll do it next time.
That's good.
I'm going to put it in.
Look at me when I put it in.
It's just like you said.
It feels good even though I'm a virgin.
I'm so happy.
I can move.
I feel so good.
I want to touch you.
How do you feel? I feel good.
I'm glad that you love him.
I'm glad that I could have
sex with you for the first time.
I feel good.
I'm glad.
You are making a good progress.
What do you think
of me? I feel good.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
You can't go yet.
Wow!
What happened to
you? I'm a pervert.
A pervert.
I'm sorry.
You were moving, weren't you?
Can you move again?
Can you do it
properly? I'm so scared.
I'm so scared.
I feel so bad.
What's that? Help me.
You're crying, aren't you?
I'm going to be full.
What's wrong?
You look beautiful.
Are you alright?
Are you nervous?
How do you feel?
Can you bear with it?
You just got out of the toilet.
You are a virgin.
You're a virgin.
I'm glad you graduated as a virgin.
How was it, Momo-chan?
It was a great kindergarten.
I'm glad.
Hey, Ringo.
Let's do our best together from now on.
Let's do our best.
We're going to do your job today.
You have to heal our tired lower body.
Please heal me.
I'm counting on you.
I'll go first.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Do you know where Matsuda is?
I haven't seen him.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Where did he go?
Mr. Matsuda, are you doing it right?
Are you OK?
Kondo-kun, can you bring me the
ceremony I asked you to do last time?
I'll bring it right away.
How is it?
Like this? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Please be careful.
Matsuda-san, do it properly.
Do you want me to stop?
Take off your jacket.
It's okay.
Come on.
Nene-san, take a rest.
That's all.
Take off your top, too.
If you don't say anything,
Matsuda-san won't find out.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry.
Keep massaging.
Matsuda!
It's time to go home.
Where did you go?
You are good at massaging.
Keep massaging.
You look like you like it.
Massage here.
You are happy, aren't you?
You are excited, aren't you?
You want to lick me again, don't you?
I can tell by looking at your face.
You want to lick me, don't you?
Well, make yourself comfortable.
Come on.
Look at me.
How do you feel
now? I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Why are you eating so hard?
Yes.
Can I give you 10 minutes to prepare
for tomorrow's meeting? Yes, it's OK.
Go on.
You can do it.
You can do it more comfortably, can't you?
Matsuda-san, isn't it great?
You did a good job.
I'll give you a reward
for finishing your work.
Your massage felt good,
so I finished all your work.
If you're forced to do it,
you have to do it again.
Do you want me to put your wings down?
I'll put them down.
Good morning.
You are very sleepy, aren't you?
You feel good, don't you?
You loved my nipples, didn't you?
I felt it a lot.
I'll give you a lot more.
I'll give you a massage.
It's getting really crunchy.
I can see it from the top of your shirt.
Does it feel good?
I'm really surprised.
You're good at turning.
You're good at it, too.
Do you want me to lick you
from the top of your clothes?
What?
Does it feel good from
the top of your clothes?
You are so sensitive.
It's so crunchy.
Yes, you are.
Amazing.
It is hot, isn't it?
No, it's just a bit.
I just licked your nipple.
I'm just licking my lips.
Do you want me to make you feel better?
You look so mean.
You don't have to be shy.
Let's take off your clothes.
It's a reward for your hard work.
You felt good just now.
It's better to do it directly.
You're more nervous than before.
Let's lick your lips.
Oh, it's so crunchy.
I want to lick you a lot.
How do you feel being licked by two girls?
I'm going to make you feel better.
Mami-chan, let's brush your
teeth more and make them sticky.
Let's do it.
Your nipples are wet.
You really love your nipples.
I want to give you a
lot if you feel like this.
It feels good to be kissed
on the tongue, doesn't it?
You like to be kissed, don't you?
Let's check how Chinchin is doing.
Can you check, Momo-chan?
He's getting bigger.
Cute.
He was so nervous.
Today, feel as much as you want.
I'll give you a lot.
Let's take off your pants.
I'll take it off.
Your voice sounds painful.
I'll make you comfortable.
I'll take it off.
Your voice is hoarse.
You are a pervert after all.
Pervert.
Do you want me to touch you?
I'm just making a noise.
I'm just playing with you.
I'll give you a lot of strawberry.
Do you like the first one?
I'll touch your nipples.
You already know everything you like.
You have a lot of pimples.
You are so cute.
I'll give you a lot of pimples.
That's good.
It makes a good sound.
Let me touch you next time.
Mimmy will touch you.
Well, I'll lick your nipples.
You're right.
It's very hard.
It's like a love bottle.
And there's a lot of gum gel.
You're so mean.
What's wrong with this nipple?
Tell me the truth.
Do you want me to lick your cheeks?
You did your best to massage me.
It was very pleasant.
You like both the nipples
and the nipples, don't you?
You're not serious yet,
but you're so excited.
What if I do more than this?
You can move your head, can't you?
You're hungry, aren't you?
You feel good even if your
legs are cold, don't you?
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Are you going to spit it out?
Are you going to
spit it out? It's scary.
You are making a funny sound.
You can do like this.
You are making a funny face.
You are so cute.
You can still do it, right?
What are you doing?
You can do it, right?
Nene-san, you are mean.
Let's touch your nipples a lot.
Let me see your nipples.
You have a very nice smell.
Are you going to do that?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm so happy.
It's wet.
It's amazing.
Are you panting?
You're panting a lot.
It's the best to drink outside, isn't it?
The room of the chief is so
comfortable that it's amazing.
You look happy.
You look very happy.
Do you want me to mix
you a drink? Yes, I do.
Is it good?
What is it? I love you.
Do you want to do
something sexy? Yes, I do.
Let's close our eyes.
I know you feel good.
You like to be close to me, don't you?
Does it feel good?
It tastes like sake.
How does it taste? Look at us.
Look at me.
How do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Don't make a sound.
Do you want me to give you a kiss?
I've been drinking for a
while, and I feel much better.
Your neck is getting warmer.
I am a little worried that I can't get
a lot of sleep because I have a baby.
I'm worried about my baby's health.
I'm sorry to bother you.
What's going on?
You like it, don't you?
You're doing it.
You're closing your eyes.
You're cute.
Do you feel good?
What do you want
me to do next? Tell me.
I want you to touch me directly.
What do you want to do?
What should I do?
Please ask me more.
Please touch me directly.
Directly?
Yes.
I can't help it.
Let's take off your clothes.
I'm glad you are so kind.
You look like a baby.
You are surprised.
You are not used to it yet.
You are so cute.
Momo-chan, are you a little bit nervous?
You are going to be found out.
You are having fun.
Wow!
You are a good girl.
I'll do more naughty things for you.
She is melting.
You are still a baby.
You look like a baby.
You have a cute voice.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You've become very flexible.
Your body is getting bigger.
I'm getting more and more like Ichi.
Get up.
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm going to melt.
This is the first time for you, isn't it?
Are you happy? Yes, I am.
This is great.
Are you having fun?
You can breathe out.
You are cute.
I'm sorry I couldn't help but cry.
Maybe you're going to go.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Did you feel good? I feel good.
You've grown a lot bigger than before.
You're right.
Great.
Let me touch you.
It's warm.
Does it feel good?
Momoka is a mother of five children.
Momoka is the oldest in the family.
Momoka's mother is Momoka.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
I've never seen a cat like this before,
and I've never seen a cat like this before.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous.
I can't open my chest.
I'm going to close my eyes.
It's very slimy.
This is the first time to watch her.
She is a very good girl.
Come here.
Sit here.
You look comfortable.
Good boy.
Sit down.
You are licking me like a baby.
I love you so much.
Do you feel good?
How do you feel?
It's starting to feel good.
Let me see.
Give me your hand.
Don't look at me.
You can do whatever you like.
I'm scared.
I'll give you a little more.
You look so happy.
It's been a long time since
I've had a baby, so I'm a little
nervous, but I'll do my best
to take good care of him.
I can't stand it, so can you
put it in for me? It's a baby.
Can you make me
feel good? Yes, I will.
Then I'll take it off.
Let me take it off.
You still look like a virgin.
Do you want me to put it from behind?
I'll touch your neck.
Are you in there?
Now, move properly.
Move properly.
Please make him feel good.
I sleep too much.
Next, I'll make you feel good.
Next, my turn.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
What should I do?
It's not enough.
It's not enough, right?
What should I do? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting older.
I'm a little sleepy.
I can't stop.
I'm sorry.
I want to join you next time.
I can move,
right? Oh, it's cold.
It's heavy.
I'm getting tired.
I'm getting old.
It's getting hot.
Let me touch your chest.
It's hot.
How was it? It felt good.
I'll move you next.
Lie down here.
It's all in.
This is the first time I've ever seen a
cat like this, and I'm so happy to see it.
I'm so happy to see a cat like
this, and I'm so happy to see it.
It's not good yet.
Are you still in a bad mood?
Are you OK?
I can't stop laughing.
Nene-san, your waist is moving.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this,
and I'm glad I was able
to see it for the first time.
This time it's my turn.
You look like you're having a hard time.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm sorry.
You are so big.
You are so cute when
you make a lot of noises.
You are going to fall down.
I was worried that he was getting out
of bed, but he was getting a lot of sleep.
He is still sleeping.
Hey.
Don't you want to go out?
No.
You still want to go
out, don't you? Yes, I do.
I want to go out with Nene-san.
Do you want to go out?
Hmm.
How do you want to go out?
I want to go out in a normal way.
OK.
Pervert.
I'm sorry.
I made you feel better.
You're getting better.
You're getting better and better.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
I'm going to cry.
How do you feel? I don't know.
I feel so good, too.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
The baby is too energetic.
I'm sorry.
You can do it,
right? I can't do it.
It's hard.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.