Good morning.
Please introduce yourself to the camera.
I'm Yuko Kono.
I'm his predecessor.
How many times have you
appeared as a predecessor?
I think I've appeared about 20 times.
I think so.
19 times.
Ah, 19 times.
Last year.
You've been a predecessor for a long time,
so I think you have a
high potential for eroticism.
That's my conclusion.
Do you have a self-awareness?
No, I don't.
I don't know myself at all.
You don't have a self-awareness.
I think you're very erotic.
Thank you.
By the way, you look like
you're having fun while shooting.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Do you think that area is serious?
Yes, it's serious.
I think it's better not to go too far.
On the contrary.
Yes, as a professional.
There are times when I can't do that.
You don't lie.
I don't lie.
I have a special project for you.
What is it?
I'll announce it someday.
I'm scared.
I have to prepare my mind.
What is it?
Yes, it's okay.
Thank you.
This time.
I'm going to invite a
lot of strong MV actors.
A lot.
I'm going to invite a
lot of strong MV actors.
MV actors?
What is it?
With a large number of people?
Yes.
I want you to have a non-stop sex.
Non-stop sex?
It's my first time.
It's your first time in your life.
Yes.
It looks amazing.
Is it okay?
Do you know how long it is?
Is it about 2 hours?
It's about 2 hours.
2 hours?
That's amazing.
It's amazing.
How long do you think it will be?
I don't know.
How many times?
I don't know at all.
I'm getting nervous.
Please do your best.
I'm going to change
the length of this video.
I'm going to make it more exciting.
I have no choice but to do it.
Can I go home safely?
I'm nervous.
I've been doing this for a long time.
I'm going to do my best.
Are you nervous?
How many people are there?
I'm looking forward to the replay.
I prepared this.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to going home early.
Are you ready?
Let's get started.
Ready.
Start.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm going to change
the length of this video.
My back is moving.
I'm going to change
the length of this video.
Do you like to be licked?
I'm going to change
the length of this video.
Do you like it?
Do you like to be licked?
Please turn back.
Show me your back.
That's good.
Do you feel good?
Show me your back.
That's good.
I'm pulling the string from your belly.
Open your chest.
Open your chest more.
That's good.
Open your mouth.
Open your eyes.
That's good.
Show me your back.
Let's do it while spitting.
Let's walk.
There are many of you.
Let's go to the other room.
That's good.
Do you want to touch her?
Touch her.
That's good.
There are many of you.
Can I put you on my back?
Let's go to the other room.
She fainted.
That's good.
Let's go to the other room.
Let's continue.
That's good.
Show me your back.
Let's go to the other room.
That's good.
Let's do it while spitting.
Let's go to the other room.
That's good.
Let's do it while spitting.
It's hard.
It feels good.
That's good.
Are you satisfied?
Do you want more?
I want more.
It's easy for you to get
a pimple on your nose.
That's good.
I went too far.
Did you go too far?
I'm going to get a pimple on my nose.
It feels good.
Do you want more?
That's good.
Let's go to the other room.
Let's do it while spitting.
That's good.
You still have a long way to go.
Let's do it while spitting.
I'm looking forward to it.
That's good.
I've been waiting for you.
I prepared lingerie for you.
Can you put it on me?
Yes.
That's good.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
You have a pimple on your nose.
That's good.
Let's do it while spitting.
You have a pimple on your nose.
Do you want more?
That's good.
Let's do it while spitting.
You're crying a lot.
Does it feel good?
Let's do it while spitting.
You have a pimple on your nose.
You still have a pimple.
Let's do it while spitting.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Let's do it while spitting.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
That's good.
Let's do it while spitting.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Let's do it while spitting.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Let's do it while spitting.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Let's do it while spitting.
Does it feel good?
Thank you for your hard work.
Can you speak?
I can't speak.
Thank you for your hard work.
I don't have much time
to hear your thoughts.
Congratulations on the
success of the project.
Thank you very much.
You had a lot of potential.
Thank you.
Please tell me your honest thoughts.
I can't speak.
How many times did you say that?
I can't remember.
Please say a word to your fans.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry I can't speak.
Please continue to support me.