Can I join you? Yes, you can.
It's good.
I want to touch it.
Is it that good?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it feels good.
Wow.
It's so big, isn't it, Chin-chin?
Don't go in there. It's too big.
Can I go in there?
Sure, go ahead.
It's so wet.
Your skin is so clean.
It's so clean.
It's cold.
It's delicious.
It's great.
It feels good.
There is a tent near here.
Isn't there a mountain?
No, there isn't.
There is no mountain, but it's very hot.
The beach is next to the beach.
It's a road.
I heard the story earlier.
I want to go to the insect farm.
I want to go.
Do they eat honey? I don't know.
What do they eat?
Is this a waterfall?
Let's get out of here.
Don't worry about it.
Excuse me.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm fine.
Is it OK if I take a bath
with you? Of course.
I didn't bring my swimsuit
because I didn't know this bath.
I see.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
It feels good.
Yes, it does.
Are you students?
Are you a student? Yes, I am.
I see.
Do you go to the same school?
What kind of friends do you have?
We all go to the same school.
I see.
Do you come here often?
This is my first time.
I see.
This is my first time to come here.
Isn't everyone a little far away?
No, it's my first time.
Can I talk to you a little
closer? No, I'm sorry.
If you don't mind.
Really?
Yes.
Then, excuse me.
Thank you.
Can I sit here? Yes, please.
Did everyone come by car today?
Did you come by
boat? I can drive.
Oh, you can drive.
That's great.
Am I in the way? No, no, no.
You don't have
to worry about it.
You can stay with us.
Why do you want me to stay with you?
I came here by myself.
I see.
That's great.
How old are all the
students? 21 years old.
Oh, you are young.
Because you are an old lady.
No, I'm not an old lady.
You don't look like an old lady.
No, I'm not. I'm 21 years old.
It's been many years.
Are you married? Yes, I am.
I am married.
But I don't come here with my husband.
I come here alone.
Do you go on a trip with
your girlfriend? No, I don't.
I don't go where I want to go.
Really? What do you mean?
I don't have a girlfriend.
I see.
I've never had a girlfriend.
You've never had a
girlfriend? No, no, no.
I'm from Rakumatsu prefecture.
I see.
Have you ever watched it with
your ex-girlfriend? No, I haven't.
Really?
Everyone around me has.
I see.
But everyone is so cool.
You can do it right away,
can't you? No, no, no.
If I can't do it for 20
years, I'll lose confidence.
Really? I don't know.
I don't have confidence at all.
I want to have a girlfriend.
What can you do to have
a girlfriend? I don't know.
I think it would be nice if I was
the same age as everyone else.
Really? I'm sorry.
I think it would be nice if I was
the same age as everyone else.
Thank you.
It feels good. It's been a while
since I came to a place like this.
Yes, it's been a while.
It's good.
Is it? Yes, it is.
I'm nervous.
Really?
Isn't it too far?
Can you come a little closer?
Yes.
It's better to be closer.
Do you have any
friends? Not at all.
Really?
It's more fun to talk with everyone.
I don't know how far it is.
If you make a mistake, it's scary.
Really? Not at all.
Isn't it easier to
talk here? Certainly.
I thought no one would come here.
Me, too.
I thought young people would come here.
Yes, they do.
I'm glad I came here today.
You're lucky to have met her.
I should have brought my swimsuit.
I forgot.
I want to see you today, but I can't.
I don't need it.
Really?
It's so beautiful,
isn't it? I'm so happy.
If you are a young girl
like us, it's better to be
a young girl than an old woman
like me, isn't it? No, no, no.
I don't think so.
I don't have any needles.
I don't feel anything.
I'm absorbing everything.
I think you have a lot of needles.
Try touching it.
May I?
I'll try.
Touch it properly.
It's so soft.
It's very soft and feels good.
Really?
Yes.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
It's amazing.
What?
Do you want to touch it?
Can I?
Yes.
I feel like I'm being sucked in.
Really? I'm so happy.
Your skin is beautiful.
It's so white.
You don't go out,
do you? No, no, no.
I don't go out.
It's good.
I think it's really good.
I see.
I'm old, but I feel like I'm
getting energy from everyone.
Really?
I feel like I'm getting more energy.
Really? Yes, really.
By the way, everyone's reaction is so cute.
Really?
I've never been told that.
Really? Excuse me.
Excuse me, I'm watching you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You said you've never
had a girlfriend, right?
Yes.
Have you ever had such an experience?
What?
No.
What about you?
What?
I've never had such an experience.
What? You haven't?
What?
No comment, please.
It's a secret.
It's cute.
But you don't like it, do you?
What don't you like?
I don't know what a man
without experience is like.
It's embarrassing and
I don't want to do it.
Really? Isn't it cute?
I didn't know you could do that.
I thought it was cute.
Do you want to see my boobs?
What?
Are you serious?
Do you want to see
them? No, I don't.
Well, this is.
..
No, I'm fine.
I want to show them to you.
I want to see them.
Do you want to see
them? Then, let's go.
Wow!
It's so beautiful.
Have you ever seen
boobs? Yes, I have.
I've seen them in the middle
of a pornographic video.
Oh, really?
In a pornographic video?
Yes.
I see.
It's the first time I've
seen them in real life.
I don't know what I should do.
What should you do?
I don't know what to do.
I think it's beautiful.
It's really beautiful.
Do you want to touch it?
What should I do?
Can I touch it?
Can I touch your belly?
Yes.
What?
What? No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Can I touch your belly?
Yes.
Really?
Let's touch it together.
Ready, set, go!
It's pretty big, isn't it?
Is it? I think it's H.
H?
It's huge!
Really?
It's really big.
I've never heard of it.
Is that so?
I'm going to touch the edge cup.
It's really soft.
You can touch it.
Like this? Yes, you can.
I want to touch it.
Is it that good?
Wow, it's amazing.
The one you are looking at is
also amazing, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Wow, it's amazing.
How is it? It's amazing.
It's changed.
Next, next, next.
Is it OK?
I'm so impressed.
Are you impressed?
Yes.
Is it OK?
No, no, no, no, no.
You look great.
Do you feel your
nipples? Yes, I do.
Can I touch your
nipples? Yes, you can.
How can I touch your nipples?
You can touch as much as you want.
Your nipples are getting hard.
Are they getting
hard? Yes, they are.
Can I touch it? Yes, you can.
It's hard.
Isn't it painful?
No, it doesn't hurt.
How do you feel? It feels good.
Is it your first time to touch it?
Yes.
It feels so good.
I don't know how to do it.
It's so good.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'd appreciate it if you could
tell me how to touch boobs.
How to touch
boobs? I don't know.
Well, like this.
Like this?
Doesn't it hurt? Not at all.
Like this.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Is it painful? Yes, it is.
Do you feel pain in
your neck? Yes, I do.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
It is stronger than I thought.
It might be painful if I squeeze your neck.
But it is not painful at all.
I want to try it.
OK.
Like this.
It looks like this.
Does it hurt more if I do this?
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
Let me see.
It doesn't hurt.
Like this.
It's okay.
Don't touch your nipples.
Like this? Ah, yes, yes.
Ah, it feels good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Do you want to
press it? Yes, it's okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good because
I can touch it firmly.
How does it feel when you lick it?
What?
It feels good when I lick it.
I want to drink a lot.
Do you want to drink a lot?
If you don't mind, I'll drink a lot.
Then I'll drink a lot.
No, no, no.
Can I drink a lot? Yes, you can.
You can drink a lot.
You can lick my hand.
Does it feel good?
Please rub my hand.
It feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Have you ever seen the sunset?
What? Yes, I have.
Tomorrow?
No.
Do you want to see it?
Can I?
Yes.
Can I show it to
you? Yes, you can.
Uncle, come closer.
Yes.
It doesn't disappear.
It's very easy to see.
It's dyed.
It's pink inside.
Is it your first time to see this?
Yes.
It's like this.
Do you want to touch this?
May I?
Can I sit here? Yes, you can.
Thank you.
Be gentle.
How is it? It's very hot.
Is it hot?
You're good at touching.
I'm just trying to touch gently.
It's not your first time, is it?
No, it's really my first time.
Really? And, well.
..
My fingers are tired.
It feels good, though.
Oh, it feels good.
Can I touch your
ear? No, you can't.
How about here? No, I can't.
Can I touch your
ear? No, you can't.
I've never been touched so much.
I can't believe it.
It hurts so much.
I can't move at all.
You were pulling the string.
It's true.
Wow, it's amazing. I've never been
touched this much, and I feel good.
Why don't we put it inside?
If we put it in such
a place, will it get in?
Yes, it may get in.
Oh, yeah.
It's not there.
Doesn't it hurt?
It doesn't hurt at all.
It feels really good.
It feels good.
I don't know how to move it.
What should I do?
It's okay as it is.
Try to move it more.
Look at me.
Is that so?
Yes, that's right.
What's wrong? I don't like.
..
I don't like...
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I know, I know.
I want you to lick me a little more.
Can I lick you?
Yes.
Come here.
Oh, like this?
Yes.
Oh, it's so good.
It's so good.
Oh, it feels so good.
Can you kiss me this time?
Can I? Yes, you can.
Can I?
Yes.
It's my first time.
Is it your first time?
Yes.
Yes, it's OK.
Oh!
Oh! I can do it.
Do you love me?
Yes.
I want to do it, too.
Do you want to do it? Yes, I do.
We are standing side by side.
You can do it.
I can't stand it.
Oh, it's hot.
Here you are.
How is it? It's great.
My lips are softened.
Really?
What's next? Please.
Is this really your first time?
Yes.
Really?
You are really good at it.
When I kissed you,
didn't you react a little?
You haven't got up
yet? No, I haven't.
You must have got up,
haven't you? Yes, I have.
It's the first time to meet
you in the waiting room.
Well, I want to give you a bath.
Can't I lick you?
Can I?
I want to lick you.
If you don't mind, I
want to ask you a favor.
Can I?
Yes.
What happened to your kiss?
Why is your hand
like this? I'm sorry.
By the way, my hand feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Like this? That's great.
How do you want me to touch you?
The way you touch me now.
Yes.
But I want to lick you.
Yes, please.
May I?
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
I can't stand it.
What's wrong?
Are you OK?
What? It's amazing.
This side, too.
Can I lick it? Yes, you can.
Oh, no.
Ah, it's hot.
It's hot.
Is it?
Yes, I feel good.
Let me see.
Oh, it feels so good.
Does it? Yes, it does.
What is this?
If I ask you to eat one by one,
will you get angry? No, I won't.
Then, I'll eat one by one.
It's good.
It's not good.
It's too good.
You can't drink it.
I'm sorry.
I can't drink it?
You can't drink it yet.
Hold on.
OK.
It's so good.
Can I say something?
No, you can't.
But I want to say something.
I think you're not ready yet.
Oh, my bag.
What? Is that so? Look at this.
It's full.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What should I do?
But you've never put it in a bag, have you?
No.
Then, why don't you put it in a bag?
Don't you want to go there
rather than go to Ferrari?
I want to graduate as a virgin.
Do you want to graduate today?
Yes.
Then, from the back.
Put it in.
Isn't it difficult to do from the back?
I'll teach you, so it's okay.
Yes.
Next, lower it more.
I'm going to do it.
More, more.
Yes, yes, there.
Yes, there.
Yes.
It's so good.
Did you get it?
Yes.
It's so good.
Let me move it.
Wait a minute.
If you move now, I'll be gone soon.
What?
I'll be gone?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's heavy.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Can I move as it is?
Can you move?
Can you give me a
hand? No, you can't.
OK.
Oh, no.
I can't do it.
What?
Do you feel better? Yes, I do.
Can you feel my heart
beating? Yes, I can.
It's beating fast.
Is it beating
fast? It feels good.
I'm sorry.
Oh...
It feels so good.
I'll get it all over your face.
Move your head.
It feels so good.
Give me a kiss.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, it feels good.
Hey, come here.
Sit here.
Can I sit on it? It feels good.
It feels good.
Yoichi!
Can I stop? Yes, you can.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
I want you to put it in from the back.
From the back?
Please follow me from behind.
Is this place OK? A little more.
Here?
Yes.
I'll put it in.
OK.
It feels good.
Follow me from behind.
It feels so good.
I want to go there, too.
OK.
Let's go.
Don't you want to
go there? Not yet.
Not yet?
I'm curious about it.
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
I'm going now. See you later.
Thank you.
It's time to go home.
See you later.
We are the only ones in the
hot spring, aren't we? That's right.
Other people don't come in.
It's not the same.
Is that so? This is normal.
I wonder if I'll come in.
By the way, have you decided on
your career path after graduation? I see.
Because it's not yet.
It's so beautiful.
Are you OK? Of course.
Are you OK? I'm sorry.
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
Isn't it very beautiful?
Such a beautiful person doesn't
come to Konnyaku, does she?
No, she doesn't.
I'm sure she'll come.
Really? That's great.
I'm so lucky.
I'm lucky, too.
It's so beautiful.
That's great.
There are so many people.
I'm nervous.
Hey, hey.
Yes?
Are you a college
student? Yes, I am.
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
I'm 20 years old.
Wow, you're young.
Are you here alone?
Yes, I'm here alone today.
Do you often go to the hot springs here?
Do you often go to the
hot springs? No, I don't.
I like hot springs, so I go to many places.
Are you alone?
Do you come later?
No, I'm alone today.
It's our first time.
Oh, is it? Yes, it is.
I was surprised.
I feel good.
Chikkun, can you
see it? I found it.
It's amazing.
It's really big.
What kind of bread
is it? I don't know.
Is it EF? I don't know.
It's crazy.
Great.
How old is she? I don't know.
She is so beautiful.
Hey, hey, hey.
Yes? Yes, yes, yes.
What are you talking about?
What? No, no, no.
Well, well, well.
It's a little bit of a gossip.
It's a gossip.
Do you have a girlfriend?
What? No, I don't.
What? Even though you are
a college student? Well, yes.
I see.
What grade are you
in? Second grade.
Second grade?
I'm not that popular.
I see.
Are you in the same high school?
Yes.
I heard that you don't
come to the temple often.
You are so nice.
I'm always welcomed.
I'm the first visitor.
I see.
What kind of circle do you join?
You all have good bodies.
No, no, no.
You have a lot of muscles.
I'm going to tell you something.
What is it? You look tired.
It's a sports club, isn't it?
It's a sports club.
I play basketball.
I didn't know you could
train your body like this.
That's right.
That's amazing.
There are a lot of leaves.
Let's take a picture together.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
It's embarrassing to be so obvious.
Aren't you embarrassed to
be surrounded by men like us?
I'm a little embarrassed.
When did she leave?
Don't you have a
girlfriend? No, I don't.
Well, I've known her since high school.
I see.
That's about it.
You've never seen her, have you?
What?
Shut up! Shut up!
Is that so?
Have you ever kissed
her? No, I haven't.
Oh, I see.
Do you have one? I have one.
What about you?
I broke up recently.
Oh, I see.
What kind of girl do you like?
I like pretty girls.
I see.
So you're not the type of old lady like me.
No, I'm not.
No, no, no.
I'm not an old lady.
You're not an old lady.
I'm an older woman.
No, you're not.
I'm a very beautiful woman.
I wonder how old an old lady is.
You're beautiful.
It's beautiful.
I'm glad to hear that.
I've been curious about it for a while.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
You don't know what it
means, do you? No, I don't.
Really? Yes, I do.
What?
I don't think so.
What's wrong?
Really?
You must be kidding.
No, I'm not.
I see.
What?
You're standing.
What? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's a mountain.
It's amazing.
It's big, isn't it?
Is it? It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
I'm embarrassed.
Can I touch it?
What?
No?
Can I? It's amazing.
I've never seen such a big one.
Can you stand up and
show me? Really? I see.
It's amazing.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Isn't it too small for
you? If you ask me.
..
It's big.
Show me.
I'm smaller than it.
Really?
Yes.
It's more than that.
It's as big as your face.
Great.
I want to see it.
Can I do it with this?
But isn't it a little
big? I'm hiding it.
It's a little hard.
Is it a little hard?
A little, a little.
Hey, lady.
What?
You're touching it too much.
Wow.
When you're young, you get really stiff.
No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey. Why are you
taking it off? Hey, hey, hey.
Wow.
It's embarrassing.
No, no, no.
I think I saw it.
Please hide it.
I can't.
Why?
Because I'm holding it.
Please don't hide it.
Wow.
It's hard.
Have you ever been touched
by a woman? Yes, I have.
Oh, I see.
Wow.
It feels good.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Hey, miss.
What?
Are you licking me? No, I'm not.
You're not saying
you don't like it?
No, I'm not saying you don't like it?
You're too big to fit in my mouth.
It's so good.
It's so hot.
Ah...
It feels so good.
I'm going to be 100 this year.
Wow...
Ah...
It feels so good.
Ah... It's amazing.
Ah… Ah… Ah… Ah… I love you.
Love… Ah…
Wow, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
Oh, it's hot.
I'll give you some water.
Oh, it's sour.
、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、、
Oh, it's hot.
Your boobs are really big.
What?
Can I touch it?
How is it? It's very soft.
Touch it.
It's very soft.
Wow, it's amazing.
You are amazing.
Look at this.
You are eating it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Wow, it's amazing.
You are soft.
You are amazing.
Please lick my boobies.
Do I have to lick your boobies?
Do I have to lick your
boobies? Yes, you do.
Wow!
Hey, you come here.
No, I'm fine.
Come here.
Are you OK?
Are you okay?
It's hot.
It's amazing.
I think I got used to it.
Did you get used
to it? Yes, I did.
Can I have a look?
It's the first time for you to see it.
Take a good look.
It's amazing.
Wow! Touch me.
Touch you?
Yes.
But... What?
Can I?
Yes.
Then...
Like this.
What's this?
Can I touch you?
Wow!
What's this?
What is this?
I took it off by mistake.
Stop it.
Oh, no.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Ah! Touch my belly.
Touch my belly.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! It feels good.
Ah!
What should I do? It feels good.
Here, drink this.
You want me to drink it?
Yes.
What? Hold this.
Wait a minute.
Ah...
Mmm.
Ahh.
Oh... Oh... Mmm... Mmm.
Oh, oh.
Uh, oh.
Wow!
Wow! I feel sick.
Go, go, go.
Your mouth is.
..
I feel sick.
There, there.
Go away!
I want my daddy.
Hurry up and put your hand in.
Are you sure? Hurry up.
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Is it like this?
It feels so good.
You're so annoying.
Oh, it's hot.
What's wrong with
you? I have a cramp.
I'm so tired.
Oh, my goodness.
Do you feel tired? Yes, I do.
It's 9 o'clock in the morning.
Are you awake?
Huh?
Yes.
Wow.
Ah.
Good morning.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's great.
I can't do it.
Oh, it's hot.
I'm tired.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
Oh, no!
You shouldn't drink so fast.
You'll spill it.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh my god.
So delicious.
Get some sleep, Shiro-kun.
Oh, I'm sleepy.
Calm down.
It's okay.
I don't want to.
Let me go.
It's coming out.
Oh, I'm sleepy.
Ah... Ah...
Ah...
It's good.
Ah... It was good.
Ah...
What's wrong? Are you OK?
I'm so nervous that I can't breathe.
Thank you for the meal.
Thank you very much.
See you.
I should have done it, too.
It was great.
I should have extended the chance.
It was good to have a graduation trip.
It was right to come here.
I want to have a graduation trip.
What are you going to
do after getting a job?
I don't want to get a job anymore.
I want to be a student forever.
Hello.
May I come in? Please come in.
She is very beautiful.
Are you alone?
Yes, I came here alone.
Are you all college
students? Yes, we are.
Are you going on a
graduation trip? Yes, we are.
It looks fun.
Do you often travel alone?
I like traveling alone.
Do you?
Wow, it's amazing.
I've been looking around
the store, and it seems
that there are many
mixed-race people around here.
It seems so.
We thought it was unusual because we were
mixed-race people, so we came to try it.
Surprisingly, there were no other women.
Isn't it close?
Isn't it a little narrow?
We need to use a little more space.
I don't know if I can use it widely.
I've been looking at it for a long time.
Isn't the valley dangerous?
It's very dangerous.
You've been looking at it for a long time.
It's dangerous.
It's not a swimsuit, is it?
Because this is a hot spring.
Does that mean it's completely under that?
What is that? That is.
..
I've been looking at it for a long time.
It looks very soft.
Oh, I see.
Because it's a bath, they enter
naked, don't they? Well, yes, but.
..
You knew such a woman
would come in, didn't you?
You have a beautiful skin.
You have a beautiful skin, too.
I don't think so.
You look like you are in your 20s.
I look like I'm in my teens.
The water is running.
You, too.
Did you go to the sea after sunbathing?
I went to the sea for a while.
It's amazing.
It's close.
I didn't like it.
You didn't say you didn't like it.
You haven't gone to the bath yet, have you?
Oh!
Then, how about a little more?
Do you want to warm up?
Maybe it's better to stick together.
If possible, I want to
get along with you more.
If you want to get along with
us, you should wear a towel.
What?
I don't have a towel.
Then, what should I do?
Stand up and show me your swimsuit.
Stand up?
What kind of swimsuit did you bring?
Show me your swimsuit.
If we show you our swimsuit,
will you show it to us?
You don't have a swimsuit,
so you can't show it to us.
I want something like a swimsuit.
Something like a swimsuit.
I think it depends on everyone.
If you show it to us, we'll show it to you.
What if you let us enjoy your swimsuit?
What should I do if it gets wet?
It's a little transparent.
Is it fun to look at your
body? It's super fun.
Who's going to stand up first?
..
Well, but... Well, but... If you let me
see it, I think I'll show you mine, too.
Oh, really?
I wonder if you'll let me see it, too.
Oh, my god! Well, but.
..
Well, but... Who said
they wanted to see it?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Who's the real bachelor?
What?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I just did it.
Oh, no. I'm going to fall.
You're falling.
Oh, no.
It's broken.
Why are you coming
and going? Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
You're sweating.
I'm sorry.
You couldn't stand up, could you?
You are amazing.
What happened to the stain here?
You stained your swimsuit.
This is the hot spring.
Are you all right?
Oh, I can see it.
Oh, I did it.
I can see the goldfish.
Oh, no.
The goldfish has very beautiful nipples.
And the boobs are very beautiful.
I dropped it.
I'm in trouble.
I've scratched it myself.
Show me your teeth.
No.
I want to brush my teeth.
Before brushing your
teeth, show me your teeth.
No.
If I show you my teeth,
can I brush my teeth?
I don't know what to do.
Wow.
Wow, that's great!
It must have been hard for you.
Yes, it was.
Wow, that's great!
Wow, you are standing up.
Look.
You want to touch it,
don't you? Yes, I do.
First, touch your own poop.
Scrub, scrub, scrub.
My own poop? Yes, yes, yes.
How do you scrub your own poop?
I'll show you how to brush your teeth.
Wow, you are close!
How do you brush your teeth?
Where do you like to touch?
You like the tip of your tooth?
Where else do you like to touch?
What do you like?
You like rabbits the most, don't you?
What do you like? I like Paris.
Do you like Paris?
What else do you
like? I like eggs.
Do you like eggs?
You like eggs, don't
you? No, I don't.
Do you like
everything? Yes, I do.
All of them feel
good, don't they?
Why do you feel so good?
You feel good, don't
you? I'm so happy.
Look at this.
Do you want to touch it?
Do you want to
touch it? No, I can't.
Oh, you touched it.
Look at this.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
It's soft.
What's wrong with you?
Are you about to come out?
Oh, it feels good.
We are so kind.
What's wrong?
Do you want to be spoiled?
Can I be spoiled, too?
There are a lot of mosquitoes.
Oh, it feels good.
I want to move my tongue more.
Oh, it's great.
Oh, my.
It's a pity that I don't have a girlfriend.
I'm so sad. I'm always alone.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm going to show you a video
of how to clean the cat litter box.
I can't stand it anymore.
Do you want me to stop?
I have to ask you nicely.
Someone may come.
Eww, I feel sick to the
bottom of my stomach.
That's not fair to Saki-chan.
Oh dear, you look like you're in pain.
Oh, no!
You were holding it in
your mouth, weren't you?
Let's do it again.
Come on, come closer.
Oh, my God!
Come here and show me more.
Oh, my God! Humming.
Oh, you got on my nipples.
Oh, really? Yes, yes, yes.
It feels good.
Are you standing on
my nipples? I'm jealous.
Oh, you're standing on my nipples, too.
Wow, your nipples are really hard.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's wet.
Really? Let me see.
I want to see.
What is it? It's a puss.
It's a puss?
What are you going to do when
you see a puss? I don't know.
It's a good puss.
Ah,
Oh, Oh,
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
It's really messy.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Oh, you're rubbing!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah, it feels good.
Rub your Grandpa's feet.
Please rub here.
Yes, yes, yes.
You are so kind.
Thank you.
Look, look, look.
You rub here and there.
Your legs are moving.
Yes, they are.
You feel good, don't you?
Your nipples are moving, too.
I'm sorry.
You're wet.
Can I lick you?
Do you want me to lick you?
Oh my god! It's disgusting.
Come here. Let me see your penis.
Oh my god!
まずきっていいのでw もう、どこまでいれる?
手が、
やばい、やばい、やばい。
Oh, no, I'm already full.
Can I move my butt?
Oh! Wow!
Oh! You are really!
Wow! You have a lot on your butt!
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
You have a lot on your butt!
You can get a lot of hair out!
You are so cute.
Wow, you can take it out again.
You can take it out a lot
because you are a baby.
It feels good.
I will make you feel better.
I'll make you feel better.
How can I make you feel better?
Oh, my God!
Your friends are petting you.
Show me more, In-chan.
Your friends are doing this to you.
Don't do that, In-chan.
You're so nice.
In-chan? It's going in.
It's going in.
Oh, my God.
His butt is drooping.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's warm.
My eyes feel good.
I'm going to go.
Mom, I can't stand it.
You can't stand it anymore.
You can do it.
Oh my god!
No no no!
I feel so good!
Oh my god!
Wow, that's great!
I feel so good! It's so hot.
I don't want to look at it.
It's hard to breathe.
My chest feels good.
I'm thirsty.
I'm going to be caught.
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Ah, it's hot.
Ah, it's hot.
It's not good.
What's wrong? I'm sorry.
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no!
Soma-san, you too!
Please!
Somebody, please come!
Oh, no!
is a a
a
k
a a a a a a
You are so big!
Here comes Teki-chan.
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, your belly is so comfortable!
Please use your belly a lot.
Yes!
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, your belly is so comfortable!
Oh, it feels
good! Ah, it's cold.
Ah, it's cold.
It's cold.
My shoulders are cold.
The baby's mother is crying.
Do you still want more?
It's so good!
Did you get wet?
You're soaking wet.
You are so wet.
You want to have a lot of sex, don't you?
I'll do something good for you next time.
You are so wet.
You are always stiff, aren't you?
You are getting sleepy, aren't you?
You feel good, don't you?
You want to go, don't you?
You are showing off a lot.
Oh, no!
What's going to happen?
Did you explode?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Go! Go! Go!
Oh, you have a very dark one.
You have a very dark one.
Do you want to do it more?
Wow, it's amazing.
It's amazing.
It feels good, doesn't
it? It's amazing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good, doesn't
it? I feel so good.
I feel so good.
I can't allow myself to be in pain.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, no!
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, no! I'm so tired.
I've never had such a hard time.
Oh, no. What
happened to me? Oh, no.
I'm sweating.
Oh, no. I'm sweating.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! I can't get up.
I'm soaked.
It was great.
Thank you.
I'm so satisfied.
You guys were great.
Thank you so much.
I left my towel somewhere.
See you later.