What?
I knew it.
Are you Noc?
Yes, I am.
I remember you.
We talked about Scottish
Fold at the grass baseball game.
I know you.
I'm shopping at a convenience store.
I think you look like him.
It's a little far.
I live nearby.
Is that so?
Are you going home today?
Yes, that's right.
You don't have a job?
No, I don't.
Oh, I see.
I see.
If you want, I can take a
picture of your face for your
wife if you give birth to
a child in the first priority.
But I'm really okay today.
You can just look at my face.
Please pet me.
Really?
I just saw you a little.
It's a coincidence, isn't it?
It's not easy.
Really?
He's here.
Good morning.
It's cold.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm director Takahashi, and
I'll play your husband today.
I'm Takahashi.
I'm Chihiro.
You're cute.
I don't need that this time.
It's not a collaboration,
so I don't need that.
Is there anyone else who has
nothing to do with Mr. Karaki?
The person I took on a
double-Decker trip with is him.
He's beautiful, isn't he?
From this moment on, please don't
hold back because he's your real husband.
I got it. I'll do my best.
I don't have to hold back, do I?
I think you don't have to.
Don't overdo it.
Don't hold back.
Actually, I want you to
kiss me right now, but if your
partner finds out about
it, I think your plan will fail.
Anyway, it's your mission to
make me look like a real couple.
And I want you to get
along with your husband.
She is a bit weak.
I want her to get along with Inoue-San.
I want her not to be like that.
And I want her to make
the target's wife jealous.
I want her to flirt with the target's wife.
It's just right, isn't it?
I wonder if it's okay.
You're good at spoiling.
I'm so nervous that my
partner's wife is nervous.
I wonder if it's okay.
Are you okay?
I don't care about your age.
I don't care about your marriage history.
I don't know how old I am.
Didn't you see the e-mail I sent you?
What was it?
You didn't see it, did you?
I put it at the end.
Have you seen it?
I don't know.
Was there such a thing?
I think a little over 10 years is fine.
She is in her 30s now.
Isn't it about 10 years?
I got married when I was 22 years old.
I think it's about 10 years.
It may be better not
to give a clear answer.
I don't have a child.
Oh, like a boss?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
You can take care of your wife naturally.
If you flirt a little too much,
I think you're doing your
best for your husband's job.
I'm totally fine.
Yes, I did.
No, but it's nice to wear glasses.
Really?
It looks good on you.
Really, really, really.
From the morning.
Please don't be in the usual tone.
No, because the glasses look great on you.
I have a great glasses face.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, I see.
It's about time.
This time, I'm going to take care
of the staff and one more person.
I see.
Thank you.
Abe-chan quit.
Oh, really?
Karaki-San will do that again.
I saw it the other day.
What are you doing at work?
I was told not to take the female staff.
Of course.
I'm the only man.
I don't know why, but I was having sex with a lady
while I was working, so I'm concentrating this
time, so I can't make a mistake because there
are only men, so I'm scared if I make a mistake.
I don't want to see it.
It's OK.
No?
You look sexy.
Are you OK?
Yes.
I can't get in touch with
you until we get in the inn.
Please be a couple.
Thank you.
It's about time.
Let's hold hands.
It's warm, isn't it?
It looks fun.
There it is.
The car is square.
Take a picture.
I can't get any closer.
It's coming from here.
Mofu-San.
You're smiling.
I'm looking over here, so be careful.
There's a smoke.
I got it.
Is the photo okay?
Yes, it is.
Start the engine.
Turn on the engine
and put on the seat belt.
The other car is coming.
I can't find the pin.
It's coming.
Go straight ahead and don't
let the traffic light catch you.
Go straight ahead.
You are young.
We are 30 years old.
Really?
My husband's skin is very beautiful.
Your wife is also very
beautiful, as rumored.
Rumor?
It's nice to be young.
I don't think I'm young.
How is it?
You look good in glasses.
Really? Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
How old are you?
5 years old.
5 years old!
That's great.
It's tough.
We don't have kids yet.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
I'm 6 years old this year.
So, you met when you were in your 20s?
Yes, I met her when I was in my 20s.
Where did you meet your wife?
I used to play baseball.
Oh, you did?
Yes, when I was in college.
It was like a club.
My wife came to see me play.
Yes, that's right.
You came to see her?
Yes.
Did you know each other at that time?
Did you talk to her?
I was a little curious.
Because there is a cute girl.
Such a beautiful person.
I talked to her.
How long have you been
married to Takahashi-San?
How many years?
About 10 years.
Is that so?
Yes.
I see.
It's been 10 years.
Time flies.
So you got married as soon as
you graduated from university?
Well... Well... Well... 25?
24.
24?
Yes.
I see.
So, when you graduate
and get a job in a company,
you'll feel safe, right?
Yes.
When you get used to your job.
Oh, I'm going in front.
So, where did you take your child today?
Today, I happened to take
him to my family's house.
Oh, really?
I was able to take care of it.
You've never had a date with your
wife since you were a kid, have you?
No, I haven't.
Sometimes I take care of it at home.
I've had a lot of dates.
I remember a little.
That's pretty much the
case when you're a kid.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, it is.
Shift the dial to the maximum.
I can't see you.
I can't see your face.
Do you go on a trip together?
We don't go on a trip much.
Because you are still young?
We used to go on a trip
before we had a baby.
We went to the hot spring.
We go to the hot spring.
The hot spring is really good
The yukata is fresh I'm thrilled.
I often go on a trip with my wife.
I don't have children, so I often
go to the sea or the mountains.
I often show 50% of the
beauty of a woman's yukata.
Is that so much?
I think you look good in a yukata.
Really?
I'm so happy I'm
worried What should I do?
I think you look good
too I want to see Yes, it is.
It's at low speed, isn't it?
What?
It's not a driving, it's at low speed.
You.
Really? I didn't notice.
I thought the engine sound
was too loud, but it's at low speed.
It's been running at
low speed all the time.
All the time?
The engine will burn out.
Are you OK?
I didn't notice.
Today, the upper body is naked.
I'm not interested in it.
You don't want to see it that much.
You just want to see it.
No, I don't.
I don't want to see a man's skin.
The shoulder width is wide.
It's because it's baked.
It's solid.
It's manly.
I'm jealous.
I'm so happy to participate.
I'm sorry I'm sorry.
It may be close to a five-year divorce.
No, no, no If so, I'll take care of my
wife I see Let's exchange Let's go.
You've been here for
10 years, so it's fine.
It's coming.
I was surprised.
It's so fast.
Don't let it go.
Follow me.
I couldn't catch up with you if I was slow.
I'm sorry.
The engine was on fire and it exploded.
What are your hobbies?
Hobbies?
I like to go to hot Springs.
I like cats.
Do you have a cat?
A cat is biting a cat.
A cat is biting a cat, isn't it?
I want to buy a pet.
I heard that many
children want to buy a pet.
I want to buy a pet.
Usually, you buy a pet instead of a child.
That's right.
It's good.
Oh, good, good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good.
No, no.
I'm in front of my husband,
but when did you fall
in love for the first time
and become a wife?
I thought I'd ask you, but
I'm a high school student.
What grade are you in high school?
I'm in the second year of high school.
How old were you in high school?
About 16 How old are
you? I'm 16 years old.
Are you in the same class? Yes.
What made you start dating?
It's not like we started
dating, but it just happened.
It's close Was the seat close?
There is also that
The same class.
Gentle feeling I was doing it I was
playing soccer Did you play soccer?
Where did you go on a date when
you were a high school student?
You can hear it well You can hear
it well Karaoke Karaoke in that era?
Movies Do you practice
together after club activities?
That's right.
Great It's been a long
time since I've seen you.
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
I feel like I'm a detective.
I want to see your wife's face,
but I don't think I can see it.
I'm curious about your wife's expression.
I'm curious what he is doing.
I got a message from my
mother saying happy birthday.
I got a shock.
Put the steering wheel
on the steering wheel.
Put it on carefully.
I have no choice but to go ahead.
Oh, I think it's good.
Oh, it's not good right behind.
It's a little over there.
Two of them are about there.
Oh, one more.
It's okay here.
It's coming, it's coming,
it's coming, it's coming.
Aim, aim, aim.
I don't look at the camera much.
Under the window.
I'm looking at the situation.
Mr. Aoki, are you all right?
I can't see this way.
It's just a square.
All right, I'll go, too.
I'll leave it in the car.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Are you drunk?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
My husband is used to it.
No, no, no.
It's no big deal.
My wife is happy, too.
She's rarely praised today.
Thank you.
No, no.
I'm a salesman, so I feel good.
It's a little further
from here, so if you're
going to the bathroom,
you should go ahead.
It's coming, it's coming, it's
coming, it's coming, it's coming.
Let's take a look at the inside of the car.
Please turn your head to the front.
If you turn your head too
much, you will be suspicious.
Please turn your head to the front.
Are you okay?
Please enter the entrance of the car.
It's amazing.
Mr. Inoue and Mr. Chihiro are escorting.
He is escorting by hand.
Great! Great!
It's as planned.
He is coming.
Great! Great!
As planned.
Welcome.
He is coming.
Let's go.
Please.
Oh, come on in.
Welcome.
Oh, I'm here to take a look around.
This is the kitchen.
You can actually use this.
You can use it like this.
I'll do it.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Stupid.
I'll do it.
Where are the sweets?
It's open.
Take off your shoes.
Here it is.
Thank you for it.
Itadakimasu.
When it gets cold, we
don't come here often.
That's right.
We come here when it's warm or in summer.
But we don't come here often in winter.
It's a little cold.
That's right.
I'll put the heater on.
It's a little calm.
Is that so?
It's like I'm in my parents' house.
Today, I'm going to use this
color and put a button here.
Oh, I see.
This is a button.
Everyone is cute.
It's a holiday.
Please eat a lot.
I'm a little hungry.
Haru-chan, please tie it up there.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Why are you two there?
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
I want to give it to you.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear that.
Please take it easy.
I'm not sure.
I'm sorry.
It's tough, isn't it?
It's a little tough.
It's nice to do this.
If you live in the city on a daily basis,
you have to change your mood.
I'm sure you'll get a lot of comments.
I'm sure you'll be surprised.
Was it a mansion?
It's a mansion now.
It's a mansion, so there's no garden.
That's right.
You can have a barbecue over there.
It's a little bit.
I am going to take a bath.
I don't like it.
Do you have a toilet or something?
That's right.
After taking a bath, you can drink a beer.
It's ideal.
From now on,
we will prepare a hot spring.
We are going to prepare a hot spring.
I'll prepare a seat for you.
Oh, really?
When you enter,
first, you can sit in the lady first.
Oh, that's great!
You can sit in the lady's seat.
Then, I'll follow your words.
It's a good room.
This is it.
It's a room that can fit four people.
It's big.
Which one fits?
I'm sorry that I couldn't see it.
Ahaha.
Well then, Haruna.
Put it up like this and prepare a bath tub.
Oh, I see.
Well then, the two of
you will prepare a bath.
Oh.
I'll prepare it over there.
Ah, I see.
Please.
Oh, like this.
Yes, please.
Let's go.
I'll get ready.
Thank you.
This way.
Please.
Thank you.
I'll get ready.
Please take your time.
Thank you.
It's a nice room.
The previous room was not good.
What?
But... He's flirting
with his wife.
He's flirting with her.
I'm sure he's in a bad mood.
But he looks happy.
No, he's not.
What?
That's not good, Takahashi-San.
Maybe he's in a bad mood.
I don't think so.
But he looks like he's in a bad mood.
He's in a daze.
Hey.
What?
It's okay.
You haven't gone to bed yet.
I can hear your voice.
It's okay.
You don't have to speak out loud.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
You haven't slept yet.
You might want to do something.
Then... It's okay.
It's fine.
It's just a little bit.
It's okay.
It's fine.
We came here together.
I'm afraid my voice will be recorded.
It's okay.
I'm still preparing.
I see.
It's okay.
I'm going to take this off.
It's okay. He won't come back.
Come here.
It's wet.
Are you okay?
It's okay, right?
Since you're our nurse,
don't do anything unprofessional.
No way.
It's okay.
I don't want to.
I'm so happy to have you together.
No.
It's okay.
I don't want to.
I'll put you in.
Kizu's heading to the bedroom.
Ah, yes, I'm coming.
Ah, Mrs. Nakajima.
Are you ready?
No, hold on a second.
Oh, I'm in the bedroom.
Yes, I'm coming.
Was that the time to get ready?
It's hot.
Excuse me. I'm ready.
Let's go.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Let's go.
Please put your clothes here.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
This is a hair tie.
The bath is big.
Let's take a bath together.
Great.
The hot spring here is very good.
Please change your clothes.
You must be tired from driving, right?
Yes, I am.
Wow, you have a nice style.
Your underwear is cute.
You look good in this color.
Thank you.
Chihiro-San.
It's cold.
It's late.
It's embarrassing.
I don't think it's cold.
I'm getting fatter and fatter.
I don't think so.
Not at all.
It's cold, so let's get in quickly.
It's cold.
It's warm.
I'll go in first.
It's cold.
Oh, it's a river!
Excuse me.
It's cold, isn't it?
It's warm, isn't it?
It's warm.
It's getting warmer.
This is amazing.
It's wide, isn't it?
That's right.
It's quite wide.
I hope everyone will join us.
I agree.
It's wonderful.
It's a nice hot spring.
It's healing.
I wonder if it's embarrassing
to take a bath together.
I didn't think we would
take a bath together.
I don't think so.
Do you get along well with your husband?
Yes, we get along well.
That's good.
How about you?
Well... Sometimes...
we quarrel a little, but...
we get along normally.
I'm glad to hear that.
My husband is young, so it's good.
I see.
He is full of energy.
My husband is old.
He is old.
There is a difference in age.
There are many people,
so the way of thinking is old.
I was worried.
It's a little sad, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's a little sad, and it's fun.
It's not a big deal, is it?
No, it's not.
I feel like I'm getting bigger.
That's right.
I was wondering if it would
be okay to travel together.
The couple got bigger.
I think it's too much.
It's okay.
Are you tired?
Please take your time today.
I'll wash it for you.
Thank you.
Okay.
Everyone, please come forward.
Teacher, please put out the paper.
If you don't do it right away,
um, bring the paper.
If you bring the paper out
with the paper, you can't see it.
Okay.
So, for the time being, if you
put out the paper with the paper,
um,
you can't see it.
This,
the wall behind it,
is the only thing that is visible.
Then, please confirm it.
What?
Wow, your skin is smooth.
I think your shoulders are stiff, too.
I think so, too.
Do you take care of your diet?
I didn't know that.
It's amazing that you can
wash your hair with that.
It's refreshing, isn't it?
It's good to be young, isn't it?
I'm sure you'll be told that it's messy.
You can put it in hot water.
It's warm.
It's been a while since I've had a bath.
I don't know why, but
Yano-San's face is a little swollen.
It's because of the sideburns.
Are you all right?
The sideburns are fine,
but the face is swollen.
I'll give you a massage.
You don't have to push yourself too hard.
I'll give you a massage from here.
Does it hurt?
It hurts a little.
Is the view good from here?
I can see the mountains.
It's beautiful.
Oh, really?
Is he an idiot?
Wait a minute.
I was surprised.
What are you doing?
I told him to go back.
I was surprised.
Are you all right?
Chihiro-San, you look like a little girl.
Do you usually have a day off?
I see.
I hang out with my friends.
We drink together.
I think it's getting hot.
I think so, too.
It's getting hot.
I'm going to take a bath.
Here you are.
I'm sweating.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm scared.
I can't see anything.
You can be quiet.
Did you wipe it properly?
I have to increase the number of cameras.
I can't hear your voice.
I don't know what to do.
Please come in.
This is my husband's room.
It's a nice room.
It's hot and I can't go up.
Are you okay?
I went in too much.
It felt really good.
I was able to relax.
You were relaxed.
Really?
I forgot my ring.
Where is it?
I don't think so.
Maybe I took it off
when I was taking a bath.
I might have left it there.
Are you okay?
Hey.
I'm not feeling well.
Can I go to bed?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Oh, I see.
I think it's in the bathroom.
I'll go check it out.
Maybe it's in the bathroom.
There's no one here.
I don't know.
I don't know where it is.
Tegoshi, you haven't seen it yet, have you?
Let's go to the front.
I was surprised.
What?
I was looking for a ring,
and my husband left it there.
A ring?
What?
A wedding ring.
It's okay. I'll look for it later.
It's okay. You should look for it first.
But... Did you look for it?
I was looking for it,
but I couldn't find it.
If you stay here, you'll
end up in a strange place.
I'm afraid that I'll get a cold.
You might get a cold.
I'm afraid so.
I don't have a fever.
No way.
You have a fever.
Yes.
Do you wash your face?
I haven't seen it yet.
You haven't seen it?
Okay.
When you wash your
body, It's amazing, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Please look for it.
I'm looking for it, too.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Is there a gap or something like that?
I couldn't see it at all.
That's right.
Oh!
What is it?
No, it's a little different now.
Oh, it's not here.
Yes, it's lower.
Is it lower?
Hello.
What?
Where are you?
Oh, hello.
Are you here?
Can I take a picture of you?
Yes, sure.
I don't have anything.
Okay?
I'm going to sit down, too.
I'm in trouble.
Huh?
What should I do?
I'm going to sit down, too.
Okay.
What?
This.
The gap between the line and the line.
If you touch it, it will come off.
Yes.
What should I do?
Oh, wait.
Uh.
I don't know.
What?
What should I do if I come back now?
I don't know.
Ah, yeah.
It's hot.
The pants are a little, a little.
There is no panties.
I can not see.
Can not you see?
Do not see.
Do not know.
I thought I was a little here.
I've lost my panties.
I was so angry.
This is the story.
This is a little.
I was surprised.
She is standing.
She is attacking.
She is different.
She is a woman.
She is good.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Where did you get hurt?
On my back.
I was in a hurry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Just a little.
You're strong.
Don't make such a loud noise.
Did you find the door?
No one will come back
until I give the order.
I don't want to do it, but I have to do it.
Do you remember the last time we had sex?
Yes, I do.
I remember it, too.
Do you really remember it?
Yes, I do.
Really?
I want to be in your arms.
Yes.
I'm not in a position to do that today.
Oh, no.
I can't do that.
Do you have a reward for your hard work?
What?
I'm helping you, aren't I?
Yes.
What's your reward?
My reward?
Can I do it next time?
Can't you do it today?
After this?
After the meeting?
Yes.
But it's too late.
Oh.
I have no choice but to forget about it.
Yes.
Are you all right?
Where were you?
I don't know.
You should go home safely.
Yes.
I'll be fine as long as I can
go home in a good mood.
Really?
Yes.
After the meeting?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was worried about you.
I'm really sorry.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I can't use it.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop crying if I do this.
I'm really sorry.
I'll help you.
It's like your raw manko.
Wait a minute.
Are you still okay?
If you do that, I'll go.
Will you go?
I'll go.
No, you can't.
Can I really say it?
Yes.
I'm serious.
Then, slowly.
I just had a little bit.
It's itchy.
Be careful.
Please close your mouth.
You have half of it left.
No. You can do it.
Please strain your mouth.
Strain your mouth.
You have the fifth one.
The fifth.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
Please listen to me seriously.
Today's plan will be decided
by whether or not this will fail.
It's a turning point.
After this, the husband
and Jiro have a serious sex.
A serious one?
Yes, a serious one.
If it's not serious enough,
the whole plan will be ruined.
They show off how close they are.
And by doing so, by making her look at him,
she'll be able to overcome her jealousy.
And she'll be able to create a
state where she can't be calm.
I think that no matter what she does, even
if she panics, she'll be able to do it.
The fact that she's having
sex with her husband
and the fact that
she's stealing his wife,
The first goal was to make her
take away her husband's belongings.
After that, she went to her husband's room.
Then, Chihiro went to get
something from a high place.
Chihiro asked her husband to help
her get something from a high place.
Chihiro went to her husband's room.
Chihiro went to Irori's
room with her husband.
When you enter the room,
you will see Ichihiro's face.
Ichihiro will go to the room and call her.
Ichihiro will enter the
room with her husband.
You should start the conversation
as soon as you enter the room.
Ichi...
You should start the conversation
as soon as you enter the room.
Please start right away.
You don't have to hold back.
You don't have to hold back either.
It's like having sex with your lover.
When the sex begins...
I'll call Takahashi-San.
Then I'll call Nana-San and
ask her to help with the cooking.
I asked him to lead me to the front of
Irori's room and let me peep into his room.
After I peeped into his
room, Mr. Takahashi,
who was supposed to be
in charge of the meeting,
brought Mr. Nanase to his room.
He brought him to his room.
I also prepared some sake.
I've already prepared a drink for her.
I'll talk to her and calm her down.
We'll have a drink together.
I see.
I think it's best for her to
be sympathetic this time.
There's no way to threaten her this time.
I see.
I think it's better for her to
be comforted by each other.
I see.
Is it okay?
If Takahashi-San's surgery goes well,
you can come back to the monitor.
You can observe her for a while.
Really?
If they don't do it,
it's easier for her to panic.
Yes.
It's easier for her to panic.
If you're calm, it won't be like that.
If you're in a normal state,
you shouldn't have time to think.
You should be relaxed.
Will I be okay?
You'll be fine.
What?
You can do it like you did before.
Like you did before.
I'll do my best.
Are you ready?
Please go back to your seat.
I'll do my best.
I'm getting tired.
She is here.
I want to go in again.
I want to sleep more.
Before I go to bed, I'd
like to ask you something.
Yes?
May I come in?
Yes, please.
I can't get what I want in the
kitchen because it's too expensive.
Can you help me?
No problem.
Excuse me.
I'll be right back.
I'm nervous.
It's funny.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I shouldn't have said that.
You are kind.
Do you lick me?
It feels good.
Oh, I feel good...
I feel good!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got relieved.
Please take your time.
Let's go, let's go.
Please think about it.
It's a little scary.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
I'm sorry Wow, she's so cool.
She's my wife I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
My back feels really good.
Ouch!
It feels good.
It's hard.
I don't really feel well.
I feel sick.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sick!
I'm sorry.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
It felt so good.
Oh, my.
It was great.
Was it?
Yes.
What should I do?
Well.
I should hide it.
I see.
I have to change.
Oh, I see.
What should I do?
I should hide it here.
Are you hiding it?
Yes.
I was feeling good.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I'll go back.
I have to change.
I've already done this much.
Let's go.
Come here.
It's okay.
You should calm down.
Thank you.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry.
My husband...
My wife...
I think something's wrong
with you two this morning.
I think it's the first time you've had a
fight with my wife and your husband.
If you don't tell my wife
about it, it won't end well.
Don't tell her which one is wrong.
It's not like I'm going to do it.
I'm going to make a shirt.
I haven't had a wife like
that since I got married.
I haven't.
When I first came here, I
was told not to come here.
And when Takashi-San came
here, I was told not to come here.
Did you have any experience of coming here?
No, I didn't.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
We can't help but talk about it later.
It's hard for both of us.
It's hard.
Thank you very much.
Your wife is still young.
There are many things to come.
I think so.
There are many things.
To be honest, I was a little upset.
Isn't it?
No, I don't think so.
Really?
It's the first time you've
seen someone other
than you having sex
in front of you, isn't it?
Yes.
Right?
It's a rare opportunity.
Yes, it is.
Right?
It's the first time you've seen someone
other than you having sex in front of you.
It's amazing.
It's a great thing, isn't it?
He is a person I know.
Yes, he is.
It's a great thing.
After 5 or 6 years, a wife will lend her
husband to her husband for 10,000 years.
It's the same as love.
It's the same procedure.
It's not like that, is it?
If the person doing it is different,
you can say, Oh, that's how you do it.
You can say,
Oh, that's how you do it.
Just now,
in the bathroom,
you saw me, didn't you?
I was in a bit of a difficult situation.
I see.
How was it?
It was painful.
Why?
I was surprised.
It was my first time.
I was nervous.
I was surprised.
You were surprised?
I was curious.
You were curious?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
I was looking at you.
Thank you.
You look like a child.
It's not fair.
It's a little unfair.
Don't make me look away.
You guys are studying, aren't you?
He's gone to love.
I understand.
Wait a minute.
Calm down.
It's okay.
I'm glad.
My wife is doing more amazing things.
I'm watching over you.
If you don't do something, I'll be upset.
I'm sorry.
Really?
You touched my wife today.
My wife?
I didn't mean to.
I know.
Don't touch her.
I didn't mean to.
I'm looking for it.
It's just a little bit.
I see.
She's moving it.
She's looking for it.
She's moving it on her own will.
I see.
It's no good.
I've been listening to the sound.
It's too quiet.
I see.
This time, she is accepting it.
Look.
She doesn't hate it.
What do you think of this
from a woman's point of view?
She is completely accepting it.
She is touching her stomach.
She is touching her chest.
Amazing.
It's beautiful.
If I can hug you like this...
You won't let go of my hand.
You know women.
I know.
You remember me.
You remember me even when you're married.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I don't know if it's going
to be conquered or not.
This is...
There's only one piece left.
That's true.
Can you do it?
Probably.
If you can't do it,
Can you do it?
You can do it with your hands.
Let's try it again.
Let's try it.
Here?
Yes.
Just stay still.
You should go as far as you can touch.
When your wife's
consciousness is somewhere else.
If you go in this state, you can
hear the sound of something.
I see.
It's already being manipulated.
I think the gravity will be 30,000.
What is that?
What?
That.
This?
I'm not going to use it. It's just
something I personally want to see.
I'm going to hide it.
I was thinking,
It's fine.
There it is.
It fell.
Yes.
It looks so good.
It's a dress I want to make.
No, it's not.
It's completely down.
For the time being, you can put it away.
Really?
I'll put it in front of you.
I'll open the gap a little.
The door is open.
When you stop moving, you can breathe once.
When you are doing something.
When you are talking to someone.
When you are taking a picture.
When you are active.
When you are in a good mood.
I miss you so much.
I'm sorry to say this in front of
you, but I'm excited just to kiss you.
I agree.
It's so nice to have a partner
who forgives your body.
I felt the same way at first.
It's easy to feel.
I was surprised.
The moment you were ready.
The moment you betrayed.
The moment you waited at home.
The moment you did it.
I still remember.
It's beautiful.
I said I was embarrassed.
You are beautiful.
I'm sorry.
At that moment,
my heart was taken away.
I'm sorry.
I resisted with my hands at the end.
I'm accepting it, but.
the last pose.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with your face?
I can't feel my face.
Your face is a little swollen.
You have round eyes.
You have beautiful eyes.
What's wrong?
Take off your clothes.
Show me your beautiful eyes.
I want to see your beautiful eyes.
Even if I drop my upper
body, I have to be careful.
It's beautiful.
When I was looking for a ring in the
bathroom, I saw my wife posing like this.
From behind.
Do you see?
It's coming in from behind.
It's so deep.
It's amazing.
It's so tight.
Do you want to see it?
Don't you want to see it?
It's closer.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry
Did you wash it with your wife's hands?
What should I do?
Don't look away.
Look for it while stepping on it.
I can't see anything.
I'm so happy.
This is really big.
I have to take off my panties.
I'm embarrassed.
I could only see a little while ago.
But, look at me closely.
I'm not your husband.
Do you look down on me?
I want you to look down on me, too.
I've always wanted to look down on you.
Really?
Yes.
That hand is cruel.
That hand is slow.
You look like you're really sleeping.
Do you remember?
I want to surprise you.
I remember.
Really?
Yes.
You were having a lot of sex.
You were enjoying it, weren't you?
Wow, look at the other side.
You look like you're enjoying it.
Your lips are delicious, too.
Your lips are really...
I can't keep this posture for a while.
A little more.
Oh, my God.
Your head is still there.
What?
Just a little bit.
I don't want you to put it in yet
I don't want you to put it in yet.
Just a little more.
Just a little more No?
You'll be found out.
I want to put it in.
You'll be found out
It's frustrating.
I want to put it in.
I'm so tired.
Oh, my God.
I can't stand it.
Takashi, please look at the monitor.
Rufina, what are you doing?
Are you trying to put it in?
I'm trying to put it in.
Really?
I forgot. I want to put it in as it is.
I want to put it in, but...
I want to put it in, but if I put it
in, it will be a burden to work.
Don't rub it.
Wait a minute.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
It's gone.
You look sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
She's tired.
Wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop.
I want to lift your hip.
Wait, stop, stop.
I don't want to stop.
What?
You can't. Your hip will go up.
Seriously?
You're fighting against your instincts.
I'm in trouble with a fight with a cat.
I can't help it because my back is up.
I can't help it.
I'm in trouble.
It's hot.
Let's go over there.
No, not now.
Let's go to your husband.
Hey, you are sleeping.
You are so small.
I'm going to sleep for a while.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Huh?
Are you alright?
Hey, listen to me, Hey.
You always said that you
don't want to be taken by others.
You said that.
I was talking to you before,
and I asked you to do this today.
I wanted you to do something like this.
So I asked you this time.
You're surprised, aren't you?
So my wife may be a little
shocked, but when I saw my
husband treating my wife
like that, I was a little moved.
I thought I could understand that a little.
I thought I could accept it a little.
But I don't think he does it
because he doesn't like his wife.
He loves his wife so much.
But he doesn't spend
much time with his wife.
I don't want him to change.
I don't know if I should do it again.
In order to be with
your wife for a long time,
you want to enjoy various
things, such as stimulation,
and more and more with your wife.
You don't want to enjoy this every time.
It's different.
Sometimes I feel like this is bad.
I think so, too.
She may be a little out of her mind.
For example, while being
looked at by other people.
Look.
Let me take it off.
Let me take it off in front of your wife.
Like this?
Yes.
Look at me.
I'm a little shy.
You are really shy.
You have a beautiful voice.
I'm a little shy.
Did you peep at me?
I peeped a little.
You are so naughty.
You were doing like this to me.
Do you remember?
Do you want to come here?
I want you to do it with me.
I'll give you a bath.
Is it your first time in love?
Please relax.
My wife doesn't get angry.
Don't you get angry?
I want to see you doing that.
If you do that, I'll do it for you.
Does it feel good?
It feels better than when
you were in the bath.
Your eyes are also very good.
Do you want to put up with it a little?
Give me a kiss.
How do you feel?
Wow!
It's harder than before.
Wow! It's hard.
It's mixed up.
Put it in your mouth.
Let me see.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
It feels so good
Let me see your wife's boobs.
You have a nice face.
Show me your gentle face.
Do you feel good?
Good boy.
You are good at it.
You are the best.
Nana, do your best.
Do you want me to do it?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Do you want to do the same as before?
Because it was in the middle.
Do you want to do the same?
Do you want to put something in?
It's a little dangerous.
Do you feel good?
You are so soft.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold your tail.
Show me your beautiful face.
Come in again.
Does it feel good?
Move it more comfortably.
Good.
Which one do you feel better?
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Good boy.
You have a good face.
Is it in your belly?
Let's see from the back.
Nana-San.
Is it in your belly?
Look.
He is looking at you.
No.
I can't see anything.
Do you feel good?
Don't look at me.
I'm going to put it in from behind.
Lower your head like before.
It's disgusting.
Does it feel good?
You're doing a great job.
What's wrong?
Your nose is bleeding.
Let's have a doctor check your nose.
I'll check your nose.
Wow.
What's this?
It's messed up.
I've been looking at it, so it's messed up.
Your nose is bleeding.
It's a big deal.
Good girl.
Let me see your mouth.
Good boy.
How do you feel, Oku-San?
Are you happy?
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Lie down.
Listen to the story of Takai-San and Jinbo.
Which is better, Takai-San or Jinbo?
Which is better?
Tell me.
Which one do you like?
This one.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
I feel good, too.
I'm so sorry...
I feel so bad... You're crying?
I feel so bad...
How about this?
Wow! Look at this!
It's amazing!
Honey!
It's round, isn't it?
It's the one I put in earlier, isn't it?
How did you do it?
You put it in from the side, didn't you?
Just a moment ago.
What are you doing there?
Look at me.
You should look at me with your big eyes.
Does it feel good?
You don't want to look at
me with that look any more.
me with that look any more?
Look at me.
I'm really sorry.
She's crying more than earlier.
I have a stomachache.
I'm the husband's only baby.
I did it.
More?
You were greedy.
You did.
I'm really sorry.
You put toys in your stomach and cried.
I'm going to sleep.
You were sleeping.
I don't want to.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
Oh, it's great.
It's great.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
I'll make you hard.
Can I put your hair in the big hair comb?
Yes.
You're so kind.
Please put it in.
You two are wearing the same clothes.
Which butt is better?
I want to see both of you.
Oh, she is shaking.
You are four-legged.
Which butt is better?
Both buttocks are good.
I'll put it in.
Again?
You're fast.
Oh, my God!
Wow!
You've shed a lot of hair.
Yes, I have.
Look.
You've shed a lot of hair.
It's nice to see you.
You look like a meat.
How was it?
In front of your husband.
Me and your husband.
It was so sudden that
I couldn't say anything.
Were you surprised?
This is not bad.
Did you feel good?
It was good, wasn't it?
You had a very good face.
I was about to melt in your eyes.
It hurts.
I love you.
Is this it?
This may be it.
How is it?
I can't catch up with it.
This is it.
It's dark.
I can see it.
Oh, I can see it.
Oh, they are smiling.
What a couple.
They may get along well.
They are getting along well.
That's good.
They are getting along
better than in the morning.
Wait a minute.
Where is it?
It's no good.
Is this it?
OK.
I can't see it anymore,
so let's go over there.
Yeah, I'd like to talk to him.
Thank you for your hard work.
I walked home with my hands.
You were in love.
I came back home with a smile.
You may have been disappointed.
But it was good.
It was a success.
I was wondering what would happen.
I was very nervous.
You were not nervous at all.
That's right.
You were having fun by yourself.
No, I wasn't.
You were having more fun than me.
You looked like you were
going to cry at the end.
Did I?
That's amazing.
When we were hugging?
I was wondering if you were okay.
I was worried that you
would cry at the end.
But it seems to be like that.
Is that so?
I was told that I was going to get married.
I was relieved.
But you didn't look like you
were going to get married.
I was relieved.
Thank you very much for your success.
Thank you.
Aren't you tired?
What?
Aren't you tired today?
I'm always tired.
I'm tired because I have to work hard.
Because you have to work hard?
What if I fail?
That's right.
It's not easy for a young person.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to send my girlfriend.
Let's go on a trip next time.
Yes, let's go.
Is it okay?
Let's send this.
Please put your luggage over there.
I got it.
I'll send it to you.
Thank you for your hard work.
Can you sign this?
Yes.
Please sit down.
I was going to say the same thing.
Oh, really?
I was a little late.
I'm still looking at it.
As it is.
If you go back to the
professor, you'll be fine, right?
Yes.
The professor will be here soon.
Can I take you to the hotel?
Yes.
Can I?
I might not be able to take you back today.
Really?
Then...
It's okay.