I met Hiroshi-san through
my friend's introduction.
We've been married for half a year.
He's always calm and kind.
Our marital life is very fulfilling.
Are you going to take your boss, Abe-san?
No.
Today?
He rarely talks about work at home.
He's waiting for his boss to come home.
She is waiting for him to come back home.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Hello, ma'am. Nice to meet you. I'm Abe.
Nice to meet you, Abe.
My husband always helps me.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Not at all.
Please come in.
It's small, but please come in.
Thank you for coming.
It's a nice house.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I asked you to come here all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
I asked you all of a sudden,
so I could only make this much.
No, it's enough.
I'm really sorry.
But you have a nice
house, and a beautiful wife.
You have a good personality.
No, I don't.
You have a nice house,
but you are a little shy.
I think you are a little shy.
No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
No, I didn't mean that.
I heard you were coming all of a sudden.
I was drinking a little bit.
I usually drink a little more.
You should have told me earlier.
I'm sorry.
You wanted to show off, didn't you?
You wanted to get such a beautiful wife.
Is that so?
Well, just a little.
No, no, no.
You don't look like such a beautiful woman.
No, I don't.
At this level, I thought you
wanted to marry an ugly woman.
Then, what is this?
You are so hideous.
You are terrible.
At least, you should
have a little more bra.
I'm sorry, but I'm not a zombie.
I'm excited when a
beautiful woman does this.
My wife's meat is exquisite.
It's a little embarrassing.
I think it's exquisite.
I'm always happy.
This is a masterpiece.
Please try it.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
I'm sure she'll love it.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice.
No, no, no.
It's my job.
No, it's okay.
Here you are.
I didn't want my wife to come with me.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Does your wife drink?
What?
Do you drink?
I drink occasionally.
Does your wife
drink? Yes, she does.
Give it to your wife.
Oh, I see.
You drink as it is.
As it is?
If you don't mind, I'd like to
have a cup of tea with you.
No, thank you.
You don't know how to joke.
I'm sorry.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Bring me some chocolate.
OK.
I'll bring it.
Please.
The food is delicious.
Thank you.
You must be hungry.
No, I'm not.
I'm so sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry. I only had one.
Oh, really?
Don't worry about it.
Then, you drink it.
Me? Yes, you.
Thank you.
You're a good wife.
I'm a good wife.
Why did you like him?
He's surprisingly manly.
You're kidding,
right? He said so.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
You have to work hard at your company.
You got married to such a beautiful woman.
I'll do my best.
You bought this with your own
money, didn't you? Yes, I did.
I overdid it a little.
You have to work hard.
Drink it.
Thank you.
You too, Momo.
Kanetaka Shoji's Yoshida Senbu is also
a strong drinker, isn't he? Yes, he is.
You have to understand
that and invite him.
I got it.
What's next?
He only drinks with both hands.
Really?
Don't forget to set it up.
I got it.
That's a lot.
Are you okay with the expenses?
I'll do something good.
Don't worry about finishing a big project.
I got it.
I've just finished a big
job, so I'm a little relieved.
I'm out of my mind.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I guess I wanted to get excited
and introduce you to my wife.
Oh, that's what it
was about? Yeah.
Aren't you drinking too
much? Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, really?
I'll be right back.
You bought a house in
such a nice place, didn't you?
You must be happy.
No, it's not like that.
I was introduced to this house by a friend.
Did you have such a friend?
I don't think so at all.
I just happened to have
a junior from college.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Here you are.
Thank you, Momo.
Thank you.
Don't drink too much.
It's such a waste.
No, it's not a waste.
It's a thousand percent a waste.
Would you like to
have a drink? Oh, sorry.
I didn't notice.
Here you are.
Thank you very much.
I finished my work a while
ago, so I want to drink with you.
I like the highball over there.
I drank it in the car.
I was drinking with the director.
I always have dark eyes,
so you had the same thing.
Who has a red face? I'm mature.
Drink.
Hey, drink up.
I'm sorry, but I can't drink anymore.
You only say what common
people say, don't you?
You're a stereotypical human being.
You're so mean, boss.
You're so mean.
You have to be able to argue with me.
I see.
I'll try harder.
But you always say, Mr. Abe, Mr. Abe.
I'm just saying.
I know, right?
It's embarrassing.
I can't help it.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Are you OK? I'm OK.
Drinking makes me stronger.
It's a way to improve my English.
Thank you.
Make a lot of money.
Be careful.
It's so good.
Wow, it's so good.
You're getting more and more manly.
Here, here.
Thank you.
Wow, it's so good.
Here.
You're getting more and more manly.
I don't usually drink this much.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm fine.
And you!
Don't show your nipples!
Go home!
Didn't you wear a
shirt? I took it off.
I'm sorry.
I didn't notice.
Are you OK? It's okay.
It's okay.
You can still drink more.
I'm going. I'm going.
Oh, you're going to drink more?
I'm going to follow you.
Abe-san, you're a strong drinker.
I'm a heavy drinker.
I'm sorry, Abe-san.
He seems to have been drinking too much.
He was drinking as usual.
Besides, he hasn't been home lately.
That's true.
He's been working hard on his own project.
Is that so?
He must have run out of alcohol.
He doesn't talk to me much about work.
I see.
Well, there are a lot of
people like that in the company.
Where did you get
married? What? Well, I.
..
I'd like to know more about you.
I'm embarrassed.
You're sleeping, so it's okay.
I wonder if she still thinks of me.
Wow, it's so hot in here.
You're like a beauty and a beast.
No, I'm not.
No, I don't.
I don't know if I can
say this to my wife, who
seems to be happy to have
such a wonderful house.
I don't know if I should tell you
this, but I have something to tell you.
What is it?
In fact, I found out that Honda
has been neglecting the economy.
Why?
I was surprised, too.
I didn't know such a serious and
carefree guy would do such a thing.
It's a little hard to believe.
Well, to be honest with you,
that's what I'm worried about.
However, as far as I can
tell, at least 2 million yen.
2 million yen? I have it.
But why?
I don't know the details, but I'm sure...
It was October, wasn't it?
I wanted to make a good living for a
beautiful wife with a nice house and a loan.
Well, that's the first step for
a man who does business.
Fortunately, I'm the only
one who knows this fact.
Fortunately, I'm the only one in charge.
I haven't told my family yet.
There's a good chance
I'll have to pay more.
Abe-san, what should I do?
If my family finds out, it won't
just be a disciplinary action.
I'm sorry if I'm the
only one who thinks so.
Well, if you think about it
normally, it could be a criminal case.
Mr. Abe, is there anything we can do?
You don't want to
ruin the lives of two
people who seem to be
happy right now, do you?
Yes.
But the fact that you've
done it doesn't disappear.
I'm sorry, but if it's
about 2 million yen, I
can pay it off at my
disposal as the manager.
Is that so?
You don't want to abandon him, do you?
Can I really do
that? You can do it.
At this stage.
But this time, even if you save him,
I have to stop him somewhere.
So,
I'll tell him,
I'll tell him not to do it again.
I'm really sorry.
It's not like you're apologizing.
I don't know what to do.
Calm down, ma'am.
I'm the only one who knows this fact.
I'll save you two before it's too late.
I'll do anything I can.
Thank you.
I wanted to hear your resolve.
I wanted to ask you something.
Are you ready to do
anything to protect their lives?
Yes.
I'm glad you were loved
by such a beautiful lady, and
you said you would do anything
so as not to be found out.
What is it? Ma'am.
Do you know anything about marital life?
What is it?
Don't you know?
If you come here in this
situation... My husband is sleeping.
What should I do? No, no.
I'm sure you know.
Please don't.
You said you'd do
anything to protect this life.
You said you would do
anything to protect me.
I did say that.
You know what I'm going to do, don't you?
No.
I'm going to make sure you don't find
out about the crime you've committed.
It's too soon to say it's free, isn't it?
I said it's free.
So, are you going to pretend
you didn't hear anything? That's all.
I'm not just going to tell you that she's
a prostitute, and that she's a prostitute.
I'm going to tell you that she's a
prostitute, and that she's a prostitute.
That's all I'm going to tell you.
All right.
If you don't like it, I'll excuse you.
I beg you.
Please help me.
Then, let me help you.
No, that's... I'll tell you.
I don't think you're good at sex.
You don't have to sweat.
You sweat because your body doesn't rest.
You don't have to lose everything.
Give me your tongue.
Put your tongue out.
It's hard to do it next to her, isn't it?
Put your legs together.
I'm going to puke.
I'm going to cry.
You just have to keep quiet.
You can do anything.
You have a beautiful white skin.
Why are you so
nervous? I have a cramp.
You have a cramp,
don't you? I have a cramp.
You have a beautiful pink cramp.
Let me do it.
I'm sorry.
Are you sick?
I can't stand up because I'm excited.
Do you want to sit down?
You don't look like you're in a bad mood.
I can't stand your impatient face.
Let's go to bed.
Are you sleepy?
Your husband is sleeping next to you.
And you are playing with your body.
I'm so embarrassed
that I'm going to hide it.
Please do it.
It's boring.
I'm lucky to have such a face.
It's worth saving him.
Right?
I have a wound on my left leg.
I can see a wound here.
I have a wound on my right leg.
She is still in a bad mood.
She has a finger in her mouth.
She is drooling.
You have a lot of pimples.
Can I take it
off? It's up to you.
If I tell you to take it
off, you should do it.
You are so stubborn.
Take it off.
I'm going to take it off, too.
You're such a clumsy girl.
You want to protect him, don't you?
Can you do me a favor?
You know what to do, don't you?
What should I do?
Are you going to comfort
me with your hands?
Do you remember, ma'am?
Let's go around.
What should I do?
Ma'am?
Don't be so serious.
Deeper.
How is it compared to his?
He's small, isn't he?
I've seen him on a business trip.
It's like this.
You're not satisfied,
are you? No, I'm not.
It's written on your face.
Are you trying to be
a woman? No, I'm not.
I don't think so.
What do you mean?
I'm going to cut your nose.
I'm sorry.
You have beautiful hips.
You made a hole in my hip.
I'm sorry.
You have no balls.
You have a wife's tumor.
Ahh, it's so tight.
My wife… I feel sick.
I feel sick.
I can't do it.
Ahh, it's so tight.
I feel sick.
My wife, I really feel sick.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to send you to hell.
I can't send you to
hell with that little girl.
Don't make me cry.
I'm going to cry.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I enjoyed the meal of 2 million yen.
It was a good one.
I'm going to break the egg.
You like a big Chimpanzee, don't you?
You're used to it.
Do you mind here?
Is my Chimpanzee so good?
No.
I've told you three times.
Don't make such a loud voice.
Give me your hand.
Huh?
Yes, that's right.
I'll do my best.
Don't make a loud voice.
Oh, my wife.
Oh, you're naked.
I don't think you can get up here.
Oh, you feel good.
You have to keep your voice down.
My husband found out.
Look.
Do you like me that
much? Wait a minute.
I think I can do it, too.
Wait a minute.
I can't do it.
You can't move like that.
You must have come out of a tightened hole.
It was stable,
wasn't it? Yes, it was.
It's because you tighten
it, isn't it? No, it's not.
Please pull it out a little.
No, it's not.
Because you tighten it,
I wanted to take it out.
It's terrible.
You wanted to have a
uterus, didn't you? No, it's not.
Honda's wife is such a good woman.
It's annoying.
Anyway, I'll come again.
I don't think I can tell Honda
what just happened here.
If I told him a little more,
he would understand.
I'll let you go.
So, my wife.
Again.
I need to take a bath.
You look like you want to cry.
You said that to me many times
the other day, didn't you? No, I didn't.
You understood what I said, didn't you?
You are still so sensitive to my needs.
No, I'm not.
You are still crying.
Chikubi, you have grown up so much.
No, I haven't.
Your body is honest.
I was surprised.
Chikubi, you are about to leave.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Hey, wife.
I'm a man who is
dissatisfied with your desire.
I came to give you a massage.
You have a lot of wrinkles.
I brought this because I can't be
satisfied with such a beautiful wife.
Please don't say bad things about her.
Don't do that, please.
Don't do that.
Look at your face.
If you say something like that,
I want to break your face even more.
Have you ever used such an
erotic woman? No, I haven't.
You're an adult.
Look.
That's why when you
get married to a boring
man, you start to say
that your body is lonely.
It's fun, isn't it?
No!
Wait, Sumire-chan.
No?
What's the matter?
You want me to comfort you, don't you?
Your back is trembling.
That's why I'm here.
I don't know what to
do with such a beautiful
and nasty face, and
it's all because of him.
You don't know anything about men, do you?
You have such a big boob.
Your panties are wet.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good
around here? Here? Here.
You don't have to make a loud voice today.
I want you to apply it directly to me.
My wife, you have to do
what I tell you to do, or you
won't be able to go back
to the way you used to be.
Open your eyes wide.
Please don't look at me.
Please sit on my lap.
Go away.
Don't be stubborn.
I told you to go away.
You are a bad girl.
Don't do that!
No!
Please don't come closer!
Can you see it? It's so full of pus.
It's so full of pus that you can't feel it.
It's about to fall apart.
Nene, look!
I'm holding you.
You are scary.
He goes so fast.
He is so small.
He is not a human being.
Look at your tongue.
You have been coughing for a long time.
Show me your tongue.
You know that you want your
body, don't you? Telephone.
What's the timing?
Are you all right?
It's a call from a woman.
It's all right.
You'd better go out.
Please don't.
No.
Wait.
Hello?
Is it going to be
late? It's all right.
If you don't take care of
yourself, you'll be exposed.
I'm sorry.
Welcome.
I'm not sick.
It's okay. It's okay.
I was cleaning up.
Okay. I'll wait for you.
Do your best at work.
You didn't find out, did you?
You didn't find
out? Please stop it.
She hasn't noticed it yet.
She is very sensible.
She usually notices
when I make such a noise.
Something is going on.
That's how she is.
She is very sensitive.
Look.
Turn your back.
Show me your face.
You are still eating.
You are so naughty.
Raise your leg.
Oh, you don't like it.
You are still eating.
You are so naughty.
You have a lot of pus.
Your anus is swollen.
You can't lie down.
You have a lot of pus.
You can lie down on your favorite place.
Mom is looking for氷.
The mother is looking for a peanut.
The mother is looking for a pear.
You have a lot of hair on your body.
You have a lot of hair.
You want me to comb
your hair more, don't you?
I'll do it for you.
I want you to comb your hair more.
Your nipples are so soft.
This is a good place, isn't it?
What are you doing?
The house in Shinjuku is wet
with your DOSUKEBEJYUU.
I'm sorry.
He doesn't feel the smell of
disgusting DOSUKEBEJYUU.
He is a bad Anpontan.
Don't cry.
Please let me off.
I've been through a lot.
I've had a hard time.
I'm getting old, too.
I'm getting older.
Will you take care
of me? I'm in trouble.
Please go.
I washed the mangoes in the
salt water and they came out again.
They didn't come out?
What is it? Look.
You are getting used to it.
Do you want me to touch you?
Do you want me to do it?
You do, don't you?
You didn't know that I
was such a gentle girl.
You are such a bad boy.
You are so useless.
I'm sorry.
I told you before, didn't I?
You're the only one who feels good.
You have to understand
my feelings and forgive me.
Power balance.
You understand, don't
you? Give me a hug.
Let's continue.
Ouch!
Let me see your tongue.
Your tongue feels good, doesn't it?
My chest is sensitive, isn't it?
Please lick my chest.
Oh, it feels good.
It hurts.
You lick, roll, and suck.
More.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
You can eat more gently.
Have you ever been pinched by her
chin with such a beautiful soft voice?
You have never been pinched.
I'm going to do a pie-fishing.
I'm going to pinch your boobs.
I'm going to rub your
cheeks and make your boobs.
I'm going to put a vine on your boob.
Look at me.
Look at this.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Your tongue is playing.
I'll give you a treat.
Here you are.
Oh, it's hot.
I'm going to put the baby to sleep.
I'm sorry for my poor english.
This is the first time
I've ever had a baby,
so I'm a little nervous,
but I'll do my best.
Oh, my God, oh, my God
my God, oh, my God
※I have no idea what he is saying.
You feel lonely, don't you?
You also feel lonely.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to eat it.
I'll give you a present.
I'm going to eat it all.
I'm sorry.
I know you've been doing
this since you were little.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ughh~!
Just, look what I did to my mouth.
Ughh~! Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm the only
one who can't eat it.
I like it.
Today, I'm going to show you how to get rid
of the hair on the back of a cat's head.
I'm going to show you how to get rid
Oh!
Oh, you're so silly.
Oh, don't be scared.
Oh!
Oh! Dad, I'm sorry.
I'll put you in bed.
Please let me go.
You're so sentimental.
I'll put you in bed.
Please let me go.
I'll put my room smell on your bed.
No! Let me go.
Manko, you're lonely, aren't you?
Let's go to the bedroom.
Please.
Come on.
Let's do it here.
Wait a minute.
Don't be noisy.
Who the hell are you?
Hello? Yes, this is Abe.
What? You haven't received the order yet?
What? Are you in the hospital?
I'm terribly sorry.
I understand.
I'll send it to you right away.
I'll be back in 30 minutes.
Yes, yes.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Ma'am,
I'll be back in 30 minutes.
See you later.
What's wrong, Momo? You don't look well.
No, I'm fine.
I see.
Oh, I know.
Why don't we go on a
trip to refresh ourselves?
We've had a lot of work lately.
Yeah, you're right.
I know. Where should we go?
How about Atami?
Now that I think about it,
I'm getting excited again.
I'm feeling better.
Let's do it again.
What? Ah, Momo, Momo.
Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah, I feel so good in my throat.
Ah... Ah...
While she was with her husband,
she remembered her behavior with
Abe-san, which can be called humiliation.
It reminds me of the
time when I was a child.
I shouldn't have done such a violent thing,
but I can't get that sex out of my head.
Don't look at me like that.
You look very beautiful.
It looks good on you.
What is this?
You look so disgusting.
You don't have a high place
for him, do you? No, I don't.
I see.
It's not good to have sex in the morning.
You need to have the energy to do it.
Please let this be the last time.
It's up to the wife.
Don't you want to take a rest?
I'll do anything for you.
You want to protect our lives, don't you?
It's up to the wife.
You are not crying?
He is so kind and gentle.
She was licking her lips
and biting her lips lightly.
She was licking her
wife's breasts all the time.
Please.
You've had a dream, haven't you?
There's no place like this.
You are a man who
can't satisfy a single wife.
I'm glad I was able to do something.
You look good.
Please stop.
Please lick me.
You look like you want to be licked.
I want to be licked.
No.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to lick me.
I'll lick you more.
Stand up.
Let's have fun.
You've never had sex in your life.
Stand up.
Come on.
Come to my mouth slowly.
You want me to lick
you, don't you? Come on.
Come on.
I'm not used to licking.
I'm going to give you a shot.
Take a deep breath.
This is a video of me eating a baby's food.
It's a video of me eating a baby's food.
I'm not good at eating.
Today, I'm going to show you how
to get rid of pimples on your face.
I'm going to show you how to
get rid of pimples on your face.
You're so cute.
It's delicious.
I pulled it out earlier,
but it's still like this.
You can't eat so much kimchi, can you?
a few shots
Today, I'm going to
show you how to make the
most delicious fried
chicken in the world.
Mew!
You are a good wife.
You can't do a good job of petting.
Mew!
You want a pet, don't you?
It's written in the book.
You have to put up with it.
You can't stop crying,
can you? No, I can't.
Oh, really?
Are you crying?
Yes.
This video is an original copy.
The original version of this
video is not available for download.
・・・ arbitrarily
paper
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
It's the middle of the night.
What is it?
You don't have to be so aggressive.
Now...
You're fine. Don't be so aggressive.
I'm tired.
You don't have to be.
It's a lie, isn't it?
The fact that Honda
made an error is all a lie.
There's no way he made an error.
You're saying he lied?
Yes.
You're the worst!
I want to hit you.
But your body reacts to it.
Stop it.
What are you going to do?
No.
You have a lot of bruises.
What are you going to do?
You are a human being,
but you are so full of blood.
You lost to my Chimpanzee, not to a lie.
Do you want to quit?
You don't want me to quit, do you?
I'm not asking you. Do you want to quit?
Do you want to quit?
Do you want to quit this?
How many times have you made me live?
I want to know the truth.
Don't think about him now.
Tell me what you want
to do in this situation.
Please continue.
Help me.
What?
Please, put me in the coffin.
I lied to you because I thought
I couldn't satisfy a good woman.
You were like that.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God!
You can't kill him by stabbing him.
I can't stop it.
My life...
It feels good, doesn't it?
It smells good, doesn't it?
I'm going to give you a hand.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I want to cry.
I want to cry even more.
Please, let me cry a little more.
Please! I'm sorry.
I have a horse.
I'll give you a little more.
I'll give you some rice.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
You are better than him.
Of course.
Ah----
Ah… Oh, no, no, no, no...
Ugh… Oh, no…
Oh, no…
I've got a problem
when I'm told to be quiet.
Oh, no…!
This is terrible…
I'm going to break.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad you are in the toilet.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
She is so impolite.
I'm so sorry.
I'm tired.
You can't have sex for such a long time.
What is this?
It's a box, isn't it?
Come in and sit in the box.
Come in the box.
I'm sorry.
I'll tighten your leg.
Please lie down.
Don't stop.
I love you.
I love this cat.
I love you, too.
I love you.
I'm sleepy.
I'm scared.
I can't drown.
I can't stand it anymore.
You like this, don't you?
Oh, please help me more.
Mom, I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it longer.
I can't do it.
My waist is broken.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
You are sleeping, aren't you?
My favorite baby.
Oh, no!
What should I do?
Watch out! Please help me.
Mother, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, mother! Mother.
..
What can I do? I lost.
You are the best woman.
It's the best sex.
You don't have to worry about it.
It's a big deal.
Let's continue this relationship.