It looks like that.
Rio-chan, Rio-chan.
Hello.
Thank you.
We are friends.
You are so cute.
We are cute.
We are three sisters.
We are three beautiful sisters.
I'm looking forward to it.
Your cute friends are cute,
aren't they? Yes, they are.
They are so cute.
Let's walk together.
Let's go.
It's like a cafe.
They are cute, aren't they?
Ryo-chan is cute, too.
What's your friend's name?
What's my friend's name?
She is a college student.
A college student?
Can I ask your name? I'm Jun.
I'm Gen.
I'm Rio.
What's your name? I'm Erika.
You are so cute.
You are unique and cute.
I'm Erika.
You have a good style.
I'm embarrassed.
People who are embarrassed
will not wear this, right? Erika is shy.
Erika is shy.
She is cute.
She is flamboyant.
They seem to get along very well.
They stand out from the crowd.
Yes, they do.
Pay attention to them.
They stand out from the crowd.
I was worried about Rin-chan.
I was worried about her.
She is in the middle of the crowd.
She stands out from the crowd.
White is not dirty.
If white is dirty, pink will be dirty.
They get along very well.
Are you a college friend?
Yes.
It seems that you have been dating
since you were in elementary school.
I think so.
How long have you
been dating? About a year.
What is the reason?
Circle?
Do you want to
eat this? Yes, I do.
I didn't know that three cute
girls are in the same circle.
I didn't notice at all.
Do you want to
eat this? No, I don't.
It was green.
I didn't eat it.
It smells like avocado.
That's right.
What does it taste
like? I don't know.
Is it a tennis
circle? Yes, it is.
Do you know tennis? No, I don't.
I only wrote my name.
Only your name?
Yes, only my name.
Only my name.
Rio-chan, you don't usually
talk like that, do you? No, I don't.
Because I'm not
attracted to you.
It's a sexual harassment.
Rio-chan, I know you.
Can you tell me your name?
My name is Erika.
Erika-chan.
My name is... She's
asking your name.
She is asking me.
This is Jun.
Jun.
She is really.
I don't have any trouble with her.
She is taking a picture of me.
Wait.
Did you change your mind?
I don't have a button.
You don't have a button.
I want you to push it.
It is very far.
You can take a picture of me.
Can I? Yes, you can.
It's good, isn't it?
Let's take a picture.
Do you want me to take a picture of you?
I think you can take a
picture of me by yourself.
It's okay.
I'll do it again.
You're not supposed to do this.
It's not like that.
You should say, It's okay.
It's more important to be buried.
It's important to be buried.
It's a waste of data.
I don't erase it.
I'm addicted to it.
It's cute.
Rio,
I wonder if it's
transmitted properly today.
Yes.
Maybe.
What did you say to me?
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to do it, but I'm going to do it
You've done it a lot?
Have you ever done it with
three people? Yes, I have.
Really? Sometimes.
I don't do it often.
If the schedule doesn't match,
do you do it with two people?
I do it with two people.
Like this.
Rotation.
I think you already know.
What are you going to do today?
Are you going to ask me?
What are you going to do?
What? What am I going to do?
I'm going to say,
Wow!
What are you going to do?
Are you going to ask me?
What am I going to say?
What are you going to do?
Wow!
You don't guard your fans, do you?
I don't guard my fans.
I do erotic things.
Really?
Are you OK, Eiko? I'm OK.
You are Ryo-chan's friend.
They are all crazy.
You are so cute.
You are so beautiful.
Wait.
It's easy to drop it.
It's hard to eat.
But it's fun to eat.
Yes, everyone is like a gyaru.
It's fun to eat and I like it.
You don't hate it,
do you? No, I don't.
I like it.
How about you? I like it.
What do you like?
Especially?
Yes, especially.
You like Enchi?
What is your specialty? Eko-ki.
Oh my god! That's amazing.
That's when the music stopped.
Eko-ki.
Oh my god.
That's amazing.
What?
Your hands are amazing.
Do you tap?
Do you watch it? Yes, sometimes.
How does it move?
It's like a piano.
It's smooth.
Smooth?
Yes, it's smooth.
Sometimes I watch it.
What is your specialty, Rio?
My feet are like this.
What is that?
I've never done that.
My feet are like this.
My legs are soft.
My toes are so healthy.
My toes are messy.
Your toes are messy, don't
you think? Yes, they are.
You look like a ballon d'or.
I'm messy.
That's the way to do.
You are messy even in a period of time.
People say my lips are loose.
They say my lips are loose.
It is said that it is loose.
I ate a lot and it is
loose around my mouth.
But, it is getting bigger.
I didn't know that.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
Actually...
No.
Really?
Yes.
What is your favorite flavor?
This is a cookie.
Everyone says it is a cookie.
So, I say it is a cookie.
It's called Koki-shibari.
If it's Koki, it's silica.
Oh, I didn't know that.
We still have it.
We'll start when you say your name.
Say my name.
Ushi? Ushi Naka.
Naka.
This is the best.
I love it.
Do you like it?
Don't you want to wear it?
I want to wear it.
We both feel good.
I was going to pick up the lottery.
It's too difficult to pick up the lottery.
What do you like? I like.
..
I like ears.
I like eyes.
You don't go out.
I want to go out soon.
I like outside.
Then, go out quietly.
Let me sleep.
Come here.
It looks like a conditioner.
It's good for smooth skin.
It's smooth.
I'm tired.
I'm going to write a letter of apology.
It's really hard.
I'll take it.
I'm going to write a letter of apology.
I think I need more time.
It's hot.
Again.
I'm wearing a hat.
I'm wearing a cap.
I'm going to call Yangan.
Where did you
buy this? Harajuku.
It looks like it's going to sell.
Yangan? Okay.
Let's do it.
Really? Let's do it.
Hey.
Ryo-chan is asking.
Stop it.
Why are you suddenly
doing this? Stop it.
You are dirty.
Pants.
I can see your underwear.
What do you usually
look like when you start?
When you are in a big group.
When I'm in a big group?
It depends on the person.
Do you have the best outfit?
The best?
What is the last one?
What is the last
one? I don't know.
6?
5?
Suddenly, everyone is...
Suddenly, everyone is... 6P?
6P?
4P?
You have few days, so do your best.
You can do it with both hands.
You can use your hands as much as you want.
I can do it in time.
You can do it in
time? You have legs.
I have legs.
You can use them
as much as you want.
I can use them as much as I want.
It's good.
Leave me alone.
It's my first time to deal
with three people alone.
I'm alone.
Come here.
Can I? Come here.
This pose is not good.
Do you want to take a rest?
Take a rest? Take a rest.
What do you want to check?
Who will be fit?
It's between us.
It's annoying.
If you don't have the back of
your hand, you can do it like this.
I'm stuck.
It's important.
She is not sitting down.
I have to hold her down.
The baby's neck is coming off.
Her neck is coming off.
It's not good.
She is standing up.
It's true.
It's great.
She is the fastest.
She is fast.
I want to see your body.
I want to see you in this sexy outfit.
And this pink.
Let's wear it.
I want you to wear it.
It's cute.
If you have a jacket,
why don't you take it off?
Take off my jacket?
I don't have a jacket.
It's too obvious.
You are so bold.
I can see it.
It looks like cabbage.
Lettuce.
Can you see it?
I can't see anything.
This is the point.
It's in my stomach.
I want to wear it on my stomach.
On your stomach?
My stomach hurts.
Harajuku is Harajuku.
Yes, it is.
I want to wear it on my stomach.
On your stomach?
On my stomach?
I want you to show me your underwear.
Underwear?
Yes.
I want you to show me your top.
My top?
If you take off the
J, all of them will fit.
Oh, really? It's connected.
Then, I'll take off the J.
Why?
I'll take off all of the J.
Judging from this relationship, if
you take off the J, all of them will fit.
I'm serious.
I think this is better.
This is better.
I'll take off the J.
Open J.
Why? I think J.
Y. Park has already seen it.
It's from Alitagoria.
Wow.
That was quick.
I've only seen one.
That's good.
Everyone has already seen the butt.
I'm used to seeing it.
I've seen it a lot.
Don't shake it.
I'm sorry.
It's a really good butt.
Stay still.
Manko is so cute.
Why?
Not cute, Manko is cute.
Manko is cute.
We will see later.
She is so cute.
Let's go to the top.
Then, let's go together.
Not together.
Let's go in order.
In order.
Good butt.
This is a large one.
Is this large, too? It's big.
Here's the butt.
It's all right.
It's hard to see.
It's a part of the body.
I love it.
It's like an alien.
It's big.
It's a good size.
Good.
It's not good name.
It's not good.
It's not good because I can't get in there.
Good.
Next.
YANGA, take it.
I want to see.
I'm curious.
I'm so curious.
Ready, go!
I'll wash my hands.
YANGA.
He is so cute.
It's so cute.
Where did you
buy it? It's so cute.
It's so cute.
Let's stand in a line.
Look back.
Butt.
She is putting a tablecloth next to her.
She is trying not to push it out.
She is a bully.
She is the strongest in the middle.
She is crushed.
Butt.
I'm surprised.
He is being pushed.
Who is pushing my head?
Let's make it smaller.
Put your knees on here.
It's OK. Support it with both feet.
What do you think?
Good girls have different colors.
What do you think? Right.
Like the color of
your underwear.
Right.
Do you all do T-backs?
Do you do basic
T-backs? Yes, we do.
Let's look forward this time.
If you look at my butt,
you will look forward.
Which side do you like? Front or back?
I like the back side.
But I want to look forward.
Because it's a big deal.
Why? First J.
First J.
J cup? J cup's J.
J cup's J.
It's totally different.
But it's very soft.
Is it weak?
Yes, it's a service.
No.
Service.
J3.
Then it's J cup.
No.
J3.
First J.
It's Jikubi.
She is going to have a hard time.
A hard time?
Hurry up! Next!
Next?
Jane doesn't go for a long time.
Jane goes fast.
She goes in order.
I see.
It's big.
But Jane doesn't have it.
What did you buy?
G
Niozuri Niozuri It's so red!
Niozuri
Jizuri Jizuri Jizuri
It's big
It's big It's cute It's cute?
It's cuter than Manko
It's cute
Paikawaii is in charge
I'm in charge of Paikawa.
So cute.
You look like a hero.
Paikawa Pink.
Wait a minute.
You are the cutest character.
I'm going to the center.
I'm going to get it.
Yes.
I have to go where I can go.
I want a good role.
Do you want?
I can't win the entertainment industry.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you do it all at once,
your chest will hurt.
Are you okay?
It's not that bad.
No, it's thin.
It's thin.
It's a great neck.
I can't do it! I can't do it!
I can't do it! I can't
do it! It feels good.
It feels good.
What? Cute.
Hello.
Chikukawa.
It's like a
yuru-character, isn't it?
It's like a yuru-character, isn't it?
It's like a yuru-character,
isn't it? He is cute.
Don't crush him.
He is too cute.
He is cute.
His nipples are cute.
He is going to be gone.
Don't push him.
We grew up with the same boobs.
Paishiman.
I'm embarrassed.
Oh, no.
Paishiman.
You don't have a weapon.
A weapon?
Don't say that.
It's a trademark.
Yes, it's a trademark.
Are you going to take it off?
Are you going to
take it off? It's a little.
..
It's a little... It's a little... It's a
little... It's a little... It's a little...
It's a little... It's a little...
It's a little... It's a little... It's a
little... It's a little... It's a little...
It's a little... It's a little...
Let's do it one more time.
One, two, three!
So cute!
I'm a little embarrassed.
But you can't come out when
you're helping your friends.
She's always coming out because she's shy.
Pink is the same, right?
Pink is really shy.
〔Their baby is crying.
〕 It's a baby pink.
It's a pink baby.
It's cute!
Awesome!
What a cute baby.
It's a baby man.
The baby is wet.
He is wet and unable to use his strength.
He can't use his strength.
He is about to use his strength.
The baby is crying.
I'm nervous.
Why? Let's go.
Let's go.
I'm nervous.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I feel good.
I'm nervous.
What about you, Mako?
Well, I'm going.
You're not going
yet? No, I'm not.
I have to work hard.
You're not going yet?
I'm going.
I'll be patient.
No.
No?
Is it hot? It's hot.
My face is red.
Right? It's hot.
It's hot.
She'll come out soon.
It's really hot.
Welcome.
She's coming from over there.
I want you to come out soon.
Are you going to come out soon?
She is coming out soon.
Deja vu.
Welcome.
It will be 100 years soon.
This is a 100-year-old mango.
What is ah?
What is ah? Ah, it went in.
It went in.
Please stop the video for a while.
I don't have a bath,
but is it okay? It's okay.
I've been bathing.
It's not easy.
J is the first to succeed.
I'm not a little girl.
Chiku-taro looks lonely.
No, I'm not lonely.
I'm not lonely.
OK, I'm going to take off my top.
Good bye.
I'm leaving.
Chiku-taro.
So cute.
I'm leaving.
Look at them.
They are passing by.
They are kind.
It feels good.
She says it feels good.
Do more.
Do more on this side, too.
I'm touching you.
I'm touching you properly.
It feels good.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm going to go.
I went there first.
I'm holding the camera now.
It hurts.
Yay! It hurts.
It's bad.
You are doing weird things
with doing your breath.
You are doing nonsense.
No, keep stop.
What kind of man is
this? It's a baghead.
But, this is not bagged, it's a baghead.
How about yourself?
You are not chained.
Like what?
You are a baghead.
Yes, I am.
My name is Nariman.
Chained.
You are like Chinedeman.
There is a vertical thread
and a horizontal thread.
This is a vertical thread.
People are connected.
Do you want to sing? Stop it.
Do you mean the thread of man?
Yes, the thread of man.
The thread of man.
I'm going to pee.
Well, let's eat.
The thread of man.
Let's eat.
Have a nice day!
I can't stand up.
I don't have time to rest.
You are so cute.
You are doing great.
You are doing great!
Oh, you are drooling.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, you are panting.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a baby crying in front of me, so I'm a
little nervous, but I'll do my best to
make the video fun and enjoyable for you.
I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy
it, so please look forward to it.
Three-man-ko? Three-man-ko.
Then, self-man-ko.
Self-man-ko?
Let's do self-man.
Self-man.
You are good at self-man.
Ecchi.
Stop it.
I can't open my eyes.
I am a little worried about
my daughter's health.
I am worried about her going to a hospital.
Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman,
Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman,
Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman,
Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Selman, Sel I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm going to the bathroom.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you going to go,
Selma? It feels good.
She's going, she's going.
She's going, she's going, she's going.
She's gone.
It feels good.
Do you use toys?
I don't use toys.
Toys? I like toys.
I like toys.
I like position changes.
Do you want me to put it in the middle?
Do you want me to put it
in the middle? In the middle.
I put it in the middle.
What kind of toys do you have?
What kind of toys?
I have a lot of toys.
You have a lot of toys.
I think this one is better.
Which do you like better?
I like this one.
Wait a minute.
Did you put it in? Yes, I did.
It's in my eye.
Does it feel good?
Oh, no.
I think something is wrong.
I think it's crushed.
I'll do it for you.
It's too tight.
It's too tight, so it's crushed.
It's not crushed.
Do you have any
questions? Put it on her.
Which one do you like, Suiko?
Which one do you like more?
Do you need a hand? Kiss her.
Say, I did it!
I did it!
Do you want to be stronger?
I've been stronger since the beginning.
You've been stronger since
the beginning? Be nice to her.
I'm so happy.
She is raising her hand over there.
It's me.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
She is kissing you.
Can I kiss you?
Do you want to kiss me?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a chimpanzee play with a baby.
I was surprised to see a
chimpanzee play with a baby.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a chimpanzee play with a baby.
You are so energetic.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a mother and a baby play together.
I'm glad I was able to see it
for the first time in a long time.
Do you want to
put it in? It's erotic.
It's erotic.
Do you want to put it in?
You are being pushed out.
Does it feel good?
Let's go to bed soon.
Are you going to the beach?
Did you have too much
fun at the beach? Yes, I did.
My dad is lonely.
Chimpo! Chimpo!
Chimpo train!
Chimpo train was late.
Chimpo!
Chien!
How is Chimpo?
How are you feeling?
I was left-handed,
so I was a little sloppy.
Wow!
I didn't think you were left-handed.
It's the same, isn't it?
I'm left-handed.
Let's go with Chiku.
Chiku!
I might be Chiku-kawa.
Chiku-kawa?
What if I'm not Chiku-kawa?
What if I'm not
Chiku-kawa? Here we go.
One, two.
Chiku-kawa.
A little.
A little? A little brown.
A little Chiku-kawa.
It's a beautiful circle.
Chiku-kawa.
Chiku-kawa is blue.
She is very surprised.
Look at this.
What?
This is Nakayoshi.
Look at him while he is attacking you.
Chikubai.
Chikusubai.
Oh, no.
He is getting fat.
How is your physical condition?
Your hands are getting bigger.
My hands are getting bigger?
I'm doing push-ups with my chest.
Your hands are getting bigger.
It's getting bigger.
Really? Look.
It's true.
Look.
It hurts.
It's getting bigger.
I can't do it from this side.
It's here.
Really? It's here.
It's in my pocket.
Pocket-chan is in the video.
Pocket-chan!
She said Pocket-chan
It's a new series.
Pocket-chan!
What's wrong?
Let me take a look at your neck.
I'll give you a treatment.
He is sleeping.
He is funny.
Oh, no!
He is getting bigger.
Is he? I don't know.
He is hard.
Hard? He is hard.
He is playing.
I'm curious about the future.
I want to see it.
Do you want to see it?
Don't you want to see it yet?
Mr. Ozashi?
What?
How is it?
It smells like sweat.
Really?
You can't see it from now on.
I can see it.
Don't peep into other people's house.
Thief! Thief!
How are you? I'm fine.
Tama, how are you?
So soft! So soft.
Feels good.
I want to touch you.
Wow, it's so beautiful!
It's so beautiful!
It looks like a house.
It's a chimney.
It's red.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Is this your original
hair? Yes, it is.
I see.
Can I touch your
cheek? Yes, you can.
Touch her nipples.
This is not good.
I'm nervous.
It's going to break.
It's so beautiful.
Tama is amazing.
Tama baby.
I'm watching you.
Amazing.
It's so soft.
It feels good.
It's like playing with a ball.
It's so soft and feels good.
The ball feels so good.
Play with it properly.
Show me what you are good at.
I'm not good at it yet.
Not yet?
Not yet? You are strict.
I need to improve myself.
I'm going to eat it.
Let's eat it.
It's hard.
Really? It's delicious.
It's pasta.
Itadakimasu.
Can I eat it?
Itadakimasu
Ah!
It fell
Itadakimasu It's good
It's good?
It's good
Pink
Pink It's your turn to
stand out It's Pink's turn
Pink is the most conspicuous color.
This is pink.
Double Shun.
It's not triple.
Now it's pink's turn.
Pink.
The sound of pink is a little.
Erika-chan will be a double feather, and
the three of us will be a triple feather.
I'm sweating.
I'm sorry.
It's prepared.
This side.
What are you
pinching? I lick it, too.
It's delicious.
Is it good?
Then, I'll put it on your nipple.
Your nipple.
Do you want to taste it? Sorry.
Do you want to taste it?
Yes.
It's good that you two lick it.
It's good.
It's sweet.
I'll lick your tongue.
It feels good, right?
I want to lick your mouth, too.
Let's do it together.
What should I do?
Where are you going?
Does it feel good?
Wait a minute.
It's easy to lick.
This is easy to lick.
Does it feel good? It's soft.
I can't get in.
It's delicious.
How about this?
I'll taste it first.
It's scary.
It's a good day.
It's a bad day.
It's a very good day.
It's great.
It feels good.
Shall we put it in?
Yes, let's put it in.
Let's put it in.
Let's put it in from the J.
I want to pee.
Pee? I want to pee.
Can I put it in first?
Why?
Are you sure? I'm going to do it.
I'm watching you.
Oh, no.
Let's go over there.
Why?
I'm watching you.
I'm going to do it.
Oh, no.
I did it.
Don't make me laugh.
You did it.
I was patient.
You were patient,
weren't you? Yes, I was.
What did you say? I was patient.
You'll see it soon.
You're holding it.
I'll show you.
You'll see it soon.
You're holding it.
Pretty face.
It's almost over.
Wait.
You'll see it soon.
I hate it because everyone is watching.
Everyone says they love it.
Maybe they are a little.
They say it won't come out.
Won't it?
But everyone said it a lot.
But I'm going to wipe it.
It's the same when you wipe it.
It's the same when you put it out.
If you don't come
back, it's going to start.
I'm going to put it on.
Here you go.
What kind of penis
is it? Baki-baki.
Baki-baki? Baki-baki.
Baki-chin.
Baki-chin is great.
Great, great.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Does it feel good? Great.
There's a lot in there.
Great.
I feel so good.
Can you do something for me?
Can you do something
for me? I feel so good.
I feel so good.
If you can't move, you can move.
I can't move my hands.
Please sit down.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
Oh my god! It's so erotic.
It feels so good.
It's really erotic.
I'm so happy.
You are happy, aren't you?
I'm going to go.
Are you going to go?
Wow!
Really, Mara?
Mara, are you OK?
I want to put it in quickly.
Do you want to put it in quickly?
Decide in the next turn.
Do you want to put it in
the next turn? I'm wearing it.
Which one do you want to wear?
I'm going to wear it.
OK.
Oh, it feels good.
Which one do you want to put in?
I want to put it in.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
If you lick the one that
feels good, you put it in?
If you make the nipple
feel good, you put it in first?
Rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
You are so violent.
Do I smell violently?
You are so violent when you smell.
I feel so good.
I'm going to go.
She is so violent.
I feel so good.
I can't choose.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors, go!
I'll play rock-paper-scissors with Elio.
What should we play?
Let's play Iimara.
Iimara? What should
we play? Iimara.
Do you like back?
Do you like back? Yes, I do.
Let me see your butt.
Let's wait.
Here you are.
We are waiting.
I have to look for it.
This is a good Mara.
It's a good Mara, isn't it?
Mara is the best.
Mara is cute.
She is cute and soft.
She is so cute.
I can't say weird things.
I can't say weird things
because I'm so cute.
She is a good Mara.
Don't move!
You are moving too fast!
You are moving too fast.
Don't move!
Let's do normal back!
Let's do normal back.
If you can see, I can't.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you happy?
You look like you feel good.
Ahhhh!
She's going to pop it up.
Ha ha ha ha!
I'm gonna help you.
No, no, no!
No, no, no! I'll help you.
Ha ha ha ha!
No, no, no!
They are playing with each other.
Let's face the mirror.
Oh, you're right.
What?
What are you doing?
Oh, it's Eno-chan!
It's Eno-chan!
Do you want to show your armpit?
Show me your armpit.
You're sweating a lot.
Oki-check! Oki-check!
It's so beautiful!
I'm beautiful, too.
Too beautiful?
You're so beautiful.
You're drawing a super-bending.
Too beautiful!
Too beautiful! I'm gonna go.
No! No! I love Oki.
I love Oki.
Cute!
Cute! I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'm going to sleep.
You are going to sleep?
It's nice to fall asleep.
I'm going to sleep.
It's nice.
Wow! Great! I can see it.
Great!
She is touching me.
She is asking me to touch her.
Oh, it feels good!
Go away! It's you.
Because Chien-Po is
concentrating on Man-Po.
5th?
What?
What should I say?
Man-Guri?
Why do you say that?
Can I have a tissue?
I'll check the tissue.
Tissue check.
I wiped it.
It's OK.
It's good.
Sleep here.
Sleep?
I'll do my best.
From behind.
She wants to do it herself.
I'm going.
Slowly.
Give it to me.
I don't want it.
Look, look, look.
Look, look.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
It's in your nose.
It's a good smell, isn't it?
It's a good smell.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Wow, I can see your butt.
Don't look at my butt.
Put it in slowly.
Put it in, put it in.
Oh, no.
It's in there.
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
Can you see it? I can't see it.
I can't see it.
Are you embarrassed?
I can see it.
Can you see it?
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
It's getting better.
She is a bit shy.
She likes butt.
Let's put her on the top.
She is on the top.
Oh, no.
She is itchy.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
She is too itchy.
You feel good, don't you?
You are getting bigger.
Let's go, let's go.
You too, Nocchi.
You feel good, don't
you? You are scary.
Eri-chan, do you want to go?
Eri-chan wants to go.
I feel good.
My butt is soft.
I'll show you my favorite toilet.
I like it.
My favorite toilet.
I'll pee.
He's already here.
He's here! Let's see him.
Here he is!
Hello!
He's finally here.
Hi!
Welcome!
He's in the paddock.
Hi!
What are you doing? Look at me.
You don't like it,
do you? Look at me.
You are touching my butt again.
You are touching my butt.
I'm sorry for the noise.
I was in a hurry to go to the bathroom.
Sorry.
We'll go back to the bed.
Be careful not to fall off.
Please come back to the bed.
Does he look like us?
They do look like us.
Then, let's go back to the bed.
Hey, Genki.
He is a good perch.
This is Ichin.
She is so cute.
Wow!
This is Marimiyamani.
Wow! She is so cute.
She is so cute.
This part is so cute.
She has a heart.
She is looking at me.
You can't keep your fingers!
You are flitting, right?
You are being mean!
Do your best!
No, you are too much!
No way!
I can't keep my fingers!
Urkan is playing.
You can't do it.
Don't look at the camera.
Rangyu, look at me.
It's impossible Do you?
I want to see your reaction.
It's too sour.
It's impossible.
I say, oh!
You feel good, right?
Do you feel good?
You feel good?
You are sleepy, right?
Show me your armpit.
Take a photo of me.
It is beautiful.
It is beautiful?
You feel good, right?
You feel good?
You feel good? Don't touch me.
I will do it again.
Oh no.
He is very aggressive.
He is in the baby's belly.
Does it feel good? He will die.
Komaru is in a bad mood.
Does it feel good?
Let's go back home.
He will die.
How was it, Komaru chan?
It was a good progress.
It was the best.
It was cute.
I'm here.
I'll take a break.
Are you going to take a break?
Are you going to die? It's hot.
I'll take a break.
It's so gross.
Isn't it terrible? Look at this.
Look through the mirror.
It's so gross.
Let's post it on Twitter.
No, I don't.
Yucchi!
Why are you on my back?
Why?
You are a good girl.
Yucchi!
Yucchi! She is leaving.
She is leaving.
I'm so glad!
She is leaving soon.
Let's touch her nipples.
I can't move.
I'm sleepy.
Let's do our best.
Her nipples are very straight.
They are very straight.
Are they straight?
I'm going to move.
Everybody, look at each other's face.
Look at the face of Elion.
Look at this side too.
Cute, isn't it?
It's like a pet.
What kind of cat are you?
You're Chiku Kawaii.
Blue and pink.
Only two of them.
I'm so sorry.
Do you want to be petted?
Do you want to
be petted? It hurts.
Stop it.
She left.
She is so cute.
Shin-chan is not allowed to touch the butt.
Touch his body by touching his buttocks.
A butt.
Touch his butt and check his
face by touching his buttocks.
Touch his breasts and check his face.
Oh, he was touched.
Say ah.
Oh, my, why? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel? I feel good.
You are cute.
I feel good.
I have to thank Kanji.
Thank you, Kanji.
Kanji, aren't you resting too much?
Kanji, hurry up.
Kanji, put it on.
Kanji, let's do our best.
Kanji, aren't you resting too much?
Kanji, let's put it on.
Oh, it doesn't fit.
Kanji, Kanji.
Does it fit?
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Touch it.
It feels good,
doesn't it? Touch it.
It feels good, doesn't
it? It feels good.
It feels good.
I'm so excited.
I want to see it.
Do you want to see it?
Can you see it from
here? I can see it.
Wow! It's so cute.
It's so cute.
Here you are.
I love you, Sei-chan.
I love you, Ichi.
Ero.
More.
You feel good, don't you?
You are the best!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Look at Kanji's face.
What are you going to do?
She started with a straight face
and ended with a straight face.
Wow, it's gone.
It's gone.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't
it? It feels good.
it? I feel so good.
I feel so good.
Oh, there is a pony.
Oh, no!
Stop it!
Don't stop it!
Don't stop it! Don't eat it.
Don't eat it.
It feels good.
It's close.
It feels so good.
Aty, you are sweating.
Am I?
I'm sweating all the time.
You look like you are holding it in.
Can I go now?
What? Where are you going?
Where do you want
me to go? Just like this.
No, no, no.
What do you mean? No way.
I told you.
No way.
Thank you.
You are not the first one.
I'm not the first one.
Go! Go!
Why did you do that?
You are so nervous.
Because I won the championship.
I got it!
Did you really get it?
Are you sure?
Here we go!
Wow! It's out!
Wow!
Are you sure?
It's out!
It's warm!
Did you really get it?
Let me take the responsibility.
J, take the responsibility.
Do you want to taste it?
J, you have to take the responsibility.
Stand in a line.
I'm going to kiss you while licking you.
Look at the camera.
If I touch you a little,
you'll get up right away.
You got up again, didn't you?
Oh, no! Let's lick it.
Kiss!
So cute!
Everyone is kissing.
It's warm.
Can I lick your hair?
Let's lick your chin.
I'll go first.
Here you are.
Did you get permission? Oh, no.
It's getting worse.
I think you can put it in your mouth.
Can you put it in your mouth?
Yes.
I'll put it in.
I'm going to put it in the bag.
It's a choice.
I don't want to.
It's not fair.
Did you put it in the bag?
Yes.
You are so cute.
Look at the face.
So cute.
Let me see.
I want to see your face.
I want to see your face through the mirror.
Ero.
Very Ero.
It's time to go to bed.
Let's go to bed.
Why are you so energetic?
There were three of us.
Don't you think it's too early?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel so good.
Don't move.
I'll put you in the room.
No! No, you can't.
If you do that, I'll want to take it out.
No, you can't.
Do you want to take it out?
But I feel good today.
Oh, no.
You can't.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good? Oh, no.
I can't stand it.
You can do it.
Wait a minute.
You did it.
Did you feel good? Yes, I did.
She wants you to lick her nipples.
She likes her nipples.
I can feel my nipples.
It feels good.
It's so hard.
Is it hard? It's so hard.
I'm sorry.
What's your favorite?
My favorite is.
..
I like bag.
Bag? I like bag.
Show me your bag.
Let me see.
Kawamanko.
Come here.
You are so cute, Maruko.
You are the most naughty one.
You are so naughty.
Are you shy?
You are running away from me.
No, you are not.
Yes, you are.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Does it feel good?
Your legs are moving.
I'm going to give you a massage.
You are moving a lot.
Close your legs.
I can't stand it anymore.
You are going too far.
It's so good.
You want to have sex with youkai?
I don't have enough yopkai and chinchin!
Not enough chinchin!
I want to have sex with youkai!
I don't have enough of chinchin!
You're too powerful.
Not enough chinchin...
Which one will go
first? She gave up.
You're so fast!
Look this way!
Show me where you're going.
Let's go together.
I want you to go.
You want me to go? I'm going.
You want me to go? Sorry.
You want me to go?
I couldn't hear you say.
Is that so?
Is that so? I'm sorry.
Are you angry?
I'm not angry because I feel good.
Are you angry because you feel good?
You're not angry.
Look at me.
I don't feel good.
You guys are noisy.
Are you noisy?
It's your fault.
Why? Look at me.
You are so cute.
You are so beautiful.
You want me to lick you, right?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Open your legs a little.
It's a little deep.
He is writhing and crying.
He is not feeling well.
Riki seems to be nervous.
He looks so smooth.
Marumi-e
Ecchi
Yabai?
Which one is Yabai?
I want you to go I want you to
go I want you to go Let her go.
Let her go.
Go, go, go.
Oh, you lost.
You lost.
Who was it?
It was Ise-chan.
What are you two doing?
One of your hands is dirty.
I'm sleepy.
Are you sleepy?
Are you happy?
I'm going to touch you.
Oh, no!
Are you going again?
I'm going this time.
Oh, no!
Take it out! Take it out!
Can I go?
Take it out!
I'm going!
Yes! I took it out.
I took it out.
Then, let me take it out.
OK.
I'm going to take it out.
It's so soft.
It's coming out.
It's amazing.
We need Jane.
Jane is not good enough.
She needs a boyfriend.
Then, you don't like a boyfriend?
No.
I hate it. I hate it.
Jun.
Why? Why?
I hate it.
My princess.
It's disgusting.
My prince.
What? It's hot.
I sweated a lot.
It's hot.
I want to take a shower.
Hey, what are you
doing? I'm washing.
Put it in.
I'm washing.
Be careful.
You don't have
to wash your face.
You don't have to wash your face.
Do you want me to wash your face with salt?
Let's wash your face with salt.
You don't have to wash your face with salt.
Mom, I'm washing my face.
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right.
You're a fan, so you can't do it.
I can do it.
Let's take off the towel.
I'm hungry.
You're hungry.
I want to go to the bathroom, too!
I'll turn it on.
First, my nipples.
Nipples.
Why?
I'm going to pee.
I'm going to wash my body.
OK, I'll wash my nipples.
I'm going to pee.
She is very active.
She is getting bigger and bigger.
Are you getting taller?
You've grown up.
You've become easier to wash.
I'm the last one.
It's difficult.
It's not good.
My gums.
It's strange.
Oh, my stomach hurts.
I feel nauseous.
It's not good.
My stomach hurts.
It's a bad day.
※This is the first time
to see such a scene.
Oh my god!
※This is the first time
to see such a scene.
Oh my god!
Wow!
The three of us were really excited.
We were so excited.
We were really excited.
There was a lot of sacrifice.
I couldn't move.
Like this? Yes, yes.
I'm going to wash you.
Look at me.
Don't mess around.
I'm going to wash you.
Does it feel good?
The other side.
I'm going to push you.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a mother and her
daughter playing with a
baby, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous
because I've never seen a
mother and her daughter
playing with a baby before.
Everyone should wash the dishes.
You should wash the dishes.
That's right.
It's on Thursday.
Wash the dishes...
You have to wash the dishes.
That's right.
What are you
playing with? A coin.
I want you to do it again.
What?
I want you to do it in a sexy way.
Do you want me to do it in a sexy way?
Yes.
What are you going to do?
Do you want me to lick you?
Are you done?
Yes.
You are fast.
By the way, I think I got
a good pat on the back.
That's true.
I got a good pat on the back.
I want you to get a good pat on the back.
A good pat on the back?
Let's move on to the next one.
I'm going to get a good pat on the back.
I see.
Let me see your hand.
You are amazing.
Oh!
It's getting too tight.
Your hand is getting too tight.
How about this?
Please touch my hand.
Oh!
You are so naughty.
Chikkun, let's go.
Do you feel good? Very good.
Ero.
Very good.
You are so cute.
Your eyes are dirty.
Do you want to be licked?
Do you want to be licked
by Jay? Jay licks you.
Yes.
Don't look at me like that.
You are licking your lips.
You have to put more.
More? More.
Good girl.
I can't put it all.
You can't?
You can say it louder.
Louder? Say it louder.
How is it? It feels good.
It's really hard.
It looks good.
Can I eat it? Let's do it.
It's coming out a lot.
It's scary.
Wow.
It's a lot.
I'm sorry.
I was a little scared.
I'll bear with it.
It's a lot.
It's amazing.
It's hard to do as a child.
It's hard to see.
Yes, it is.
Wow!
You put out a lot.
Yes, I did.
You are a warrior.
Yes, I am.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Yay!