Do you want to force it?
Would you like to try your hand at it?
Can I try my hand at it?
Wow that's amazing.  It fell a lot.
*This is a
derivative work of the Touhou Project.
I am going to sleep.
I can't do it anymore.
Wow, amazing.
He is in a good mood.
He is gone.
He is gone?
It is coming out a lot.
Oh, that is great.
It is like a movie.
It is painful.
I feel good.
It hurts so much.
It feels so good.
Did you feel good? Yes, I did.
Well, then.
Thank you.
Good luck.
That is great.
That is wonderful.
Mr. Kanaka's wife.
She has a very big belly.
I am sorry. Do not be nervous.
Let's take it easy.
Let's go to bed.
My room is hot.
I bit your hair.
Good night.
Thank you.
You are beautiful.
Good night.
What is wrong? Your hands are shaking.
I am nervous.
This is really wonderful.
I hope you like it.
How is it?
It is really wonderful.
Me too.
It is embarrassing.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
You look fine.
It is beautiful.
It is wonderful.
You have a nice boob.
Your nipples are...
I am sensitive.
It is embarrassing.
I don't want to say that.
You are a little girl.
Do not do that.
It is rare.
I really do not like women who are angry.
I am sorry.
I am so hungry.
I am hungry, too.
I am going to sleep now.
I am so tired.
You have to get used to it.
I am used to it.
No, no, no.
It is not a big deal.
Thank you.
You are wearing short pants again.
It is wonderful.
Really?
Are you sure?
I will open it for you.
Thank you very much.
You are welcome.
Do you want me to
open it for you? Yes, please.
How is it? It is wonderful.
I feel it.
I really feel it.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I am sorry.
It is amazing, isn't it?
I feel like I am going to puke.
You are going to feel better.
I am going to puke, but I am going to puke.
Children have a lot of fun as they grow up.
Children are happy to be with their mother.
There is a
way to have fun, but it is not so easy.
Children are not very good at playing
with their mothers.
Do you feel good? I feel good.
..
It is warm!
What is wrong? I got a cold.
It is still warm.
It is nice here,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
I am so happy.
It is wonderful here.
Oh, you are so positive.
I was taught by my mother.
I see.
You are doing well.
It is hard, isn't it? Yes, it is.
This video is a derivative work of the
Tohoku Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
The author of this video
is a former member of
the Tohoku
Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
Are you OK?
You are good at this technique.
I didn't expect you to be so good at it.
How do you feel?
It's hard, isn't it?
I will do it again.
Oh, no!
I will do it, too.
OK.
Let's see what we can do.
Oh, no!
This video is
a new way to get used to the new baby.
But I am still not used to it.
I am still not used to it.
But I am getting used to it.
I love you.
I feel like
my love is deepened when I do this.
I always feel something fresh.
I didn't do this.
You are doing your best.
I can't stand it anymore.
I will change my clothes again.
See you later.
I can't stand it anymore.
It is hard to imagine how much of
a crybaby I was when I was a kid.
I was a bit of a crybaby when I was a kid.
But I was a bit of a
crybaby when I grew up.
I was a bit of a crybaby when I grew up.
It is a shame, but it's
not that I am not a crybaby.
Oh, it feels good.
Wow, it is great.
You can lie down here.
Look, look.
You are enjoying it.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, it feels good.
It is the first time for
you to lie down on my lap.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I am not sure if I can say it.
Do not worry about it.
You look so fat.
I am so happy.
I feel so good.
Are you going to bed early today?
Yes.
What is this? It is a pillow.
A pillow?
Yes.
This feels good.
Really?
Yes.
I want to talk to you.
I got it.
You are always like this.
Your technique is good.
You can do it by yourself.
I got it.
You are the best!
Do you feel good?
Yes, I do!
It is the same as always.
I feel good.
Please hold me tight.
You seem to be in a good mood this year.
I am glad to hear that.
I was very excited and hungry this year.
I am happy.
I prepared a toy for you.
What is it? It is a toy.
A toy?
Have you ever
used it? No, I haven't.
You haven't?
No.
That is a shame.
I haven't.
It's
a rare opportunity, isn't it? Yes, it is.
It is a toy.
Look, there's something like this.
This is the
one you always use, right? Yes, it is.
Can you show me how to use it?
Me? Yes, you first.
It is a little difficult, but...
I put it here...
and put it here...
I wonder if it fits.
Is it OK?
Are you all
right? Yes, I am fine.
Look at this.
It's swollen, isn't it?
It is swollen,
Isn't it? Look at this.
It's swollen, isn't it?
I am glad I found you.
If you haven't done anything yet, you
can do it like this at first.
Do you know how to use a router?
I do not know how to use a router.
Then, I will show you how to use it.
Have you ever used
a router? No, I haven't.
I don't think so.
This is the first time
I have seen such a thing.
It feels good.
The sound is amazing.
The sound is amazing, too.
It feels good.
Wow, it is amazing.
It is a great feeling,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Is it just hitting?
No, it is not just hitting.
Really?
Yes.
Please spread
your legs and put your hands inside.
Oh, you put your hands inside.
How do you feel?
Your hands are shaking.
Yes, they are.
Are you OK? Yes, I am fine.
I am going to put my hands inside.
It is OK because your hands are connected.
Put your hands inside.
Yes, put your hands inside.
I am going to give you a massage.
I am going to massage you.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
I feel a little strange.
It feels good.
You have been doing a lot of massage lately.
Yes.
This is the first time
I have ever seen a baby cry.
I was surprised to see a baby cry.
I am sorry.
What? I am sorry.
Ouch!
I am going to fall.
I am sorry.
It is okay.
You should practice this side.
This side? Okay.
Yoshikawa-san, how do you feel?
I am a little nervous.
You are a little advanced.
I am fine. I can do it slowly.
I feel good.
I am a little scared.
I am used to it.
It is amazing that you can do it so well.
Let's do it.
This video is a derivative work of the
Tohoku Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
Please enjoy it with your eyes only.
I am glad I was able to reconnect with her.
I feel so happy.
I am glad I got along with her.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying like this.
I am going to
take a picture of the baby's face of her.
I am going to take
a picture of the baby's face.
He is playing with me.
It is amazing.
He is doing it.
He is playing to me.
Does it feel good?
Is it good?
He is playing with me.
Is it good? It is amazing.
What?
Do you feel good?
I can play alone.
It is amazing.
This is the first time
I have seen a baby in a baby carrier.
I am so happy.
You look sick.
You look like a mischievous girl.
Wait a minute.
I will give you a hug.
Do you want to go home?
My wife is tired.
I can't do this.
Do you feel good?
You have
never used it, have you? No, I haven't.
Are you not used to it?
I have to get help.
I will do it later.
I will help you while you put it in.
While I put it in?
Yes, while I put it in.
I am going to
do a massage with a special machine.
I am going to massage the back of my neck.
I see.
There are many ways to use it.
You want a real one,
do not you? Yes, I do.
It is too big now.
Let's put it here.
From the top.
It is a big one.
Look this way.
-How do you feel? -Good.
This is the first
time I have ever seen a baby cry like this.
I am so happy.
How do you feel? I feel great.
I feel great, too.
Did you get a good
night's sleep? Yes, I did.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel great.
She is smiling.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying like this.
I am sorry, too.
Thank you.
It feels good.
This is the first time I have ever seen a baby crying in front of me
I feel so good.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I will wipe your back.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I am sorry I am late.
I am so tired.
Are you feeling good?
Do you want to lie down?
I am sorry for this.
So, you feel good? I feel good.
I like it.
I will take off your hand.
Thank you.
The four of us are connected.
Great.
Do not cry, do not cry, do not cry.
Are you comfortable?
Oh, you are getting a lot of excitement.
Let's take a break.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it like this.
Let's do it normally.
You can go to bed now.
This is the first
time I have ever seen a baby cry like this.
I am sorry.
Did you feel it? Yes, I felt it.
I felt it.
Did you feel it? Yes, I did.
It hurts.
Oh, good boy!
OK
Oh, you have already taken off the mask.
Is it OK? Perman.  I can't.
I can't.
Are you feeling better?
I feel much better.
Yeah, like I am in the poop.
Now, can you move
more? Yes, like that.
Like that.
Is it painful?
I feel like going to puke!
Oh, you feel anything?
Yeah, right now… You know,
I can feel like I am going to throw up!
Oh my gosh!
Are you feeling good?
Yes, I am!
Good job, keep going!
I am so glad to meet you.
Did you have
a good time? Yes, I did.
I feel so good.
Are you full? Yes, I am.
Have you slept for
a long time? Yes, I did.
How did you feel? It was good.
You enjoyed
it, right? That is great.
I am glad to hear that.
Let's work together.
I'd like you to listen
to what I have to say.
What do you mean?
I'd like you to show me your clothes.
I see.
Can I? Excuse me.
Can
I take off my clothes? Wait a minute.
What? I am sorry.
Do not worry.
I am not talking about the question.
What? Well.
..
What? Wait a minute.
Don't look at me.
Wait a minute.
What?
What is the matter? Do not worry.
It is about the question.
Do not worry.
Wait a minute.
I am sorry.
Oh, today... I was off today.
Oh, I see.
I am sorry.
You are wearing a cute underwear.
Oh, I see.
Wait a minute.
Can I wear it today?
You can wear it today.
It is nice to have
this much free time, isn't it? Yes, it is.
If you do not mind, please take a look.
How do you like it?
It is beautiful.
Thank you very much.
You do not have to thank me.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
How do you like it?
It is very beautiful.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I have a lot of things to tell you.
Oh, yes.
You do, do not you? Yes, I do.
I never listen to what my husband says.
What? You
do not listen to anything? No, I don't.
Can you show me more? Oh, yes.
What? Oh, yes.
Oh, yes.
Please take a good look at it.
Here you are.
Hey, what are you doing?
It's a little funny, isn't it?
I was a little surprised
because it was too big.
Do not hesitate to show me more.
Excuse me.
Are you serious?
It doesn't smell at all.
Can I take it off? Of course.
Let me see your beautiful breast.
Does it work?
How is it? It is beautiful.
Please look.
Please look at me carefully.
Do you hate this kind
of thing? No, I don't.
Oh, I see.
So, you like it.
Well, I don't know.
You like boobs,
do not you? Yes, I do.
It is not only boobs, is it?
It seems that you are looking down.
Could you show me your important part?
Yes.
It is a bit dangerous.
You are doing what you always do.
I am doing what I always do.
You are beautiful.
Yes, I am.
Actually...
Do you like this kind
of thing? Yes, I do.
Take your time.
Please look at the
beautiful part of my house.
Wow, it is amazing.
It is beautiful as usual.
Is it?
Should I open it more?
Yes, you should.
I want to show you more closely.
Please look at this.
How do you like it?
Please look at it carefully.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Please do not look at it.
I am looking at it.
I like to be looked at.
I was thinking.
You are a little wet.
I am sorry.
I am wet because I am naked in this place.
If other people see you
naked... You, too... I do not like it.
You like it.
Because I like to be embarrassed.
Do you always look like this?
That is what it looks like.
It's
the same as usual, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Do you always enjoy
like this? Yes, I do.
Because you
were holding the microphone just now.
Yes, I did.
What is wrong?
What is going on?
I think it is a little tight.
It is tight.
Excuse me.
What?
What are you
going to do? Oh, I see.
You three are
neighbors, aren't you? Yes, we are.
Oh, I see.
What?
Oh, you don't
like it? No, I don't.
It is OK.
Let's have fun together.
Oh, you don't
like it? No, I don't.
like it? It is okay.
It is okay.
I played with you too much.
I am sorry.
You always do such a thing.
Isn't it good to
do this? It is small.
I am doing my best.
Please look at him.
Oh, it feels good.
I am going to kiss you.
This video is
a derivative work of the Touhou Project.
If you like it, please subscribe
to the channel and give it a high rating.
I have been beaten by many people
next to me, but I have become so hard.
You are fine.
Yes, I am fine.
I didn't know it was so painful.
I do not like this kind of pain.
How do you feel? I am sorry.
It is okay.
I hope you enjoy it.
Are you okay?
It is so intense, isn't it?
I didn't expect it to be so windy.
Really?
Your body is like this.
It is very beautiful.
This video is
a derivative work of the Touhou Project.
I am doing such a thing, and I am being
touched by a person who doesn't have a body.
I hope we can get along with each other.
I am waiting for you.
I am sorry.
Do you want me to take off your panties?
What are you doing?
Isn't this fun?
Are you having
fun? I am so sorry.
But...
I am so sorry.
You can feel more.
I am sorry.
I am sorry for coming back.
Ah...
Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah...
You have a lot of blood clots.
I am going to put a lot of food in the box.
Please lick my mark properly tonight.
I know. I know.
I will lick it a lot.
I do not know
if it is better than mine, but it is burnt.
I know.
Please touch my nipple.
I am so sorry.
Are you OK?
Stand up straight.
I am so sorry.
You are getting better and better.
I am sorry.
You are good.
You are very active.
Let's kiss.
I see.
You are a good boy.
You are a good husband.
Please look this way, too.
I am so nervous.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Well, I am going to lick you.
How do you feel?
Are you licked by your husband?
How do you feel when
you are licked by a dog?
Dog is very naughty.
How do you feel?
I am glad.
Do you want to lick this side?
It is getting warmer and warmer.
It is a little different from when
I was at my husband's house.
How is it compared to your husband's house?
Is it bigger over there?
It is a little slanted over there.
Slanted?
It is a little different.
It's a 500-year-old house, isn't it?
Do you feel good around here?
It is a strange feeling.
It is just right. It feels good.
It is really good.
This is the first time I have
ever seen a cat with such a good technique.
I have never seen a cat with such a
good technique.
It has been a long time.
Really? I am glad to hear that.
It feels good.
I am so excited about this kind of thing.
I agree.
My wife is looking down on a man.
I don't like that.
She looks like she is in a good mood.
I see.
I am jealous.
You look like you are in a good mood, too.
It is so comfortable.
Your wife is so good.
It is so soft.
You look more
comfortable than when I was eating.
Do I?
Both are comfortable.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
It feels so good.
You can do it.
This is your true nature.
But you were licking me so hard just now.
That is because I'm
feeling better and better.
We are the same.
Let's enjoy it.
Hey, how do
you feel? I feel good.
You smell so good.
Your tongue is wet.
I know, I know.
You smell so good.
You are shaking.
You look so good.
You and my husband, too.
He is talking with all his might.
Yes, he is.
He is trying to imitate a very erotic way.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What is this?
Are you okay? Yes, I am okay.
I am sorry.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25, 26,27,28,29,30,31,32,33
It is a hot spring.
But it is very delicious.
I am getting jealous.
It is delicious.
I am jealous of the person next to you.
But you feel good, too.
I understand. I will do my best.
Is it weak here?
It is a little sensitive.
Oh, it is sensitive.
I see.
It is refreshing to be
kissed and waved hands.
But it is a little harder than before.
It feels good. It is a fresh feeling.
Can you do that much for my wife?
I hope you do not do that.
Oh, my God.
You can do whatever you want.
I love this kind of thing.
You are very sensitive.
Do you like to eat? It is fresh.
It is fresh, isn't it?
Can you feed me?
I will feed you a lot.
It is the first
time I have ever seen such a finger nail.
It is hard, isn't it? It is scary.
It is not scary at all.
I am going to give you a massage.
I am going to massage your back.
How was it? I like it.
Really?
Yes.
Was it good?
I feel good.
I am going to give you a head massage.
Do not do seizures!
Do not do seizures on your back!
DON'T DO SEIZURES ON YOUR BACK!
I am going to bring you to my home.
It feels so good.
It is like I am in a hospital.
I feel like we've become
really close today.
Yes, we have.
But I wish we could be closer.
Yes, let's do more of what we usually do.
More? Yes, more.
I don't know.
Let's use that.
Yes, let's use it.
You are all wet.
I am sorry.
Are you okay?
This video is a derivative work of the
Tohoku Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
Please use the translation function
of YouTube as a reference.
It is a very strong reaction, isn't it?
Well, I feel good just to do this.
I feel like something is buzzing.
It is getting more and more overflowing.
It is embarrassing.
What are you doing?
It is buzzing from there.
Don't shake me.
She is moving a lot.
Are you OK?
She looks comfortable.
Her hips are shaking.
Are you OK?
Mother's movements are very
different from the previous video.
The movement
of the neck is different from the previous
The video, and the movements
of the chest and head of her are different.
It is not as
if the movement of the neck is the same
as the video, but it's
different from the video.
It is difficult to understand the reason
for this difference.
Yes, that is right.
Is it okay to do the acupressure here?
You wanted it so much, didn't you?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Please look at where
you are breathing and moving your body.
Please move your body.
How is it?
What is this?
Are you crying?
We are going to use a special machine,
and I am going
to give you a massage with my hand.
You can just do whatever you want.
I do not like this kind of massage...
I am sorry.
Are you okay?
I am going to go.
Okay. You can go as much as you want.
Your nipples are so dirty.
Did you go?
This is the first time I have ever
seen a baby crying like this in my life.
I am sure it is a lot different from
when I was in the neighborhood.
Are you okay? Let's do it.
Good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's painful, isn't it?
I am sorry.
It is okay.
I want to go there.
I can't do it anymore.
It is okay.
I don't want to do it.
I can't sleep anymore.
Are you OK?
I can't do it anymore. I am going to faint.
I do not feel like I can do it by myself.
Let's put it in.
I put it in.
It feels good,
doesn't it? I see.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Does it? I envy you all.
You always want to put something in
your mouth, do not you? I will put it in.
I will put it in.
I am glad.
Did you put it in?
I couldn't stand it.
Let me know how you feel later.
Thank you.
It is really tight.
Is it hard to deal with?
Are you okay?
Are you OK?
Let's show it to your husband.
You look so comfortable.
I am not comfortable at all.
Do you feel it? Yes, I do.
My wife is so.
..
What?
I know, right?
Your husband is pretty amazing, too.
That is not true.
I am not that cute.
No, no, no.
I put it in there.
It's tight, isn't it?
It is really tight.
It is tight.
I want you to show me your face again.
Can you show me your back?
You have a beautiful body.
Are you OK?
You are very strong.
You are strong.
Are you OK?
[Crying] I am sorry.
I am sorry.
I will not do it again.
It's terrible, isn't it?
She is gone again.
I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
This is the first time I have ever seen
such a thing.
Can you hold it in your arms?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I am going to die.
Turn your back to me.
I want you
to show me your beautiful buttocks.
Oh, it's good.
Is it around here?
Yes, it is around here.
Oh, it's good.
You can move your hips as much as you like.
Can I move?
Yes, you can move more and more.
Are you OK? Yes, I am.
Let me give you a hug.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Let me give you a hug, too.
It is heavy.
I can't do it.
You can't?
I want to take it off.
You can take it off.
Oh, it's heavy.
I can't do it.
It feels so good.
How do you feel?
I can't move it.
You are like a child.
It feels so good.
This video is
a derivative work of the Touhou Project.
If you like it, please subscribe
to the channel and give it a high rating.
It feels good to touch
my mom's body to her mouth of the earth.
It feels good.
It feels good when you touch me.
You have been touching me for a while.
I am sorry.
You do not have to be patient.
It is gone.
I feel like I am being attacked by a demon.
It was dangerous.
I thought you could do a little more.
No way!
You were so strong.
I was able to finish it in a second.
No way!
It was a different way to finish.
I felt like I could finish it in the back.
No way!
Is that so? I feel strange.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
I feel good when I look at you.
I have never seen you like that before.
I am showing you
a face that my wife has never seen before.
It has been a long time since I have had
a young baby, and I am so jealous of you.
I like young babies.
I know.
I am so jealous of you.
I am getting older.
I want you to be with me all the time.
That is what you want, isn't it?
Yes.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It is about time.
I feel like I want you.
I am sorry. I can't do this alone.
Is that so? That is great.
You know, I like to
be patted by other people.
Is that so?
Yes.
My mom is crazy.
I knew it.
I am sorry.
How do you feel? I feel better.
Really?
I can't lose to you.
I want to get along with you more.
Let's get along.
I am sure you will feel good.
You have seen my wife, haven't you?
Let's get along.
I feel like I am going to throw up.
I am going to throw up.
That is a lot.
You were in trouble.
No, I wasn't.
It felt so good.
Did it?
I am so happy to have a girlfriend like you.
Tonight, right?
Yes.
Will you do it again?
I might do it again.
That is great.
Then, let's go home.
Let's go.
Are you okay? Yes, I am fine.
I am looking forward to seeing you.
Mr. Yamaguchi.
Mr. Junagana.
Mr. Tanaka.
You have only been married
for a year, haven't you? That is right.
It has been a year.
I am looking forward to seeing you.
I am embarrassed.
I have never done this before.
Sui-kun.
Yes?
You took it off.
Eh?
I took it off, too.
Then, let's have fun.
Let's have fun.
Wow.
I am going to take a bath.
Hey, lady.
I am sorry. I do not need any electricity.
I am sorry.
It is over there.
Oh, I see.
I am going to look at your skin.
Oh, go ahead.
Please look at my skin.
Look.
It is hard.
It is harder than I thought.
Your wife is so cute.
I am sorry.
Oh, my God!
She is That is so cute!
That is great!
Even the fingers of her feet are cute.
Oh, my God!
What is that?
I can't stop moving.
Are you heavy? It is great.
Good boy.
You are a good boy.
You are beautiful.
You have a lot of muscles.
Let's eat.
My wife is getting bigger and bigger.
How about your wife?
She is getting bigger and bigger.
My body is getting bigger and bigger.
This is the first
time I have ever seen a baby cry like this.
The baby is crying.
Fubuki, 26, is the oldest in the world.
Fubuki's father
is the Go-chan of the Go-chan family.
He is the father of
Fubuki, who is the second oldest in Japan.
Fubuki is the first child to have a child.
Fubuki's father, Go-chan, is
a manager of the Go-chan family.
Look!
That is amazing!
I want to eat it, too.
It is good,
isn't it? It is delicious.
I am going to show you how to make a toy.
I have a toy at home.
I have two toys.
This is a great toy.
Do you know this?
I have seen it before.
I have seen it in a video.
I am going to sleep.
When?
Yes.
The baby is crying.
Does it feel good?
You can cry once.
How do you feel? It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
The baby is crying.
I am glad.
I can't do it anymore.
I will do it more.
Please do it more.
I have done it once.
I want to do it more and more.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying like this.
The baby's crying is so cute.
I am sorry.
Did you have fun?
I had a lot of fun.
I will give you your wife back.
Your waist is cracked.
It is more exciting than stretching.
This is good.
It is getting harder.
This is the first time I have ever seen a
cat like this, and I am very happy to see it.
I am glad I was able to film this video.
I feel good.
Do you want to change
the bed? I feel good.
the bed? Hey, Suzuki.
This is my wife, Fella.
I feel good.
Your wife is good at cooking.
Thank you.
I am going to do my best to wash it.
We have a guest.
He was a dog born in 1964.
It has been a long time since we've
talked about dogs to each other.
He is a dog that
has been living in our home for a while.
He has been a pet for more than 10 years.
I am going to give you a massage today.
Look. It is the one in the dustbin.
You can throw it to the trash bin.
I hope the balloon will not fly away.
It is a waste of time.
You can't do anything.
It is broken.
President, please.
I can't get the answer.
Here you are.
Thank you.
This is a video taken in the morning
of the day I gave birth to my second child.
I am going to show you a video of the
day I gave birth to my second child.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I am sleepy more than usual.
What is wrong?
You only talk to me.
Do you want to go back again?
I feel like I am in a dream.
I can't help talking about the game.
It must be fun.
I have never had such a good time.
This world is a good place, isn't it?
I am going to get addicted to this game.
How is it, ladies?
Is it OK if I just touch your mouth?
Where else do you want me to touch?
This is the first time I
have ever seen such a cute baby in my life.
I am so happy to see him.
Look, look.
Wow!
It is a surprise.
Oh, my.
I am glad to see you.
Ah! Ah! I am sorry.
I am sorry to make you feel bad.
I am sorry.
Ah!
Ah! I am so sorry.
I am so sorry.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying like this.
I am going to give him an IV drip.
Oh, my stomach.
I am going to puke.
Hey, wait a minute.
I am so full.
Sue-kun, I put a lot of it in my stomach.
Oh, I see.
It is okay.
What? Let me out now.
Are you sure?
Yes.
President, are
you sure? Yes, I am.
Sue-kun, did you let
me out? Yes, I did.
I felt great.
How do you feel?
It was the best, boss.
Thank you, wife.