Hifully Transparent
Planes, Earth, Sea of
I'm Akari Mitani.
What I'm good at is...
...feeling good.
Let me squeeze a lot of your raw
chinpo with these 70,000 pieces.
I'm Mina Kitano.
What I like is...
...the eyes of a whole
body that amateurs can't do.
I'm Riho Hashimori, and my
favorite thing is that I continue to
be in the top three without
stopping even though I'm told to stop.
I'm not going to stop today.
I'm Ichika Matsumoto.
Ichi-chan's favorite body parts
are my back and upper body.
I want to do a lot of upper body.
I'm Arisu Nanase.
Do you like Chikubi and Anna-ryo?
Do you like it?
Even if you don't like it,
let me do a lot of mischief.
I'm Misono Maka.
I want you to kiss me all the
way to the back of this manko.
I'm Yayoi Mizuki.
I want to lick you until your
wrinkles become smooth.
Good bye.
I'm Rima Kudai.
My favorite play is to get
a lot of kisses and a kiss.
I'll never let go of your kiss mark.
I'm Simire Kuramoto.
My specialty is licking your
penis with my messy mouth.
Of course, I will make you
feel good with my messy manko.
This is my daily song.
Hi, I'm Ayaka.
You know, saliva is a drink.
Let me get drunk with your saliva.
Who is good?
Me?
This time, we are going to show
you the behind-the-scenes video
of our new album, which will
be released on the 1st of July.
Please look forward to it!
Hello!
It's been a while! I did it.
No, you didn't.
I want to have a nipple.
Which one do you like?
Of course, Ichiko.
Look at me.
Don't look at my nipple.
It doesn't feel good.
Don't fail.
Show me.
One.
Which one is it? Let me see.
I haven't licked it yet.
I don't think I've licked it yet.
I don't think so.
It's already crispy.
It's not that it's already crispy.
What do you mean?
I'm sure you got a little drunk.
Wow!
I feel like I'm running out of breath.
You're holding it in.
You're putting on a face.
Cute.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to put it out.
It's gone when you ate it.
I love you.
I'm number one.
Wait a minute.
You want to put it in a
real manko, don't you?
I promised to put it in a real manko.
You don't do that, do
you? Wait a minute.
I promised.
Please give it to Koha.
I don't do that.
I don't do that, either.
Give it to me.
I want to eat it, too.
Wait! When did you
put it in? I'll put it in.
Do you want to put it in
this smooth bean paste?
It's my bean paste.
Do you remember?
Do you remember everyone's mangos?
This is the 10th person.
That's right.
All of us put mangos in it.
Yarin-chan.
I'm jealous.
You wanted to eat all of
them, didn't you? That's right.
I'm jealous.
You are a happy man.
We've warmed up our bodies.
We're all in the same color, right?
Who liked the
doggy? I'll heal you.
You're tired, aren't you?
I want to be healed, too.
It's a great ending.
We're at the limit, aren't we?
We're at the limit.
It's OK.
Wow, wow, wow.
Is it coming out? Yes, it is.
It's coming out a lot, isn't it?
It's coming out a lot.
I'm so lucky.
I want to take a picture with you.
Who did you like the most?
The future was good.
I want to go to the past.
I saw the panties.
I saw it.
I just saw it.
It was a purchase.
I told you.
I heard it from Rima.
Did you hear it?
Everyone is happy.
Raise your hand if you like panties.
Raise your hand.
I saw it.
I saw the panties.
I have a lot of money.
What are you talking about?
What were you guys doing just now?
I'm asking you what you were doing.
Nothing.
I was thinking of selling my underwear.
You haven't sold it yet.
Did you buy it? No, I didn't.
You're such a liar.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're a girl, but you're
wearing panties and you're lying.
You're a coward.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm not lying.
I don't need your excuses.
Do you know how to
make money? No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of work to do.
Women... What?
What? What? What? Women.
..
...earn a lot of money.
A lot of money?
80's women earn a lot of money.
What? I've never heard of it.
I'll teach you the movement of Kijoi.
Come here.
Yes!
I'm looking forward to it.
Kijoi?
I'll show you Kijoi in Tokyo.
Thank you.
Take off your clothes.
Take off your coat.
It's summer.
That's all you need.
You graduated from a
boring life, didn't you?
Yes.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
No, I'm not a virgin.
Most men have weak nipples. Remember that.
Yes!
Do you know who was
born in the 1980s? No, I don't.
It's that Samoari!
What?
So, men in the 80s are usually short-nosed.
Are you serious? I'll show you.
I'll show you.
Can you see it? No, I can't.
I can't see it.
Senpai.
It feels good.
It's coming out.
Is it coming out?
Is it coming
out? I can't see it.
I want to see it.
Show me.
It's true.
It's really coming out.
You have a good voice.
You can be a man.
Your face is red. Are you okay?
You can do it, right?
I'll do my best.
Glasses are important,
right? Yes, they are.
What are you doing?
Wow!
Wow! I feel so good.
You look so good.
I was so nervous.
Are you serious?
Serious?
I haven't done it yet.
What?
What? Is this it?
You still have 20 minutes to sleep.
What?
Get ready, Kanae.
Yes.
Wow!
What? It's too early.
It's too early.
This is.
..
not included.
What?
Senpai, it's not included.
It's not allowed, right?
They are definitely pretending.
Let's watch it together.
Are you sure? Let's watch it.
Excuse me.
Is this a human skill?
My butt is shaking.
Are you serious?
This is the technique I learned today.
Wow!
You guys should try it too.
Can you do it?
You can do it as if I taught you.
Can you do it? I'll show you.
Well, well, well.
I've known you for a long time.
I don't know how to do it.
Please.
Wait.
First of all, sex starts with a
kiss, doesn't it? But senpai.
..
No, but senpai... Until
you show me your face.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm going to look at you a lot.
I'm going to look at
your happy faces a lot.
Senpai, what should I do if I kiss
you and my mouth is full of saliva?
I'll give it to you.
What?
I'll give it to you and make you drink it.
Give it to me? No way.
Should I put it in my mouth?
I want to see it.
It's like water.
I drank it.
Thank you very much.
You look happy.
What?
Isn't it fun to kiss
with everyone? I see.
I see.
Wow, you have a very kind face.
Wow, you are sitting very comfortably.
You like to be touched,
don't you? It's true.
I can't stand it.
My body is shaking.
Next is Sera.
All of us?
It's better if all of us do it.
Wow!
Look at her pitiful face!
It's just like she was born.
You can try harder.
Harder?
It feels good, doesn't
it? It feels good.
Wow!
If you make such a voice,
your throat will be dry again.
Open your mouth.
You still have a long way to go.
Come here.
You want more, don't you?
You want to put up with more, don't you?
Show me your face.
Can I? Like this.
Wow!
It's coming out.
What?
No, no, no.
She said no.
She said you should put up with it.
Hang in there! Hang in there!
You did it!
Come on!
Ready!
Go!
Who's going first?
Who's motivated?
I don't have it.
Yes, you do.
Then, I'll go first.
Are you sure?
It's easy to see.
I'll put it on my back.
Yes.
It's good.
Ms. Uwakori,
Do you have a rubber band?
I don't have anything.
What?
I'm sure I have a rubber band.
And I'm not a girl today.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
This is the first time I've ever done this.
You haven't put it in yet?
I'm going to put it in.
I'm making a voice.
You can't make a real voice.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Really?
Does it feel good?
How does it feel?
What's wrong? It's too hot.
Too hot?
Too hot? It's too tight.
It's too tight?
Is there a place like
that? Yes, there is.
Where? There.
Do you know where
it is? It's amazing.
I'll lick you.
Yes.
Can I kiss you?
Do you want me to kiss you?
Yes.
I'm so happy that I'm so
tiny in my mother's womb.
Touch me.
I wanted to do this.
This is Akari's.
Oh, it's this one.
It's cute.
Wow.
It looks a little dangerous.
Wait a minute.
It's too early to use it yet.
Next.
Yes.
Wow.
It's amazing.
You like sundae,
don't you? Next.
Then, I'll put it on.
Let's go!
I want to touch it.
Did you feel it? Of course.
Wow! It was amazing.
Really?
Yes.
It moved quickly.
Thank you.
Wow, it's wet.
I know it's cold, but are you all right?
It feels so good.
Hey, you guys.
You can't see Hameshiro
if you put your panties here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's right.
We're going to show Hameshiro.
Like this? Oh, no.
I'm so scared.
Let's lick our nipples together.
I can't believe that
Akari-senpai noticed this so soon.
I'm scared.
She's making a lot of noise.
I want to make a noise.
Akari-senpai is so cute.
I might cry.
What do you mean? I'm scared.
I can't do it anymore.
You should attack more.
Go, go, go.
Alice, you shouldn't do that.
You should let a man
do it first, then a woman.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
First, let the man go, then the woman.
I'm sorry.
You have a weak neck.
Show him how to do it.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to go next?
Yes.
Then, I'll go next.
Is this okay? That's great.
I'll go this way.
I want more.
Senpai is asking you.
I want to touch you so much.
I love you so much.
Wow!
That angle!
What do you mean? Look.
It's amazing.
It's great.
Ah, glasses.
Ah, wait.
I'm going to die.
You're going to die.
You have a cold.
It's after you become a man.
Yes, senpai.
I understand.
I'm going to cry!
Can I touch your
boobs? Yes, you can.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Can you feel the softness
of my boobs? Yes, I can.
Can I touch your
boobs? Yes, you can.
Here we go.
OK.
Wow!
How do you feel?
At first, it was narrow and warm.
It was narrow.
Am I narrow?
Yes.
Hang in there.
It was very hard.
Wow! Wait a minute.
Is it really scary?
I'm going to fall out.
What?
Wait a minute.
Are you going to fall out?
Is it OK?
Is it really OK?
I'm going to fall out.
Wait.
I want to see it.
Oh, it's coming out.
It's glasses.
You can't stand it, can you?
It's coming out.
This is the crow. It's warm.
It's amazing.
Wow!
Thank you, Senpai!
This is the end!
Wow! It feels good.
Did you feel good? I felt good.
I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
Not yet.
I'm not sure.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure it's not enough.
It's not enough.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
It's ticklish.
Senpai, you are better than me.
Wow, amazing.
Senpai, you are getting used to it.
Yes.
It feels good.
Wow, amazing.
I'm sorry.
Here you are.
It's so scattered.
This is it.
Wow!
It's dangerous if you see it.
Dangerous?
Does that mean we're not used to it?
Is it the best in the world?
It's the best!
It's the best in the world.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy.
It's like a baby's booger.
It looks like a baby's booger.
I'm so scared.
I'm sorry.
I'll have a bath.
Oh, no.
I'm going to have a bath.
It's the second bath.
Great.
Oh.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's better to take off your pants
than to take off your underwear, isn't it?
Yes!
It's better to take off your pants
than to take off your underwear.
MISOWA, a phantom
thief Let's start.
Don't do that!
Don't do that! Hey, move away.
Move!
Then, I'll let you out.
Thank you.
Let me out, too.
I'll let you all out.
I want to be in the center.
Do you want to be in the center?
I spilled it.
So, you are the center, right?
Shut up!
What about me?
Solo?
No way!
You want to be solo?
OK, I'll let you be solo.
You are a great producer.
It's great that you give me a job.
You are the man among men.
You are right.
I want to be on a TV show.
I want to be on a variety of TV shows.
Like a singing show.
I'm good at singing.
Me, too.
I can dance.
Dance?
I can dance, too.
I'm the best.
What? I'm the best.
No, it's not.
How do you like
it? I like it, too.
How do you like it?
Do you want me to wear it?
Who smells the
best? It's too hot.
Who do you like the most?
I like Oppai, too.
Ms.Kawashina.
Ms.Kozachi, right? Me, too.
Who do you like the most?
Please make a program called Oppai Heaven.
Me! I'm the MC.
I came up with it.
Let's play games together.
Really?
Do you want me to do it?
Do you want to
see it? It's true.
It's great.
I'll do it for you.
But I don't like it.
Hey, stop it.
It's a game, so we have to be fair.
Hey, it's a game.
Well, let's go, producer.
Let's go.
One, two.
If you want to play baseball,
I agree to this kind of game.
Out!
Sale!
Yoyoi no Yoi!
Don't take off your clothes.
What do you want to see, Hoshida-san?
I want to see your boobs.
You are so honest.
Are you talking about this?
Then, I will show you my boobs.
Your boobs? This way.
I'm going to take it off.
It's a big pudding.
And this underwear is a
present for the producer.
But there are still items left.
I want to take it off quickly.
It's hard.
Let's do it again.
I wanted to lose.
Mishida-san, you wanted
to see it, didn't you?
Today, I made a lot of strings!
Do you want to join us?
Hurry up and take it off.
I don't want to mess it up.
I really like to mess it up.
New panties?
This crotch part.
Let's hit it.
I can't see.
I'll hit it.
One, two.
If you want to play baseball,
you have to do it like this.
Happy New Year!
Out! Safe!
Yoyoi no Yoi!
Happy New Year!
We've been waiting for this moment.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
We'll let you go.
Please.
Koishida-san's...
It's Koishida-san!
Four producers! It's so manly.
Can I climb to the top?
I want to climb, too.
Please don't make fun of my producer.
What's going on?
Who called a child? I'm an idol.
Idol? I'm an idol.
Idol?
No, I don't want to.
What's with that tacky dress?
What?
Why are you wearing it, Producer?
No, no, this is... Hey,
did you miss the time?
Go play at the park.
Why don't you play at
the slide? I'll play, but.
..
You'll play?
But I'm an idol, and I have
a bond with you, Producer.
I won't lose to you
girls in this tacky dress.
I'm not going to lose to you girls.
Unfortunately, I like erotic girls like us.
I'm not a kid!
I'll never lose!
Today, I'll not perform on the stage.
I'll throw away the microphone.
I'll use a chimpanzee
to compete with the girls.
I'm not a kid!
Don't put your hat in too deep.
That's right.
You like a fierce face, don't you?
I can hide this hand.
Try it.
This is how you do a fierce face.
What are you talking about?
Stop it!
You let an idol do such a thing.
Do you like such
people? That's right.
If I die, I can't go back, can I?
I can lick your toes, too.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good when I do this.
I can't get my hands and feet out.
You can't get your hands
and feet out, can you?
If you can't get your hands and
feet out, try to get your mouth out.
You can't do that.
You can't shake your head.
I can't shake my head.
It's dangerous.
Do you want me to show
you something better?
You are an idol anyway.
You've never seen a flower, have you?
Enough! Enough!
Please be tired.
Why?
You could have let me lick you a little.
It doesn't matter if you don't do it.
I can do it.
It's dangerous if you do it like that.
I think I'm going to cry.
Why?
Come on, get in front of me.
I'm not interested.
Show me your idol boobs.
Show me your teeth.
Don't do that.
My mouth will make you feel better.
My teeth will make you feel better.
Give it back to me.
I'll put it under your teeth.
Really? Try it.
Try it.
Have you ever been
there? Yes, I have.
Really? Yes, I have.
Do you know the feeling
of going there? Yes, I do.
I feel like my stomach
is going to explode.
Really?
Then, why don't you lick me?
Then, please lick me.
Are you really okay?
You will lick me, won't you?
I don't want to.
How is it, Rori-manko?
It's great!
Your butt is still blue, isn't it?
It's still blue, isn't it?
She says it's delicious.
Idol's manko is delicious.
She says it feels good.
This way, this way, this way.
Put on your footwear.
Excuse me.
Please put me in.
I'm happy.
There is no place to fail.
There is.
Please put me in.
Wait a minute.
I'll put it in.
What are you doing?
I'm the first one to put
all of the producer's.
Wait a minute.
Wasn't it 100,000?
It's not 100,000.
Now we're finally in the same body.
It feels good.
No way.
You'll put it in, won't
you? I'll put it in.
Show me.
It doesn't feel good,
does it? It feels good.
We are better than usual.
I don't think so.
I'll help you at least.
I can't help it.
Look at me when you're in a good mood.
I don't want to.
Come on, come on.
Can you keep up with my speed?
Come on, come on, come on.
Look at me when I'm in a good mood.
I can't stop.
This is a slow-motion team dance.
I don't want to play with you.
Shall I give you a tight
hug with our manko?
It's an idol manko.
It's just a drop anyway.
That's right.
There's a lot of it.
It's a lie to say a lot.
It's too much.
What a waste.
I want a mobile phone!
Mobile phone! Mobile phone!
What a waste!
If you become an idol, you can do it.
I can't open it.
It can't be helped.
You've been holding back
a lot, so you can't do that.
It's definitely overwritten.
No, it's not.
I overwrote it.
No, you can't.
I failed.
It's no good.
It's the end for us.
I don't want to eat beans.
No, it's no good.
It's no good.
The baby couldn't be satisfied.
It's a big baby.
Why don't you talk to me anymore?
I don't have much time to talk to you.
Why don't you give me a foot massage?
Tell me how you feel
that I don't let you go.
Wasn't a foot massage enough?
It's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good,
it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's
not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's
not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not good, it's not
I'm so happy.
Why?
Come on, let's have fun.
You feel good, don't you?
Why do you feel good?
Let us go out whenever you want.
Let's go, let's go.
Go on, go on.
Don't be shy.
Don't cry.
I can't.
Marumi.
Good bye.
Let's give her a hug.
I think she is lonely.
Let's make her feel better.
I'm sorry.
If you're upset, you can take this.
I'll take this.
If you don't want to
dance, you can go home.
I don't want to dance.
I don't want to go home.
I'll show you my sexy dance.
I'm happy.
I'm a producer, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a
sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex
worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker,
I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm a sex worker, I'm
Can I spit it out as it is?
No, you have to spit it out with a manko.
Here is the best manko.
Here is also.
Where?
There's one here, too,
but why isn't there one?
It feels so good, doesn't it?
As I thought, you're a
birdie with a sexy body.
I have a good one, too.
Hey, Toyo-chan, you're humiliating me.
I'm humiliating you,
but I don't want to lose.
As I thought, this jump is amazing.
Come on, come on.
It's a little bit hot.
It's hot.
It's so heavy.
It's overflowing.
I'm so happy.
Hey, idol.
Your favorite producer
has made other girls cry.
Really?
Why did you make other girls cry?
I don't want it.
Don't you want it? It's a waste.
If you don't want it, I'll lick it.
That's all?
It's said that leftovers are bitter.
You said you had a lot
of things to do, didn't you?
I still have a lot of things to do.
You look a little cute.
I'm hungry.
Why don't you stop
me? You're amazing.
I'm going to these girls.
I don't know what a producer is.
I'll quit.
I'm going to form a group with these girls.
Welcome.
Welcome!
Are you sad, producer?
Look back at me with your small steps.
Show me your cool side.
Please rewind.
Can you do it?
How is it?
I'm afraid of the answer.
You can't rewind,
can you? I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Please do more.
Everyone says more.
I can't do it.
She is a producer, but in
the end, she is our manko.
We have the opposite opinion.
That's strange.
Producer, we will make
you feel good with our manko.
You look pathetic.
Look, manko is beautiful.
Look at Mac's beautiful butt.
Why don't you look at me?
Mac is right in front of you.
Look at me.
I'm not good at this.
You can fix it as it is.
No, no, no.
Open your eyes.
If you fart like that,
I'll leave right away.
Then I'll fart in order in the back.
Then I'll fart in order, too.
Oh, it feels good.
Chirp, chirp, chirp, chirp.
That's the real chirping train.
Don't smoke.
It's so comfortable.
I have to take out my sperm
before I get on the train.
I'm going to jack this train.
My sperm has been squeezed out.
You look like you've been squeezed out.
I have to take out a lot of sperm.
I'm so happy!
I want a croissant, too!
I want a noodle, too!
Me, too!
Please!
I want the rest of the soup.
Give me the rest of the soup.
Give it to me.
Hey, hey.
Let's do it together.
Let's do it again.
I want you to give me a lot of milk tea.
You're a stubborn boss.
You made me a mess, so
please take responsibility.
Thank you, new member.
This time, the five of
us will make our debut.
And you're the producer.
I want to get along with you more.
I'm so happy!
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
※This is not a sound effect.
Mom!
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
※This is not a sound effect.
In...
In... In... In...
Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi,
Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi,
Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi,
Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi, Nakadashi Someone is crying...
Nakadashi!
Dashi!
Who?
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Nakadoshi!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh!
The next day
Darling,
Do you want to go out with me?
We haven't decided yet, have we?
Let's come here!
It's fun!
Let's enjoy! Let's drink.
Your face is getting red, isn't it?
You have a very colorful face.
Did I make you drink too much?
It's just a little. It's special.
How is it? Chikira's little bunny.
I've seen a lot of them, and just
looking at them isn't enough, is it?
No.
I think it's better.
I think I'll have more fun.
I want you to touch me with your big hands.
I want you to feel good.
Ah, it feels good.
Your eyes are beautiful.
We are also.
It's refreshing.
My husband is making me relax.
You want to lie down, don't you?
You must be tired.
Come here.
All of us...
There are only three of us here.
Don't be shy.
It's okay.
Please show me a lot.
First of all, where do you want to touch?
Do you like my nipples?
Then, let's touch a lot.
I'll touch you gently.
Are you here?
Yes.
Oh, it's getting harder.
It's getting warmer.
Yes.
Don't be shy.
Don't look at me.
Let me hear your pleasant
voice and pleasant face.
I'm going to ask you
something I don't understand.
What's going on with the katana
under your husband? Great.
The shape of the katana is
clear even from above the skin.
It looks like it's going to
break through and come out.
Yes.
You have a wonderful sword.
We are very interested in this sword.
Can I take a look?
Can I kiss you? Beautiful.
It's like the first sunrise.
I want to sleep.
I want to put a lemon in my
mouth right now, but I can't wait.
Can't wait?
How do you feel?
Don't be in a hurry.
Let's enjoy it slowly.
It's hot.
The back of your head is strong.
It's wonderful.
Your balls are big.
Isn't this the best in Edo?
Is this the rumored Kotetsu?
I've heard of it, but it's
the first time I've seen it.
It's there, isn't
it? I'm so excited.
Do you want me
to make it harder?
Please make it harder.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it.
I want to smell it, too.
I can't get enough of this smell.
It's so relaxing.
You want to experience each
person's technique, don't you?
Husband, do you like
deep throat? Deep throat.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's my proud move.
It's a cat.
My husband's sword is so
long that I can't cut it deep.
How is it?
It's hot, isn't it?
It's no fun if you just lick it, isn't it?
Please enjoy it even if you are blind.
Oh, it's good.
Tana-san, this side too.
It's a luxury to have both.
Please look at it a lot.
It's time for you to change your clothes.
I'm sorry.
I feel so relaxed.
It's time to get ready.
Let's get ready.
Let's change your clothes.
〈Fuwa〉
I want you to feel my pulse.
I'm going in.
Please take a good look.
I'll take my time.
I'm going to make you feel the
warmth of your husband's arms.
Oh, you're in my arms.
I told you that I won't
let go of your hands.
I told you that I don't
have a fever, didn't I?
I think I'm going to have a fever, too.
It's too early to get a fever.
I'm more sensitive than usual.
Why? Why? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, darling.
I'll go first.
Hey, hey, you shouldn't do that.
You should go first, darling.
I'm sorry, but this is the first
time I've ever felt so good.
Can I borrow it? Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it's cool.
It's so thick.
Look at Sota.
You look like you're going to be
satisfied with just this, don't you?
I want you to move a lot, too.
Are you all right?
Were you able to put up with
your fierce temper? I'll go first.
I want you to follow me from behind.
I want you to take a deep breath.
There are people here.
Oh, my God!
If you don't move, she'll move on her own.
Oh, I see.
I'm getting greedy.
I want more and more.
I'm useless.
I'm so sorry.
【Harry】 【Harry】
Please… Give me… The best…
【Harry】
Best…
You have not only a solid
body, but also a great stamina.
You have a great back.
That's a good point.
I have a good point.
You understand me.
I want you to be my partner every day.
Really?
Usuki, please use this
cushion to feel good.
I'm so happy to see your happy face.
What's that? There, there.
Help me.
Please, please.
Ouch!
Oh, oh, oh! Turn around.
I'm OK.
Please, please.
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, oh, oh! It's leaking.
Oh, my god! It's coming out of my body.
Oh, my god!
It's so strong and strong.
Next, this side.
Oh, my god!
It's been a long time since
I came to the first class.
It's more than I thought.
I've never been so serious with a customer.
Oh, I see.
I'm sure you feel good, too.
There, there.
Are you all right?
I didn't mean to do this.
It feels so good.
Is this the second time
you've had a voice like this?
Did you go out?
It's amazing to see you two together.
I've never seen a husband like you.
Can I clean your room?
Please make it clean.
Oh, it's hot.
We got wet with this today.
Let's enjoy more.
Let's go to bed.
The night is long.
It's so hot today.
It's always hot.
Let's read it together.
Shall we read the comments.
We might not be able to
read it if we read it together.
You did it.
What is it?
I heard a rumor.
Rumor is that you and
Sunny are living together.
I'm here.
Isn't it great? Yes, it is.
Let's go home.
I don't want to talk to you.
I heard a rumor.
Three of us are having an extension party.
Is it true?
Do you want to go out?
I want you to know it.
How much is it?
I don't have to tell you.
Oh, no.
If it's this much, we can
just go without anything.
It's definitely not enough.
No, it's not.
Eguchi-san, bring it.
Is three enough? I don't know.
Because.
..
I can't read that much.
Then, let's not talk about it.
Let's go home.
Let's go to the tapioca.
Let's go to the hospital.
Is there a place where
we can buy it at this price?
What? Is there a place where
If you say that there
is a place where we
can buy it at this price,
isn't it this much? That's right.
Isn't it this much?
Isn't this enough?
It's not that cheap.
We don't have a lot of money.
We are in need of a lot of money.
You are right.
We can't afford it.
How about this?
No, I don't think so.
How about this? I'm so happy.
Is this enough?
A little bit more.
What?
It's not enough.
It's really not enough.
You are so cheeky.
You are happy, aren't you?
You think it's not bad, don't you?
Because three of us are doing this.
You are not happy.
What is this?
I'm going to feed you.
This is our food.
Drink it.
It means you are happy.
What is this?
Stand up and show me.
Show me.
Let's take a look.
What's going on, Chinta?
What's going on with your pants?
I've seen it a lot.
Chinta, be quiet.
I'll show you.
Chinta's Chinta.
Komichinda.
It's gross!
Isn't it big? It's true.
It's bigger than a tent.
It's a good tent for a tent.
You're getting carried away.
If you do that, it will
stick to your mouth.
It looks smelly.
You are lucky.
You are happy, aren't
you? You are happy.
Do you want me to
hold it? Yes, please.
Here we go.
It's moving a lot.
It looks good.
It's perfect!
I'll take a picture for you.
Can you open it? Here we go.
It looks good.
I'm happy to take a picture with you.
I'm happy, too.
I think it's a good idea
to separate the legs.
Wow, it's a nice color.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It's amazing.
There's no choice but to take it back.
It feels good.
Doesn't it feel good?
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
How do you feel? I feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
It's harder than before.
I can't stand it.
I'm worried about you, aren't I?
Please do something for me.
Really?
Please don't do that.
I'm so sad.
I'm so angry.
I can't do that.
Oh, my God.
What's this? It's amazing.
Wow! It's so dark.
Do you want to sit
down? Let's sit down.
We're kind, so we'll give you a chair.
It's fun to sit on the chair.
It's fun, though.
Look.
It's great.
It's a good view.
Please sit down.
What's this? It's so wet.
The tip is shiny.
It smells, doesn't
it? Yes, it does.
It smells so much.
It does, doesn't it?
Are you washing it properly?
Yes.
I'll clean it for you.
You're so kind.
It's so shiny.
It doesn't matter which one.
It's clean now.
Why did you make
it clean? Me too.
Let's do it in order.
OK.
What is this?
It's a special one.
We don't do this with that much money.
Bring more next time.
Who do you like? Tell me later.
Let's wait for your answer.
Who do you like? Tell me.
Make up your mind.
Wow, your tongue is so soft.
You look so good.
How do you feel? I feel good.
Then say it more.
It's hard to understand.
Thanks to you two, it's so beautiful.
Right?
I'm so grateful.
But I don't know if it stinks.
You should wash your face.
Are you washing your face properly?
I'm not washing my face.
Who was the most comfortable?
Who was it?
Tell me clearly.
Who was the most comfortable?
Who was it?
How do you feel?
It's hot? I can't decide.
I don't feel anything.
It's like the one in Jumanko.
How do you feel?
It's meaningless if you just feel good.
Yes.
You three don't have to lick me.
How do you feel? I can't decide.
You can't decide.
What?
You have to decide.
I need to pee.
I won't lick you anymore.
Don't lick me.
Come on, let's go to bed.
Come on, go to bed.
OK! It's time to get up.
It's time to get up.
The day I made a baby
food, I went to the candy shop.
I made the candy with a lot of effort.
I was a little embarrassed about
making candy with a lot of effort.
Choco is an adult cat
who doesn't know that.
For Choco, it is the greatest
pleasure to touch the floor.
Look at this.
Chinta, it looks good on you.
It looks good on me, doesn't it?
Isn't it cute? It's perfect.
Let's make it beautiful.
Isn't it great to stand
like this? It's great.
What's this?
Isn't it great?
Yuka, look at Jintan.
He is playing with my manko.
He is so luxurious.
Jintan, Jintan, you are so big.
Jintan, you are so big.
Jintan, you are so chubby.
Hey, you two.
Can I?
Jintan, look over there.
Keep an eye on them.
Hurry up.
Is it just us? Maybe.
We are here.
Let's do it in a special way.
I like it.
Did you bring a needle?
What did you bring with you?
Oh, you didn't let me go.
It's okay if you don't bring one.
I'm sure you'll bring one.
Let's do it.
Oh, it's like GD.
Who do you want to call first?
Do you want to go first?
Is it okay? It's okay.
Really?
Can I go first? Yes, you can.
I think Chinta is pretty good.
Really?
Yes.
I'll put it in for you.
Are you happy? Thank you.
Are you scared?
What do you think?
You can do it if you want.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
Look carefully.
Look at this.
I'm not wearing anything.
I'm bare-skinned.
Is it OK?
Yes.
I did it.
You did it.
Chinta, be happy.
We're studying.
It's the first time for you, isn't it?
It's the first time for me, too.
Oh, no!
You are almost like a virgin.
You should be kind to a virgin.
Yes.
You have a big neck.
Have you ever been hit?
No.
I'm going to make ramen.
We haven't put it yet.
Which one do you
like? I don't mind.
Really?
Ichi-piko is kind.
Then, I'll put it in.
Gyaru-chan is also kind.
Ichi-piko is a very good one.
Of course.
Isn't it big?
It was a little dangerous.
What about the hardness?
It was very dangerous.
I want to put it in soon.
It's a little strong, but it's really good.
You like boobs.
I'll show you my boobs.
Do you want this?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby eating a baby's food.
I was surprised to see a
baby eating a baby's food.
I'm going to take a bath.
Yeah! That's all.
Oh! Don't stop.
It's dangerous.
Isn't it dangerous?
I'm not going yet.
What did you say?
I can't take a bath.
Bye-bye.
I'm going to take a bath.
You are such a good girl.
I want to go.
You want to go?
You can't go yet.
We are not looking forward to it.
That's right.
We don't know anything at all.
I don't want you to do
it, but you have to do it.
You have to do it.
I don't want you to do it from behind.
I want you to do it.
Who will do it first?
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
OK.
Rock-paper-scissors.
I'm strong today.
You are strong.
I'm lucky.
I'll buy you bubble tea later.
OK.
Thank you.
What should I do?
Your panties are wet.
I can see your underwear.
It's the best.
You don't have to see it.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Chien-chan, shake
your hips more seriously.
Do your best.
Do it more seriously.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's terrible.
Is it terrible? Oh, shit.
Oh, it's painful.
A little.
I thought I was the one who ate it, but
I didn't know I was the one who ate it.
It's all thanks to you.
It's open.
It's open, so let's go.
Let's go.
Let's eat.
First of all, the bag is dangerous.
It's open.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
Isn't it great? It's so good.
It's so good.
It's like a tank.
I'm going to make you a bigger one.
Go for it.
It's so good.
Look at this.
It feels good.
Chinta, it's great.
Move your waist.
Chinta, it feels good.
Chinta, it's great.
It feels good.
Move your waist.
It's great.
Chinta, you are awesome!
I know, right?
That's it! That's it!
It feels so good!
Please do it!
It's intense!
Awesome!
It feels so good!
Chinta, you are awesome!
Awesome! Awesome!
Let's go! Let's go!
Oh, it's so good.
It feels so good.
Hey.
It's mine.
You don't have to say that.
I said it's mine.
It's mine.
Thank you for the meal.
What are you doing?
I'm playing with the apple.
I'm happy.
Oh, my God!
It looks delicious.
They are so focused on the food.
It's too big.
It's so big.
It's so good.
I want to eat it so much.
You are going to eat it, aren't you?
I want to eat it.
Are you ready? Yes, I am.
Here we go.
Wow! Erotic! Oh, no.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Oh, no.
This is really gross.
You can't read it.
You're still in a dilemma.
I'll take it.
I'll take it again.
It's awesome.
I'll take it, too.
Next, Rima.
Look, Chintan is wearing her eyewear.
Isn't it great? It's great.
Oh, no.
I want it.
Is it okay to be so
aggressive? I can bear it.
Can you?
You've been bearing it for a while.
I can't.
But, the more you put up with
it, the more popular you will be.
It's better to be popular.
You want to be popular, don't you?
I'm not popular.
Wait, Chinko!
You want to be popular, don't you?
Did she really say that?
Oh, no! She's serious.
Chinko, how many times did you get angry?
Oh my god!
Is this a pre-sale?
It's a pre-sale.
Is this a half-ready?
This is awesome!
Isn't it?
Wow!
This is awesome!
Isn't it?
How much do you eat?
It stinks! It's so smelly.
Move.
Come here.
It's so spicy.
Eat it with spicy sauce.
It's so big.
What?
You still want to eat a box of lunch?
You have a big mouth.
What? I'm Marumie.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm Marumie.
You're sleeping a lot again.
You're sleeping a lot.
I'll give you more.
Thank you.
You're so kind.
You're too kind.
I'll do it for you.
You can do it, right?
I can't do it yet.
You have to do it.
You can do it.
I'm not here.
I'm here.
I feel good.
I'm sleepy.
I'm here.
Our shop is... Please show me.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm starting to miss you.
Pitta, lend me your hand.
I want you to lend me your hand, too.
You'll be back soon,
right? You're so cute.
You're so cute.
We can go out now.
Yes, we can.
Then, let's go together.
Let's go together.
I'm so happy.
It's coming out.
It's amazing.
How many times did you go out?
Three times? That's amazing.
Wow, it's amazing.
RU-chan, isn't it?
Isn't it great?
We are going to be friends.
Oh, let's do it together.
We are going to be friends from today.
Let's take a picture together.
What? Come here.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Cheese!
That's a good one.
Let's listen to this song.
Let's listen to the next song.
There are a lot of children.
It's exciting.
It's amazing.
Are you shooting a movie?
Is it the future?
No, it's the future.
It's the future, isn't it?
I don't know English.
I don't know words.
I'm an alien.
I like you, my friend.
What?
Did you say you like me?
Do you like me?
Isn't it crazy that you like me?
Because I'm a robot.
That's right. Androids are made by AI.
But we can understand their charm.
That's great.
Well, shall we go?
Brother, come here.
It's fun here.
What? Is it fun?
Hey, look this way.
It's been a while since I had
a meal, but I'm still nervous.
My nipples are swollen.
My nipples are delicious.
I've been nervous since I was born.
I'm hungry.
Really? I'm so happy.
It's delicious.
I'm going to eat it all.
Is it delicious?
Let me eat it, too.
But there is no
Sadako, you feel good, don't you?
You know Sadako, don't you?
That's my girl!
I'm number 2, not number 1.
I'm number 3, not number 2.
You're like a human.
Hmm?
Hurry up and program it in your head.
Did you get the feeling of the future?
Then I'll teach you how to feel better.
Do you know how to feel better?
Do you know how to attack?
What did you
study? Oh, it's hot.
I want to touch it directly.
What is this place
called? I don't know.
It's called Manko.
Manko, Manko.
You seem to be interested in Manko.
Manko, water is coming out.
My manko is coming out, too.
Water is coming out.
I'm sorry.
I have to make this
level of the composition.
Please watch it carefully.
Do you want to have more fun?
Please sleep a little.
What? Manko.
Manko.
Ah.
I want to put it in too.
Oh, my.
It feels so good.
I'm going to put it in.
Oh, I put it in.
Does it feel good?
Oh, it feels good.
She sofa laughs like a
kid and she is a good girl.
She talks about winter camp.
She talks about love water.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to do that.
Water, water.
You're drinking water, aren't you?
Next, put in a new one.
Put in a new one.
Water, water.
You're drinking water, aren't you?
Do you like drinking water?
Let's drink a lot of water.
Oh, it's cold.
What?
It's raining a lot.
Let's take a look at the sky.
It's slippery and not
going well than before.
Yes.
It happens.
It's amazing.
Who is working hard?
Can you hear the sound of water?
Can you hear it? It's coming.
It's coming.
I can't believe it! Sit down.
I'll show you the body of a future woman.
You ate it from the spoon.
You ate it.
It feels good.
Can I sleep? Yes, you can.
Kima-chan, you are so cute.
Kima-chan, you move your
tail without my permission.
You are so cute that I want to hug you.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry. Please let me hold you.
No, I don't.
I'm glad to meet you.
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good.
What do you mean?
I feel like I'm getting
wrinkles on my face.
If you don't feel good, I'll
give you a piggyback ride.
I can't stop my waist.
Let's go.
Wait.
It's new.
What? It's white.
It smells like a human.
You are amazing.
Give me some ramen.
Give me.
It's me, Moyu.
Hey, you still have a lot of pimples.
I don't know what to do with it.
Oh, it's open.
It feels good.
Hey, this hand is open.
Hold my hand.
Hey, you have a lot of pimples.
It feels good.
Hey, you feel good, too.
Oh, more, more.
Take me to the back.
Oh, that's right.
It's about to come!
It feels so good!
It's coming!
It's almost!
I gave you a wonderful moustache, so you'll
give me a stomach massage, won't you?
I'll give you a stomach massage.
What are you going to do?
I'm in pain, too.
How about you, Nishi?
Tell me how it is.
It's coming!
Yes, it came out.
It's coming…
It's still shocking, even
though it's only the second time.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
It's a white cat, but it's
a very cute white cat.
I don't want to give it
to you, but I want you
to touch it so that it
will stand for a day.
Give me more.
It's the best, isn't it?
Let's do it more, Reika.
It's the best, isn't
it? Do it again.
It's the best, isn't it?
Let's do it more.
Let's take a break.
Oh, Koi-chan.
Oh, that's good.
Hey, guys.
The last big fight is about to start.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Why? Look.
What?
I'm waiting for you.
I can't run.
We only listen to what you say.
Excuse me.
There is a strange person.
Can I lick you?
I will lick you with my soft hand.
It's been a long time since I've had a
bath, so I'm going to take a bath now.
I'm going to take a bath now.
Oh, it's hard.
I'm good at taking a bath.
I'll give you a bath,
so take a video of me.
If you don't take a picture, I'll bite you.
I'll bite you.
Can I take a picture of you?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a picture of you.
Mom, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to be found out
that I didn't wash my hair.
She is wet.
She is wet? Yeah.
She is wet all over.
She is wet.
I'll wet her.
Isn't it good?
No?
Don't do it, or I'll get angry.
I won't.
I want to eat it.
If I put it in my mouth, it will feel good.
I want to put it in my mouth.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
Let's put it in the back.
In the back?
This angle is dangerous.
Let's put it in my mouth.
I want to put it in my mouth.
It feels good.
Can you put it in?
Put it in?
Yes.
I want it.
I want to sleep.
Me, too.
Manko is erotic.
I'm sorry.
It's not good.
I feel so bad.
Lie down here.
The baby is coming out.
Do you want me to get it out?
No, I don't want to.
You felt so good.
Did I?
Did you feel good? Yes, I did.
Did you? Yes, I did.
Do it again.
Again, again, again!
Everybody comes!
What, everyone comes!
Everybody comes! It's painful.
..
Hey, what?
What am I doing?
Still, I can't go out?
Already everybody comes!
It's coming out a lot.
Oh, no.
It's dripping.
Hey.
What's up?
It's dripping a lot.
It's fast.
Can you bear it?
Yes.
Look at this.
Seishi.
Oh, no.
What?
Is it bitter? No, it's good.
Is it good?
Yes.
Is this enough?
What are you doing?
You do it on your own.
You put it in your mouth.
It's painful, isn't it?
How are you feeling?
Your face is so cute.
Are you ready?
Let's go together.
Let's go.
Do you know what
it is? I don't know.
I feel good.
It's warm.
Is it full? It's dripping.
It's great.
It's full.
It's coming out.
I feel like I'm an angel.
Help me! Help me!
It's coming out.
It's warm.
I'm going to take a picture of the cat.
The cat is coming out of the hole.
I want to be comfortable with the cat.
Maruyama Shrine
She's making her way into a baby's room.
Wow!
Are you OK? I'm excited.
Oh, no! I'm going to fall.
I'm going to fall.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
I feel so bad!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
It hurts!
Nakadashi! Bye!
Nakadashi!
Nakadashi! Nakadashi!