Good morning.
Today, I'm going to
introduce you to a couple.
I want you to take a look at her.
Yes.
As I said earlier, the
contents are detailed.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Can I ask you a question?
Yes.
Do you know the couple kisser?
No, I don't know.
You don't know?
It's a place where couples
meet and exchange
girlfriends and do
something a little erotic.
Have you been
there? No, I haven't.
You haven't, have you?
Do you have an interest
in such a place? I see.
It's suspicious, isn't it?
But I want you to experience the
atmosphere and give me a comment.
Of course, you don't have to
exchange or do anything erotic.
Of course, we will pay the full price.
I want you to experience the atmosphere.
If you have any comments, that's fine.
Do you have time?
How long will it take?
It will end in about 30 minutes.
What should I do?
You two look good together.
What's the difference?
About three months ago.
Yes.
At a club.
At a club?
Yes.
That's unexpected.
Yes, it is.
How close are you?
Well, just a little.
I see.
You two are close, and
it's only been three months.
I don't think you have any complaints.
Well... Do you have
any? No, not really.
No? That's good.
Do you have any? I don't.
I don't know.
Oh, you don't know.
What is it?
I don't talk about other men.
I don't know anyone at all.
Oh, that's hard.
That's because she believes in it.
Oh, because she believes in it.
But you think you're
not attractive, don't you?
No, I don't think so at all.
Really?
I'm going back to the topic.
Is it OK?
I want to be a reporter
for the general public.
Like a date that is a
little different from usual.
I wonder if it's fun.
If you do it, I'll give you a gift.
Can you do it?
Do you want to try it?
Can you do it? Well, yes.
Thank you very much.
I'll explain it.
It's a program like an amateur reporter.
It's a program like that.
It's a program where amateurs go to
various shops and report their impressions.
This time, it's a project
called Couple Kissa.
Is it okay? Yes, it's okay.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to try it.
I want to try it too.
Go ahead.
I'm sleepy.
I didn't sleep well.
It's fun, isn't it? It's fun.
It's good.
He said he wouldn't be sad.
I'm not sad.
I believe in you.
Do you have a strange
feeling about your boyfriend?
Because he is a man?
No, I don't think so.
Show me.
I don't feel anything.
Look at me.
Do you have a crush
on him? No, I don't.
I'm not looking at you.
You don't care, do you?
Q. How old are you now?
A. I'm 20.
Q. Are you sure?
A. Yes, I am.
Q. Do you watch MMA?
A. Yes, I do.
A. No, I don't.
I don't come here often, but I don't
come here often while looking at this.
What is this?
What's wrong?
I don't usually do this.
He is shy.
He is cute.
I can see his nose.
You want to see it, don't you?
I'm looking at it.
I think you can see it.
You're wearing a woman's clothes.
It's cute.
You're really a woman.
You're a woman.
If you could just say that
you'll participate in the event.
No.
I'll leave that to you.
Everyone is excited.
Isn't it too early?
What are you talking
about? It's too early.
You're a woman,
aren't you? I'm a man.
It's your first time
to come here, isn't it?
Yes.
You don't have to be careful at all.
You don't have to be like this.
You've come all the way here.
It's normal.
You don't have to be afraid.
Look.
Oh, it's fast.
It's not fast.
It's fast.
It's like a robot.
You don't have to be shy.
It's my room.
It's okay.
It's your first time,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
We don't have a microphone.
Let's use a small one.
Microphone, microphone.
You are a great father.
Please turn on the microphone.
It's just a memory.
I found it.
You two seem to have made a mistake.
What?
What are you doing?
You should come here.
Yes, you should come here.
That's right.
You should come here.
Did you teach me how to play?
How to play?
Please teach me how to play.
Hey!
You can come over here.
I'm trying to run away.
Can I touch you? No, you can't.
You look mature.
I'm not.
I'm not fat.
You're not fat.
What if the groom comes?
I'll be like, I'll be
like, I'll be like,
I'll be like,
You should come this way.
No, no, no.
This way, this way.
You should come this way.
What should I do if you come this way?
Do you have any plans to have sex?
Can you make it
come true? No, I can't.
You can't make it come true? Are
you seeing someone? No, I can't.
Do you have any
plans? No, not yet.
You don't have a neck, do you?
I don't have a neck.
Really?
I'm a little seduced by adult play.
Isn't this crazy?
Why are you touching me?
Don't you have any complaints?
No.
Girls are sexier than you think.
I don't know what kind
of shoes you are wearing.
You said you don't have a voice actor.
Don't be scared, everyone.
Sit down, sit down.
Show me your face.
I'll lower the chair in front of you.
I'll sit in front of you.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Here.
No.
You are really kind, aren't you?
Yes.
You are.
It's not noticeable, is it?
On the contrary, it's not noticeable.
Look at it closely.
Is it not noticeable?
It's the first time to hear
the sound of the microphone.
How do you feel? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm surprised.
Your face is surprisingly calm.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting stiff.
Your eyes are wobbly.
Can you hear my
voice? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I want you to look at
me in a beautiful way.
You're a girl, aren't you?
Are you going to eat it?
You are eating too much.
Do you want to poop?
You don't want to, do you?
You don't have to poop as a man.
This is the first time for me to meet you.
Oh my god! It's the first
time for me to meet you, too.
Hello.
Are you really not
the worst? No, I'm not.
There is no such a thing.
I'm not a human.
Look at this.
It's suspicious.
It's like being touched by a goldfish.
It's terrible.
My boyfriend has gone crazy.
What? It's a lie.
It's a lie.
It's terrible, isn't
it? Look at this.
Wow!
He's gone crazy.
After all, men are like this.
Look at this.
He says it's super cute.
I thought so.
Stop it.
You wanted to see
it, didn't you? I did.
It's cold in Japan.
It's cold.
Look down.
It's a little bit scary.
It's scary.
I have been waiting for you all the time.
Thank you.
You have a long hair.
Hair is so long.
I am surprised.
Why?
You are so cute.
Do you have a boyfriend?
She has already got up.
It's beautiful, isn't
it? Look at that.
It's beautiful.
I know.
It's clean.
It's a facial make-up.
It's amazing.
No, I don't know.
It's been a while since we did this.
You look like a teenager.
It's soft.
Ah!
It's a little big.
You want to forget, don't you?
It's a little different
from what I'm saying.
It's terrible, isn't
it? It's terrible.
I'm going to cry.
No, no, no.
I'm about to cry.
Have you ever heard of it?
No.
I'm going to cry.
You don't usually cry, do you?
No, because I can't
hide it even if I can see it.
Wait a minute.
Let's leave her alone.
OK.
Let's get in the way.
Don't look at her.
OK.
I like boobs.
She likes boobs, too.
You look flat.
How do you feel? I'm not flat.
To be honest, my body is flat.
You don't have to worry about it.
It's OK.
Leave it to me.
What's going on?
It's being played.
Ah!
Hey!
What are you
doing? It's a success.
It's not that easy.
I'm sorry.
I think I'm going to lose.
Mom, is it okay?
I'm going to lose.
Oh, well.
I've lost five minutes.
How was it?
Well,
I think I need to concentrate.
I don't think so.
Really? I'm happy.
Are you happy?
You have a good one.
No, I don't.
It's not bad.
It's good.
This is good.
Do you want to pull up?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm going to show you my body.
It's a round.
It's wide.
Your style is perfect.
Let's use it.
This is the first time I've ever
seen such a scene in a movie.
It's like a scene from a horror movie.
It's the first time I've ever
seen such a scene in a movie.
Oh,
Oh? Let's have fun.
Women have sexual desire.
But they don't know women's sexual desire.
Oh, It's so tight.
But I'm happy.
You're wearing a warm bag.
You look like a girl, don't you?
I have to play with it.
I know, you have to play with it.
I have to look at it.
It's not good.
I can't stop it.
She's gone.
She's been killed.
How is it?
I'm going to do it.
Do you want me to do
what you want me to do?
No, I want you to do what I want you to do.
That's rude.
It's beautiful, but it feels different.
There is such a world.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
It is a derivative work
of the Touhou Project.
I'm glad to see you two.
You look pitiful.
You look totally fine.
You are completely immersed in the world.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's a real man's love.
It's strange, isn't it?
It's strange to be able to do it normally.
It's intense.
She is so tired.
She is so happy.
You look so happy.
You look happy.
You are a man if you
don't give this kind of things.
Yes, I am.
Oh, I see.
It feels good.
Do you want me to carry you on my back?
Do you want me to carry you
on my back? On your back.
It's a little bit hot.
It's hot.
I'm hot.
You are hot?
I'll bring you a tissue.
I'm hot.
It's hot.
You should take off your clothes.
What's going on?
There are so many of them.
They are so cute.
Excuse me.
Are you free now?
We are shooting around here.
What is this?
What is this program?
It is a program where
amateur reporters go to
various shops and talk
about their impressions.
Sounds interesting.
I'm interested in it.
Could you tell me your name?
May I ask your name? I'm Shiori.
And your boyfriend? I'm Ken.
Shiori and Ken.
Thank you very much.
May I ask your age? I'm 22.
I'm 23.
You are 22 and I'm 23.
You seem to be one year apart.
Where did you meet each other?
I'm a college student,
too. I graduated from the
university a year ago, but
I'm a college student now.
Are you both college
students? Yes, we are.
Do you have any dissatisfaction
with each other? Yes, we do.
What do you feel?
He is a little jealous.
Jealous? Yes, he is.
I think he is a little too much.
What do you do?
What do I do?
It's embarrassing if I don't say it.
I don't like to say it.
How do you do? Do you keep it a secret?
I don't think I know much about it.
You don't?
No.
Do you have any complaints
about your boyfriend?
Do you have any
dissatisfaction with the company?
Even if I send an e-mail, they don't reply.
I think they don't like it.
Is it a temptation to
reply quickly? Yes, it is.
I will tell you briefly.
I introduce this time.
This is a program called
assault amateur reporter.
Amateurs go to a place
called a couple cafe.
They enjoy there.
After that, they comment on the impression.
It is a program of such content.
What is a couple cafe?
A couple cafe is a place
where a lot of couples gather
and exchange their partners
to do something erotic.
Exchange partners?
But we don't exchange partners.
We just want you to see the atmosphere of
the place and talk about your impressions.
You don't have to go to college today.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's amazing,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
How do you feel? I'm nervous.
I've never been to such a place.
I'm nervous.
Please sit down.
We are reporters.
So, please tell us what
you want to talk about.
Is there anything you want to talk about?
Please take your time.
You look happy.
Thank you.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm so happy to see you, too.
How often do you go
to Kansai? Once a week.
Once a week?
Yes, once a week.
I'm so happy to see you.
I don't know if I can do it.
Do you want to do it?
Like this? Yes, I do.
But it's difficult, isn't it?
If you don't mind, I'd
like you to mix it up.
But it's just a little bit.
Yes.
It's just the atmosphere.
It's okay.
It's okay, isn't
it? Yes, it's okay.
I've never seen a place like this.
It's my first time.
It's very active.
There is a floor for adults.
I've never seen a place like this.
Is this a cover?
Yes.
It's a cover.
Oh, it's hot.
It hurts.
It's hot.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
It is a derivative work
of the Touhou Project.
Let's start.
Wow! I'm nervous.
Wait a minute.
I'm nervous.
You are nervous.
Are you okay?
We are going to do our best.
Please support us.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
It's been a long time.
It's beautiful.
Could you take a look at it?
What do you think? It's so cute.
It's too far away.
It's like a wall of my heart.
I want to enjoy it.
You want to enjoy it, don't you?
It's interesting.
How do you feel?
It's my first time.
Oh, is it? Please come in.
Please come in.
I'm nervous.
Let's participate.
Yes, let's.
What's up?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to have fun.
What are you here to have fun?
I'm here to have fun with FIT.
I'm looking forward to it.
I don't know until I try it.
It's better to go there
to feel the atmosphere.
It's boring just to watch it.
It's like a flower of the wall.
There is no need to say bad words.
Just do it.
We are like brothers.
It's amazing.
Is it amazing? This is normal.
This is normal.
Do you come here every
week? Yes, every day.
Do you know each other?
Yes, we know each other.
Are you a naked couple?
It's like a family.
It's like a family, isn't it?
It's like a family,
isn't it? I'm nervous.
I'm nervous.
Your face is stiff.
How do you usually
feel? I'm nervous.
I'm nervous.
Can I change my clothes today?
Are you ready?
No, I just came here for sightseeing.
For sightseeing?
Yes.
What's that?
Isn't that a camera?
Anyway,
she's my girlfriend.
If you don't
mind... But, well...
That's normal.
It's a secret scene.
That's right.
Yes!
You can hold it in, can't you?
Don't growl like that!
She doesn't like it, does she?
She's jealous, so she
doesn't want to get up.
She's drooling a bit.
No, no.
Don't get jealous.
You have to overcome your jealousy.
You have to change your attitude.
You don't have to touch your boobs.
You don't have to do that.
Let me change my attitude.
Please don't do that.
Why?
You just have to change your attitude.
You can't say that.
I'm in a good mood.
You should say,
You like my best girlfriend, don't you?
You are so cute.
I'm not.
You are cute.
She said, yes.
I see.
She is a good girl.
I think it's going to be fun.
You are so small.
If you are a man, you should play with it.
What are you
talking about? Stop it.
This is not a toy.
It's amazing that you don't touch it.
I told you not to touch it.
Don't touch me.
I'm naked.
I want my girlfriend to touch me.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'll get touched, too.
Please touch me.
She doesn't look good.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Could you give me a moment?
Mr. Kuroda.
I'm sorry to bother you.
This is not the one, this is not the one.
You, you, you.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is a serious business.
You should play a little.
I'm not sure.
Don't do anything.
It's a little hard.
You're right, Mr. Kuroda.
Wait a minute, please.
I can't believe I'm
living in a place like this.
I'm a serious person,
so please don't touch me.
Why are you touching me?
My hands are in the way.
Don't attack me.
Why are you touching me?
Please stop touching me.
You're smiling.
I'm not smiling. I'm just rubbing my hands.
No, I'm not.
She looks like she's having fun.
Yeah, she is.
She's having a lot of fun.
I think she's having the
most fun out of all of us.
Wait a minute.
You've come this far, and
you're being so persistent.
Don't touch me.
I'm going to break that flow.
Wait, wait, wait.
Touch me.
It's okay.
Don't push your boobs against my face.
Please stop it.
Stop it.
Why are you angry?
It's not the place to be angry.
Please stop it.
Stop it.
They are arguing.
I'm being told that I'm amazing.
Why are you messing with me?
Let's have a fight.
I'm looking forward to it.
You're very strong.
I'm not good at this.
That's right.
I'm scared.
You're quite strong.
Are you okay?
I want to eat it.
You want to eat it, don't you?
What are you doing?
You are a bad girl.
It's good.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's definitely the light of boobs.
It's so red.
It's so cute.
It's the image of boobs, isn't it?
It's the image of boobs.
You look like you are from Hokkaido.
This hand is mine.
You are persistent.
Stop it.
No one is persistent.
You resist.
I don't want to resist.
You don't want to
resist, so you don't resist.
You don't resist.
You always resist.
When you were in ATC, you resisted.
What's this?
It's an old one.
What's this? Oh, no.
It's broken.
Yes, it is.
Let me see your hand.
It's broken.
What's this? It's all red.
It's all red.
Do you have a
new one? Yes, I do.
I have a new one.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you for coming to our date.
She is a female gyu.
So, she is a bit old.
Wait a minute.
Red panties.
She is a bit old.
Raise your hips.
Wait a minute.
What are you
doing? Wait a minute.
She is not a baby.
Great.
Wait a minute.
I'm so happy!
Please don't touch me.
Oh, you touched me.
Why did you touch me?
I'm so happy!
Oh!
You look so happy.
You're so into it.
No, no, no.
You like it, don't
you? No, I don't.
What are you talking about?
What are you touching? Stop it.
Red underwear.
Hey.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Are you OK?
You always stay in your room, don't you?
It's hard to breathe.
This is the world of the lung.
Why are you standing up?
I'm standing up.
Are you standing
up? No, I'm not.
I'm standing up.
No, you're not.
Can you make it
bigger? I don't know.
This is a serious person,
but this is not good at all.
It's different from what I've heard.
It's true.
I didn't know that.
You are standing so much.
What are you doing?
Well, well.
What are you
doing? I'm so jealous.
Where?
Here, here, here.
Please put it on.
Can I?
What are you doing?
You don't have to do it.
Stop it.
I'm fine.
I told you not to do it.
What are you doing? Stop it.
I'm not doing it.
Her hair style is very feminine.
What are you doing?
Why did you shut up?
Why are you so quiet?
You don't like it, do you?
No.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
This is the toilet.
It is the toilet.
Don't do that.
I do the same thing.
I bind my hands.
Don't do that.
What are you
doing? Here you are.
Thank you.
Don't touch it.
I'm a little worried.
No, I'm not.
I know, but you're holding my hand.
Don't touch me.
Stop it.
How about this?
How do you feel? I don't know.
Why?
You feel good, don't you?
Let's go inside.
It's very spacious inside.
It's cold, isn't it? It's good.
Are you comfortable?
I don't know if I can move.
You don't know?
It seems that you are saying
that you feel comfortable.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Don't you feel good?
I don't know if I feel good or not.
Let's take a look.
I don't know.
But I feel good.
Let's take a look.
I'm cold.
I feel the pain of my wrist.
I'm getting worse.
I think I'm getting worse.
I'm getting more and more serious.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
I've never seen a cat like this before,
and I've never seen a cat like this before.
What's up?
She is very attracted to you.
I'm sorry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Look this way.
Meow.
I'm a deadbeat,
aren't I? You are.
I'm a deadbeat.
It's gonna work out.
Still a little
sluggish? That's right.
I guess you couldn't get over it.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
But you're doing well,
aren't you? I'm a deadbeat.
He's got a tan.
Why?
How do you feel?
I don't feel good.
Why don't you do it yourself?
I'm doing it myself.
You didn't do it on purpose,
did you? No, I didn't.
I just felt good.
You don't feel good.
I felt good.
I don't know.
What do you know? I don't know.
Naked? No, no, no.
Can you tell me your
name? I'm Osami.
Mr. Osami.
What about your
boyfriend? I'm Lee.
Mr. Lee?
Yes.
Aren't you
Japanese? No, I'm not.
I'm from Korea.
Are you Korean?
Yes.
Are you studying
abroad? Yes, I am.
Are you a college student?
Yes.
Do you have a part-time job?
I have a part-time job at a gas station.
Gas station?
Yes.
That's good.
Thank you.
What about your girlfriend?
She is a student at a vocational school.
Where did you meet her?
We met at a drinking
party about two months ago.
At a drinking party.
Is it a group
marriage? Yes, it is.
I see.
I haven't asked your age yet.
How old are you?
I'm 22 years old.
22 years old.
How old are you?
About the same age.
I'm in my twenties.
Twenties.
Yes.
You seem to get along well.
Yes, we do.
Do you have any dissatisfaction
with each other? No, we don't.
No, we don't.
Where did you like her?
She is kind to everyone.
Kind?
She is friendly.
She looks kind.
Yes, I like her.
Did you confess your
love to her? Yes, I did.
I'm glad that you have
such a cute girlfriend.
I'm shooting for a program
called Tatsugeki Shirooto Reporter.
The content is that
amateurs go to various shops
and get their impressions
and comments at the end.
This time, I'm going to a couple's cafe.
Do you know a couple's cafe?
No, I've heard of it.
How did you hear of it?
A cafe where couples go.
That's right.
I don't know the details.
A lot of couples come together.
They exchange partners.
They do erotic things and play.
It's a cafe like that.
You've never been there,
have you? No, I haven't.
Are you interested in it? Well.
..
No, never.
Never? That's good.
You are very active.
How about your boyfriend?
I've never seen him.
You've never seen him?
Yes.
Are you interested
in him? A little bit.
A little bit?
You look like a pervert.
It is a program that I would like
you to stay in the store for about
30 minutes and look at the atmosphere
and comment on your impressions.
Is it okay? Can
you do it? I see.
Yes.
Is it okay just to look at it?
I don't have to exchange it, but I want
you to enjoy the atmosphere of the place.
This time, we will go to the playroom.
I want you to go to
the place where such a
thing has started and
give us your impressions.
If I can, I'd like to do it.
Do you really just watch it?
Yes, I just watch it.
If I'm invited to do something,
I just refuse to do it.
Really?
Yes.
You just watch it?
Yes, I just watch it.
I don't ask you to change anything.
Of course, I make a joke.
We will also release a
video, so I hope you can do it.
You have a subtle look on your face.
I just look at it.
I just look at it, but
all the customers are
ordinary people, so
they come to enjoy it.
I'm a person who lives in Tokyo,
so I might come close to you,
so I'd like you to take good
care of yourself in that area.
Are you okay?
If you have a strong will and
refuse, I think it's okay at all.
I'm just looking at you.
Can you refuse?
Yes.
I can't rely on you.
I'm nervous.
Are you OK?
Yes.
Can you do it?
I just have to look at it.
Here it is.
Can you wear it?
Yes.
Thank you.
How do you feel? I'm nervous.
My heart is pounding.
Your boyfriend is also nervous.
How do you feel?
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing,
isn't it? I'm sorry.
I think I'm more stressed out than you are.
I'm sorry.
You two are reporters.
We're not here anymore.
Are you okay?
Can you do some interviews?
What?
Can you do some reports?
Reports?
Yes.
Come here.
Well,
Yes.
Can you do some
interviews? Well, please.
You are already there.
I can see you from a distance.
Yes.
Please.
What are you doing here?
This is a private school.
Don't you know anything?
Do you know the system?
It's my first time.
Oh, is that so?
This is a place to release yourself.
I don't know if my girlfriend
is different from yours.
Hello.
It's no problem.
It's hot, isn't it? It's hot.
Hello.
It's getting hot.
What are you going to do?
She seems to be motivated.
If she wakes up, she will
be switched to this side.
It's a rule.
This is the first time for you, isn't it?
How do you feel?
My heart is beating so fast.
How do you feel? I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Well, let's go to bed.
Is this your first
time? Yes, it is.
It's good, isn't it?
Is it your first time to have a boyfriend?
Is it your first time to
have a boyfriend? Yes, it is.
You look so energetic.
No, I'm not.
I will go to the vet.
I'm worried about my daughter's health.
I'm afraid to carry her.
I'm worried about her.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a baby crying in front of a camera.
The baby is crying.
I don't get it.
Boo!
How about hearing none?
Reading none?
It seems to be reading none.
I don't know about this.
What does it say? Disgusting.
The baby is crying.
It's hot, isn't it?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm not sure if it's because
it's cold or because it's cold.
Ouch!
Are you OK?
What's wrong?
What's wrong? I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I can't help it.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying so loudly.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry.
Please let go of me.
Let go of me.
You are doing well.
You are touching her.
Everyone is embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
What are you going
to do? Don't cry.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
It's been a while since I've
She is so small.
She is so cute.
She is being petted.
How do you feel? She is so cute.
She is so young.
She is so energetic.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm so happy to see a baby cry like this.
You're not hurt? No, I'm fine.
You don't have a tumor?
I'm not sure if I can do it.
Actually, I've never done this before.
I've never done this before.
Can you do it with your hands and feet?
No.
I can't do it.
Dad is crying.
Ten years have passed
since my daughter was born.
I am going to die.
I can do it.
This is...
There are so many!
I can't believe it.
It's cute, isn't it?
This is my girlfriend.
Wow.
How old are you?
70.
It's hot.
It's cold.
It's cute.
I'm sorry.
It was good.
I won't do it again.
I don't know.
Can you tell me
your name? I'm Kenji.
What about your girlfriend?
She's away from you.
That's good.
How did you get to know each other?
He was a friend of my younger brother.
Is he your younger brother's
classmate? Yes, he is.
That's how you got to know each other.
You are so close.
Do you have a crush
on him? Yes, I do.
I have a crush on him.
Well... I don't
want you to hear it.
I feel like I'm treated like a child rather
than a woman because we are friends.
I see.
I'm away from him.
If you are away from him when
you are 10 years old... I've done it.
What?
What do you think of your boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
He is young.
He has a lot of male friends.
I think he is playing with them.
I don't like it, but I don't play with it.
This is a program called Shirooto Reporter.
You've never seen it,
have you? No, I haven't.
Shirooto Reporter.
You don't know it?
It's a program in which an
amateur goes to a lot of shops,
and gets their feedback
and comments at the end.
I don't want to say anything weird.
I don't expect it.
Do you know about couple kisser?
I don't know in detail.
I've heard only the name.
I don't know the content.
I don't know.
We just enjoy the atmosphere of the place.
You don't have to exchange.
You don't have to do anything special.
That's right.
Visiting ceremony.
A little bit? A little bit.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
I came to this cafe.
What is this?
This is the place.
Is this a place for people who live alone?
Yes, this is the place.
What is the reason?
Because this is a cafe.
I'm a doctor, so I have to
eat, right? No, you don't.
It's a place where you can play.
I think it's a place like that.
It's a little different from my image.
What kind of image do you have?
I don't have such an image.
You don't, do you? I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I'll call you.
Let's try a different way.
Okay.
If you like, you can go to the doctor.
No, I don't want to.
Let's ask him.
You two.
Let's ask him how he feels.
I'm sorry.
The seat over there is big, so
maybe you two can sit over there.
It's okay.
I'm not going to do anything,
but I'm going to sit next to you.
It's okay.
My favorite actress is my girlfriend.
I'm not your girlfriend.
I'm your girlfriend, too.
I think that's the purpose.
This is the best.
Do you want to
touch it? No, no, no.
Sit down.
Why?
Do you want to touch it?
Me?
Do you want to
touch it? This is yours.
I know you don't like it.
It's okay if you don't touch it.
Are you okay?
Let's do it together.
No, I'm fine.
I'll put it on your shoulder.
Wow, it's big.
You should touch it carefully.
You don't know what it is.
It's very elastic.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I can't touch it.
Can I touch you?
Do you want to touch
this side? No, it's OK.
How do you feel sitting here?
I feel comfortable.
Do you feel comfortable?
How about you?
I feel comfortable.
This is the place.
Good morning.
Let's get up.
No, no, no.
It's OK.
Sutan.
No, no, no.
Yes.
She is also like a type.
She is angry.
She is throwing her right hand.
She wants to go.
I'm not throwing her.
No, no, no.
I'll try it.
Don't do that.
Don't care about me.
I'm not doing it because I'm tired.
The excuse.
What is that?
Wow!
I couldn't see it.
It's a sardine.
It means it's very popular today.
Yes, it is.
It's a sardine.
It's easy to use.
Don't look at me. I'm doing it by myself.
Did you see that?
Do you know that?
She is wearing a tight-fitting clothes.
Yes, she is.
It's different from a striped shirt.
Then, I'll wear a suit.
Then, I'll wear a jacket.
I'll wear a jacket.
It's hard, isn't it?
You're a normal person.
You don't usually do
this, do you? No, I don't.
How is it? It's normal.
Is this normal? No, it's not.
I'm sorry.
He is a little stubborn.
He is not good at touching his boobs.
He is good at it.
Please stop.
He is a little docile.
You like that.
You are going to be a new experience.
He is a little tired.
I caught it by myself.
Is it hard? It's hard.
It's hard.
I'm sorry.
Hey, help me.
You're a man.
I can't help you.
Hey, stop it.
There are a lot of people
who don't usually do this.
In fact, I also run a company.
After all, humans are balanced.
I think it's good to have
various experiences.
How is it?
How is it? It's good.
I'm going to cry.
Let's do it.
It's OK.
Can you touch it?
He is touching it.
He is a grown-up.
They seem to be having fun.
No, it's not like that.
It's like this when you put on
a tight suit and move a little.
This is what it looks
like when you open it.
Stop it, please.
Don't put your chest out.
I'm putting it out.
I'm going to borrow Kenji.
No, no.
Please come in.
I'll wash my hands.
Please sit down.
Go to the next room.
She is also a player.
No, no, no.
Is this the place? No, no, no.
No.
Haruka, Haruka, what
are you doing? It looks fun.
Please stop it.
What's wrong with you?
Let's go to the new house.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bye-bye.
Come in here.
No, no, no.
Lick it, lick it.
Let's put our hands on the card.
Do you want to do it?
Put your hands on the card.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can do it like this.
It's small.
It's small, so I'm going to make it bigger.
It's hard when it's a baby.
It's big.
This is good.
It's amazing.
What are you doing? Stop it.
Don't do that.
Don't be peaceful.
Let's have sex in love and peace.
That's right.
Let's end in peace.
No, no, no.
Let me go first.
You just let me go.
Let me talk to you.
I'm going to sleep.
No, no, no.
It's hard, isn't it? Stop it.
Because the size is different.
How do you feel to be seen by such a woman?
In the hot gaze of a woman.
Scary.
I'm scared.
I told you I'm scared.
Stop it.
It's hard, isn't it?
But it feels good.
It's not fun.
It's different.
I made him laugh.
That was my aim.
Is that so?
This is my hobby.
What are you doing?
She is shaking her head.
I want you to touch her.
Then, I will touch her boobs.
What are you doing?
You are not injured, are you?
I've never touched a girl.
How can you touch her?
I've never touched her.
Her legs are not bad.
What's wrong?
What's this?
You are not injured.
It's not dirty.
It's difficult.
I can't hide it.
What does it look like from behind?
I want to see it.
Light on.
It's made of aluminum.
It's open.
I was surprised.
You were surprised?
You didn't look at the
boobs, did you? Oh, it's soft.
You don't have a daily
life, do you? No, I don't.
life, do you? He is cute.
He feels good.
He is provoking.
He is sleeping.
Let's sleep here.
Let's sleep side by side.
At the end, I was able to see a baby
who had been crying since a while ago.
I think this baby was
the first baby I've seen.
I was able to see a baby in a new home.
This is the first time for me.
Good morning.
These two are the oldest.
What are you doing?
Are you crying? Yes, I am.
I'm sorry.
She is crying.
It's terrible.
It's really terrible.
It's embarrassing.
Do you remember this?
Let's hug together.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How many times are you saying it?
Are you looking at it?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I was surprised.
Look, look.
Can you see that?
Wow, there are a lot of coins.
A lot.
Did you feel good?
Did you feel good? I felt good.
I was surprised.
Oh, really?
Do you like this scene?
You can wear it again.
It's funny.
It's funny, isn't it?
It's funnier than I thought.
I'm addicted to it.
You're addicted to it.
Was it your first time today?
Was it your first time?
Yes, it was my first time.
Did you have fun in front of people?
It was fun, wasn't it?
At first, I was a little surprised.
Everyone is like that.
But it was fun.
Really?
And there were beautiful ladies.
Was it fun to be
complimented? It was fun.
That's what she said.
It was good, wasn't it?
It seems that Kano-san was satisfied.
It's fun.
It's not fun.
What are you doing?
It was delicious.
You two don't have the same values, do you?
Do you keep this relationship?
If you come here, you
can play with many people.
If I stay here, I'll go out.
That's right.
Do you want to do that?
If you don't have the
same values, I don't care.
Can I take a picture of you?
What?
Can I take a
picture of you? Sure.
I'll take a picture of you later.
Please.
If you don't like it, you can go home.
No, thank you.
Can I take a
picture of you? Sure.
I'll take a picture of you later.
Please.
Take it off.
I'll take a picture of you.
I don't think it's good to be so close.
Let's move closer.
How was it today? I was jealous.
You were jealous, weren't you?
You didn't have to come this far.
I want to have a full house.
Do you want a full house?
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
I see.
You're the only one who's not having sex.
Yes.
I'm the only one.
What do you want me to do?
If you do your best today,
I'll give you a reward.
What?
Where do you like to be attacked?
First of all, Kuri-chan.
Oh, you want me to
attack Kuri-chan right away?
No, not right away.
Not right away?
From here?
Yes, from the neck.
I don't know.
Open your mouth.
Where do you want me to lick?
Where do you want
me to lick? Tell me.
Where do you want me to lick?
Where? I don't know.
I don't know.
Don't turn around.
I don't know how to turn around.
I don't know.
Like this.
Put your feet together.
OK.
Where? Look.
There?
Yes.
How should I sit there?
How should I sit
there? How? Like this.
Here.
Is it okay here?
Yes.
Like this?
It's better if the stimulation is strong.
Is it weak and strong now?
It's just right.
Like this?
Yes.
It's getting a lot.
What are you going
to say? You said it.
You said it 9 times, didn't you?
How many times did you say it?
3 times? 3 times.
9 times? 4 times.
You said it 4 times, didn't you?
Tell me the answer.
Somehow.
Somehow?
Can I roll over?
Yes.
Your chest is very big.
Can I roll over your back?
Back?
Yes.
Your hair is very long.
Is that so?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
It's very round.
Can you lie on your back?
Turn your butt this way.
I'm sorry for the baby's crying.
You are good at lying on your back.
You are so cute.
Look at me.
Do you feel good?
Oh, you are going to cry.
Oh, no!
This side is painful, too.
Let me see your tongue.
Oh, it came out a lot.
Are you satisfied now?
Yes.
Really?
Do you want me to touch you?