It was delicious.
It was amazing.
It was my first time to
eat a proper course meal.
I was nervous.
Me, too.
Was the table manner OK?
I may have made a mistake, but it was OK.
I see. It was delicious.
Thank you for today.
It's been a year since we started dating.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm not used to this look.
What?
Don't I look good?
No.
You look great.
Really?
You look beautiful today.
You look more mature than usual.
You don't usually say that.
It's a little hot.
Is it hot? It's cute.
Is your necktie bent?
It's a little bent.
I'm really happy.
It's embarrassing.
It's a little embarrassing, isn't it?
You dropped something.
What's that?
Actually, I was going to give
it to you while we were eating.
But I didn't have the courage to do so.
Oh, sorry.
Please marry me.
Wow, really?
I've never thought about it.
Really?
Yes.
Does it mean yes?
Really? Of course.
That's great.
I was worried about what I
would do if you turned me down.
Were you that worried?
Yes.
I would never turn you down.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
I see.
I think it's the right size.
Isn't it too big? It's perfect.
That's great.
Thank you so much.
I was surprised that you
were able to adjust your size.
I'm so happy.
I was so surprised.
I'm glad.
I was worried about you.
But I've been thinking
about it a lot lately.
Really?
I thought it was a little strange.
I was a little nervous
before, but I thought it
was because it was a
restaurant I wasn't used to.
I'm so happy.
My dream was to get married.
Really?
Do you want to have a
wedding ceremony? Of course.
I wanted to wear a dress.
It will definitely suit you.
Really?
I've gained weight recently,
so I have to lose weight.
You are beautiful as you are now.
No, I can't show it to you.
I see. You are beautiful at all.
Will you go on a diet
with me? Of course.
Really?
Let's do our best together.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to see your dress soon.
Really?
Will you choose with me?
Yes, if it's okay with me.
Yay!
You say embarrassing things.
I promised not to do
it until we get married.
I made a promise to you,
but I don't want to break it now.
But let's break it.
I've kept my promise so far.
Let's get married a lot.
OK.
I'll keep my promise until then.
I don't know if I can do it.
I don't know.
Then you have to report to your father.
Oh, I see.
Are you okay?
When I went to say hello to my
father and mother the other day,
my father was looking
at me with a scary face.
I didn't get angry, but
I was trying, wasn't I?
After that, didn't your father
say anything about me?
He said you were a good person.
Really? Oh, that would have been nice.
But this time it's a report that you're
getting married, so are you nervous?
No, I'm really nervous.
I'm so nervous.
I'm afraid I'll get hit.
My dad used to…
But I've never seen you get hit.
Don't worry.
I see.
I'm so nervous.
Don't worry.
We're going alone.
I'll do my best.
Yes.
I'm nervous.
Why are you nervous?
Because I've never
been to a place like this.
But you said you would
work hard on your diet with me.
Well, that's right.
But I don't want to leave you.
That's right.
I don't want to leave such a person.
Am I okay?
No, you're fine.
Oh, really?
What are you worried about?
No, no, I don't know anything.
Excuse me.
Thank you for coming to the concert today.
Is the cost decided immediately?
Yes.
I'd like to prepare for the wedding.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
How long do you plan to hold
the wedding? In half a year.
In half a year?
Yes.
Then, we will do our best to hold
a wonderful wedding in half a year.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Do you have a course?
How many courses
are there? I see.
There is a wedding course, but I
recommend you to have a full body massage.
Then, I will do a full body massage.
I see.
Is there anything you are worried about?
I am worried about my back.
So, I would like to have
a full body massage.
I'm going to have a check-up.
Oh, I see.
I'll have a check-up on your back.
I see.
I'm going to go now.
See you later.
Do you have any
allergies? No, I'm fine.
Oh, you don't have any allergies.
No, I don't.
I see.
There are so many menus.
Would you like to
have a look? Sure.
I've never been to a hair salon
before, so I don't know much about it.
Have you been to a hair salon before?
It's been a while.
I haven't been to a hair salon
recently, so I don't know much about it.
I think a lot of things
have changed, so if you
don't mind, could you
write it down in detail? I see.
I just need to write down the reason.
Oh, I see.
You can skip the parts
you don't understand.
I see.
I'm going to prepare a drink.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's like a herb.
Yes, it is.
It's more effective when the body warms up.
I see.
It's a strange taste.
Yes, it is.
It's a little warm.
Where did you meet?
When I was a student, I
was in the same class as you.
I see.
Did you date each other
when you were a student?
No, I dated him after I
became a member of the board.
It's been a year.
It's been exactly a year.
It's good that you know each other well.
No, I don't.
I've learned a lot from dating.
I see.
Did you propose
to her? Yes, I did.
I envy you.
It's not a big deal.
I'm glad to hear that.
What attracted you to her?
She is kind and beautiful.
And she is good at cooking.
We get along well.
She is cute.
We get along well because we live together.
If we are not on good terms,
we don't come together.
That's right.
Do you have any other questions?
I don't have any.
Do you have any concerns?
This is my first time to come here.
Is it okay?
On the contrary, do you have any concerns?
Q. Do you have any advice for
people who have a hard time breathing?
A. I recommend you to hold
your breath even if it hurts.
Q. Do you have any advice for
people who have a hard time breathing?
A. I recommend you to hold
your breath even if it hurts.
Q. Do you have any advice for
people who have a hard time breathing?
I'm a little nervous, is that okay?
Why are you so nervous?
Please have a drink.
Thank you.
It warms me up a little.
It's good.
Are you okay? Are you a
little relaxed? Thank you.
My body is getting warmer.
That's good.
I'm going to use oil for the test, so I'd
like you to hold the machine for a moment.
Your husband is very kind.
Yes, he is. I don't know how
to say it, but he's very kind.
He's got a good vibe.
He's calm.
I'm not the type to quarrel
Is he a rich blue? I guess so.
My husband told me so.
But when I got married, I
found out that he was a nice guy.
Really?
Besides, my husband and
Kanna are absolutely fine.
I think he is a nice guy.
But it's a big decision in my life.
I think so, too.
So I'm a little worried.
I think it's okay if
it's just the two of us.
I'll try my best to believe that.
It's a little embarrassing.
I didn't know I'd wear something like this.
I know.
I'm afraid I'll be seen.
I'm wearing it, too.
Really?
Yes.
Isn't it embarrassing?
Didn't you have anything
to wear? No, I didn't.
I have a big butt.
Really?
Yes.
I'm nervous.
Don't worry. You'll fall asleep.
Can I fall asleep? Yes, you can.
I see.
Excuse me.
Are you ready?
Yes.
This way, please.
I'm ready.
Thank you for coming.
I'm going to start the operation.
It feels so good.
It's slow, isn't it? Not at all.
I gained weight.
Really?
Yes.
Do you work out?
I go to the gym on Mondays.
I see.
I envy you because you go to the gym.
Don't you go to the gym?
I don't go to the gym.
I've been to the gym,
but I don't go to the gym.
But if you can keep it like
that, I think it's good at all.
Your skin is
very... It's strange.
It feels like it's well-maintained.
It's getting dry recently.
It's dry, isn't it?
Yes.
It feels great.
Your shoulders are a little stiff.
Yes, they are.
It's very easy to get stiff shoulders.
It's easy to get stiff shoulders
and have a bad posture.
I'm going to increase the pressure here.
First, please sit down.
It feels great.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
Please relax.
The right side is more stiff.
Oh, really?
I'm going to put some pressure on it.
How is it? Does it hurt?
No, it doesn't hurt at all.
It doesn't hurt at all.
It was like a part-time job at first, but
when I realized it, it was a full-time job.
Thank you very much.
There are a lot of women, but
there are also couples like this.
It's okay. Please relax.
Please relax.
It may be hard for men, but
we are women, so please relax.
This area is easy to
get lymphatic circulation.
Just by letting the lymph flow,
you can feel your body lighter.
It feels good when I put it on.
It feels good when you put it on.
Was the wedding six months later?
Yes.
Did you decide on the
wedding dress? Yes, I did.
What kind of design is it?
It's quite simple.
I can see a little bit of a hole in the
back of the neck and the back of the neck.
I see.
I can see a little bit of a hole in the
back of the neck and the back of the neck.
I see.
It's hard for me to do
it, so I'll give it a try.
I'll do it when I get a full score.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm going to start.
It's a strange feeling,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
There is also an expansion effect.
It's getting better.
What is this?
This is a self-healing water.
Oh, I see.
It's like a unique blend.
Oh, it's a little different.
Yes, it's a little special.
Is the pressure okay?
Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Then, let's start using the oil.
When you use the oil,
this part will get in the way.
Yes.
Can you take it off?
I'll leave it here.
This is a mixture of herbal tea and soju.
It's okay. Please relax.
I'm nervous.
I think it's embarrassing.
It's a nice wedding candy.
I'm going to use this.
I'm going to apply the ointment.
It's an important part
because it's connected.
Does it hurt? No, I'm fine.
It's effective.
I'm going to apply the ointment.
It's good to feel that the
oil is soaked into the skin.
Moisturization is also important.
Oil is moisturized, so the skin
looks beautiful when it is moisturized.
The tension also comes back.
I'm going to massage your back.
Excuse me.
Please relax.
Are you okay?
Please sit down.
Is it okay if I sit on your lap?
Yes.
If you don't want to sit,
please raise your legs.
How do you feel?
Please open your legs a little.
It feels so good.
Does it hurt? It feels good.
It's embarrassing to be touched.
I don't think there are
many opportunities like this.
I don't usually get touched.
Raise this leg, please.
Don't raise it too much.
Okay.
I'm going to take out the oil.
How do you feel here?
How do you feel?
I feel very good.
If you press a little harder,
it will be more effective.
What do you do?
Harder?
Yes.
I'm not good at it.
It's okay. If it hurts, please tell me.
I see. Then I'll do it.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Could you wait a moment?
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'd like you to push
the game a little harder.
Could you do that?
OK.
Please relax.
You don't have to be stiff.
It's okay if you don't have any pain.
Please let me know if you feel any pain.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Please raise your legs.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Excuse me for this side.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay.
Please relax.
The pressure point is
not good for your body.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I have a different feeling than usual.
This is a proof that you are relaxed.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I broke something.
It's all right.
I'm going to cut it.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to change my clothes.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
I'm going to use a foil.
Excuse me.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay.
I'm relaxing.
I've already operated on Mr. Kanna.
Yes.
There are a lot of lymph nodes here.
I see.
The blood flow will be
better if you let it out.
Your skin will be beautiful.
I see.
Excuse me.
How is the pressure?
It's just right.
Do you massage
like this? Yes, I do.
I can't relax unless I use
my body, such as massage.
I see.
I put on weight.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Okay.
It's pretty stiff.
Oh, I was told so earlier.
Oh, really?
I'm going to focus on loosening it.
I understand.
Did it hurt?
No, I put my hand in my pants.
Is there anything you want to say?
Well, there is no meaning
if I say it from the top.
Oh, is that so? Directly.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was a little surprised.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Well, it's a common thing.
It's a sign that you are relaxed.
It's all right.
It's all right?
Wait, wait, wait.
It's all right.
It's all right, isn't it?
Yes, it's all right.
It's not good for your body to be stiff.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's pretty stiff, so
I'm going to loosen it.
No, that's a little...
It's okay, it's okay.
Please relax.
No, but... It's relaxing.
I have a girlfriend next
to me, so it's a little...
It's okay, I can't see it.
No, but...
I'm going to loosen it.
I'm going to apply a little more oil.
Do you want more oil?
That's not what I meant.
Wait a minute.
Please relax.
She told me to stop.
It's okay. Just relax.
No, it's a little... It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
It's okay.
It's not a massage,
is it? It's a massage.
It's very stiff, isn't it?
This is strange.
You have to loosen it.
No, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
Please relax.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Please don't do that.
It's all right.
I'll keep it a secret from you.
But...
By the way,
Kanna-san is very relaxed.
What do you mean?
This is a magic mirror.
From the other side, it's a mirror.
You can't see this side.
Do you want to see?
What are you doing?
Are you okay? I'm okay.
I can't see this side.
No, that's not what I mean.
Because...
Please stop.
Please relax.
Please let me stop.
What are you doing?
But I'm relaxing.
What? That's strange.
Relax, relax.
I'm okay.
I'm sorry.
Please don't do that.
Why are you doing this?
It's for your beauty.
No, I mean...
Please don't do that.
It's terrible.
You're getting stiff
while saying such a thing.
Do you do such a thing? It's strange.
But you don't get sick at all while
saying such a thing, do you? No, I don't.
Please relax.
What's wrong?
Do you want to add some oil?
No, it's enough.
Please stop.
You're doing this while
saying such a thing.
You're getting harder and harder.
I don't want to.
I don't want to see her like this.
But you can't see it.
What are you doing?
You don't want to be
seen, do you? No, I don't.
I'm kissing you.
Why are you kissing me?
No way.
That's impossible.
Your skin is very hard.
Are you usually in the middle?
No, I don't do such a thing.
You have a very beautiful face.
You have a very erotic face.
I want you to touch me more and more.
This side feels good, right?
This is the first time I've ever seen
Kana-san in such a costume, and it's amazing.
Kana-san, you look great in that costume.
It's strange. What do you mean?
You look like you're asking for it.
It's not like that.
I would never do such a thing.
Have you ever done
such a thing? No, I haven't.
I would never do such a thing.
No, I would never do such a thing.
Then, please look at me.
What are you talking about?
How relaxed you are.
Please look at me.
Excuse me.
Kanna-san.
How do you feel? It's heavy.
You can lick as much as you want.
Excuse me.
It's amazing.
It's amazing,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
It's getting harder than
before, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Kanna-san, you don't
put up with it so much.
Tetsuya-san, you put up
with it, don't you? No, I don't.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Is it funny?
I can't help laughing at you, Tetsuya-san.
Tetsuya-san...
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to quit?
She's been doing it for a long time.
It's not fair.
You don't have a girlfriend, do you?
Do you always lick her so meanly?
I've never had sex with her.
You haven't had sex?
I decided not to do it until
I die, so I'm taking a break.
But I'm licking the house of
someone other than Tetsuya.
Please don't say that.
It's amazing. It's already full.
While looking at Kanna, think
that you are being licked by Kanna.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my stomach is growling.
You don't want to put up with
it anymore, do you? No, I don't.
If you haven't had sex with your girlfriend
yet, do you want to do it with me?
Wait a minute.
You won't let her do it, will you?
No, it's something we've decided.
It's something you've decided,
but she's betraying you first.
I can't stand it anymore.
Have you ever seen
her boobs? No, I haven't.
Have you seen other people's boobs
since you started dating? No, I haven't.
Why are you taking it off?
It's a waste if I don't
touch other people's boobs.
Don't touch me.
Your breast is being
touched by someone else.
Don't say such a thing.
I have a girlfriend.
But she is with someone else.
What are you doing?
Don't you have sex?
You're doing such a bad
thing, aren't you? Stop it.
What a terrible thing.
You're so afraid of yourself.
No, I'm not.
I'm not that kind of person.
Maybe I did something strange.
Did you do something
to her? No, I didn't.
She always wanted to have a
baby, didn't she? No, I didn't.
She's not that kind of person.
She's a big girl.
She's got a baby in her belly.
Put your hands together like this.
Tetsuya-san, you've been holding
it in for a long time, haven't you?
Make your hands hard.
Please, this time...
You keep saying, please stop, but
you don't let go of your hands at all.
Actually, I wanted to have a
normal relationship with you.
I don't want to have a relationship
with anyone other than my girlfriend.
How long have you
been dating? One year.
One year, right?
You haven't had sex for a year?
No.
Ta-da!
Wait, wait, wait.
You haven't seen this room for a year?
Hey!
You haven't touched or licked here?
I haven't done such a thing.
Oh, well.
Give me your hand.
If I don't drink this water,
Hanna-san won't be satisfied.
What do you mean?
I want to drink more.
I want to vomit more.
I have to vomit.
I'm going to put you in my arms forever.
I love you, Guri.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm not crying, I'm not crying.
No, no, no.
Then, I don't have to
put it in? No, no, no.
If you do that, you'll betray her.
Betray? Then, look.
Who is betraying?
Are you sure?
You may not be able
to have sex from now on.
I'll warm you up.
Are you okay?
Do you feel you are being
licked by another man?
I can't take it anymore.
Please put it in.
May I?
My husband is sleeping over there.
Please put it in.
Okay.
Oh, my.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You are like this.
Even though I am massaging your head.
I'm sorry, but I can't help it.
It's okay, isn't it?
She's a terrible actress.
Why did you do that?
Are you tired?
You say it's terrible, but you're so tired.
I'm a little scared.
Look at my nose.
No, I don't want to see it.
Oh, it's getting harder inside.
Stop, please stop.
Can I stop?
Then, please look at each other.
The one with her and the one inside.
It's like having sex with your
girlfriend, isn't it? No, it's not.
It's like having sex with a girl.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so scared.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Please look at the camera.
Can you see me?
I can see you very well.
Please come closer.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
What do you want
me to do? Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
I'm so excited.
What's wrong? I'm so excited.
You're always lying.
You're so excited.
You said you weren't excited.
There's a lot in there.
Your girlfriend is looking at you a lot.
Please stop it.
Are you going to stop it?
Are you okay?
She is sleeping.
She is shivering inside.
Do you want to be
violent like your girlfriend?
Are you okay?
You have a nasty face.
I can see it well.
You have the same attitude as other people.
Hey!
I'm sorry, my son.
You're such a lovely boy.
No, no, please stop.
You're such a bad boy.
You're happy, aren't you?
You're excited, saying, Stop it.
No, I'm not.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Did you take it out of your stomach?
Let me see your stomach.
You took it out so much.
You have a lot in your stomach.
Excuse me.
Do you have a stomachache?
I'll give you a special massage.
Oh! It feels good.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying in the water.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat in a bath.
I was surprised to see a cat in
a bath for the first time in my life.
I don't know.
It's up to you.
She is very sensitive
to the sound of water.
So she uses a water purifier.
She is a very gentle cat.
She is very gentle when she wakes up.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, my back.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no!
Ah, it felt good.
Would you like to come again?
Yes, I'll come again.
Are you okay?
Are you depressed?
Can you leave her alone?
I can't leave her alone.
Look at this video.
Did you just take this
video? She can't wait.
She's waiting for you.
She is shaking her hips.
She is shaking her hips so much that
she is worried about the hospital bill.
What's wrong with you?
Are you excited to see this video?
Really?
If you do that, your girlfriend
will leave you after marriage.
Shut up! It's our fault.
It's all our fault.
It's not our fault, is it?
It's all because we
don't satisfy your desires.
You shouldn't do that.
Are you okay?
How many times do I
have to do this? I'm sorry.
She's been here all the time.
Slurp! Slurp!
Ah, ah, ah, that's it.
That's it, that's it.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
She might be saying a lot like me, too.
I may not be able to
be satisfied with such
a wrinkled penis because
I had such a penis.
It's hot!
I didn't know her pussy was this hard.
I can't be satisfied with that.
That's right, you have to lick it more.
Hmm!
Ah!
Your left hand is resting.
Hmm!
Oh, my God.
It's intense, isn't it?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
My girlfriend might
be in the back, like this.
You can't satisfy me with that.
I need to make it harder.
You have to make her feel good.
You have to make yourself feel good.
This is the first time
I've ever had a baby, so
I'm a little nervous, but
I'm going to do my best.
Masa-san, are you having sex now?
Are you satisfied with just licking me?
If you want me to say, say it.
If you want me to be depressed, say it.
Oh, my nose.
If I don't put a lot of it in
here, I'll feel like I'm satisfied.
It's not our fault.
No, it's not. It's not our fault.
I'm not satisfied with myself and
Mango, so I have to leave it as it is.
※It is not a sound effect.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm going to sleep.
Oh my god! It's so hard.
I'm so sorry.
I made you so nervous.
I made you cry, didn't I?
Are you satisfied with just one visit?
She's been to so many places.
〔Crying and panting〕
You look good.
〔Laughing〕
You look better than when you came here.
I'm going to bite you.
Your face is going to be bitten.
It's good.
It's good for your body to feel good.
Ah!
I've got so many pimples.
I don't know what to do
with a woman I don't know.
You're such a bad groom,
putting me in such a mess.
What are you going to do?
I think I can still do it.
Can you?
I can still do it, but what should I do?
It's not enough, isn't it?
What are you going
to do? I'm ready.
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
It's hard, isn't it?
You can do such a violent thing.
I'm sorry.
Please pour more.
I've saved up so far.
「」「」
It's hot! It's hot!
It's hot!
You had a lot of fun, didn't you?
I hope you'll bring your girlfriend again.
It's okay if you don't like it.
I'll be waiting for you.
Let's have fun again.
How was it?
ST, how was it? It was good.
Was it good?
Yes.
How was it? I'm glad.
You are glad, aren't
you? Yes, I am.
You will come again.
Really? Yes, anytime.
Shall we go? Yes, let's go.