The food was delicious, wasn't it?
Yes, it was good.
Yes, even the dessert was delicious.
What's the matter? Why don't you sit down?
Ah...
You look a little strange today.
Do I? Yes, you look.
..
What?
Do you have something to say?
No, I don't have anything to say.
Thank you so much for today.
You checked out my shop.
No, it's nothing.
It's all for you.
I can't get used to your suit.
It's cool and nice.
Really?
Yes.
It's fresh and nice.
Are you sure? Yes, I'm sure.
The suit is fresh and nice.
Is it?
Yes, it looks good on you.
I made it for today.
Is that so?
But I don't usually wear it.
It's nice to wear a suit once in a while.
I think so.
But it's a little tight.
What is this?
Please marry me.
Yes.
Are you sure? I'm so happy.
How do I look? You look good.
Do I? It's perfect.
It's just the two
of us, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm glad.
Actually, I wanted to
propose at a restaurant.
But I didn't know the timing.
I'm not used to it.
I'm sorry.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I wish you happiness.
I'll do it.
Oh, right.
I have to give you a wedding.
You said you wanted to do it.
It was my dream to give you a wedding.
Then, let's make it a little flashy.
There are a lot of people.
It doesn't have to be that big, but if you
can wear a wedding dress, that's enough.
I have to go and choose a lot of things.
I've always wanted to wear a wedding dress.
One day I want to show my
husband a beautiful wedding dress.
But in order to do that,
I have to throw it away.
No, not at all.
I don't know why, but I'm a
little worried about your belly.
It's embarrassing,
isn't it? No, it's not.
What?
You have a good body.
It's not like that at all.
No, it's not.
Is that so? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I promised I wouldn't do
that until we got married.
I promised, but I'm fine today.
No, you can't.
You have to keep your promise.
And you should keep your promise
and do it after you get married.
So, you are looking forward to it
until we get married, right? Yes, I am.
Thank you for taking care of me, Ryota.
I love you.
I love you more.
No, I don't.
But I have to go to say
hello to Kana's father.
It's all right.
No, no, no.
Kana's father is scary.
It's all right. He's not that scary.
That's only for Kana.
It's just you, isn't it?
If a stranger like me went there,
I wonder what they would say.
I'm with you, too.
You'll be fine.
Yeah.
I'm sure you'll get what you want.
I think I'll go home.
What?
You said you'd go with me.
Yeah.
Well, I know.
I came all the way here.
This is the menu.
It's written in various languages.
Yes.
It's great.
Excuse me.
Yes.
Hello.
I'm Chibuna, and I'm in charge of today.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Miyashita.
Are you planning to have a
wedding with Estee Lauder? Yes, I am.
I proposed to her the other day.
Thank you so much.
Does Estee Lauder go to your wedding often?
I've been there a few
times, but it's his first time.
Oh, it's his first time.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Don't worry.
It's your first time to
wear a wedding dress.
You must be excited.
Yes.
I want to look beautiful
when I wear a wedding dress.
Have you decided the dress yet?
I'm going to decide it soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
Are you the type to decide
it right before the wedding?
Yes.
I'd like to do a lot of things together.
I'm excited.
I've done a lot of things for the first
time, so I'm excited about a lot of things.
I'm excited.
That's right.
Today, do you have a 90-minute
body care course? Yes, it's okay.
I'd like to have a drink
before the operation.
I've been drinking it for a while,
but if you don't mind, I'd like to try it.
Oh, then I'll try it.
Thank you.
I'll pour it for you.
This drink has a high metabolism
and improves your immunity.
Oh, I see.
It's original.
Is there a place to put it out?
There may be quite a few.
How long have you been dating?
How long have you been
together? About 3 years.
It's like a proposal on an anniversary.
Yes, it is.
How did you start dating?
Originally, our parents were good friends.
We knew each other from childhood.
It's a little hard to
understand, isn't it? Yes, it is.
If you get married, you'll get along
with your family, won't you? That's right.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll go get ready, too.
Yes.
Please wait a moment.
Please come in.
You are very polite.
It seems to be a good shop.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
If you say so, there is no doubt.
I'm looking forward to what
kind of surgery you will have.
I wonder what kind of surgery I will have.
I wonder if I can do it.
You know, about female estheticians,
there was a very beautiful woman.
What?
Come on, Ryota-kun.
No, no, no.
Why are you looking at me?
No, that's not what I mean.
Excuse me.
Thank you for waiting.
This is the original
herb tea from our store.
It has a relaxing effect and a
blood flow improvement effect,
It has a good effect on the
kidneys, so it's good for the kidneys.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
It's good, isn't it?
I don't usually drink herbal tea.
Is it better to drink it all?
Is it better to eat it
like this? That's right.
It's delicious.
I feel like my body is getting warmer.
I feel the same way.
Do you?
I feel like I'm getting taller.
That's amazing.
Wow, that's amazing.
Since you have a chance, I
would like to invite you, Ms. Ryota.
Oh, this way, please.
Here it is.
Thank you very much.
Are you from
Hiroshima? Yes, I am.
What's the matter?
He is a very nice person.
But sometimes I feel like I
don't want to be with him.
Do you feel anxious?
I like it and I want to get
married, but I'm a little worried.
There are a lot of people who
have such worries before marriage.
I see.
It's called marriage blue.
Ah, marriage blue.
I'm not good at it.
I see.
But it's okay.
You'll be confident when you get beautiful.
When you get beautiful,
you'll be more slender.
I see.
Let's get beautiful.
Yes. Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Yes.
Do you want to change your clothes?
I'll show you around.
Yes, please.
This way.
Yes.
You look very nervous.
I'm nervous because it's my
first time to be an esthetician.
I can feel your nervousness.
Excuse me.
I'll show you around.
You changed your clothes, too.
Are you still nervous?
No, it's my first time.
You should relax.
OK.
Take your time.
See you later.
OK.
This way, please.
Let's take a picture.
OK.
I've prepared extra pictures.
Do you have a couple
picture? No, I don't.
It might be difficult to see.
I see.
Could you please turn off the lights?
Shall we start the procedure?
Yes.
I'm going to touch your whole body.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Do you have any particular concern?
My waist, my legs, and my shoulders.
Your whole body?
Yes.
Do you work hard?
How do you feel?
I feel a little stiff.
I see.
Let's check your legs first.
Okay.
Please tell me if it hurts.
How is the pressure? Oh, great.
It's just right.
Do you feel any
pressure? No, I don't.
Your body is getting warmer.
Your body is getting warm, isn't it?
Yes, it's quite warm.
It's the effect of the tea.
It's amazing. It's so quick-drying.
Yes, it is.
Does it tickle? A little.
Please bear with me because it
is easy to accumulate waste here.
Excuse me.
I'll put it on top.
Okay.
Your shoulders are very stiff.
It hurts a little around here.
Are you okay?
Do you want me to
massage it? I'm okay.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
I'm going to sit down
and give you a massage.
Can I sit down?
Yes.
Please make yourself comfortable.
Dresses are decorated.
That's right.
If there is a needle
here, I can't cut it cleanly.
Don't be nervous.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ms.
Tachibana, you're very good at massaging.
Oh, really?
I've never felt so good when
I've been massaging before.
It was a little painful.
I'm glad to hear that.
Since all the muscles here are connected,
can I massage the lower part of the bust?
Yes, please.
Can I take this off?
I'll massage from behind.
Excuse me.
Do you take off your clothes
when you take a bath? Yes, I do.
I'll try not to show you.
Please relax.
Thank you.
I'll start from your armpit.
Does it hurt? No, it's okay.
It feels good.
If you loosen this part, the
position of the bust will be higher.
Oh, I see.
But it's a little embarrassing.
It's okay because you can't see it.
We are both women.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'm a little embarrassed because I'm hot.
It's okay. It's the effect of tea.
There is a hand in the middle.
I'm glad I have this.
It's a little embarrassing
to show this to you.
I've never shown you naked before.
I see.
Ahem.
It's over.
If I massage your back like this,
you will feel better.
Oh, I see.
I'll give you a massage.
Can you stand up?
Is it okay if I massage your head?
Yes.
It's a little embarrassing.
It's okay.
Is it okay if I use a little more force?
Yes.
It's more effective if
you massage with force.
I see.
It feels good here,
doesn't it? Yes, it does.
Can I make it a little
stronger? Yes, please.
Are you okay? Yes, thank you.
It's a good reaction,
isn't it? I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's a proof that it works.
That's right.
Hey, Kana-san.
Yes?
Do you want to feel better?
Yes.
Then I'll put a little more effort into it.
Please do.
Please wait a moment.
Yes.
Yes. What's wrong with me?
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Please answer me.
Yes.
I heard that you want to
be stimulated more strongly.
Is there any problem if
you change to a man?
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Well, this is what you are
doing, so please relax and enjoy.
Yes, I understand.
I'm going to start.
Please.
I'm going to start from the back.
I'm going to start from the front.
Yes.
Please relax.
I can't see from here, so please relax.
Are you okay? I'm okay.
You have a stiff neck.
Is that so?
Your body is shaking.
Are you okay? I'm okay.
I'm going to apply it.
What's the
matter? It's a little.
..
It's easy to get a lump here, too.
Women's fingers can't
be stimulated completely.
It's better to stimulate it properly.
It also has the effect of boosting up.
I see.
Oh, I see.
Can you open your
eyes like this? Yes, I can.
At first, you may feel
a little embarrassed,
but when you go home,
you will be satisfied.
I see.
So, please relax and open your eyes.
Yes.
How about this? It's a lot.
I've done a lot.
You've done a lot, so
I'll give you a little more.
I'll put on some oil to
make it more effective.
Yes.
Excuse me. Could you check the temperature?
Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, too.
Yes.
Please let me know if it hurts.
Okay.
Is it okay if I put
pressure on you? I'm okay.
It seems to be accumulated.
Is that so?
I'm going to speed up a little.
Do you see the needle coming out a little?
Did it come out? It's effective.
I'll continue.
Okay.
I think it's good for the abdomen.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Please open your legs.
This lymph is also easy to accumulate.
I want you to be in a position
where you can flow the lymph.
I would like you to
be in a position that is
easy to flow, so can
you stand up a little?
It's okay if you put your weight on it.
If you hold it down by yourself, it
will be much easier to get the effect.
Is this the position?
How is it?
You have a lot of acupuncture points.
I would like you to stimulate
this part of your nose.
Is that okay?
Yes.
I'll add more acupuncture points here.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Is the pressure okay? I'm fine.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm sorry.
Can I continue? Please.
All right.
I'll stimulate you at the same time.
Excuse me.
It seems that you need a man's
strength, so I will replace you.
Oh, well, I'm in charge
of women's shoulders.
Don't worry about it.
Did you loosen your
back a lot? Well, yes.
It looks good.
I see.
Then, please face up.
Face up?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm going to use the oil.
Is the temperature okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Are you nervous? Yes, I am.
I didn't think I would
be kissed by a woman.
It's okay.
Please relax.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I'm going to massage your lymph nodes.
Does it hurt? No, it doesn't.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Oh, Ryota-san.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
It's just a physiological phenomenon.
But...
I have to loosen here, too.
It's okay.
Please relax.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
I'll massage this side as well.
Are you okay?
I have a headache.
Please stop.
It's okay.
Don't be patient.
Please wait.
How do you feel? It hurts.
Do you want me to press harder?
Do you want to go? Do you
want to go faster? I'm going.
Of course, I'll keep it a secret from you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
This bandage is a magic mirror.
If you remove this bandage,
you can see the surgery of Kana.
Do you want to remove it?
Do you want to see it?
What?
No.
What should I do?
Kanan-sama wanted you to change into a man.
What?
You understand, right?
No...
What do you mean? I'll continue.
Please concentrate on this side, too.
No...
It's already like this.
Do you see it? Here.
Now, I'm going to put this on you.
Did you put it on well?
Look, Kana-san seems
to be feeling it a lot.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a thing.
You're going to have a stomachache.
You've had such a good meal.
Did you become like this
because you ate so much?
You're going to have a stomachache.
She is having a lymphatic stimulation.
You have a weird look.
Can you look in the
mirror? No, I can't.
Can you see yourself in the mirror?
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Are you so worried
about him? No, that's.
..
I'm having so much fun
in a place you don't know.
It's okay.
It's okay to sweat a little.
I'm just doing the same thing.
I'm just doing it.
Kana, I'm just being forced to do it.
Do you really want to check it out?
What do you mean?
Kana, how do you feel?
It was delicious.
You wanted it for a long time, didn't you?
You don't have to think about it.
You've been holding it in for a
long time, haven't you? I'm so sorry.
I've been whining a lot.
Can I do it alone?
How do you feel?
I see that you are excited to
hear other people's whining.
You are also excited, aren't you?
No, no, no, please stop.
How do you feel?
Are you more excited than usual?
No, no, no, I don't know.
We promised not to do
that until we get married.
Is that so?
Of course, you're going to get a headache.
Let's do it.
We'll do it.
Because you're eating so much.
Hello everyone, this is Natchi♡
Let's start from the back of your head.
Your neck is very soft.
It's good.
※This is not a sound effect.
One, two, three, four...
Five, six, seven...
Eight, nine, ten...
I'll stimulate with this.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please don't do that.
Please.
You're enjoying it, aren't you?
You're drooling.
Let's enjoy it, too.
Are you okay? Let me play with you.
You want to sleep, don't you?
You haven't slept for
a long time, have you?
Let's sleep comfortably.
【The sound of Kana's stomach, 】
Hmm, let's do it.
Kana, what are you feeling?
I haven't done it for a long
time, so I'll go right away.
Let's do the same thing.
It's going to break.
I'll do it.
Don't speak.
Ready?
It's getting more and more fun.
Please be honest with yourself.
You wanted to do this, didn't you?
I'll give you a lot.
Do you feel good? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Your nose is amazing.
You are moving by yourself.
How do you feel?
Your back is moving.
Can you stand up?
Can you see this?
This also has a great effect.
Please look at the camera.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're beautiful.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Can you lie down?
I'll put you on the bed.
Excuse me.
Can I put you on the bed?
Are you having so much fun?
I hope you have a lot of fun, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What do you think
of me? I feel sick.
I'm doing the same thing.
I feel sick.
Yeah, this is also a rule, isn't it?
Are you going to sleep?
It's about time.
Are you satisfied?
【Mai】
【Dad】 【Dad】 【Yuki】
【Dad】
I'm going to take a shower.
Do you want to feel better?
You want to feel better,
don't you? Be honest.
What do you want
me to do? Like before.
It's better than taking a
shower, isn't it? It's very hard.
Please pinch my boobs more.
Really?
For example, like this.
Oh, it feels good.
It's a little harder.
It feels good.
Really?
Oh...
Doesn't it feel better now?
Oh... Oh...
Please enjoy the sound of my teeth.
I think it's better if you
put your tongue out more.
It's getting better.
It feels good.
It hurts, baby.
This side, too.
I'm going to do something
you've never done before.
What is it? I can't.
If you can't, I'm going to stop.
I'm going to stop.
Please don't stop.
Please forgive me.
I understand.
What's wrong? I feel good.
Do you feel good?
I feel good when I scratch my neck.
That's good.
ーWhat kind of feeling is this?ー
This is my favorite part of my body.
Oh, I see.
What's wrong?
I've been dumped.
What do you mean?
It's a little rough and sensitive.
It's time to eat it.
What's wrong? Your body is stiff.
I was touched like this and it feels good.
You wanted to feel good, didn't you?
Wow, your stomach is beating.
Kana-san, you have a
little bit of tape on your face.
I'm sorry.
It's a good thing.
I can't stand it.
You can't stand it?
Give me the tape.
Where? In the bag.
Please help me.
I understand.
What position do you want me to put you in?
How do you feel?
Please don't bully me.
I'll put you in if you
tell me the truth again.
I will put it in the box.
Please put the baby in the box from behind.
Then, please stick out your butt.
Do you understand? It's coming in.
Are you satisfied with half of
your body when you grow up?
You have grown up a lot.
Do you feel any pain?
I'm going to go there soon.
What's wrong?
You are going there soon.
You were feeling good, weren't you?
You are taking a rest.
I'm going there soon.
It hurts.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Do you want to stop if it doesn't work?
Have you ever done it by force like this?
Let's put it in.
I'll put your right foot in.
Ah!
I!
C... Ah!
How do you feel? It's.
..
it's hard to breathe...
I can't breathe...
It's so hard...
It hurts, doesn't it?
I...
Can you do this
while RUTO-san is there?
How...
Will you sleep with me until I get married?
Are you sure? Yes, I'm sure.
You can sleep more.
I'll give you more.
What's wrong?
How do you feel? I'm so sorry.
I feel so bad.
I'm sorry.
You are hitting your butt.
Sigh...
Are you coming to
see me again? I will.
What?
Aren't you going to change?
You don't like it?
Do you want me to show
you something interesting?
Something interesting?
What?
He wants to be petted.
It's annoying.
You were doing like this in the bathroom.
Now, Kana-san is tired.
Yes, I'm tired.
Are you okay,
Ryota-san? At this rate.
..
Oh, Ryota-san...
I'm sorry.
You've been holding back.
You've been holding
back, haven't you? I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
Oh, it's so hot.
I can't believe that you're here!
It was great to see you!
I'm so happy to see you!
、、、
Are you done? Yes, I am.
I am so glad you are okay.
Your stomach is making me feel bad.
I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
I feel really good.
〔I'm so sorry.
〕 〔Let me drink a lot of water.
〕 〔I'm so sorry.
〕 Why did mom's face turn red?
Why did she turn pale all of a sudden?
Oh, it's so soft.
Oh, it feels so good.
I'm so sleepy.
I moved a lot.
I'm so happy.
I'm so sleepy.
I've never made you
cry, but you made me cry.
Did you sleep
well? It feels good.
It's intense.
O挺我們 Our The
The
The The The The The Ooooooop!
Ooooooooop! Hahaha.
That's so pervert to be
big chubby all the time.
Luuuuurp!
I can't believe I put in so much juice.
I'm sorry.
I watch the Youtube videos.
I eat green tea.
I eat snack.
I have a girlfriend.
She is eating the noodles.
However, my girlfriend is
on the other side of the floor.
I watch the videos.
I'm so nervous.
What kind of nerve do you
have, you pervert? I'm sorry.
She's.
..
She's...
That's right.
It's her fault, isn't it?
Yes.
Today, I'm going to show you how to
make the most delicious ramen in the world.
Oh, I'm so scared.
Oh, my stomach is growling.
Hey, what's going on, Kana-chan?
Mom, what do you want to do?
What's wrong
with you? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong
with you? I'm sorry.
I should have brought you to the bathroom.
My baby, how do you feel?
Do you feel good?
I know you feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
You were humming and when I
You were humming and when I fell
Kana-san, you were out
of breath, weren't you?
Let me out of breath, too.
It feels good.
It's the best.
Oh, it's the best.
Are you going to give me a massage?
Oh- Oh- Oh- Oh- A-
Oh-
Oh- It's very good.
Oh- Oh- Oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh a 20 Yeah.
Oh, it feels so good.
Ahhhh!
Oh!
What's wrong?
Oh, it feels good.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
I am exhausted.
Ah... ah... ah...vrooom...
Hey, I can hear you.
Touch my bean curds.
Help me!
Oh my god! Oh, it's heavy.
Mr. Tachibana, will you go out with me?
What?
I don't want to.
Why?
I have a girlfriend, but I can't go out
with someone who does such a thing.
There is no reason to refuse.
I refuse.
Oh, my...
All right, all right.
It's like...
The staff is waiting for me here.