I just let it go.
I see.
So I might have been hit on the shoulder or the waist.
Could you please look forward a little?
Yes.
Thank you.
If it hurts, please tell me.
I'm going to stretch it out a little bit.
I'm going to shake it a little bit.
It's warm, but don't you feel uncomfortable?
Yes, it's okay.
I'm going to stretch it.
It's nice and warm.
Your body gets warm when it's cold.
Yes.
Your body is very beautiful, but do you do any exercise?
Exercise? Thank you.
I don't do much, but sometimes I go to the gym.
It's hard to keep going to the gym, isn't it?
That's right.
Just a little bit.
How often do you usually massage?
I've started to get addicted recently.
It's about three times a week.
Oh, so there are various types of tampons.
I'll try it.
I wish I could find a place to put it in.
I'd like you to repeat it.
It feels great.
Thank you very much.
I'd like you to open your legs a little.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I think this massage is good.
Don't you feel uncomfortable?
No, it's my first time.
It's a body massage.
Just like this.
Let's move on to the other side.
I'm going to run my heart through all the clogged parts.
It's solidified.
I guess it's going to be like that if I don't walk.
We've been living the same life for a long time.
Excuse me.
Your buttocks are very stiff.
Is it possible for you to dress up as Yotsunbai?
Yotsunbai?
Please wait a moment. I'll fix the plan.
Oh, sorry.
Thank you very much.
Please.
Yes.
Yotsunbai.
Normally.
You can lower it as it is.
Oh, yes.
Excuse me.
Yes, please.
It's a warm oil. What do you think?
It feels like it's getting warmer.
It's good. I have a cold.
It feels like it's working.
Then I will stretch it a little.
There is a little clogging here, so I will loosen it a little.
It's a little ticklish.
It's a place where lymph nodes are gathered, so it may tickle.
I'm sorry, I moved.
It's okay.
Yes, thank you.
Then, shall we go straight to Aomuke?
Aomuke.
Yes.
By the way,
Now, in the rotation campaign,
You can perform surgery while applying steam to your face.
How is it?
Steam?
Yes.
You can perform surgery while experiencing the aroma of the aroma.
Oh, I'd like to try it.
May I?
I think you'll fall asleep soon.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, is it because it's warm?
This is the scent of herbs I'm using this time.
Oh, it's a nice scent.
I'll use it as it is.
Yes.
It's sweet and my favorite scent.
Oh, really?
If the steam is too strong, please tell me.
Yes
I think it will gradually hit
I will continue to use the oil
Please
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
It's a little painful, isn't it?
I'm going to loosen it a little.
Yes.
The steam is coming out.
How is the scent?
It's amazing.
It's a good scent.
It smells really good.
It's warm, too.
I see.
Please relax as it is.
I'm going to change the massage a little and do it from the chest again.
Yes.
It's a little gentle massage, so please relax.
Is it a little hot in the room?
I think it's okay because it's just a massage that makes your skin better.
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to relax, but my skin feels very sensitive, so if you have any problems, please let me know.
I understand.
Your back is moving. Are you okay?
Are you ok?
Yes.
Does it tickle?
Please take a deep breath.
Yes.
Breathe in and out.
I'm going to massage the lymph nodes.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm going to massage the lymph nodes.
How is it to be touched with your fingertips?
Please take a deep breath.
I'll press a little harder.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to massage your other side as well.
I think your body is going to get hot right now.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Massage?
I'm not trying to do it.
I...
I'll take it off because it's dirty
Please tell me if it's noisy
What's wrong?
Is it better to massage here?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Let's rest a little longer.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to cry.
You're the one who gets the coldest of the coldest.
That's why I'm holding you.
I'm sorry.
Ah...
Is it a little hard?
Oh, that's right.
You are busy with your work.
I'm going to do it all over your face, so can you turn your face to the side?
I use facial steamer to moisturize my face.
I think it will be more effective if you rub it.
OK.
I'm going to massage your lymph nodes.
I'm going to open your back a little.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't know you could do this.
You know, I'm not a good person.
I'm sorry.
Ah
Do you often go to places like this?
No, I don't really go to places like this.
Really?
So this time you happened to choose our store.
Yes, I saw it on the flyer.
Oh, thank you. It's a new store, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
It's free right now, so you can get it done for free.
That's nice, Tomomi.
I hope you can use this opportunity and experience it.
If you like it, you can visit us.
I hope you like it.
Excuse me.
Have you ever used aroma oil?
No, I haven't.
Yes.
This is the store.
I use the original special aroma oil.
Oh.
Facial steamer.
Yes.
It has a facial effect.
Oh.
I use the aroma oil on the facial steamer.
Thank you very much.
I also try that.
Oh.
Is it free?
Yes, of course.
We can do it in a special way, so if you're interested, I'd like to try it.
I see. I'll prepare that as well.
Yes.
It's a cold wound, isn't it?
I'm going to do the other side as well.
It's easy to get cold even if you do it like this.
It has a good smell. It has a relaxing effect and a beauty effect.
If you take a deep breath and breathe in, you will be able to feel it better.
It does have a good smell.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to massage your head.
It's very effective.
The other side.
Hmm
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no!
Yes, it was written that it was free.
Please try it.
If you like it, I think you can go home.
I'm going to massage your whole face.
Okay.
Would you like me to massage your face?
I'm going to massage your whole face.
Okay.
Do you want me to massage your face like this?
Yes.
I'm going to massage your whole face.
I'm going to apply it to the whole face.
Is there any part of your body that you are interested in?
I'm interested in the whole body.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask me.
Please listen carefully.
How about it?
Is it expensive?
It's free.
I see.
Please.
I'm going to get ready.
Please tell me if it was hot.
Oh, yes, I got it.
Yes, I do.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
I think you can do it, so please give it a try.
This is the end of the video.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
...
Ah...
Ugh!
...
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Oh!
A-ah-ah-ah-ah...
Ah!
Ah...
oh
ah
Ah!
No, no, no, no, no, no.