I'm going to make dinner.
Oh, yeah.
I'll talk to you a little more.
Do you want to talk?
I want to talk.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to talk?
Yes.
You're always so sweet.
When I talk to you, I feel so calm.
Really?
Yes.
Okay, just a little more.
Just a little more.
What are you going to make for dinner today?
What do you want?
Can I make omelette?
Yes.
Your omelette is delicious, so it's okay.
It's just omelette.
I want to eat fried eggs and rice.
You want to eat rice, too?
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat vegetables, too.
You want to eat vegetables, too?
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat shoronpo.
I want to make a shoronpo.
Please make it.
Let's make it together.
Okay.
While reading books.
Let's make it together.
Shoronpo is a condom.
I didn't buy any materials today.
Let's make it together.
Wait a minute.
Let's spend more time together.
Tsuyoshi, you haven't changed at all.
Are you a good boy?
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm sorry.
Tsuyoshi?
It's morning.
Come here.
Are you up?
I'll be late. I have dinner.
Eat dinner.
Again?
You always come home late, don't you?
Really?
You're so busy with work.
Well, it's cold.
You'll be late if you don't get ready soon.
I'm always alone at night, so I feel lonely.
I want to eat with you.
I think you'll get a job soon, so let's eat together.
I'll be late. Get ready.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Isn't that my sister?
I thought she was working at the same time.
Hey, sis?
Sis...
Where is she going?
・
I'm not sure if it's okay to see it.
It's cool.
It's noisy.
Is it okay to see it?
It's written.
What should I do?
After the operation, she is in a state of trance.
She is in a state of trance.
I can't do it anymore.
Really?
That's enough.
You are so cute.
If I hadn't had sex with you, I would have been a normal girl.
I wouldn't have been able to have sex with you.
It's not good if you don't have a tail.
Ah!
I have a bad feeling.
I am afraid.
I have a very bad feeling.
Why are you crying?
I am scared.
Can you feel my pain?
Are you okay?
It's okay, it's okay.
What are you doing, Rin-chan?
I...
Onee-chan.
What are you doing?
Higashante.
Hey, Neneko, wake up.
Wake up.
Neneko.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
I'm going home.
Is he your younger brother?
He knows you well.
Take him home.
Sigh.
No no no, it's fine.
That's fine.
Yes.
Sigh.
Miya-chan.
Miya-chan, stop it.
Stop it.
You're not going to stop.
Hey.
Miya-chan.
Stop it.
You're so pretty.
Stop it, Miya-chan.
No, don't do that.
You'll get hurt.
Are you really going to do it?
I'm going to hit you.
No, don't do that.
She's coming out.
Don't do that.
Don't do it.
It's hard.
Stop it.
You'll feel it when you're hit.
Give it a few shots.
Oh, no.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come on!
Ah!
Uh!
Oh!
Ah!
Oh, no!
Oh!
Ouch!
It's okay, it's okay.
What's wrong, Sato?
Hmm?
Well, you know...
Clouds are slowly falling down.
When I see them,
I feel so calm.
That's true.
When I look at them.
It's nice, isn't it?
My heart feels so calm.
That's all.
You feel so calm, too, don't you?
It's annoying, isn't it?
You don't have to do that.
I have to cook.
Let's talk a little more.
You want to eat rice, don't you?
Then...
Can you give me a little massage?
You don't have to do that.
Sure.
Come here.
I won.
You're the tallest, aren't you?
Huh?
You're the tallest.
I mean,
I like you.
I like you the most.
No,
I like you more.
What?
I won't lose.
Yes.
Good boy.
You did well today.
You must be tired.
Let's take a break.
I'm still cooking.
Really?
My mom and I are late for work.
I know.
She'll be back soon.
Right?
Yes.
Just a little more.
It can't be helped.
I wish I could have a peaceful day like this forever.
That's right.
Taka-kun, wake up.
It's morning.
Good morning.
I have to go out.
Wake up.
Eat breakfast.
Thank you.
I'm going to work late tonight.
I'll cook dinner for you, so eat it.
I have a part-time job today, too?
Yeah.
I have to go now.
But I had a part-time job yesterday, too.
I have a lot of part-time jobs, so I'll go.
See you.
I'll get up soon.
Hey, sis.
I'm going. See you.
Wait a minute, sis.
Let's leave her alone.
She's been busy lately.
I'm not a good person at all.
Sister?
I don't think it's the right way to work.
I'm going to take a walk in front of the station.
What's on the 8th floor?
It's different from the white site here.
What the hell am I doing?
What?
What is this place?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I want to go home.
I'm tired.
I was so scared.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I have no voice.
I'll keep singing and dancing.
It's not like that.
I don't think so.
It looks like this.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Hey, hey.
Go home.
No, no.
Hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
What do you want me to do?
This is the only way to think.
Hey, sis.
You want this, right?
Sis.
Come on, come on.
Hey, it's me.
Sis.
Hey.
Hey, sis.
I won't move.
If you want, you can do it by yourself.
Hey, hey.
No, no, no.
Calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
I'm looking forward to it.
You can do whatever you want.
I don't know what to do.
Don't shout.
Be quiet!
Let's go home.
Let's get up and go home.
What are you doing?
Are you serious?
I told you not to do that.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't know.
I'll...
I'll take care of it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
No!
I can't do it!
It's delicious.
I don't want to die...
Is he new?
No.
He's younger than me.
Seriously?
I'm going to touch him.
Stop it.
This guy is dangerous.
He's going to fall.
He's a friend.
Big sis.
I'm not your big sister, but I'm your big brother.
We're brothers no matter what you do.
I'm looking for you, but I'm your big brother.
You can do it!
Are you going to bed soon?
I think I'll go if I stay a little longer.
Be careful.
I can't eat anymore.
Really?
I already ate.
You can't eat anymore.
I can't eat this much.
I can't wait anymore.
Is your time okay?
It's still okay.
It's okay.
Oh, that's right.
Today too.
I'm full.
I'm hungry.
Oh, really?
Good luck.
Thank you.
What about dinner?
I don't need it.
Really?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Have you eaten?
Yeah.
You've been working hard lately.
You're not late for work.
Yeah.
That's what I'm sorry about.
Did you get a boyfriend?
What?
What are you talking about?
I can't get a boyfriend.
What?
I can't.
You're mean.
No, I mean, you know...
It costs a lot of money to buy clothes.
Yeah, that's right.
It's a waste of money.
You know, you've been wearing a lot of hair lately.
You're not really like that, are you?
What? No, I'm not.
You look so pretty.
You're not weird.
No, I'm not.
You really like me, don't you?
You don't need a boyfriend, do you?
What?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
Why?
You really don't have one?
I'm pretty, aren't I?
I'm fashionable.
I see.
All the girls are fashionable.
You can be one of them.
Yeah.
You're so pretty.
You don't have to be more beautiful.
Even when you go to college,
There must be a lot of weirdos.
That's not true.
It's okay.
I'm not worried about my mom.
I really like you.
I'm a good old man.
I'm worried about you even though you're so cute.
I'm worried about my mom.
But it's okay.
Isn't that too much?
That's not true.
I don't want to be a loser.
Why?
I don't want to spend money.
I've been chosen by the last place.
Not a card?
I want to get a body line.
No, I don't want to show that.
You're too good.
I know, right?
Because...
I don't have a boyfriend.
Then, what about you?
I don't want a girlfriend.
You don't want me?
It's good to have you.
You really like me, don't you?
Of course I do.
You're a good person.
You're right.
You don't have to have someone you like.
No, I don't.
Do you have someone you like?
I don't know.
I might be able to.
You're wearing glasses like you used to.
Why did you wear contacts?
Your glasses were so cute.
I have to go now.
I have to go too.
I have to go.
I'll be free next Sunday.
Let's go together.
I'll go first.
See you later.
It looks so delicious.
Of course she likes you more than her siblings.
Maybe she thinks too much.
Why is he here?
Where is he going?
I'm hungry.
Open the door.
Is he my boyfriend?
No, he's not.
No way.
I'm curious.
What is he doing?
I'll wait.
I wonder what he's doing in his stomach.
I'm curious.
I'm worried about her.
Se-chan...
Is she in there?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
I'm trying to do something.
I'm sorry.
Let's go back.
More.
It's hot.
You're not done yet.
Hey, come on.
I'm not done!
You're sweating.
I'm not done yet.
Are you okay?
What do you want?
I want to die!
She's laughing.
You can do it!
You're mad at me, aren't you?
It's cold.
What are you doing?
What?
Why are you touching yourself?
I'm sorry.
You are in trouble.
My legs are painful.
You are not in pain.
I'm sorry.
More! More!
Hurry! Hurry!
Are you OK?
More!
Do you want more?
You need to give me more.
Give me more.
Stop it.
Who are you?
Let's go home.
Are you okay?
Let me go.
You said sister.
Yes.
Sister.
Let me go.
You are younger than me.
Sister.
Look.
I got a new Chimpo.
What are you doing?
Look.
Chimpo.
Sister.
I'm Kota.
You're addicted to Chimpo, aren't you?
Stop it, sis.
I'm your little brother.
You're amazing.
Let go of me.
Sis.
She's licking him.
I don't know.
You're addicted to Chimpo.
You're addicted to everything.
I don't understand.
You're licking everyone, aren't you?
No, I'm not licking anyone.
I said I'm not licking anyone.
Why are you standing up?
You're not standing up, are you?
No, I'm not licking anyone.
Oh, that's right.
I'm licking everyone.
You're not licking anyone.
Chikkun, how is Chikkun?
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
No, it's delicious.
It doesn't matter to anyone.
No, it doesn't matter to you.
Mom, if it's Chikkun, it doesn't matter, right?
It doesn't matter to me.
I know.
It doesn't matter to anyone.
No, it doesn't matter to you.
No, no, no.
More, more.
How is it?
You are moving.
I feel bad.
Look at her face.
She is in pain.
I feel bad.
Do it again.
Come on, come on.
Stop it.
I'm still taking pictures.
Don't do that!
What?
What's wrong?
Ichi...
You're out of breath.
I'm so hungry
I want more
You're saying something cool, aren't you?
You're doing it while saying something cool, aren't you?
This is bad.
It feels good.
What is this?
I'm sorry.
You're fine.
I didn't mean to do this.
I can't, I can't do this anymore.
I love you, Na-chan.
Let go of me...
I love you...
I can't. I can't.
Aki. Aki.
Wake up.
I'll be back at 11.
Come on, wake up.
Good morning, sis.
You're not awake.
Let me sleep a little longer.
I'm sleepy.
Why? I have to go out for a bit.
Where are you going?
I have some business to attend to.
What business?
I'm going to meet some friends.
I see.
You came home early.
What?
You always come home late.
I'm worried about you.
It's okay.
Don't worry about me.
We used to go out together on holidays.
You don't do that these days, do you?
What are you talking about?
Let's go again when you calm down.
But I feel lonely.
What? You are so cute.
You love me, don't you?
Stop it.
What?
You are not involved in strange things, are you?
Strange things?
Lately, you've become very beautiful.
Really?
I mean, your clothes...
You've become more fashionable.
Really?
I feel like you're different from usual.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
By the way, I'm making fried rice in the kitchen over there.
You like it, don't you, Aki?
Yeah, I love it.
Get up and have breakfast.
Got it?
I'll be right back.
Are you really leaving?
What do you mean, I'm really leaving?
I'm going. Bye.
Here.
I'll go with you.
Huh? Why is it here?
This way?
I'm sorry.
you can keep this away for another day or two for as long as you want?
You want to keep talking!
Many times, they told her to misuse the service orders, but she didn't for sure.
I changed her relationship with her ex-boyfriend
to move to a lower level.
It worked out great.
What she said was so frequent.
I felt sorry for her that she moved to a lower level.
Wow, that's amazing.
I said I was going too far.
I'm already addicted to it.
It feels really good.
Are you okay?
It's so hard.
Hey, let me do it.
kun
oh
kiss
show your hand
A little more?
Let me see your tears.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Amazing, amazing
Your body is moving so fast
Is it painful?
Ah, it feels good.
Even if it's painful, it feels good.
Hey, don't cry.
Come on.
It's not just you.
But...
Whoever it is,
please just feel free.
You want to lick it that fast?
It's good, isn't it?
How is it? Is it good?
What are you doing?
Oh, no.
Look at me.
You like it, don't you?
Move this side as well.
You're the cutest when you're like this.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
This scent is the cutest.
lol
What's wrong?
You can't stop eating at 3 o'clock.
I'm hungry.
Wanko
I want to sleep.
How many do you want me to sleep?
How many do you want?
I want to sleep.
I'm sorry.
You're so annoying.
I'm sick.
Hurry up.
Are you sure you're okay?
Move it by yourself.
I want to take a closer look at your nails.
Look at me.
Look at my hand.
Look at my wide-open hand.
Yes, yes, yes.
Look at my hand.
Ah!
Is it better to go to the back?
Back, back, back!
Back?
Ah!
What are you doing?
Hey, that's too much.
What are you going to do?
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Hey, are you okay?
What is this?
I'm sorry.
You want to be in that team?
I want to be in that team.
It's hard, isn't it?
Look forward next time.
What are you doing?
I'm listening.
A new girl is coming today, right?
Let's go together.
Come on in.
Look forward.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Hey, hey, hey.
I saw a new person walking around.
I saw him walking around.
Hey, hey, hey.
Who's the new person?
I saw him sitting on the floor.
Hey, hey, hey.
What's going on?
What are you doing?
What are you guys doing here?
We're in the bathroom
It's not like that
We're just sitting in front of the door
And then
We're like
Who's that?
This is my little brother
Your little brother?
Oh, you're brothers?
Really?
What are you guys doing?
Please don't do that.
Hey, sis!
It's hard.
Are you serious?
It's getting harder.
Please don't do that.
It's hard.
It's OK. You're the big sister.
Please don't cry.
You're making a mess.
I'm sorry.
You're the big sister.
Wait.
You're saying big sister.
You're making a mess.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to look over here.
My brother is stiff.
It's too stiff.
No, no, no.
Stop it!
Don't touch her!
What are you doing?
She's mine!
Don't touch her!
Let's make her do it!
Sorry!
That's too much!
Take it off!
This is fun!
Come on!
It's okay!
I've never seen this before!
Take it off!
Look at this!
It's on my shoulder!
No!
Wait a minute!
Stop it!
Hey!
My little brother!
He's sleeping!
Amazing!
He wakes up!
You know,
this woman,
she can sleep with anyone.
Really?
If she's a man, she can sleep with anyone.
Wow!
He's got a shovel!
What do you think of my brother's Chimpo?
It's delicious!
Wow!
You did it, my brother!
Oh my brother!
Don't resist!
Wake him up!
I'll do it for you.
It's good, isn't it?
He's saying, ah.
Damn it.
It's not like you can do anything.
I'm sure of it.
You have a great face.
You can do it.
It's amazing.
I don't know.
Really?
So you don't have any memory.
You don't even realize that it's going to fall off.
Don't drop it.
No?
Why not?
You love it, don't you?
Hold on.
Don't drop it.
What?
I want to put it in your mouth.
Are you okay?
I told you to be patient.
You can put it in your sister's mouth.
I didn't believe it.
I'm scared.
I want to cut it.
I'm still standing.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
I've always wanted to see it.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
I know, right?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Don't be angry!
What's that on your face?
I can see my sister's mark in front of me.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to faint.
What?
I want to do it.
You can do it.
Stop it.
No, don't do it.
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
Don't you know?
You don't know?
I don't know.
Don't you know?
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
No...
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
It's so hard!
I can't do it anymore.
Wait a minute.
You're going to die?
Are you okay?
This is bad.
Ouch!
What is this?
What is it?
I'm scared.
Did you decide it at home?
What are you doing?!
What is it, Tanaka?
Aki, help me.
Aki?
What are you doing?
Aki, what are you doing?
Wait!
Akina!
No!
Wait!
Why?
Akina!
No!
Ah!
Wait!
What are you doing?
Akina!
Hey, wait!
No!
Hey...
What?
Hey!
No, don't do it.
What?
No, no!
What are you doing?
Hey!
Wait a second.
Go away.
Stop.
What are you doing?
No, please.
Hey, don't!
Hey, stop it.
Please stop it.
No, please.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Let go of me!
Stop it!
Come on!
No!
Let me go!
No! Let me go!
No! No!
No!
What are you doing?
Come on, hurry up and cry!
Wait a minute.
Wow.
She's a big sister, so she's a good match.
What do you mean?
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
What do you mean?
Come here.
Hurry up.
It's hot.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.