Good morning, Shin.
Good morning.
I'm sleepy.
What are you doing?
I'm reading a book.
What kind of book? It's a novel.
Is it interesting? Yes, it is.
Can I have a look? Sure.
Why are you studying?
I don't know why.
Why? You don't have to say no.
You are cute.
Let's watch it together.
Let me see.
Together?
Yes.
It doesn't look difficult,
does it? No, it's not.
You like this kind of thing.
Yes.
What's wrong?
What? Are you shy?
It's a little close.
Is it close?
Do you want me to go away?
No, that's not what I mean.
Can I go closer to you?
I'm a little shy.
Are you shy?
What?
You're not running away.
I'm not running away.
You're not, are
you? Come closer.
Good morning.
What are you two doing?
I'm reading a difficult book.
What is this? It's difficult.
It looks boring.
Shuu-kun, are you reading this?
It's interesting, isn't it?
It's interesting.
It's boring.
What is this?
Are you off today?
Yes.
Do you read this on your day off?
I don't have anything to do.
Let's do something more fun.
Let's do something fun.
Let's do something fun together.
We are now brothers and sisters.
Right? Right.
Let's do something fun.
We have such a cute sister.
What's wrong? Nothing.
You are watching too much.
No, I'm not.
You were watching.
She was looking at you.
No, she wasn't.
Do you like boobs?
No, I didn't mean that.
I just happened to look at you.
She was looking at you a lot.
How about this side?
Shu-kun, look at me.
Look at me.
You like my boobs,
don't you? Look at me.
Shu-kun, look at me.
You like this, don't
you? No, I don't.
What? I'm in trouble.
Why are you in trouble?
Why are you staring at me?
You like my butt,
don't you? No, I don't.
You're happy, aren't you?
What do you think?
Which one do you
like? I can't say.
Come here.
I have to study.
Study?
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you
going? Oh, I see.
You did too much in the daytime.
You were too dry.
I had too much boobs.
No, you didn't.
But it was cute.
Yes, it was.
I don't want to tease you.
I know.
I want to tease you so much.
You had a lot of boobs.
Maybe I did too much.
Did you?
Didn't you look at my legs?
Didn't you see my butt?
Isn't it me?
It's definitely me.
I think it's me.
What?
You saw my butt?
Really?
I think I saw it.
I think it's me.
Really? It's me.
No way.
What's up? I'm studying.
I'm studying.
Oh, you're studying.
Do you want me to teach you?
No, no, I can do it.
You can do it?
Yes.
Really?
Didn't you make a mistake here?
What?
Oh, yes, I made a mistake.
Let's see.
This is different,
isn't it? Let's see.
It's been a while since I
saw this, so it's difficult.
This is difficult. How can I do it?
It's difficult to do it as it is.
How can I do it? I don't remember.
It's difficult. How can I do it?
It's a little hot in this room, isn't it?
It's a little hot.
Let's turn on the air conditioner.
I feel like it's really hot.
I feel like I'm going to get sticky.
What's wrong? Are you embarrassed?
No, that's not it.
You were watching.
I haven't seen it.
You haven't seen
it? No, I haven't.
Is that so? You have to study.
I have to study.
It's difficult.
What was it?
Yes, that's right.
I think it's right.
It's difficult.
Can you solve the next question?
Yes, the next one.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right, that's right.
Hm? What's wrong?
No, it's just a little...
Do you have a
stomachache? No, not really.
Hey, are you really okay?
Are you not feeling well?
Do you want me to check on you?
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Do you have a stomachache?
Do you want me to give you a massage?
Are you okay?
Does your stomach hurt
so much? I'll help you.
I'm going.
Are you going?
Your stomach hurts.
What?
What? Wait a minute.
What's wrong? Wait a minute.
Did you take it out by any chance?
What are you doing? Nothing.
Did you wash your
pants? No, I didn't.
It's dirty.
Why is it dirty? Nothing.
My sleeves.
..
What?
What is this?
Did you take a
picture? Let me see.
Let me see.
Why? Did Pekka do something to you?
No, he didn't do anything to me.
That's suspicious.
What did he do to you? Nothing.
Really?
Yes.
You have a hard brain.
No, I don't have a hard brain.
Why do you have a hard brain?
I have to clean your brain.
No, I'm fine. I can do it myself.
But it's dirty, isn't it?
I'll clean it for you.
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Your reaction is cute.
I'll give you more foam.
How is it?
Do you like this?
It's very hard.
I wonder if it's clean.
What?
What's wrong?
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this,
and it's been a while since
I've seen a cat like this.
I'm glad I was able to see
this cat for the first time.
I'm going to clean your ears.
You have a big earwax again.
Do you want me to
clean it? No, it's okay.
You have a big earwax here.
Can I? Yes, you can.
Why?
You gave birth to Rika, but
you don't give birth to me?
Why?
Ah, wait a minute.
I'm hungry.
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Shuu-kun gave me a lot.
Did he?
What?
What do you mean?
I licked him a little, and he came out.
Did you lick him?
Really?
I didn't lick him.
But you were washing your underwear.
I just touched it and took it off.
What? You just touched it and took it off?
Yes, and I licked it.
What?
I just licked it.
But my technique is superior.
But you took it off as soon as I licked it.
It was really hard.
I see.
I didn't look at it.
I guess my technique was great.
No, no, no. I just touched it.
Let's ask Shu-kun.
Shall we?
Which one did you feel
better? Let's ask me.
OK, let's ask.
Hey, Shu-kun.
Shu-kun, listen to me.
Listen to me.
You're up.
Can I sit here?
Hey, which one do you
like more, me or Rika?
Which one?
You just said it, didn't you?
But you said it to me, too.
I just touched you.
But my Ferra felt good,
didn't it? I can't choose.
No, you can't.
But you've been looking
at my boobs all the time.
You want to touch them,
don't you? No, I don't.
What about my boobs?
You were looking at my boobs.
What about this one?
Don't you want to touch it?
Don't you want to
see more? No, I don't.
Do you want to see
more? Look at this.
It's so transparent.
Which one do you
want? Look at this.
I can't choose.
Why not? It's boring.
Do you want to see
more? No, I don't.
Do you want to see more?
Which one do you want to see?
How about this one?
Which one do you like more?
Mine is bigger, isn't it?
You like the one that is not
big, don't you? I can't choose.
What? You can't choose?
Let me touch it and make sure.
Which one do you
like? Both are soft.
like? I like both.
Which one?
Which one? Choose one.
I can't choose.
Which one do you
want? That's right.
Which one do you want?
It's getting bigger.
Why?
You just took it out.
I'm sorry.
Let me see.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me see, let me see.
No, no, no.
Ah!
It's getting bigger.
Oh, no.
Let me see.
It's embarrassing.
Which one do you
like more? I don't know.
You don't know?
Then, choose one.
That's too fast.
I feel good when I wear it.
Which one do you like more?
You can decide this time.
Which one?
Which one feels better?
Both?
The one in my mouth is soft
and feels good, right? No, it's me.
No, it's not.
Hey, you.
You did it again.
You did it so hard and went to the back.
What are you doing?
I want to do it, too.
Hey, you.
Hey, which one do
you like better? I like.
..
Oh, come on!
Oh, come on! I want more.
I want it.
I don't want it.
Give it to me.
Which one do you
like? Choose one.
Which one? Choose one.
Choose one.
You know which one, right?
Which one do you want to
have sex with? I can't decide.
Come on, decide.
Which one do I want to have sex with?
Then, put your life on the line for
the one you want to have sex with.
That's right.
Put your life on the line?
What do you mean?
So, which one do you want to have sex with?
Put your life on the line for the
one you want to have sex with.
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Can I have a cup of coffee?
Yes.
You can have a cup of
coffee, can't you? Yes, I can.
Which one do you want?
What should I do? Tell me.
What should I do?
She wants a snack.
I want you to be excited.
It looks good, doesn't it?
You can put a lot here.
Choose.
Which one? Tell me.
Which one do you like?
Come on, pick one.
Can't you decide?
I can't decide.
It's boring.
You want to pin it here, don't you?
Don't you have to pin it here?
Do you like it?
You have such a big boob.
You want to touch it, don't you?
It must feel good.
If you don't do anything, I'll lick you.
Do you like it?
I want you to lick me.
Look, your nipples are very long.
Aren't you excited to see this?
Do you want to see more?
Do you want more?
More?
Wow, your nipples are so long.
Are you excited?
Hey, look closer.
Then, I'll lick you.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Ahhhhh!
Huh?
Ahhh!
Ahhhhh!
Wow…
Which side of your
neck do you want to lick?
Which one do you want
to choose? This one.
It's my nipple, isn't
it? I can't choose.
You can't?
Why?
Why can't you choose?
How about a kiss? A kiss.
Which one do you want?
Do you want me to show you my phone?
Do you want to see your face?
You want to do like this,
don't you? Look at me.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
※This is the first time
I'm doing this, so I'm
not sure if I'll be
able to do it properly.
【The sound of a cat's sneezing】
Hey, are you sneezing properly?
Hurry up and start sneezing.
Which one do you want to bet on?
Of course, I want to bet on you.
Do you want to bet a lot?
Can I bet on you?
Which one do you
want to bet on? Tell me.
You want to bet on me, don't you?
Which one do you want
to hang it on? Hang it here.
Hang it on my pussy.
Let me touch you like this.
Do you want to get married?
You are so sleepy, Rika.
Himawari is also sleepy.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Shouko, choose me.
Shouko, put a lot of sushi on my coat.
My coat is better,
isn't it? It's my coat.
Hurry up and put it on me.
Put it on me.
Please.
Hurry up.
Oh, my God.
Which one is
yours? Mine is bigger.
Mine is bigger.
Mine is definitely bigger.
Really?
Which one is yours?
Two people? Two people.
Two people?
So, three people?
Let's do it like that.
It can't be helped.
Let's do it with three people.
No, no.
I'm going to give Chikubi a treat.
Chikubi is very good at it.
Do you feel good?
You are so cute.
I want to lick your nipples, too.
Which nipple do
you like? I like both.
You are so cute.
You are really sensitive.
You are very nervous.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Let me do it, too.
Oh, it's big.
Do you feel it, too?
Which one do you feel good?
Which one?
I feel good on this side, too.
This side, too?
Then, this side.
How do you feel?
Which one do you feel good?
Which one do you
feel good? I can't see it.
I can't see it.
How about this side?
Where is it?
This side?
Which one do you like? This one.
Today, I'm going to show you
how to make kimchi fried rice that
my mother-in-law made for me
when I was in elementary school.
First, cut the kimchi into small pieces.
I can't even make a sound.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. It was
hard, wasn't it? Like this.
I'm a little bit nervous.
I'm nervous.
Can I put it in? A little bit.
A little bit?
You should put it in first.
No, Rika will do it.
You like it, don't
you? It's going in.
You put it in.
Why do you put it
in first? It feels good.
Wow, your neck is up.
It feels good.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Oh, that's good.
It feels so good.
Wow.
Do you feel good?
It's better to sleep together.
It's better to sleep here.
I want to sleep here.
No, you don't.
You have to sleep here.
It's not comfortable.
Hey, go away.
No, I don't want to.
I feel good, so I'll go away.
I feel good.
No, don't go there.
I'm sorry.
Let's switch.
No, no, no.
You are wrong.
Why?
You want to put it in my
belly, don't you? No, I don't.
You are cheating.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't do that, Chikurin-chan.
Why?
You'll get cold.
I'm not cold at all.
That's not fair.
Put it in for me too.
Oh, my God! I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
Hey, next it's my turn.
Get out of my way.
I don't want to get up.
Why? It's my turn.
It's finally my turn.
I'm going to put it in.
I want to put it in.
It's hard.
Does it feel good?
My neck hurts.
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't sleep.
Go to sleep.
Oh, it's so good.
Come here.
It's a bit painful, isn't it?
No, it's painful from behind.
It's okay, isn't it?
Oh, it's so good.
Oh, no!
Oh, no! More!
I want more! No, no, no.
No, put it in.
Hey, put it in.
Why?
I told you twice.
Hey, you're not a child anymore.
Hey, you're always like that.
Why?
You're always like that.
That's right, isn't
it? That's right.
That's not fair.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
You have such a small ear.
Do you feel good?
I feel so good.
You like this one,
don't you? Yes, I do.
Here you are, Harami-chan.
Wow!
You just said it, didn't you?
Why?
I said it, but it's not over yet.
You just said it, didn't you?
It's not over yet.
That's not fair.
I like it better.
How do you feel?
Isn't it painful? I'm sorry.
You like my neck,
don't you? I'm sorry.
I'm going to take it off.
It feels good.
I feel sick.
Even if I let Rika go, she
won't change, so I'll let Shuu go.
No, you can't do that.
Because she won't change.
I feel sick.
I can't stand it.
Ouch!
Hey, isn't it too much?
Wow, it's a lot.
Hey, it's too much.
Is there any left for me?
Hey, give me some, too.
You can still stand up?
Yes, I can stand up.
Then, let me help you.
Does it feel good?
Oh, it feels good.
Ah, it feels good.
But it's soft.
Ah, it's soft.
Ah.
Ah, it feels good.
Oh, it's soft, isn't it?
Give me your hands.
You do it.
Help me.
What's wrong? Let's go.
Ouch!
You are doing great.
It's so exciting.
You have a lot of them.
Wow!
You are doing great.
I'm glad you bought it for me.
It's a little too much.
Let's do it again. You can do
more, can't you? Let's drop it.
No, this way.
Why? No, this way.
I don't want to.
Hurry up.
Why? It's too much.
How do you feel? I feel good.
Wow, your tailbone is so hard.
I feel good.
It feels so good.
Put it in my bag.
Why?
It's a good bag, isn't it?
You put a lot of things in it.
It's not fair.
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm going to fail.
It feels good.
I want to see my mom and dad.
Help me!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm so tired.
You're so tired.
I didn't feel good.
That's great.
You two made up.
Which one do you
like more? Choose one.
I can't choose.
Why not?
Let's do it with three of us next time.
At that time, you decide which one.
Make up your mind.
Yes.
Absolutely.
It's a promise.
What?
I want to kiss you.
Why? Good morning.
Good morning.
I'm sleepy.
Dad and Mom left in the morning.
Really?
They said they wouldn't come back today.
Where did you go? Are you
listening to something? I'm sleepy.
Did you have breakfast?
No, I'm still sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
The weather is nice.
What's wrong?
It's better to sit down normally.
No, I'm fine.
I feel good.
It's comfortable.
What should I do
today? Good morning.
Good morning, Kana-chan.
What are you doing? I'm sleepy.
It's just right.
It's not fair.
Masa-san, you try it too.
It's comfortable.
It's good.
I'm sleepy.
I can do it twice.
I want to sit there, too.
No.
My special seat.
What are you going to do today, Tomo-kun?
I'm going to put on my seat belt.
It's dangerous, so I'm
going to put on my seat belt.
Can you put it on for me?
It's heavy, isn't it?
Is it heavy? No, it's not.
It's not heavy.
Let's hang out tomorrow.
You can hang out with me.
What do you want to do?
What do you want to do with me?
A drive-in date.
What's that?
My parents are not home today.
Really?
They're not home.
Don't cry.
Let's do it.
What do you want to do today?
What do you want to do?
Oh, no, I'm going back to my room.
What? Oh, he's gone.
Maybe because he was a little erotic.
Could it be that he's a virgin?
What? With that face?
Isn't it too stimulating?
Really?
Because I touched you.
I touched you, too.
Really?
You couldn't stand my
sexiness, so you ran away.
Because you held my futon.
That's it.
No, no. Because I was
rustling like this, you felt good.
I was rustling, too.
No, it's me.
No, Ayaka is still no good.
Why do you say that?
It's definitely me.
No, no.
Let's do this.
I want to do this, too.
Let me ask you something.
What?
Which one do you prefer?
I'll never tell you.
I don't know.
I'll ask you.
What?
Kana, wait there.
What? Don't get up.
OK.
Wait there.
What are you doing?
What?
Are you studying? What? Show me.
Show me.
Mathematics!
Do you understand it? Show me.
Where did you
do it? Here? I see.
Oh my god.
You may not understand it.
How do you do it? Tell me.
I don't know how to do it.
Put this on here and grab it.
Am I wrong?
What's wrong?
Are you nervous?
You don't have to be nervous.
It's okay. We are brothers.
I'm older than you.
Why are you so nervous?
Your shoulders are so stiff.
I'll loosen your shoulders.
Is this part stiff, too?
Is it stiff?
Are you nervous?
You are very stiff.
What's wrong?
Are you OK?
We are brothers, so let's get along.
You've grown up so much.
I have to loosen you up.
What? Are you okay?
I'll do my best.
I'm fine.
Really? I don't think so.
Do you do this
for me? No, I don't.
You don't? Thank you.
How do you feel?
You seem to feel good.
Here, here.
Shiko-shiko.
It's getting harder and harder.
Great.
Does it feel good here, too?
Yes.
I'll give you a lot more.
No? I'm sorry.
It's OK.
You'll get it out.
I'll make it clean.
I'll wash it for you.
I'm sorry.
It's delicious.
What should I do next?
I wonder if I can do it.
What are you doing?
Oh, wait a minute.
Pants.
Pants are wet.
Did you wash your pants?
Yes.
Why? What? Nothing.
Go on.
What?
Were you washing there?
Yes.
I see.
I'll do it for you.
No, I'm fine.
What?
I'll clean it for you.
My cheek...
It's dirty.
Did you sleep well?
I'm going to clean your ears.
Does it feel good?
Tama-Tama
Why are you laughing? Well.
..
Do you have a runny nose?
You're getting bigger and bigger.
It feels good.
What's wrong with you?
Did Aya do something bad to you?
Bad? That's right.
I see.
I wonder if I can do it.
What did Ayaka
do to you? Nothing.
What?
Something you can't tell me?
Are you clean now? You are big.
Does that mean you are still dirty?
I'm going to clean your mouth.
Don't do that.
Don't you need a
towel? No, I don't.
You're getting used to it.
You're so cute.
〈 Chinese 〉
〈 French 〉
Ah!
Ah…
Oh no, no, no, no.
Hehe
Ah!
Ah! No!
Yeah!
Hehehehe
Wow! You got it out.
Yeah! You're good.
Ah!
Hehehe Oh!
Sorry! I'm sorry.
I let him go.
I see.
He was very fast.
I let him go very quickly.
I was also full of spirit.
I was full of spirit.
I see.
But when I touched his
neck, he seemed to be
in a good mood, so I
think I was more excited.
I took a nap and went to the bathroom.
That's why I went there right away.
I was so excited.
But I think I was definitely faster.
It was really fast.
I went there right away.
That's because it's in the
morning, but I'm going to sleep right
away on the second one, so I'm
more excited about the second one.
No, no, no.
I'm sure you want to be
in a relationship with me.
No, I definitely want to be
I have no choice but to ask.
Let's go to bed.
Please sit down.
Are you ready?
Which one do you want to have sex with?
What?
Which one do you want to
have sex with? I have one.
Choose one.
I was better, wasn't I?
It's me, isn't it? No, no, no.
It's me, isn't it?
Which one do you like better?
You were so excited, weren't you?
Which one? Answer me.
Do you remember my hair?
I can do it, too.
What? Oh, I see.
Do you remember the room in the bathroom?
This room is more comfortable.
Look.
Are you comparing?
I'll put it to your neck.
I'll put it on your chest.
I'll put it on your chest, too.
Look at me.
You were looking at me, weren't you?
You were looking at me
and standing up, weren't you?
You can touch it.
Did you take it off?
You have a good reaction.
It's not good.
It's OK.
You look very good.
You are a dear.
Pinpon-! Hehehe.
Little boy?
Your wrist is so cute.
He's not a pinpon yet.
He's a purring.
Are you happy?
You look so good.
You look sleepy.
You are getting sleepy.
I'm sleepy, too.
Do you like being sleepy?
Do you like it? Good night.
Which one do you feel better?
This one, right?
You're twitching.
I'll pinch you.
It feels better to lick directly.
I'm sorry.
If you lick it, it will be more sticky.
No, I really don't want to lick it.
I can't see it.
Hey, look at me.
Can you hear me?
It's good, isn't it?
Don't laugh so much.
You look like you're in pain.
You're bothering me.
You're so cute.
Are you excited again?
I'll show you something good.
Look at me.
Look at me carefully.
1,2,3,4
Do you like this one?
Which one do you
want to touch? This one.
It's so soft.
You can stand up.
You can touch it a lot and lick it.
You like it, don't you?
Do you want me to rub
your butt? No, I don't.
I see.
It's a luxury.
Do you want me to rub your butt?
Then, I'll show you my front face.
You can rub my butt.
I can see the hole in your butt.
It looks delicious, doesn't it?
Which butt do you like?
Let me touch it.
How is it? It's soft.
It's soft, isn't it?
It's a good butt.
It's good, isn't it? It's soft.
It's a little ticklish.
Really?
Yes.
It's ticklish.
It's soft.
Do you want to touch it?
How is it?
It's like a yellow tickle.
It's good, isn't
it? This tickle.
How is it? It's the same.
Which one do you like more?
I like the left one.
This one.
Oh, this one.
It's stuck.
Look at this, Tomo-kun.
My nipples are stuck.
Your nipples and nipples are stuck.
Is it erotic? It feels good.
Right?
Is it okay? I like you.
It's soft.
It feels good.
My voice is coming out.
What are you doing?
Do you like this? You like it.
Look at me.
I'm sorry if I made you feel uncomfortable.
You look more comfortable than I do.
Really? It feels good.
I want you to stop.
I'm sleepy.
You are beautiful.
You are amazing.
You are cute.
Let's kiss.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm embarrassed.
Do you want to watch it?
Yes, let's watch it together.
Let's watch it together.
She is very serious.
What are you doing?
It's embarrassing.
How do I look? Beautiful.
Beautiful?
What do you want to see?
Do you want me to
lick you? Let's do it.
Watch me.
Wow!
Why are you so good
at it? It feels good.
Because you are older than me.
It feels so good.
It feels so good there.
Wait a minute.
Did you say it? I'll change.
Change?
I'll pet you, too.
Look.
It's a python.
Look, look.
Great.
Here.
Yes, there.
You look like you feel good.
Wow, your tongue is warm.
Wow, my stomach hurts.
It's soft.
It's deep, isn't it?
Here? Yes, here.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You are twitching.
It feels good.
You look like you're in a good mood.
Oh, there.
Wow.
It's getting sunny, isn't it?
Yes.
Your cheeks, too.
Oh, it feels good.
There.
Oh, the tip of my tongue feels good.
I'm sorry.
I don't know if I can do
it, but I'm going to do it.
I can't do it.
I'm going to cry.
Your voice is cracking.
It's gone.
Tomo-kun.
Yes.
You can see both of them
well, can't you? You're all wet.
Tama-kun, which one
do you want to put it in?
Can I put it in?
Both of you are so wet.
It's in there.
You can touch it.
Put your finger in it.
Where does it come
from? It's in there.
It feels good.
I'm surprised.
Both of them feel good.
Tomo-kun's eyes are open.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Tomo-kun's eyes are open.
Oh, it hurts.
Tomoko, doesn't your
finger feel good? It feels good.
It hurts a lot.
It feels good.
Don't do that.
Itch! Oh, it's heavy.
I feel sick.
I feel a little sick.
Oh, it's heavy.
Oh, you are trembling.
I feel sick.
It's heavy.
Itch, do you feel sick?
You are licking me.
Do you feel good? Touch here.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good? Let's go.
You are brave.
No!
I'll open it for you.
No, no, no.
You are too strong.
Don't lose.
Let's go.
Tana-chan, please lick me.
Does it feel so good?
It feels so good.
I can't do it.
You can put on some weight.
I can't stand up.
You can't stand up.
Oh, no!
You lick me well.
Do you want to go?
You went away while licking me.
I'm going to lick you from this side.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You want to be licked, don't you?
It feels good, doesn't
it? I'm so sleepy.
I can't do it.
Let's do it.
I'll do it, too.
I want you to touch me, too.
Where is it? It feels good.
I'm not going to run away.
I don't want to.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
You want to put it in
next, don't you? Well.
..
Which one?
You want to put it in, don't you?
Have you decided which
one you want to put in? Well.
..
Well... What?
Which one? It's OK.
You can't choose? I'm sorry.
I have to make sure it's your sister.
It's unfair.
It's really me.
Look at the place to put it.
I'm going to put it in.
Wow.
Wow, it's so thick.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's nice.
I can see that it's so much in there.
Wow.
It's amazing.
It's good, isn't
it? It feels good.
Do you want to go
home? It feels good.
This side, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Your nipples, too.
Get up.
I can't stop you.
Mei-chan.
Good.
This part is dangerous,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
You look like you feel good.
I feel good, too.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
Do you feel good
inside? Yes, I do.
I feel good, too.
Do you feel good, too?
How do you feel, Tomo-kun?
You shouldn't move, Tomoki-chan.
Oh, no!
Wow, you're twitching.
Don't pull it out.
Oh!
Can you do it? Yes, I can.
Here we go.
Oh!
It's flipped over.
Oh, it's out of the way.
Do you want to try?
OK.
Where is it?
Here? Oh, it's there.
Oh, it's in.
Oh, it feels good.
Look, look.
You can see the inside of the stomach.
You are eating a lot.
You look comfortable.
I want you to touch me, too.
You have a lot of hair.
I want to go home soon.
No.
Why? You should go home soon.
You have a lot of hair.
It feels good.
Touch me more.
OK.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
Your legs are shaking.
It's unfair that you have a lot of hair.
Are you going to do it?
I'm going to do it!
Wow!
You're amazing!
I can't do it anymore.
It feels so good.
I want to go to bed early.
Here.
Are you going to
ride it? It's amazing.
It's amazing.
It's coming in from above.
It looks like it's going
to make a lot of noise.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
Go, go, go.
It feels good.
Go, go, go!
It feels so good.
I want more.
Oh, it feels good.
What were you doing just now?
Did you find out? Yes, I did.
It feels good.
Please lick me a lot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, you feel good, too.
Did you want to be touched, Tama-kun?
Oh, your waist is moving.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I feel so good.
I want to do it.
I'm sorry.
Wow! It's white!
Something came out.
Wow!
Sushi?
It came out!
Did it come out?
Wow!
It came out a
lot! It feels good.
Do you lick it?
Yes.
You're a gentleman.
I'm scared.
You're scary.
Tama-kun, did you take
out your stomach? I'm sorry.
It felt good.
It's painful.
Kana-chan, why don't
you take out your stomach?
Can you still do it?
Can you?
You can, right?
You can still do it, right?
You can do it at all.
Because you have a big belly.
I'm going to put it in.
Hana.
Yes.
Wow.
Wow, it's in.
Move a lot.
It feels good.
It feels good for me, too.
Oh, it's hard.
Does it feel good?
It's getting hard.
It's hard.
It's only tomorrow.
It feels good.
No, it feels good.
It's cut.
It's amazing.
It's growing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Can you see it?
Can you see it? I can see it.
I can see the part where
you have a lot of sweat.
Wow.
I feel so good.
You have a lot of sweat.
I'll go.
You'll go?
I'm going to die!
Your butt is twitching.
I can't do it anymore.
Wow! Do it again.
Do it again.
It feels good.
Oh, no!
Tomoko is moving more and more.
Your face is so cute.
Oh, no!
What should I do?
Is it over? No, not yet.
Stand up.
OK.
Does it feel good?
It feels good! Look at me.
Wow! You are trembling.
Let me hold you.
Wow!
It's so soft!
It's amazing,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
I can see your hands.
Wow!
Really?
It feels so good!
Oh, no! You dropped it.
Can I take it out? Yes, you can.
I took it out, didn't
I? Yes, you did.
You look very comfortable.
Yes, I do.
That's good.
Great.
Wow!
Let me touch your nose.
※She's not crying.
It's ticklish.
It's coming out.
It's very dark. It's pure white.
It's coming out a lot.
It's amazing.
The white one is coming out more and more.
Tomo-kun.
Yes.
Which one is next?
Today, I'm going to do it only for a day
because my mom and dad are not here.
Let's do it once.
Which one do you like next?
I like this one.
Me again?
No.
That's not fair.
I like this one.