May, what time is it now?
Oh, it's a little past 10 o'clock.
Oh, I see.
Well, I wonder if it's okay to close
my eyes a little until Kiyoshi comes.
I got home early this morning.
Yeah, it's okay.
I'll wake you up before the promised time.
I'll wake you up before you get married.
Oh, thank you.
I've been married to my
husband for three years.
Since I got married, my
life has been really peaceful.
My husband is kind and gives me everything.
I have no complaints.
Except for one thing.
Hey.
Did you fall asleep? Hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Hey.
How do you feel today?
It's been a long time.
You mean that?
It's been less than five months.
I'm sorry.
I'm very tired from work.
So, good night.
Hey.
I tried to be brave.
If you don't hug me, I'll go away.
Hey.
Did you sleep? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting for a long time.
I don't know at all recently.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do
when I wake up in the morning.
I don't know what to
do when I watch a video.
Of course, I don't know what
to do when I'm touched by Mei.
But I'm not surprised at all.
I was worried, so I went to the hospital.
Then I got ED.
And the cause is unknown.
I'm getting old, aren't I?
I was told that my role was dangerous.
So, I'm sorry for being silent.
You are still at that age, aren't you?
It's hard for me, too.
If you think so, you can break up with me.
I don't care if you break
up with another man.
I'm really sorry.
What are you talking about?
I can't break up with you.
I like you.
I can't do it.
No one can do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't break up with you.
You can't break up because
you can't do it, can you? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Since that day, I haven't had
any success with my husband.
I'm always alone, so I don't
have a liver to betray my husband.
My husband suddenly woke up and said,
Mei, you're so erotic. Look, I'm standing.
Would you like to do it with me?
I think he might be
excited like that, but I've
been secretly next to
my husband for two years.
It's been a long time, brother.
It's been a long time, sister.
I got a souvenir because I'm lazy.
I don't need that.
Oh, that's right.
Anyway, let's go inside.
Let's drink together.
Hey, Mei, get ready.
Let's have a snack.
It must have been hard for you to move.
No, it wasn't.
Everything was furnished.
Furnished?
I didn't know there was such a thing.
I only have clothes for
short-sleeved clothes.
I see.
It's not so hard to
clean up, is it? Not at all.
Then I can drink a lot.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's helpful.
By the way, is it your
first time to live alone?
Yes.
What are you going to do with the rice?
I'm going to eat out.
And I'm going to stay
over at my brother's house.
Hey, hey, hey.
You can stay over at my brother's house.
The handmade rice is very delicious.
Oh, stop it.
You're not even standing up.
Let's have a drink together.
Cheers!
I'm so happy to drink this.
By the way, how is your work going?
It's going well.
Really?
Are you alright? I'm fine.
It wasn't that dangerous.
I thought so.
How is your company?
How is your private
life? I don't know.
I think you should get used to it.
Isn't it too soon?
I don't think so.
You've been married for a long time.
Yes, I have.
But you have a good family.
It's good, isn't
it? I'm jealous.
Here you are, Aiki.
It's hot.
It's heavy.
Are you all right?
I think I drank too much.
You drank too much.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Wake me up in an hour.
I'm sorry.
I'll take a break for an hour.
Are you going to sleep?
I'll take a little break.
Really?
I'm not going to sleep.
I'm counting on you.
I understand.
I fell asleep.
Can I still stay here? It's OK.
You can think this is your home.
I'm sorry.
Weren't you worried when you came to
Tokyo all of a sudden from your hometown?
I was very worried.
But my brother and his wife
were there, so I was worried.
You were so eager to be spoiled.
I'm sorry.
If it bothers you, I'll
do it at a good distance.
No, it's okay.
You left a girlfriend in
your hometown, didn't you?
Are you okay with that?
What? No, I don't have a girlfriend.
What? Did my brother say that?
What? You don't have a girlfriend?
Kouji says he has a girlfriend.
Nice, nice, nice.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
How is your life as a couple?
You're living far away from
your parents, aren't you? It's fun.
Koji-san is cute like a child.
And he is very kind. I'm spoiled.
I see.
I'm relieved.
Don't you have any
children? Oh, I'm sorry.
Well.
..
Should I say it?
Kiyoshi-kun, are you
sure you won't tell anyone?
Yes.
Kouji-san, since 2 years ago,
you suddenly became ED.
Somehow,
at that time, you gave
up, didn't you? I'm sorry.
But why did you ask me that?
Well, I was wondering what it was like.
I didn't expect it to be like that.
You don't have to ask me.
You still want to enjoy
the night, don't you?
I'm still young, but it's bad to betray.
I'm scared.
So I haven't done it for two years.
It's terrible, isn't it?
Kiyoshi-kun, do you do it alone?
Do you want to do it alone?
Well, I don't mind.
I've been doing it alone all the time.
At that time, it feels so good, doesn't it?
But after it's over, I'm more dizzy.
Can I sit next to you?
What?
You're drunk, aren't you?
Am I not that attractive?
I'm trying to be brave and ask you out.
I'm not sure if I can
do it with Kiyoshi-kun,
but I think Kouji-san
feels the same way.
I'm going to touch you.
Touch me.
Are you okay?
Do you feel good?
But... Big brother is there.
Are you sure?
Yes.
This is not good.
I can't get up.
Touch me more.
It feels good.
Look.
Look, Hanpe-chan.
It feels good.
I forgot to touch it.
It's okay. Touch this side, too.
It's not good.
Why? Please.
..
It's not good.
Please...
I won't get up.
I'm fine.
Wow, it's tight.
It feels good.
I want you to look at me.
Touch me.
He is sleeping.
It feels good.
More.
More, please.
Let me see.
Can I lick you?
No.
Oh, dear.
Oh, my.
I can't believe my face
is covered with the curry.
Hi guys!! Uncle Sam is back
I'm going to apply it to your face.
Does it feel good? It's too hot.
I can't take it anymore.
Can I do it?
No, you have to do it.
No, I can't do it.
I haven't done it for a long time.
But...
If you want, I can do it.
But... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah...
Ah... Ah...
I want you to kiss me from behind.
I'll do it.
Do it.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! It's too big!
Oh, my God! It's too tight!
It tickles!
Wow!
Do it again! Give it to me.
Give it to me.
Oh, my legs are cold.
I slept a lot.
Let's do it again.
I'm sorry. I'm going home.
Thank you very much.
Hey!
Koji-san, are you
okay? I'm fine.
I'll bring you some water.
Thank you.
You drank too much.
Kiyoshi, you seem to have
gone home before you knew it.
Did you have something to do?
I had a job that I had to do in a hurry.
Oh, I see.
I was going to give you the movement
ticket, but I drank too much and slipped.
Let's go tomorrow.
Yeah.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
Kiyoshi, this is for you.
Thank you.
It's not much, but it's for you.
I'm coming.
Hello.
What are you doing?
Haven't you eaten
yet? No, I haven't.
Then go ahead and eat.
No, I have to get up early tomorrow.
What are you doing? Wait.
Hey, if there's anything left,
I can take it out right away.
Eat it.
Hey.
Yes.
I'll get ready.
Yes, please.
Let's have a light party.
It's a moving party.
Yes, it is.
It's a big day for a moving party.
It's about yesterday.
What?
Yesterday?
What was it?
You don't remember?
Of course I remember.
I look like this, and I drink a lot.
Please stop joking.
Please don't tell my brother.
Of course.
You don't have to say that.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
I'll walk you home.
Thank you.
You forgot this.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You're so shy.
People will notice you.
I'm sorry.
Let's be normal.
Okay.
You're cute.
After all, I don't want
to let you go home yet.
Let's do it for a while.
It's not good for
you, is it? No, it's not.
My hips are moving.
Oh, no.
I can't forget what happened yesterday.
Ah!
Give me a deep breath.
Oh!
Ah!
・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・ ・・・
...
What happened?
I want to do it again.
What?
Just for 10 minutes.
Is it OK?
10 minutes? Come here.
I'm going to change my clothes.
No.
You made me feel good.
Make me feel good, too.
Really?
How are you feeling? I'm fine.
You didn't sleep,
did you? I'm fine.
I understand.
I won't let you go.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a scene.
Don't tease me.
Let me sleep.
It's hot.
You are very wet.
Because it feels good.
Hurry up.
This is a video I took earlier this year.
I'm so sorry.
I feel so bad.
Do you want to take
a nap? Yes, I do.
Yuki is the only one who
is comfortable in the room.
She is comfortable in the room
because she can move her leg.
Are you OK? It's dangerous.
I can't.
It looks delicious.
Give it to me.
Not here?
It's not good here.
I don't like it here.
I don't want to be alone.
From that day on, I stole my
husband's eyes and called Kiyoshi.
Really? More.
Eat it.
It's almost over.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
What is it?
I feel like we see each
other every day recently.
That's right.
Are you having fun?
Well, I'm having a lot of fun.
But, is it a little dangerous?
It's dangerous, isn't it?
It's dangerous, but it's not dangerous.
What do you mean?
You know,
when we touch like
this, we feel calm.
If we keep touching for two years,
we may become like this.
Hey,
Kyoshi-kun,
do you want to stop this relationship?
Do you want to break up with me?
To be honest, I don't
want to break up with you.
Then let's continue until we break up.
Kiyoshi hasn't contacted me at all lately.
Mei!
Kiyoshi hasn't come recently.
Have you heard anything from him?
I haven't heard anything from him.
It's been a while. What are you doing? You
have a day off today, don't you? Oh, I see.
Do you have any plans? I see.
Then, come to my house once in a while.
Let's have a meal at my
house and have a drink again.
Oh,
OK.
I'll be waiting for you.
OK. See you.
Oh, Mei.
Kiyoshi is coming to my house from now on.
So, I'm sorry for the
extra meal for one person.
I got it. It's OK.
Mei, why do you only have
Kiyoshi's croquette? It's OK.
Kiyoshi says he eats a lot.
Besides, he is young.
I wanted to eat it, too.
It's OK, isn't it?
Well, it can't be helped.
Then, let's eat.
Yes, let's eat.
Itadakimasu.
Chiyoshi, let's make a toast.
Cheers!
By the way, Chiyoshi, you haven't shown
your face recently. Are you okay? I'm fine.
I'm not a kid.
I don't want to eat it,
so I'm going to eat it.
Then I'll eat it.
It's delicious.
Kiyoshi-kun, you're hungry, aren't you?
Yes.
Kiyoshi-kun.
You can come to eat every
day like your own house.
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
Aren't you sleepy? I'm sleepy.
I want to go to bed early.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to kiss you.
Are you not scared
anymore? I'm fine.
What are you going to do when you wake up?
What should I do?
Are you OK? It's not good.
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, I'm going to cry.
It's too loud.
It's okay.
Don't wake up if you drink alcohol.
I'm going to sleep.
He is sleeping.
But he is not awake.
I feel good.
I'm sleepy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Let's go to bed.
Your muscles are tight.
This is very good.
I want you to rub me more.
I'm sleepy.
Mom is crying because I am
not good at speaking Japanese.
I have been used to speaking
Japanese since I was a child.
I was good at speaking Japanese, but I was
not good at speaking Japanese at that time.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Are you awake? No, I'm not.
Then, do more.
I'll do more.
Do you want more?
Is it wet?
Yes.
Ah, it feels good.
You slept too much.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's so good.
Please eat more chestnuts.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep?
You are a good girl.
Give it to me.
I want it.
Don't bully me.
I'm going to play with a cat.
I'm going to hit a cat.
Yuki is a cat that is
very sensitive to sounds.
The cat is very sensitive to
the sound of human voice.
I was a little scared when I
heard the sound of the cat's voice.
I was worried about the cat's
health, but the cat was doing fine.
I'm sorry for you, I'm sorry for you.
You want to lick me, don't you?
I'm going to the bathroom.
The other day, I met a man who
ate a lot of chocolate and said,
I don't know what's the matter
with me, but I'm feeling good.
Please give me a kiss.
Do you want to sleep?
Is it okay to be so close?
It's okay, isn't
it? No? It's okay.
Do you want to sleep?
I want to sleep soon.
How do you feel? It feels good.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous.
Can you do it
with this? Help me.
I can't get in there.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
I'm scared.
I don't feel good.
I have no idea what
I'm saying at this point.
I'll continue to read the comments.
It's like a daily routine.
I'm not sure if I should be here or not.
I don't know if I should be here or not.
※This is not a sound effect.
I'm going to cry.
Ouch!
Ouch! It feels good.
※This is not a sound effect.
I feel good.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm hungry.
I feel the taste of holy water.
Is it good? Yes, it is.
Do you want more? Yes, please.
She is 5 years old.
She is a mom who has
been a mother for 16 years.
been a father for 16 years.
She is a mom who has
Oh my god! It's dangerous.
But it feels good.
I'm not going to throw up.
It feels good.
This video is a derivative
work of Touhou Project.
In the end, it's a video of a little
girl who is having a difficult time.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience
caused by the video.
I'll do my best to make it better.
Thank you for your viewing.
It's been a long time since
I've had a baby, but I'm
so happy to have a baby
that I can't help but cry.
I'm so happy to have a
baby that I can't help but cry.
I broke my back.
My nose is runny.
I have a runny nose.
I feel so good.
I feel so good, too.
It's all right.