That was fun.
I can't do it anymore.
What?
You can't do it
anymore? That's right.
I'm going to die.
You can die.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm the target of the director's criticism.
What am I doing?
Thank you again today.
Thank you.
I'm Hakushu, a judge.
I'm Karen.
Thank you.
Did you hear the story of this work today?
Well, I don't know.
It's okay to eat as it is.
Thank you.
I wanted to find out what kind of person
Kaede Karen is, so I decided to do it.
Today, I'm not going
to talk about the script,
but I'm not going to talk
about my performance.
After this, I'm going
to go to a nearby love
hotel and have a one-on-one
shoot with the actor.
I haven't decided the time yet.
I don't know yet.
Maybe next week.
I don't know.
I may not be in this industry next time.
Love Hotel.
One body, Karen-san.
One actor, one camera.
What do you think it will be like?
If you could tell me in private,
do you ever go to a
love hotel? Occasionally.
Occasionally? I see.
I'd like to see you in a love hotel.
If a miracle happens,
and I go to a love hotel with you,
If something like that happens,
I'm sure it's going to be like this.
I'm so happy. It's been a long time.
I'm sure it's the same for everyone.
I'm sure if you try to
do this, it's not easy.
I'm sorry, I didn't
prepare any clothes today.
I asked you to wear new clothes.
It's so cute.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, can I ask you a question?
I'm afraid I'll get hungry if I eat.
No, you don't have to.
How did you feel when
you went to the Love Hotel?
How did I feel?
If you could tell me.
I've never been there since lunch.
I don't know if it's a little exciting
Well, I don't know.
I wait in the hotel alone
and the director comes to me.
You can do whatever you want.
It can be a pattern that
Karen-chan is waiting, or it can be a
pattern that you wait in front
of the hotel and enter together.
What should I do?
Since it's a big deal, why don't we
enter the room together? That's right.
I think it would be better
if we went in together.
It's a beautiful place, isn't it?
Oh, it's a wiener.
I'm looking forward to the place
where you choose the wiener first.
I wonder what it is.
There are various meats.
I like people who are excited.
I see.
I have a question.
In your life, was there anyone
who wasn't excited? Yes, there was.
Really?
Yes.
Why? I want to know.
I want to know, too.
That's amazing.
I'm glad to see people standing in
front of me, and I'm happy to announce it.
I see. That's great.
Do you have the best situation in your life
or a situation that you still remember?
It doesn't have anything to do with love.
Do you have a favorite person,
regardless of whether it's a report or not?
I'm happy to meet someone
who I can meet right away.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's good.
Anyway, I think a cheerful
person is your favorite person.
I'm happy.
I'm glad to hear that.
I think there are a lot of
people who will answer anything
today, so please dye them
in the color of Karen-chan.
I would be happy if you could
dye the work in the color of Karen.
I think you'll answer
everything if you ask for it.
What?
A request? Please.
Please.
Like, it's not over yet.
I'm sure it's what we're
talking about right now.
Can you do it? I think I can.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you.
I'm really looking forward to it.
What I'm looking forward to is...
You're wearing your own clothes.
Of course, underwear.
I'm so sorry that I've
become a creepy old man.
I think you're the cutest.
Oh, really?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Please have a meal.
I'm sorry. I was just talking.
Let's eat.
Do you have a favorite
food? I like potato.
That's good.
Do you eat a lot? Yes, I do.
What else do you like?
I'm going to eat and go to bed.
I don't know.
I like to travel.
You are so cute.
You are so cute whatever you do.
It's delicious.
I'm full now.
Thank you for your hard work.
No, no.
It was just a little thing.
Are you all right?
From now on, I heard
that you are close to here,
so I would like to take a video of you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
You look so cute.
Am I cute? Yes, you are.
Wow, there is a hole.
Today, we are in a room suddenly.
A room suddenly?
Yes, that's right.
Shall we go to
Love4? Where? Here.
Let's go.
Shall we go? Yes, I do.
Do you? Yes, I do.
What time is it? It's noon.
Yes, it is.
Is it still sunny? No, it's not.
It's noon, so it's not sunny.
I'm taking a video of you.
Today, we are alone.
Alone.
I'm going to take a video of you.
Can I? A video.
How about you, Hamedori?
Don't you have any?
I don't have any.
How about you, Toralei?
I'm more embarrassed to be called Hamedori.
Really?
Why are you embarrassed?
Isn't it more embarrassing
to be a full staff?
Isn't the camera too close?
That's what I'm talking about.
Look, it's like this.
Is it close? Yes, it is.
I'm going to take a lot of
erotic pictures with this.
Let's go.
It's amazing.
This room is amazing.
What kind of book
is it? I don't know.
It's a book about butt.
How do you feel when you see my butt?
Oh, it's that way.
I thought you were going to stand back.
But you didn't.
It's amazing.
This is a great room.
The bath is purple.
I want to take a bath in the purple light.
You can do whatever you want today.
This is a free style, so you
can do whatever you want.
Whatever I want?
Yes.
Look at this.
It's a mirror.
Oh, it's true.
Can you see it? It's a mirror.
Is that a good one?
Can you wrap this around your neck later?
Wow!
You can do whatever you like.
Is the switch on? It's on.
Why is it so cute?
You ordered it in advance, didn't you?
I'll give it to you later.
Can I?
Is it a costume? Yes, it is.
You said something, didn't you?
It's a cute one.
Great.
Is it good?
Oh, there's a mirror down there.
That's right.
Oh, you are right. If you don't
wear panties, you will fall down.
It's embarrassing.
You will get wet.
Really?
There is no one here.
You are so beautiful,
aren't you? No, I'm not.
No one is hiding.
I thought only you and I were beautiful.
You are so beautiful.
What should I do?
You can do like this.
What's wrong with you?
What kind of sex do you like?
Iccha-iccha?
What is Iccha-iccha?
Do you mean to stick together?
Don't be mean to me.
What? Oh my gosh.
Don't you get angry?
No.
I've been curious about this for a while.
It's torn.
Yes.
What on earth is this? Look.
Ah! It hurts.
It hurts.
It's hot, isn't it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
Maybe it's not wet.
I don't have anything on me.
What?
I don't like it.
I took off my shirt, too.
It's hot.
I got hot in an instant.
It's been a while since I've seen
you, so I'm a little embarrassed.
It's been a while.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
I've never seen you like this before.
You're cute.
You're cute, too.
Let's put this over here.
You're thin.
Oh, I see.
Did you eat a potato
just now? No, I didn't.
You didn't, did you?
You look like you did.
Did you eat it? No, I didn't.
Are you sure? I'm sure.
Isn't that a bra?
What's that?
If you take it off, you'll have boobs?
Yes.
Really?
If you take it off, you'll have boobs.
Oh, you are here.
You are here.
Let me see your face.
Are you embarrassed?
You look cheerful.
Let's shave your beard later.
Do you want me to do more?
Yes.
Are you embarrassed?
Wow, you are great!
Wow, you are
great! You are sullen.
You are sullen.
You sit here.
You are erotic.
You have two dumplings.
There are two cats.
Hey, hey.
Does it hurt? It's cold.
It's stained.
I wonder if I can touch it.
You've only touched it a little.
I don't have anyone,
so you can say anything.
It's not embarrassing
because it's just the two of us.
What are you going to do?
I don't know what you're doing right now.
Look, this is all I can see.
I'm going to give you a massage.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with
you? I was licked.
Are you sure?
Can I look at you? I'm sorry.
You have a finger in your eye.
Do you understand?
It's messed up.
It's embarrassing if you stand there.
If I stand there? It's so high.
It's getting round.
What?
Like this?
Yes.
It's high.
Are you OK? Barely.
Barely safe?
Isn't it erotic? Open your legs.
Can I look at you? Look at me.
What is this? It's a strange feeling.
Are you embarrassed to be taken like this?
No.
Are you excited?
What should I do? Be careful.
Come here.
Take off your pants.
What makes you want to have sex?
What makes me want to have sex?
I like talking to you.
I like talking to you, too.
When we get married, I feel
like I want to do something erotic.
I feel like I want to touch you.
Then, I'll touch you.
My ears are getting up.
Are you getting up?
Your neck is getting up.
Did you put your finger in it?
Is it a good one?
Which one do you like?
This one?
Both
This one? I love you.
Are you shy? I love you.
Look at the camera.
Where are you
touching? I love you.
It's cold, isn't it? It's okay.
I'm taking off your clothes.
Tell me.
You're getting sleepy.
You are getting sleepy.
You are so sleepy.
Look at this.
You are amazing.
You are so sleepy.
How do you feel? I feel sleepy.
Can you sleep a
little? Let's sleep.
I'm going to take
off my panties.
You are so mean.
What are you doing?
Do you want to see my flat face?
No, I don't want to see it.
You don't want to see it?
This time, I'm going to show
you how to make a cute cat toy.
I'm going to show you
how to make a cute cat toy.
I'm going to make a video of the process
of making a baby's first baby pillow.
This is a video I took when I was in the hospital for the first time in a long time
I'm here.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
There's something like a m, isn't there?
Is it wrong?
Is it right? I wonder.
Today, I will show you how to
remove hair on the back of the head.
I'll show you how to remove
hair on the back of the head.
Do you want to use something?
Finger?
What?
Oh, you want to use your finger.
Phone.
Do you have a phone? Yes, I do.
My phone.
Great.
Are you going?
Yes.
Are you going right now?
Do you want me to bring it to you?
Yes.
I'll bring it to you.
Do you have it? Yes, I do.
Ta-da! Here you are.
It's cool.
There are various things.
There is a black one.
What is this?
It's a vacuum cleaner for chestnuts.
Can I put it in?
You can put it in and
vacuum the chestnuts up there.
Are you interested?
Which one do you like?
Do you want to try it?
Today, I will show you the sliding door.
I think this is a very
comfortable sliding door.
When you press the button
to move the door, it slides.
It smells good.
It's good.
You've been in there for a long time.
It's good, isn't it?
What is this?
Do you want to make it stronger?
Do you want me to make it the strongest?
No, I don't want you
to make it the strongest.
Why?
Then, I'll do it this way.
I'll do it like this.
Look.
Please see review 109597
on PissedConsumer.
com My husband
and I had a lot of fun.
The day before yesterday,
we were just having fun.
I had a lot of fun, too.
It was a good day.
We were having fun.
I don't know if I can say this, I can't say
this, I can't say this, I can't say this,
but I can't say this.
But we laughed a lot.
I can't say this,
but I can't say this,
She is about to give birth.
What if I don't stop after I give birth?
What?
What if I don't stop after
I give birth? She will die.
Look.
I'm not going to stop.
OK?
It's been a long time since I've
had a baby, so I'm a little worried.
I'm worried about my baby's health.
Can I have some water?
Yes.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Actually, I'm embarrassed to be seen.
I'm embarrassed.
Can I take a picture of you?
Yes.
The baby cat is calling her name.
The baby cat is confused
with the name of his mother.
I put a camera in my son's room.
He is in a hurry to see the camera.
He is very nervous when he sees a camera.
I'm sorry I couldn't help my baby.
Oh, you wanted to lie down.
Come here.
Look at me.
You can go inside.
What's wrong?
You were grunting.
You were grunting like this.
You are amazing.
You are surprised, aren't you?
Once you go to the vet, it's easier to go.
Do you think so? You are cute.
You are upside down.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I'm very happy
that he's doing so well.
I'm glad he's doing well.
When I was young, I was very
curious about the world of cats.
I'm not good at interacting with people, so
I'm not good at communicating with people.
I love this place.
Let's move a little forward.
What do you like, Taiyo?
I like this bench.
I see, that bench.
That's a great butt.
You can put three of them on it.
Yes, I can.
Let's go there.
Put your hand on your butt.
Look at this.
I have four butts.
Four butts?
Can I put this in the back?
I have four butts.
Can I?
What are you going to do?
What?
I'm going to do this.
Are you going to do this with four people?
It's dangerous, isn't it?
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby
in a wheelchair, so
I'm a little nervous.
I'm going to have to put
a lot of pressure on you.
You like the back, don't you?
Do you like the back?
Do you like it?
What are you looking at?
Have you ever seen your
own face in the mirror?
No.
You are dizzy.
Do you want some water?
No.
You don't need it?
I'll bring it to you.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to film this video.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Do you want to cool down?
Do you want to cool
down? Here you are.
Let's take a break.
It's purple.
It's going to be in the purple liquid.
The phone is waterproof.
If you want, I can bring it.
Wait a minute.
I'll bring it.
It's warm.
Do you like it?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Did you forget to wash your face?
Really?
Wow!
Wow, it's amazing.
I've never seen it in the water.
You can't see it in the water.
It's different from this.
I've never used it in the bath.
It's totally different,
isn't it? It feels good.
You are so erotic that I can't help
but tickle you while looking at you.
Don't move.
I am watching a video of a baby cat.
Baby cat is asleep.
He is sleeping deeply.
I am watching a video of a baby cat.
I went to the daycare center
and they gave me a hand sanitizer.
It's a bit funny.
Are you okay?
Don't let go of the teddy bear.
You can leave it.
Tell me when you leave.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it? It's hot.
It's good temperature.
It's fun.
Have you ever had a shower?
Since you were a child.
Wow!
What?
This is not a bath.
Wow!
Everyone is not like that at first.
Do you understand?
I'm a little nervous.
It's been a long time since I've
had a bath, so I'm a little nervous.
Do you need a bath bomb?
Do you need water?
It's been a long time
since we had sex, hasn't it?
Yes.
How long does it take to
have sex in a private room?
10 minutes? 15 minutes?
It depends on the partner.
Do you want to go out?
Let's go to the bath tub.
I don't want to take a bath.
I'll let you take a bath.
I've never done it in the bathroom.
In the bathroom?
You can wear it.
I rented it, so you can wear it.
Please wear it.
A beautiful girl.
A.
How about B?
What do you think now?
If I post this on social
media, my fans will be happy.
Is that so?
Who posted it? Oh, this one.
This side.
Oh, this is the top.
This one?
How about this one?
Do you like A?
This one?
How about this one?
This one is good.
Like this?
Close your hand.
This is the narrowest one.
This one?
What about this one?
Erika, this is Seino,
isn't it? This is Shin.
This is this kind of thing.
Can I take a video with my cell phone?
You don't have to take it off.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
You look like a fool.
When you come to school,
you will be told to go home.
Here we go.
Cheese.
Do you have something like this?
Like taking a picture with a fan?
Well, not like that.
Like in a swimsuit.
Ah, yes.
When I say, I'll take a picture,
do you have a pose that you are good at?
You look like you're going to do your best.
It's great.
Look.
Do it again.
You look strong.
Your hair is so thin.
Because it's transparent.
You have a ribbon here.
Does it make you excited?
Do you have a microphone? I see.
I'll give you a microphone.
Here you are.
Hello.
What are we going to shoot today?
It's a shooting of a beautiful girl.
I'm going to defeat the enemy.
I'm going to bed.
Are you excited?
It's bright today.
It's a nice day.
Oh, it's open.
What are you doing?
If you do like this,
See?
Right?
Wow!
Ah!
It looks like a real one.
This is the real one.
Right?
A beautiful girl warrior.
A?
What are you doing now?
You look like a monster.
Do I look like a monster?
You are really beautiful.
You are quite tough.
How can I win?
How can you win?
How can I lose?
Do I lose if I show something?
Yes, you lose if you show something.
I really want to lose to you, Soso.
I want to put something
embarrassing in the video.
Can you see me? Yes, I can.
Can you see me? A little more.
A little more?
Oh, no!
I'm going to lose to you, Captain Ishioda.
I'm going to lose.
I'm going to make you sleep with me.
The baby is still in my arms.
I try to hold him with my hands.
But..
Are you okay?
Let me see your ears a little bit.
It's done.
You're rubbing your
chest, aren't you? I'm sorry.
It's okay, I'll rub it for you.
It feels good.
But you like to rub your chest, don't you?
No? I got caught.
It's OK.
I'll rub your lower back.
Did you fall down?
Oh, you were carrying this.
That's great.
I didn't know you were in such a place.
I'm scared.
That's terrible.
【Cat's name is Romantic
Cat, but I call it Romantic Cat.
】 Romantic Cat has a cat's name.
Romantic Cat doesn't have a
name, so I call it Romantic Cat.
Romantic Cat's name is Romantic Cat.
Romantic Cat has a cat's name.
Oh, my goodness! Look at her.
Wow!
She is flying like a beautiful girl.
I wonder if she is
going to be a street cat.
Are you worried about her?
Do you hate having a
lot of sex? No, I like it.
What? I like it.
I don't like it.
What?
I'm going to sleep.
Mama and Mama's voice
and voice are the same.
It's a situation where the baby's
voice is heard at the same time.
I'm talking about the voice of the baby.
Mom, I'm cold.
I brought you some water.
Today, I'm going to show you a
video of a baby who is about to cry.
I'm going to show you a video
of a baby who is about to cry.
Today, I will show you how
to make a face mould of a cat.
First, I'll show you how
to make a face mould.
I'm sorry.
Why? I'm sorry.
Oh, you surprised me.
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Oh, you surprised me.
Mom is having a hard time
breathing and her eyes are getting red.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's wet.
What? It's wet.
I lost.
It's wet.
It was fun.
It's bright.
It's so bright.
This is the best.
Did you enjoy it? Yes, I did.
Were you excited?
Were you able to do it?
Yes, I was excited.
You got used to being a beautiful girl.
I'm a beautiful girl.
A beautiful girl.
You are sweating a lot.
Yes, I am.
I am wet.
Because the humidity was so high.
You are right.
And you took a bath.
Yes, I did.
It was fun.
I can't do it anymore.
What?
You can't do it
anymore? Yes, I can't.
What?
I am going to die.
You can die.
The police is coming.
It was fun, wasn't
it? It was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Have you been filming this all the time?
All the time?
Yes, all the time.
Are you sleepy?