The wind is so strong.
Today, I'm going to
shoot a video for Aipoke.
I'm in Odaiba now.
I was told that I can go on a date here.
So I'm going to go on a date.
But I don't know who the person I'm going
to meet is, so I'm going to meet him here.
I'm looking at the scenery of
Odaiba alone with a camera.
I've never had a date before, so I don't
know what to do if I have a date in Odaiba.
Good morning.
Ohayou gozaimasu!
Oh, you're Ohayou?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kuroi.
I'm Monogi.
Nice to meet you.
Let's hold the camera.
Please.
It's nice to meet you.
First of all, I'm from Odaiba.
Nice to meet you.
What should I call you?
I'm Kuroi Yu.
I'm Yu-kun.
I'm Momo-chan.
Nice to meet you.
I haven't been on a date much.
I don't come to Odaiba often,
so I don't know where to go.
Do you have a place you want to go?
I want to go inside.
Do you want to go inside?
Thank you.
Is it okay if we don't
take a picture together?
Oh, that's good.
I'm happy.
It's a date, so I'd like to flirt with you.
I've never done a date-like flirting.
Oh, really?
Is that so?
Yeah, that's right.
So I'm wondering if I can flirt with you.
Do you want to have a flirty date?
Do you mean you want to have sex with me?
Yes, I do.
It's written LOVE on your back.
I don't want to have sex with you.
Shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
I can't speak in honorifics.
Speaking of sexual things,
I have an ideal.
I want to have sex with you.
I want to have sex with you
because we have a gay relationship.
I want to take a picture with you.
Did you take a picture with
me when you were a student?
I took a picture with my friend.
I don't want to take a
picture with you all the time.
Why?
I don't want to take a
picture with you all the time.
Here?
Isn't it too dark?
Is it okay?
There are not many people.
I can see the restaurant.
Let's kiss.
Suddenly?
Isn't this a place like that?
Isn't it?
Someone will come.
What?
Is this a date?
That's right.
I got it right.
Yuu-kun taught me how to date.
This is it.
I found it.
It's been a long time.
I love snacks.
Do you eat snacks?
I love it.
I miss it.
Isn't it fun?
I like this, too.
It's nostalgic.
Do I have to suck it?
We used to eat it with coke.
I see.
I like it, too.
Thank you.
Is it good?
It's like...
It's like... It's
like... It's like...
It's been a while since
I had this sour taste.
Your face is sour.
Do you want some?
I'll have some.
I'll kiss you.
I'm trying to cut it in half.
Let's kiss.
It's red.
Is it okay?
What are you going to do?
You have one left.
Well, it's okay.
Then, I'll cut it in half.
It's so good.
It's amazing.
I'm getting excited.
I'm hungry.
Are you hungry?
Let's eat.
Shall we go?
What is it?
This is good.
Really?
It's good.
Do you want to try it?
It's my first time to eat ice cream.
Really?
I didn't eat ice cream before.
It's good.
It's our first time to meet each other.
What is your first
impression of each other?
First impression...
I saw your outfit today, and I
thought you were a refreshing person.
Really?
I thought you were an actor.
It's very natural today.
It's a strange feeling.
I'm glad.
What about me?
What kind of fashion do you like?
I like legs.
I'm glad to hear that.
I think men like this
kind of fashion the most.
I don't like to show my legs.
I like to hide my legs a little.
I like to wear fashionable
clothes, but I like to show my legs.
You like healthy clothes, right?
Yes, I like healthy clothes.
It's a realistic opinion.
It's a healthy foot.
I'm talking too much.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's a date.
I was looking forward
to my partner would be.
That's why I had a good impression.
I can't do anything when I'm stopped.
There are a lot of people.
I thought I'd focus.
When I go abroad,
I can say hello in a place like this.
It's like, I'm home.
Try it.
I'm home.
It's not like that, but it's
okay if it's that open, isn't it?
That's right.
I don't think it's going to be filmed.
Love.
I was forgiven for my long eyes.
I'm getting excited
because I'm in front of love.
We've been on a date for a long time.
I'm starting to loosen up.
Do you like me now?
I love you so much.
It's fun.
I'm really happy.
I'm glad.
I'm so happy.
The weather is so nice today.
It's so nice.
Hey, Yuka What?
It's amazing that there is no one
When there is no one You do like this.
Because.
I'm your girlfriend I'm
your boyfriend's girlfriend.
You are my girlfriend
I'm so excited.
What's up?
He's coming.
Let me hold you.
It's the sea.
You look stupid.
Run again.
I'm crying.
This way.
Wait a minute.
I'm embarrassed.
I thought you would do it now.
You did it.
I'm sorry, I didn't take it.
You know the promise.
Like this.
I can't see the screen at all.
It's good.
Someone is watching.
I'm watching.
I don't know It's good.
It's good I'm watching you I
don't know When I kiss you.
I feel like I feel like I feel like
I feel like I feel like I feel like.
I was looking at you
I was looking at you.
People can see us
People can see us.
Let's go to a place where people
can't see us Let's move Let's move
Don't hide from the camera
Why are you hiding your face?
Let's move You are so shy.
Finally, we are alone
Finally, we are alone I'm shy.
You are shy.
I'm shy.
You are right.
Why are you shy?
It's too late.
Because I'm not usually shy.
Why are you touching me?
I'm shy.
I might do it in this situation.
In this situation?
Because I'm playful.
Let's go to the hotel.
Put it on.
I see.
Please put it on.
Are you OK?
No.
Did you put it on?
Yes, I did.
Are you going?
Not yet.
I can't hear the camera.
I can hear the camera.
I can hear it.
You can hear it.
Let's go to the hotel.
Let's go.
I'm going to drive.
Yes, please.
Let's go.
Isn't it amazing?
It's so beautiful.
Where is it?
It's over there.
I'm excited.
I wonder if everyone is already doing it.
What is that?
Why do you say that?
Because it's such a place.
That's right.
Oh no.
I'll show you when we get in.
We haven't got in yet.
Here?
Yes.
It looks spacious.
It's beautiful.
It's a spacious room.
Really?
I'll open it.
Ready, go.
Oh! It's so big!
It's so big!
It's so beautiful.
I'm so excited.
You're so enthusiastic.
You didn't like it?
No, I didn't.
We were doing something.
It's good to see you in person.
Why did you say that?
It was a strange feeling.
Can I blame you?
Do you like me?
You're a bit of an enemy.
It feels good.
Hey, take it off.
Oh!
Are you excited?
Which one do you want to take off?
I'm excited.
I can't do both.
I can hold it.
I want to touch both.
It's like... What?
Isn't it big?
What do you mean?
It's not as big as before.
I see.
Do you care about it?
No, I don't.
I've never cared about it.
Do you like it?
Yes.
It looks comfortable.
Let's touch it together.
I'm sorry.
I'm sad.
Your reaction is cute.
Can I lick your tongue?
Do you want to sleep?
It feels good.
I like to do it without making a sound.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
Why do you feel like that?
Because I did a lot.
I've been doing a lot.
You've been doing a lot.
Am I doing a good job?
Yeah.
Because it's amazing.
It's in my mouth.
Your stomach is growling.
What kind of feral animals do you like?
I like to be licked.
Do you like to be licked?
Do you like to be licked hard?
Yes.
You don't have to go
all the way to the back.
Come here.
Lie down.
I'll do it for you.
Don't you want to go to the gym?
It feels good.
I like it more intense.
I like the big one.
It's so beautiful.
What is that?
Why are you licking it?
Lick it.
No, don't look at it.
I don't want you to look at it.
No?
No.
You never look at me.
So...
Concentrate.
I'm shy.
You're shy because it's just a date.
Stop it.
Stop it!
You don't want to?
I'll do it for you.
You don't like it, do you?
You don't like to be looked at, do you?
Aren't you embarrassed?
I like to be looked at.
What's that?
How did it feel?
How was the bath?
It was my first time.
Really.
I don't know because I'm not good at baths.
How did it feel?
I felt like I was being hugged.
Like you were being hugged?
I'm sorry.
You're so nice.
Do you want to take a bite?
No, it's too big.
You're a good actor.
You can take a lot, right?
I can take a lot.
Is it good?
Ouch!
It's hot.
I'm going to eat it all.
It's clean.
I'll wipe it for you.
You're really good at it.
Is this your first time?
Really?
No, I don't
You don't take it off
in the morning It's cute.
Because it's a photoshoot?
Yes.
Let's go.
Take this off.
It's embarrassing.
Why?
Let's go.
I'll let you go.
It's kind of...
It's kind of embarrassing.
All of a sudden.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I can't.
You're making us laugh.
Don't laugh while looking at me.
I'm sure you'll look at me.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
Look into my eyes and tell me.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You are cute.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
I don't want to be licked.
Why are you hiding your face?
I'm embarrassed.
You're embarrassed, aren't you?
I know.
I know, I know.
You look really embarrassed
I'll do it No, not yet.
Not yet.
I don't want to
date I don't want.
Let me see.
How is it?
It feels good.
You are moving.
Hey.
It felt good.
I'm glad.
Let's take a bath together.
Hug me.
I'm sorry
Are you okay?
You are sweating.
You know what?
I want you to put your face on it.
What?
Are you trying to be funny?
I'm not trying to be funny, but I
want you to put your face on it.
No, I don't want to do that.
Wait a minute.
Do you want it?
It feels good.
Oh, no.
I can't.
Here you go.
I put it in.
Did you already put it in?
Can I?
I put it in.
Why?
What?
That's how you feel.
I don't know.
Look at me.
What?
Why are you touching me?
Good boy.
Why?
You What?
I'm scared.
Why?
Why are you embarrassed?
I don't know.
Why are you being attacked?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm like a doctor I'm like a doctor I'm
like a doctor Let me see your big mouth.
Does it feel good?
Isn't it embarrassing to have tongue out?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's embarrassing to be blamed, isn't it?
It's cute.
It hurts.
My bag is not good.
What is not good?
The shape is not good.
What do you mean?
The compatibility is not good.
I'll put you on my lap.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Your shoulders are so stiff.
I want to let it out.
Can I?
Yes, you can.
Where do you want to let it out?
Oh, no.
There.
Let me go!
Give me your hand.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
It was good, wasn't it?
It felt good, didn't it?
I'm so embarrassed.
What?
You?
It's me.
It's not M.
It's true.
I don't want to be blamed.
I'm embarrassed.
It's fun to see your reaction.
It doesn't make sense.
Are you licking me?
I want to drink this cup.
Today?
Today is a cup.
I'm glad to hear that.
Isn't this room amazing?
Wow!
It's a different room.
There's another room here.
This room is cute.
What is this?
Macaroon?
Macaroon.
This room is like a fairy tale.
It's a snack room.
Wow!
That was a snack, too.
That's right. All of them are snacks.
Wow, I want to see a lot of things.
Oh, I found something good.
I'll guess.
Do I get it right?
A toy.
You're so perverted
What are you doing?
It's a toy, right?
Too bad Too bad.
Give me a hint
The hint is I was going to
give you a hint The hint is.
Ah, so when we took the
picture of today's purikura.
Was there a bit of it?
Did you put it on?
Ah!
Cat ears.
Ding!
Ta-dah!
Wow, it's cosplay!
Wow!
It means put it on, right?
That's right.
Look, it has a tail It's cute And
It's similar to the one on Purikura
It's similar to the one
you put on your shoulder.
It's black.
Then it's okay.
Me?
It's so cute.
I'll put it on.
Isn't it so cute?
It's definitely not going to fit.
Did you prepare it for me?
It's not going to fit at this point.
I can't get in.
It's creepy.
Come on.
Isn't it great?
Wait a minute.
First of all, this.
Like this?
You are so cute!
Thank you!
Give me a kiss!
No!
Why not?
Because cats are a bit weird.
I don't think they do that.
No!
Can you give me a kiss?
Do you have a cat?
I have a cat.
A long time ago?
I have a cat now.
Do you want to kiss?
I have a cat.
It's the biggest expression of affection.
Why?
lol.
She doesn't want me to kiss her.
This means.
this is mine.
I see.
No
She doesn't want me to kiss her anymore.
Do you want to change?
Can I take a video of you changing?
What is that?
Don't you have karaoke here?
Karaoke?
Can I have a microphone?
No.
What is that? Is that a bra?
Yes, it is.
It is very wide bra.
Oh, it's spacious.
How do you like it?
I like it.
Do you like it?
It's not like Chijo.
It's M, isn't it?
No, it's not.
It's not M, but you like Chijo.
I like Chijo.
It can't be helped.
It's a little difficult, isn't it?
Oh, this is how you open it.
Is it difficult?
It's difficult.
Take a picture of me.
I like it.
Isn't there a lot of people
wearing knitted tights?
On a daily basis.
You don't look at it much these days.
Do you get excited when
you see someone wearing it?
What?
Why do you think I'm wearing it?
Do you think you're full of motivation?
I think I'm a pervert.
Are you excited?
It's supposed to be worn to protect
you, but it doesn't mean anything, does it?
That's true.
It's supposed to be worn to show off.
Oh, it's got a tail.
Yeah.
It's in there.
Oh, the tail is long.
The tail is long.
It's done.
It's cute.
What are you doing?
Don't you cosplay?
No, I don't.
Is there anyone who cosplays a man?
Is there anyone who wants
to cosplay as a black cat?
Yes, I'm a black cat.
Why is your tail so long?
My tail is long.
You are a cat with a long tail.
What did you say?
I said the impression of a cat.
I found it around here.
I tried to make it cute.
I don't want to turn it all the time.
Come here.
Let's sit down.
Hey! Come here!
Why are you putting your butt here?
You look like a pervert.
Come here!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you showing your affection?
I won't kiss you because you
are a cat I already kissed you
I won't kiss you.
I'm sure she's still hungry.
I'm going to give you a snack.
I'm giving you a snack.
You want me to lick you?
Yeah.
Is it good?
Come here.
Hey Come here.
You are getting hard.
Ah.
Why are you sticking out your tongue?
It's hard, isn't it?
No, it's not.
It's hard.
It's amazing.
It's transparent.
It's hard, isn't it?
I don't know why.
Do you want to eat it?
Hey, what is this?
Hurry up and eat it!
Hey, what are you doing?
You're doing aegyo
with your knitted tights.
Hey, you.
Shut up.
You're doing aegyo.
I'm not doing aegyo. I'm touching you.
It feels good.
Is it different with knitted tights?
Really?
Do you like everything?
I like everything.
What's your favorite?
I won't tell you.
Why?
Don't rub it on me.
I'll rub it on you.
What are you doing?
I want to play with you, too.
You are moving.
Wait a minute.
Here you are.
Why are you wet?
I'm wet.
No.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
I don't want to go because it feels good.
I don't want to go.
I really don't want to go.
Eri!
What's that look?
Why are you so round like a cat?
No, no, no!
Wait!
No!
Oh my gosh!
You are so nervous.
Camera, wake up.
Come here.
Why do I have to put the camera down?
You are so cute.
Rin, why don't you try to sit on my lap?
Why are you hiding it?
Give it to me.
What is it?
Give me a kiss.
Rin was cute Give me
a kiss No, I don't like it.
You have to do it with all your might.
Thank you.
You are so kind.
You are so cute.
Cats lick the whole body, right?
Do you want me to lick you?
I want you to lick me.
I'm going to put a mark on your face.
Are you going to get angry
if I put a mark on your face?
What?
Do you want me to put a mark on your face?
What do you think? Will you get
angry if I put a mark on your face?
What?
I'm going to put a mark on your face.
That's real.
I don't know.
One more.
I got it.
What should I do?
I told you to put it on.
You told me.
That's a proof.
What's wrong?
I'm trying to help you.
Do you like me?
You like me, don't you?
I don't like you.
I just like you.
Do you?
No, I don't.
Well...
You're really eating with
all your might, aren't you?
I told you, didn't I?
You did.
You're eating with all
your might, aren't you?
You're so naughty.
You're always so energetic.
You're so happy.
Why do you tease me like that?
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'll pet you.
I don't know if I can do it.
Hurry up.
Can I show my ears?
Do you like my ears?
It feels good Are
you kidding me?
It feels good I'm sorry.
I'm sorry Wait a minute.
OK.
How do you say it?
If you say, let's take a picture of
the camera, that's what you say.
I'm in trouble What?
I'm in trouble with the reaction
I'm in trouble with the reaction.
Why?
There are a lot of orders.
I can't see it.
Stop.
No, I wanna do it!
No, I wanna do it.
Do you wanna do it?
Yeah, I wanna do it but...
It's bright red.
I'll put a face mark.
I'll make it bright red.
I told you to do it.
I did.
I don't like it.
It's true.
Which one do you like?
I like 0.2mm.
Do you like thin one?
Yes.
Say, hey, nya!
Thank you for putting it on.
Oh, it's written.
This is great.
It's a good logo.
Which one do you like?
Any one.
What's the difference?
It hurts.
It's not an AV.
Isn't this an AV?
This is not a music video, is it?
No, it's not.
It's done!
I did it!
You're doing it right
How do you do it usually?
I do it like this.
I'm going to put it in You're
shaking it You don't need it.
Your tail is so big I'm just making
fun of you You don't need it.
He's trying to grab it.
What's wrong with you?
Does it feel good?
It's a little hard.
You're cute.
I like this because it reacts a lot.
I'm going to sleep.
Show me your butt.
What are you doing?
He's drooling Is he
drooling because he's a cat?
I'm going to sleep.
I like to take a rest.
Oh, it's hard.
Give me your hand.
It's hard.
It's really hard.
You're so cute.
Why?
I don't know.
You're making a face.
It feels good.
It's dangerous from behind.
I'm so sick of it.
I want to drink it.
But... I'm sick of it.
Look at me.
You got bigger!
Because I looked at you
Look at me Look at me.
Look at me.
You got bigger.
Can you see me?
Yes.
It's getting more and more intense.
It's very intense.
Good boy.
Why are you crying?
Oh, it's painful.
Oh, it feels so good.
Ouch!
You're sweating a lot.
Oh, he's gone He's gone
again He flew all the way here.
He's so energetic
He's so excited.
I don't know if he'll get mad at me
Don't worry.
I'll clean your ears.
I'll fix them Take
a deep breath.
Did you get it all out?
It was intense.
What?
Was it intense?
Did you like it?
It's intense.
I like it.
I don't like it.
You're eating a lot.
I told you so.
Hey.
There's something over there.
I have something like this.
No, no, no.
Stop it.
It's too wide.
I found something like a jacuzzi.
Oh, yeah.
Let's go later.
I have to take a bath.
Later.
I don't want to move yet.
Why?
Did you feel good?
I won't show it to you
even if you get mad at me.
I won't use it.
Don't touch it.
Will you get mad at me?
What's that?
Are you going to summon it?
Don't worry.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
It feels good.
It's just right.
Thank you.
It's warm, isn't it?
Thank you for dating with me today.
It's a celebration of our meeting.
I'm embarrassed.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers!
It's very cold.
It's good, isn't it?
How was it today?
I want to go first.
Did you have fun?
Yes.
What else?
It was fun.
You were cute.
What?
How was it?
It's been a while since we
dated, so it was new to me.
It's been a while.
It was fun.
But...
We had a lot of sex.
I don't know why, but...
Because you're going to have sex.
Well, that's...
If I'm with him, I don't want to.
It's been a while.
Have you ever been in a relationship?
Of course I have.
I haven't.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
You were a student, so
you don't have a boyfriend.
Have you ever been on a school trip?
I have.
Have you ever seen a naked boy?
Yes.
I'm not sure if it's a boy or
a girl, but I think it's a boy.
I peeped.
You peeped.
What's wrong?
I think I'm a little drunk.
I'm drunk.
It's true.
It's amazing.
Blow on it.
It stood up!
It's romantic.
It's unexpectedly romantic.
Let me see.
Wow.
It's fun.
Because I'm drunk.
I'm drunk, so I'm feeling rich.
Are you drunk?
Not yet.
Why don't you get drunk?
Should I drink more?
Did you drink it?
Yes, I did.
How is it?
What do you think?
I love you so much.
More than any other actress.
Why are you saying that?
Because you're a wonderful 13-year-old.
I know, but...
Don't bother me.
I love you the most.
I love you.
I love you the most today.
I love you the most all the time.
Don't say such a thing.
I put a kiss mark on my lips.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
If you get angry at me on the set,
I'll say,
I put a kiss mark on my lips.
I don't know.
You're drunk, aren't you?
I can't help it because I'm drunk.
You can't see it, can you?
I can see it.
You can't see it?
It's okay.
There are people who
live in this kind of world.
I can't see it.
Why are you hiding it?
I'm sorry.
I can't stop kissing you.
Drink more.
Can I drink more?
Are you okay?
Are you standing up already?
I'm going to kiss you.
You're wearing a swimsuit.
It's hard.
You don't like it, do you?
Why do you say such a thing?
Why do I say such a thing?
Your reaction is cute.
What?
Don't do that. You'll get angry.
No, I won't.
Are you serious?
I don't care if you get mad at me.
Just one.
Just one?
Which one?
This one.
I don't want it.
You don't want it?
Then try it on me.
No.
Why?
You'll get mad at me.
Why? It's the same.
No.
I'm your lover today.
Try it on me.
No.
Why?
Why are you rubbing it on my face?
Put it on my face.
If you put it on my face,
I'll put it on your face.
Is that a good thing?
No, it's not.
Don't be stupid.
I'm not stupid.
What's that?
Are you trying to take a bath?
You're taking a bath.
You're a playboy.
No, I don't want to.
What's wrong with you?
Don't look at me.
I don't want to.
I'm not looking at you.
This is outside, isn't it?
You have to be careful with your voice.
I can't do it.
I'll do it for you.
You can hear the outside voice,
but you can't hear the inside voice.
That's right.
Look.
I can hear a lot.
Let's do it.
No, no.
Don't do it.
Get out.
No, no, no.
Mommmm~~
No, no.
No, not like that.
Like this.
You're making a loud noise.
I'm not.
You like to be petted.
Ouch!
You have a stomachache. Are you okay?
I'm patient.
You are patient.
You can't stand it anymore.
Sit down.
It's okay. You can sit down.
What do you mean?
You can go inside.
I wanted to try it.
Isn't it hard?
It's not fair.
There are many people
who are better than me.
What are you doing?
Do you like soy sauce?
I love you.
Stop it.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't make a sound.
Can't you see outside?
Yes, I can.
Really?
Isn't it amazing?
It's shining.
The night view outside is shining.
It's a beautiful view.
Put it in slowly.
I can't do it.
You can't?
He says he can't do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
You are so cute.
She loves you.
She loves you so much.
I want to be comfortable with you.
I can't.
It's so hot.
Help me.
Do you want to drink from the back?
It's so hot.
Oh, it's so wet.
It's so wet.
Does it tickle?
Yes, it does.
Did you just say that?
Did you feel good?
I felt so good.
What are you going to do after this?
What should I do?
Do you want to stay here?
I don't know.
Because it's a very fun hotel.
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Let's make it in time.
For the shooting?
Yes.
Even if we don't make it in
time, you won't blame me?
I won't.
Then, go away.
Let's stay here.
What do you think?
Oh no!
I was wrong!
Who was it?
I don't know.