I'm going to play the gachapon.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
Oh, no!
Oh, it feels good!
I don't usually say this, but
my friend recommended this.
It's on the left here.
Am I exaggerating?
The most recent recommendation
I've made is the one on the right!
I am going to try to get close
to the right with a mild face.
I've tried it a lot, but it's good.
I have the basic face
expression, like a white bean cake.
I'm going to show you how to do it.
I can't drink any more.
I feel sick.
I feel so good.
※This is not a sound effect.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels so good.
I'm so sorry.
I feel so bad.
Ah!
I feel great! I'm sorry.
Can I move? I feel sick.
I feel sick.
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
Hello, I'm Harami!
Sit back & enjoy my full performance!
Thank you for watching my full performance!
Please subscribe to my channel!
See you in the next video!
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
I'm going to take a bath.
I feel good.
I feel so good.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Haa...
Let's do it again when you're done.
Sorry, I can't do it any more.
What?
How is it? Don't sleep.
Wake up.
Did you sleep? Wake up.
I'm going to prank you.
You don't wake up at all.
Wake up.
You didn't wake up, so I hung the string.
Please put your hands together.
Are you comfortable?
Yes.
Look at me.
Are you comfortable?
Yes.
Yeah.
Ah.
Hehe.
Are you curious?
No.
Hehehe.
Sorry.
Ah.
Yeah.
It's hard.
What are you doing?
Are you sleepy?
Yes.
Are you sleepy? I'm fine.
Give me a lot.
Can I?
Ugh...
Ah...
Yeah... It's hot.
It's so hot.
Oh, I'm gonna pass out.
Don't worry.
Ah...
Oh...
Ah, it hurts...
It hurts... Ah...
Yes.
You put a lot in it.
It was pleasant.
We met again at the hotel.
Yes.
Do you remember? Yes, I do.
The old days?
Yes.
Do you remember what it
was like in the old days? I do.
Do you remember? A little.
Are you excited? Yes, I am.
Do you want more?
Yes.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no!
Ah, it feels good.
It's no good, it's no good.
No, no, no.
My arm hurts.
I'm sorry.
You are wet.
Yes, I am.
She is gone.
Yes, she is.
Do you want more? Good morning.
Good morning.
No, no, no.
I can't do it anymore.
※I'm sorry if my English is bad.
I feel bad.
I feel so good.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry.
Ah, it's gross.
I feel so bad.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
I'm so sleepy.
I feel so good.
I'm sleepy.
I'm full.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Do you have any
medicine? I'm sorry.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm not sure if it's because I've
never seen a baby cry like this before.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
I'm sorry.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
I'm so sorry.
How do you feel? I feel so good.
I feel so good.
Hello, I'm Harami! Sit back &
enjoy my full performance! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sleepy.
I feel so good.
Ouch! It's hot.
I'm so hot.
Do you like pig?
Pig?
It looks delicious.
Is it delicious? A little.
It's cute.
Let's pour it slowly.
This is an experiment to see
how much the baby can swallow.
The baby is chewing the gum.
The baby is not able to swallow the gum.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, it feels good.
Oh!
Feels good!
Oh! It feels good.
It feels good.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
It's gross!
I want to be a mom.
It's gross! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Nope.
No, no.
Ouch.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no!
What a pity!
I should have brought a towel.
Oh... Oh... oh...
Oh... It's disgusting.
It's disgusting.
Oh, I feel sick.
It's okay.
I feel sick.
Oh, it's painful.
It's painful.
It's all in.
Oh, it's deep.
I feel so bad.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm so sorry.
Are you that
excited? I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I can't breathe.
I feel like I'm going to pass out.
Hello, everyone.
You go first.
I finally understood your pain.
Ah... Feels good...
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
I can't do it. I can't do it. I feel sick.
I feel sick.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I'm sorry.