Ah, haha.
Ahaha.
I just finished the shooting.
I'm sitting on the massage
chair because I'm so tired.
Today, at first, there was no
iPhone, and I was bullied a lot on
the ground, so I was very anxious,
but the result was a lot of fun.
What was the most fun?
It was a lot of fun when a
man came in with a blindfold on.
I laughed a lot and bullied a lot.
Do you have any regrets?
All.
I had a lot of fun, so please cry a lot.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Are you used to shooting?
No, I'm not.
You'll be back soon, right?
Yes.
Today, as I told you before,
I'll do my best.
What's wrong?
What's your reaction?
I'm looking forward to it.
Really?
I'm sorry, but I have to
postpone my schedule for a day.
Okay.
I'll talk to you on the way.
This time, I'm going to do it for 24 hours.
I'm going to introduce you to a lot
of people who can say nice things.
You?
Yes.
I hope you can play with me a lot.
By the way, how many
times do you do it a day?
How many times?
Maybe 10 times?
10 times?
I don't think so.
I don't think so at all.
7 or 8 times.
That's amazing.
You are strong.
Maybe.
Maybe?
No, I'm not.
I think this is the last time we meet.
Are you going to quit?
No, I'm not.
I'll see you again tomorrow morning.
OK?
This is the entrance of this hotel.
It's sparkling.
Yes, it's sparkling.
Have a good day.
Room 603.
Here?
Yes.
Are you alone?
I'm just asking.
I'll enjoy it.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'm Karen.
I'm Otoyo.
Nice to meet you.
Can I sit here?
It's so beautiful.
I'm a little nervous.
Can I sit here?
Yes, you can.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm a little nervous.
Are you?
Yes.
Thank you.
I get nervous.
You have a lot of cameras.
That's right.
But I don't have anyone
else, so I can relax.
You don't look so nervous.
I'm very nervous.
You're lying!
I'm serious.
It's hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
Everything is beautiful.
Did you play the piano?
No, I didn't.
You didn't?
Your hands are cute.
Your eyes are short.
It's cute.
My hands are shaking.
Are you sweating?
I'm nervous.
Your fingers are long.
Can I drink this?
You already drank it.
Oh, I drank it.
Is it okay?
Let's eat.
It's good.
It's like a dog.
Why does it look like a dog?
It's cute.
It looks like a small animal.
It's soothing.
It's soothing?
It's on my lips.
Oh, yeah.
What do you want to do today?
What do you want to do?
I have a sensitive body.
Really?
I don't think you have a sensitive image.
I have a sensitive image.
I want you to make it a lot tighter.
Tighter?
Like riding on it.
Do you like it?
I like it a lot.
Is it sensitive?
It's pretty sensitive.
Is it fun?
It's hard.
Do you know what I mean?
It tickles.
What should I do?
Do you want me to kick you?
No.
Do you want me to take a
shower and go up the stairs?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to sleep?
I'm a little embarrassed.
Are you sweating?
I'm sweating a little.
You're sweating.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Open your eyes.
You're sweating.
It feels good.
Open your eyes.
I think I should keep my head down.
You're still a baby, aren't you?
Yes.
You look like you're in pain.
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
I can't get out.
Get out quickly.
Do you want to wear it?
No, I don't want to wear it.
Oh, you look great!
Why are you hiding it?
It's a little embarrassing.
Let me see.
You look great!
What is this?
This is also...
Oh, it's spinning.
Is this taken?
Yes.
Oh, it's true.
It's difficult.
Difficult?
Look, I can't see it.
It's open.
I can see it.
It's difficult.
I'm going to cry.
This is really embarrassing.
Are you ready?
This is embarrassing.
I'm going to cry.
I can't do it anymore.
Really?
I can see the juice.
It's embarrassing.
I can't do it anymore.
It's very hard.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Hurry up.
No, I can't.
Don't you want to do something more erotic?
No, I don't.
I want to see my boyfriend.
What?
Your boyfriend?
Yes.
Then, take it off.
Can I do it with this?
This is the first time for me to do this.
You are so thin.
How do I look?
You are so cute.
I want to sleep.
It's so cute.
It's so thin.
Is your abs broken?
It's amazing.
Can I touch it?
It's hard.
Is it hard?
My abs are hard.
I thought it was soft.
It's so soft.
Can I touch it?
Yes.
It's moving.
It's like a cow's boob.
It's so beautiful.
It's amazing.
I love this blood vessel.
Do you like this?
Yes.
I do make-up.
Do you want me to do it?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to pat your head?
Do you want me to do something?
That's enough.
Do you want more?
Hey, I said that's enough.
That's enough.
I can't take this anymore!
I can't breathe.
Do you want me to help you?
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
It's so good.
Can I touch you?
I want to touch you.
It's so beautiful.
Where are you from?
You're crying a lot.
You're cute.
Show me.
I'm nervous because I can't touch you.
Can I be close to you?
I'm sorry.
It's embarrassing.
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't put it on.
Put it on.
I feel embarrassed.
Put it on properly.
Did you see that?
Yes, I did.
I'm so happy.
I can see your eyes.
Look at me again.
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
Can you see me breathing?
I can't.
What should I do?
It was a scar.
Are you awake?
Hang in there.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
Why?
You can do it.
You don't have to do it one more time.
Can I do it one more time?
You can do it.
Let me help you.
I'm going to take off my clothes.
I'm going to eat.
I'm still full.
Do you want to eat this?
I'm going to eat.
Don't get up.
I'm sorry.
You stood up.
You have an awkward posture.
I can't stand it anymore.
It was hard, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
I couldn't stand it at all.
Ruri-chan.
Kako-chan is touching me.
Ruri-chan, don't you touch me?
No, I'm not.
No, no.
It's like this, right?
Like this?
Yes.
Do you know how to do it?
What?
I don't know how to do it.
I'm embarrassed.
What is it?
I don't know.
I see.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Open your eyes.
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
It's better now.
It feels good.
Did you feel warm?
I felt the same way.
It feels good.
Oh, I see.
OK.
This way.
My sweet kiss.
What?
Do you want to kiss me?
Can I kiss you?
You want to kiss me, right?
Yes.
I want to kiss you.
I've never seen a place like this.
It's great.
It's like a place for
people who take a bath.
You can do it anywhere.
Anywhere?
It's a little bit ticklish.
It's ticklish.
I'm going to try it.
Okay.
Is it okay?
Oh, it's so hard.
It's so hard.
I can't do it anymore.
Okay, let's do it again.
I'm sorry.
It's no problem.
Don't you feel like you can still do it?
I can.
Let me see your hand.
You can't see my hand?
I'll do it again.
Okay.
It's so difficult.
Congratulations.
You confessed your love to me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Thank you very much.
I love you.
It's already 5 o'clock.
Can I laugh now?
Yes, you can.
Are you tired?
No, I'm not.
My body hurts.
Hello.
Are you really alone?
Yes.
Welcome.
You are so cute.
Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
My name is Jin.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Can I sit next to you?
I'm so happy.
Two people.
Are you going to do it today?
Which one?
Three?
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm doing it.
You are so erotic.
I'm sorry.
You are so cute.
Really?
Yes.
You are wearing sexy clothes.
Your legs are beautiful.
You are looking at me.
You were looking at me.
I was looking at you.
Excuse me.
You are so cute.
I talked to my friend recently.
Really?
She said you are so cute.
Really? I'm glad to hear that.
It's true.
You are amazing.
I didn't think I'd meet you.
How long have you been alone?
I've been alone since noon.
Since noon?
Yes.
So you've been alone for a while.
Maybe.
I've been alone since noon, so I'm bored.
I think that's it.
I just... I just made a mistake.
I want to go outside.
Outside?
Yes.
Where do you want to go?
Somewhere.
I want to go shopping.
Shopping?
Yes.
Just the two of us?
Are you sure?
I don't have money, so I
want you to buy me something.
I don't have money at all.
Are you sure?
If you buy me something, I'll
treat you to kimchi fried rice.
I'll buy you anything.
Really?
I'll buy you something very expensive.
You look like you're having fun.
I want some sweets.
Sweets?
Let's go.
Isn't the bag big?
The bag is big.
We're here.
I'm happy.
It smells good.
I don't like it.
I'm so happy.
The weather is good.
Wait a minute.
Do you want me to push it?
Yay!
I'm so happy.
She is so cute.
She is smiling all the time.
I don't want to be suspicious in the store.
I'm too nervous.
It's so quiet in the hotel.
There are a lot of people.
I want to go with Karen.
I want to go with you.
Please be careful of the car.
I'll protect you.
I'll help you.
I'm happy.
You can buy anything with this.
I'll buy it.
Is it good?
I don't know how it tastes.
Let's eat.
Why are you looking at me?
I think you are so cute.
Be careful.
It's like a dream.
I will do better things from now on.
I'm a fan of you.
Are you going home?
Yes, I'm going home.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
How is it?
I want to do something.
You are moving a lot.
Uh-huh.
It's like saltiness.
I knew it.
I'm glad it's not soaked.
Ah.
It's a little big.
Is it?
Yes.
It smells a little.
Why?
What?
Something sweet and
sour came out of your mouth.
It came out.
I'm so happy.
It's hard.
I'll do it.
Can I?
Yes.
Oh!
Eh?
It feels so good!
What are you talking about?
I'm so happy!
Don't frown!
Don't bite me!
I'll bite you!
It feels so good It feels so good
It feels so good You're so cute.
That's not good.
It feels good.
This will come out soon.
Sonya drinking hot water I was trying
to show my love to her, and I failed.
I was trying to show my love
to my daughter, and I missed it.
It's amazing.
It's coming out.
You can't do that.
You can't do that either.
It feels so good.
I can't breathe easily.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
Wow!
It's so beautiful.
Ah!
It feels so good.
I can't look at her
Help me I feel like
I'm going to die.
Can I go now?
Why are you going?
Because it feels so good.
Over there.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
It hurts.
It's so good.
I really want to kiss you more and more.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's hot.
You are a pervert.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Are you okay?
I'm in trouble.
Do you feel better?
Yes, I feel better.
Oh, my god...
Let me lick your hand.
I don't know what to do with myself.
I'm sorry.
You are so cute.
You didn't notice I was peeing next to you?
I didn't know you were peeing.
You don't get up at all.
You are standing up a lot.
She is leaning on my shoulder.
Is she sleeping?
She is playing with my hand.
It feels good.
He is also cute when he is in a good mood.
Ah!
It's gross.
Is it good?
You are so kind.
Ah!
Ah! It's so good.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I like it so much.
Do you want me to put it on your face?
Put it on my face.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's going straight.
What's going on?
What?
It's hot.
Can I go?
I'm about to puke.
No, you can't.
It feels good.
I'm about to puke.
Oh no, I can't stand it anymore.
I can't do it yet.
I want to spit out my boyfriend's mouth.
Are you ready?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm going.
I'm sorry.
One more time.
I didn't say yes.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
Was it good?
How is it?
Is it bitter?
Bitter?
It's your own, isn't it?
Oh, it feels so good.
Wait, your body is so stiff.
Can you go back to sleep?
I think I can go back to sleep.
Oh, it's long.
It feels so good.
Oh, my God, it feels so good.
It's hot. It's hot.
Does it feel good?
Cheers.
Oh, that's amazing.
Oh, that feels good.
That feels good.
Oh, that's amazing.
Oh, that feels good.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
It's so good.
Does it feel good?
I want you to do something quick.
I want you to do something
while I'm washing my hands.
Oh, that.
What's that?
That feels good.
I'm going to go with you.
I'm going to eat it.
You ate it.
I ate it.
Stop it!
Ouch!
No, no!
I'm getting angry…
I'm sorry, sorry.
It feels weird, you know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
Oh, it's coming out again.
Is it coming out again?
Oh, I feel good.
Oh, it's coming out again.
Can you do it?
No.
I can do it.
Really?
Ah, it feels so good.
I'm glad I didn't cry.
It's hot.
It's time to play.
Guri Guri, she's flustered.
Really?
Yeah, she's really flustered.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay?
You're so cute!
Please!
No, I said stop.
çok çok güzel Too good!
You're very good.
You're amazing!
That was so cute.
He is very beautiful.
You can't do it slowly.
What?
I can't do it slowly.
You can't do everything.
You can do it.
I can't do it.
Did you fall asleep?
Yes, I did Oh, it tickles.
You can't go on like this.
No, I can't Oh,
it tickles Really?
Let's do it again Again?
Oh, it tickles.
Oh, oh, oh.
Um...
Good morning.
I'm sleepy.
Oh, sorry.
Good morning.
I'm sorry. I woke up early this morning.
How do you feel?
I feel sleepy.
Are you tired?
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry.
Let's sleep together.
Can I sleep with you?
I don't want to.
What?
Can I sit next to you?
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
Wait a minute.
I'm nervous.
It's hot.
I'm going to sleep.
Can I sit next to you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
You are whining.
I'm happy.
Are you sleepy?
I'm sleepy I'm sleepy.
I'm noisy I'm sorry I'm sorry.
You are so cute.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry I'm sweating
Did you sweat?
You sweat a little I'm sorry
Can I take off my shirt?
Did you sweat?
You have a lot of hair on your neck.
Do you want me to massage your neck?
Are you okay?
It's a dead body.
It's a dead body, isn't it?
You have a lot of blood on your neck.
I'm sorry.
Oh no, it's a little tight.
Can I stand up?
Yes.
Can I?
Are you going to lie down?
What?
Can't I?
It's not bad at all, but it's amazing.
Can I stand up?
My girlfriend is fine in the morning.
Eh?
Ah, it's heavy, heavy, heavy.
Ah, okay.
Ah.
Ah, wait.
It feels so good.
Ah.
Ah, I'm going to spit it out.
Ah, it's so heavy.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Wait a minute.
My nipples are weak.
Both of my nipples are weak.
Am I erotic in the morning?
It's hot.
Don't you feel hot in the morning?
Yes, I do.
Do you feel hot in the morning, too?
Yes.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's so hot.
How do you feel?
It's hot.
How about me?
Just looking at it makes me excited.
Can I touch it?
Let's touch it together.
How does it feel?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no.
It's going to be a mess.
Can I touch you?
You have a great smile.
Yes.
Can I kiss you?
I was surprised by your kiss.
Yes.
I'm sorry Your
forehead is so red.
I'm sorry, but I have to put up with this.
I'm so sorry.
You're crying.
I've been crying since
before I went to bed.
Since when?
I don't know.
How do you feel?
You look like you're in a bad mood.
It's hot.
Do you want me to wipe your tears?
Are you ready?
I'll wipe your tears.
Oh, I'm so sleepy.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm going to move.
No, you can't.
What?
I was surprised.
Which one is it?
Open your eyes.
How do you feel?
It's warm and comfortable.
It's hard.
I'm so tired.
Do you mind if I do it slowly?
Do you mind?
I'm so tired.
Toto is already in pain.
Toto has lost her ability to speak.
I'm sorry for the pain.
Your pain is not bad.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it slowly.
I'm so happy.
Does it hurt?
Yes, that's right.
Do you move by yourself?
Yes.
Because I don't have a place to move.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, you can move.
If you can't move, can you
put your legs on the floor?
I'll put my legs behind you.
It's easier for you to move, isn't it?
Oh, my God.
I feel so good.
I'm sorry.
I like a bath.
Can I give you a bath?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
You really like the bag, don't you?
I'm so wet.
Does it feel good?
I'm sorry.
It's so hard I can't help it I
can't help it Are you sleepy?
I'm tired You are tired.
I'm tired.
I'm glad you're getting better...
Let's take a deep breath.
Hmmm.
It's a little unpleasant.
I'm sorry.
It's cold.
Can I say something?
He's eating.
Thank you for your hard work.
I didn't expect you to eat so much
Oh, I'm sorry.
You have something on your finger.
It feels so good.
He's in a bad
mood It's not that.
It's a horn.
It's bitter.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry to bother you in the morning.
It's okay.
I can't go home early in the morning.
I don't know.
Did you feel good?
I feel like I'm going to sleep.
On the contrary,
I'm going to take a break, too.
I'll wipe it off.
Thank you.
Are you a person who
can do it in the morning?
Did you do it on purpose?
Maybe I did it on purpose.
I see.
Can I do it again?
Let's do it again.
Thank you.
It's hot, isn't it?
Are you tired?
No, I'm happy.
Is this the end?
Do you think so?
I should have been more patient.
Did you feel so good?
Yes, I felt good.
I felt good, too.
It's been a while since
the last time I saw you.
You're right.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
I can't believe this is the last time.
Thank you for your time.
You're welcome.
Thank you for your hard work.
I thought it wasn't enough.
It's funny.
He's surprised.
Do as you like.
Come here.
Lie down here.
Oh, you're wearing a T-mask.
I'm tired.
You're wearing a T-mask.
You're so cute.
Are you looking forward
to seeing more of Ecchi?
Yes.
Please look at me.
Oh, it feels good.
Do you want me to take it off?
I can see your buttocks very well.
Oho!
Fufufu
Ah...
Wah... Fufufu.
Ah... Ah... Ah... Oho... What
do you think you're touching?
My butt... I'm being licked.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
Ah...
Oh...
Ah... Oh...
Ah...
It's hard.
This is hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
Ah!
It's very wrinkled.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Ah, ah.
Oh.
Please don't do this to me anymore.
Do you like me?
I'm going to kiss you a lot.
I'm going to put a lot
of water on your feet.
Please relax.
I'll massage your legs.
Do you want to lie down?
You're very tense.
Really?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God...
It's good.
It's so hot.
Do you want me to give you some water?
No, I'm fine.
Why are you so sleepy?
I'm sorry.
Which side do you feel better?
I feel better in both sides.
Both sides?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to do more?
Yes.
If I drop it, it'll come out.
I want to lick it too.
Let me lick it.
Lick as much as you want.
It's hot.
Oh, it's hot.
Was it good?
Yes, it was.
What do you want me to do?
What are you doing?
It's cold.
What do you think I'm doing?
Oh...
What is it?
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
Here...
It's in.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What is it?
Mango.
Mango is so cute.
What is it?
It's a manko, isn't it?
It's not a butt, is it?
Which one do you think it is?
It's a manko.
This is my case.
Thank you.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
I said I'm okay.
I can't see anything.
No, I can't.
Ah!
Yeah.
Kimchi.
Oh!
Kimchi is so good.
Do you want some?
Yes.
I want to drink a lot.
Wow!
I'm sorry.
Can I lick you?
Do you like it?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
You're getting bigger and bigger.
Do you feel better?
ow.
ow oh.
ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow.
Thank you very much.
Really?
Wow.
I'm sorry.
You're standing up.
I have a favor to ask you.
Let me lick your feet.
Do you want to lick my feet?
Something is coming out.
Are you excited to drink the soup?
It's hot.
Can I have more?
More?
More.
I'll take it for you.
This is for you.
I'll give it to you.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for your efforts.
Thank you.
I'm going to put in the next one.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
My legs are going to break.
Can I do more?
Do more.
Do you want more?
More.
I want you to move.
I can't do it.
Not yet.
Not enough.
Stretch your body.
Give me your hand.
I'm going to fall.
I'm going to throw up.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Can I take it slowly?
No.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Your tummy hurts, right?
It hurts, huh?
It hurts, doesn't it?
Don't do it!
It doesn't hurt, does it?
I'm so tired.
Do you feel better?
I feel so good.
You can still sleep, right?
No, I can't.
I can't.
Wow.
Thank you for your viewing.