I'm going to eat it.
I'm going to do it.
I can do it.
You sit down.
I'm going to do it.
Sit down and eat.
I can do it.
Sit down and rest.
I'll be right back.
What's wrong?
I don't want to.
I broke the camera you were holding.
I'm sorry.
You're kidding.
I'm sorry. What should I do?
It's okay.
Don't worry. It's going to be all right.
But...
Get some rest. It's going to be all right.
I'm sorry. I was taking good care of him.
It's going to be all right.
Okay?
Okay.
Oh, he's here.
I'm going to the
shop.
Senpai!
I'm Kobusata.
Thank you very much.
Senpai came, so I'll go down a little.
I'm going to the
shop.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Senpai is here, so I'll go downstairs.
Okay.
Senpai, I'm sorry.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much.
But your company is closing down.
Isn't that obvious to the public?
I'm in charge of the local government, so I can't help it.
It's been two years?
No, it's been three years.
It's been since I married Marina.
I can't believe it.
You're still the same.
I'm still a moving company.
That's why you're as stiff as you used to be.
You're still the same.
You've gotten thinner, haven't you?
That's right.
My wife often says that I used to do rugby.
So you've become an elite man?
No, not yet.
I'll help you.
Are you all right?
What should I do?
No, it's all right.
I can't do it.
That's...
Don't be so hasty.
I'm Marina-san.
Huh?
That coach's daughter?
Yes.
I haven't greeted my parents yet, but...
How should I put it...
I wanted to get advice from Osawa-senpai.
Advice?
That's Onikouchi.
He's still stubborn and stubborn.
He's an old man.
Well, that's true, but...
If you have to,
get your daughter married to him.
Yes.
Anyway, congratulations.
I think she'll be a good wife.
Thank you.
Cheers!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
You did well.
Congratulations on your wedding.
And good job on your move.
Cheers!
You helped me move two times.
That's right.
At first, Takashi...
It's okay, Ozawa-senpai.
She knows about it.
Oh, I see.
At first, you helped Takahashi when he got married, didn't you?
That's right.
It's the same for Ozawa-senpai, but he also supported me mentally.
I heard from my father.
He said that the team would be well organized because he was good at taking care of others.
Did that Oniguson say that?
He didn't say a word to me.
I told you. It's still in my memory.
What? You wanted me to do it, didn't you?
Then I could have won.
Is that why you couldn't win?
But I really had a hard time with that divorce.
Thank you very much.
Are you going to cry again?
I'm going to cry.
Isn't it good to cry?
That's the time.
Will you marry Takashi, who got divorced and was depressed?
Do it at the Rakubi Obikai.
After that, get drunk and sneak into Kochi's house.
Are you going to sleep with this child?
Idiot!
I'm sorry. I came to get you out of prison.
I came to get you out of prison.
Anyway,
you shouldn't have touched a single finger
even when you were pregnant.
It's not just Kochi.
Think of us as enemies of all OBs.
If you're not happy, you'll be hated.
Yes, I'll make you happy.
Let's have another toast!
Cheers!
Let's eat sushi.
That's right.
Let's eat.
I'll start with the mackerel.
Itadakimasu.
It's really good.
I'm glad you liked it.
It's good.
That face.
It looks really good.
It's really good.
I'm sorry.
He's already gone.
You're right.
Did he really do rugby?
You can't see it, can you?
He did.
But he was often kicked out.
I knew it.
I don't think I can rely on you.
You fell in love with a man you can't rely on, right?
Well...
You can't rely on him, but what did you like about him?
He's kind.
But I wonder if it's really good to be kind to him.
I don't get it.
Isn't it good to be a kind man?
I wonder.
I don't know what to say.
Okay, let's play a game.
Game?
Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors.
What's that?
If you lose,
you have to tell me something that no one can say.
I'm going to talk to you.
Sounds interesting.
I'm curious about your embarrassing experience.
Okay, then let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Go ahead.
That's right.
Oh, about last weekend.
What?
I wanted to go to the bathroom, but I couldn't find it, so I got it from my dad.
No way. Where did you get it?
I ran home and got it from the company, but I couldn't find it, so I put it in my bag.
I just got it from my dad.
No way. Where did you get the key?
It was in my pocket.
I can't help it.
It's true.
I'll do it again.
Again?
Again.
First, I'll do it.
I lost.
Well, I'm going to ask him to come.
He's going to tell me something embarrassing that I've never heard of.
Oh, is there such a secret?
Oh, there it is.
What, what, what? Tell me.
I was talking about the fun.
That's right. That's right. I got it.
Okay, I'll be honest with you.
Actually, I had a dream.
What kind of dream?
Well, that's...
That muscular, macho rugby player...
...pushed me down...
...and that's what happened.
What is it?
You know what it is, don't you?
No, no, no, no, no.
You have to tell me clearly.
What is it?
So, everything.
What?
Did you kiss me?
So, everything.
Was it a scary dream?
Or was it a good dream?
It's a secret.
Tell me. You want to know, don't you?
Then I'll tell you when I win the next one.
Oh, sure.
Let's see...
Let's have a talk.
Okay.
It was a good dream.
Don't tell him.
You had a dream, didn't you?
And did you see her with such a dirty eye?
No, I didn't.
That's why you had such a dream.
Come on, let me think about it.
Do you like strong men?
What?
Wait, that's not it.
You can't?
No, I don't want to do that.
I see.
I'm a little drunk.
I'm sorry.
You're drunk.
I'm sorry I said something weird.
I'm going home now.
Take care of her.
Okay.
That's enough.
Bye.
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Should I bring the fridge?
Let's do it.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's go.
It's okay.
You can sleep over there.
Okay, let's go.
Can I carry all of these?
Yes, please.
Okay.
It's so light.
I'm going to the toilet.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
This is too heavy.
Be careful
Amazing
What is this?
Please put it in
It's really heavy
I'm tired.
I have to work hard.
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
Do you want to ride the train?
I can't ride it.
I don't want to take the double train.
I see.
Can you get on the train and show me the way?
Thank you.
That would be better.
I'll take the double train with her.
Maria,
I'll take the double train.
It's comfortable.
It's my first time taking the double train.
It's my first time, so I'm excited.
I'm sorry. I'll be in your care.
Okay, let's go.
All right, let's go.
It looks like there's going to be a lot of traffic.
That's right.
But I don't think it's going to work if we use high-speed cars.
All right.
Then you're the passenger.
Yes.
You can sit in the passenger seat
Okay
Let's go to the left
Amazing
You can touch a lot
Hold this
Are you okay?
Thank you
Let's ask the driver
Sit down
Thank you
Let's go
Are you okay?
I'm okay
I'll drive safe
Please
Don't tell your wife
I'm okay
Let's go
I'm counting on you
Thank you
I'll drive safely so please fasten your seat belt
I'm looking forward to working with you, Umi-chan.
I heard that your husband was also involved in sports with Ozawa-san.
Oh, that's right.
It's a long time ago.
Everyone, be careful.
I'll turn on the lights.
Are you going to turn on the lights?
That's great.
I'm going to clean up here.
Sit down.
Thank you very much.
This is great.
Thank you.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
Yes, it's not bad.
It's like a limousine, isn't it?
Have you ever ridden a limousine?
No.
It's my limousine, isn't it?
That's true.
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much for taking care of Mr. Ozawa.
Don't mention it.
It's been a while since we last met.
It must have been a hassle moving out of the blue.
It's not like that.
I was happy to meet a beautiful woman.
I don't need that kind of situation.
By the way, does Ozawa-san have a family?
Yes, he does.
Huh? He does? He's from the past?
Yes, he's from the past.
When my younger daughter graduated from college,
she got divorced from her husband.
When?
Five years ago, I had a ten-year divorce.
I see.
I've been married for a long time,
so I've always been at the forefront of the times.
Stop it.
How was it? Was it fun?
You're always making fun of me, aren't you?
Hahaha.
Life is hard work, isn't it?
I don't care if it's a lie, I just have to live brightly.
Isn't that better?
You are so cool.
I just read the lines of the novel.
Hahaha.
But that may be so.
Living brightly and fun even if it's a lie.
That's what I've been doing.
How long has it been since you moved?
Well, compared to Mr. Osawa, it may be a little less than a year.
She treats me like a princess, but...
What? You don't like being nice?
But if I say I don't like this, I wonder how greedy I am.
I'm the worst.
I'm sorry.
Osawa-san?
You can hit me if you want.
I'll do anything for you.
Don't say that.
I won't let you go like I did back then.
Until I make you mine.
I'm sorry.
No.
No!
Oh!
Oh, no!
Oh, I'm sorry. I wonder if it's okay.
I have to get out of here and climb the ladder.
I have to do it.
But I can't do it.
I have to get out of here.
I have to climb this ladder.
I can't do it.
Oh, it's hot!
Don't get cold!
Oh, my God.
It's okay, it's okay.
It owner is using diagonal
It goes straight for a while
Okay I got it
There's something you want to do
I'll do it
I'll smash everything
I can't breathe.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
It was incredible!
Let's go, let's go.
Do you feel better?
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Don't do this to me.
I'm tired. I'm tired.
Saira...
I'm so stupid.
No!
Ryo...
I'm scared.
Let's go.
Be careful.
It's hot.
Oh, it's hot.
Let's get out of here.
I'm sorry.
You did something terrible.
It's really terrible.
It's not going to work.
It's terrible.
It's cold.
It will be ready soon.
Oh, really?
Then there is a supermarket and a school nearby.
That's good.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right, Osan-san?
I'm fine.
Please open the door.
Okay.
Please wait.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm sorry.
Did you have a good time?
Not at all.
It was fun.
Really?
What would you like to drink?
Yes, please.
Thank you.
What do you want to dance?
Are you okay?
Yes, it was fun.
Really?
You shook.
Yes, I shook.
Like this?
More.
Are you okay?
Let's go to the car.
Wait.
Oh!
Here.
Is it heavy?
Are you okay?
It's okay.
Be careful.
It's dangerous.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm so tired.
This is amazing.
What's wrong?
I'm going to buy a broom.
You're going to buy a broom?
By the way, I'm going to buy something to drink
Oh, I see
In that case, Ike-chan
I'm going to buy something
Let's go together
Okay
I'll do it here
I'm sorry
I'm going to go
I'm already satisfied, so I won't do it anymore.
I'm not satisfied.
Are you satisfied?
I didn't.
You're not satisfied, are you?
Did you do it?
I don't know.
But I'll come back
It's okay.
I want to talk to you.
No, I don't want to talk to you.
Then talk to me.
No.
I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back soon.
It's hard and delicious, isn't it?
But I'll be back.
It's okay.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Hurry up.
Close the lid.
Don't.
I'm so tired.
Don't leave me alone.
Got it?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
You're so mean.
Why are you laughing?
Because it's weird.
Why? What's so weird about it?
I'm sorry.
I'm so glad you're here.
This is a nice place.
Yeah, it is.
It's close to a convenience store.
It used to be far from here.
It was inconvenient.
The supermarket was far from here, too.
Oh, right.
I'll go get some cardboard.
Thank you.
That's right.
It's not good for the bowl.
It's hard to eat
Thank you.
But it's okay.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
You too.
Let's go.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.
At least we made it in time to sleep.
I'll open the cardboard box from tomorrow.
I'm sorry. I'll leave it to you.
But don't push yourself too hard.
I'll be fine.
Anyway, Ozawa-san...
What?
You're still so energetic.
You're all glistening, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I'm all glistening.
I see.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little tired today.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Are you okay?
I can't do it because I'm not okay.
Good night.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
When my younger daughter entered college, she broke up with her father-in-law.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Well...
Well, I wonder if it's the answer to the mid-term question.
Is there a problem with such a good guy?
I see.
I'm sorry.
Come on, come on.
I'll do anything for you, so hit me now.
Don't say that.
I won't let you go like I did back then.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
Do what you want to do.
I'll make it happen.
Let's go.
My sister is in the hospital.
I'm thinking about the things she needs to do.
She's taking the medicine.
Don't worry.
I'll be here with you.
She's okay.
I'll be there with you too.
I'll be there with you.
After making a hole in the dough, cover with plastic wrap and let it rest for 30 minutes.
After 30 minutes, remove the plastic wrap and let it rest for another 30 minutes.
I'm sorry.
Is he working?
Yes.
Is he working alone?
Did you get the hang of it?
Not yet.
Then I'll help you.
Not at all.
You're right.
You like dogs, don't you?
If he finds out, it's all your fault.
It's all my fault.
Ah!
I'll take care of this Sunday.
I'm sorry I haven't made any progress.
It's none of your business. I'll take care of it. I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
What?
It's your job, but you don't know the meaning of apologizing.
Thank you for the meal.
I'll go now.
See you.
I'm going to sleep now.
I'll just sleep a little more.
Okay.
I'll get back to work.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Happy birthday!
I don't know. I guess it's like this.
Congratulations!
Who is it?
You didn't clean up at all, did you?
I don't think I did.
Why not?
I thought Mr. Ozawa wouldn't come if I cleaned up the cardboard.
When you're done with the cardboard, then you'll thinkpresents won't hang around anymore.
It's so good!
Are you okay?
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Sarah.
I'm so happy.
I love you so much.
Come on, move.
Take it easy.
We have sex, don't we?
It hurts.
I'm crying.
It's still in my mouth.
It's okay.
It's my blood.
It's still in my mouth.
Go!
You didn't move.
This is scary.
This feels awful.
Marisa's
I love you the most when you're tired.
You're amazing.
You're so strong.
I'm strong.
We're really the perfect size.
I'm sorry.
I want to do it every day.
I want to go to the hospital every day.
Oh, it's great.
It's perfect.
It's great.
Does it feel good?
It's the best.
I don't do it because I don't want you to feel bad.
I told you.
I'm sorry if I told you.
Can I go now?
Yes, you can go.
I'm going.
Amazing.
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Wow!
I want to drink too.
Me too.
Okay.
I'll drink too.
I'm not a bad person.
I love you.
She is crying because she is afraid of water.
I am worried about water.
Then okikiri
Fine, you can skip that, right
Oh
Cheese
Oh, it's hot.
It's fine.
I'm not a fan.
It's good.
If you eat too much, you'll get sick.
I'm not a fan.
Why do you keep eating?
It's so hot.
That's great.
It's perfect.
I'm so happy.
You look so cool.
Don't cry.
I'm sleepy.
Oh, it's hot!
It's hot!
I'm sorry.
No!
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
Oh, I feel so good.
What's going on?
I feel sick.
Pero no te heparé.
Pero no te.
Pero no te pero拿手。
I'm sorry.
I can't forgive you.
I don't know if I'm responsible for this.
I can't blame you.
You're so kind.
But I don't need this kind of kindness anymore.
Ozawa-san.
Mr. Ozawa, take me away from him.
Thank you for watching!