Where is the child?
I asked him to go to school after school.
Then, until about 6 o'clock.
From boring daily life to non-daily life.
Welcome.
Last week, I was
invited by Miki, a friend of
my mother, and came
here for the first time.
I'm glad you came.
I'm sorry.
What about the other
day? Here you are.
Would you like something to drink?
Water? Thank you.
Here you are.
Last time, I ran away just
because he hugged me.
I was surprised and ran away from the
pleasure that I had never experienced.
Did you do it with your husband
after you got home the other day?
Yes.
I do it right away and
start with a dramatic story.
Aoi is serious.
But, you know, I
thought it was hard to do
post-processing because
there was medicine left.
Processing?
Sexual desire processing.
Your words are vulgar.
You can't be popular with
women just because you're rich.
Oh, it's okay.
You don't have to be popular.
It's a problem if you have a strange
feeling of love with your father.
Is that so?
In fact, it was hard to
have sexual desire left.
It was hard for me to live alone.
That's why I went back to my daily life.
I stepped in again.
I know it's a road I can't go back.
What are you going to do?
It's the same as the last time.
Don't be nervous.
Show me your tongue.
I love you.
Isn't it different from the
medicine I took the other day?
No, it should be the same.
Is it the same?
I'm very nervous.
Maybe you're relaxed today.
You were nervous the other
day, weren't you? I'm sorry.
You're quite tall.
I'm not.
I can't tell the difference
between you and me.
I see.
Hey!
What is this?
Well,
I'll give you a massage.
I'm not good at it.
Please put it on the counter.
I got it.
Enjoy it.
Relax.
You enjoy it, too.
Of course.
I'm sorry.
I broke it.
Don't worry.
Are you okay?
Is it good? It's good.
The water is good.
You got used to it.
I got used to it.
Otherwise, your body will be a mess.
A mess.
Baki-baki.
Baki-baki?
Yes.
Are you going to be Baki-baki?
I'm going to be Baki-baki.
That's also Baki-baki.
Yes, that's also Baki-baki.
But I was really happy that you came today.
It tickles.
It tickles?
I feel ticklish.
Your hair is tangled.
I just touched your hair.
I know.
It feels good to be touched.
You look beautiful today.
I'm sure this medicine is
different from the previous one.
Nothing has changed.
It's just a little dark.
I just touched you, but
I can't feel it so much.
You have beautiful legs.
You sat next to me.
My hands moved on their own.
It's amazing, isn't
it? It's amazing.
It's amazing.
Your whole body is
like running electricity.
Are you running
electricity? It's amazing.
I can't remember anything.
It's okay. You'll forget.
Everyone forgets.
You'll be a good mother from tomorrow.
I was surprised.
I was really surprised.
I can't do that.
My ears hurt.
I can't do that, either.
〔Painful moaning〕 There.
..
〔Mouth open〕
Let's open your eyes.
Here.
How does it feel to be on top
of your clothes? It feels great.
You are so beautiful.
I'm so happy.
I can't believe that you are a child.
Oh, my God.
I feel it.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to mess up my hair.
I want to be more like Miku Miku.
Miku Miku? Miku Miku.
Let's start from here.
Wow, amazing.
It's flat.
Oh, it's flat.
Flat.
My nipples are flat.
You're not touching at all.
Don't make me so embarrassed.
I might hurt you.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
You have beautiful boobs.
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, there's a lot of electricity running.
I can't take it anymore.
Ah, it feels so good.
Are you okay?
Why don't you take off your clothes?
Because it's hot.
Wow, it's amazing.
How far is the sky?
It's like a dream.
It's a slumber.
It's a slumber, slumber, slumber.
That's right.
If it was usual, it would be like this.
What did you just say?
Yes, that's right.
What will happen if you cry?
I think it's amazing.
Don't tease me.
Oh, my God.
You're dirty.
I want you to do a lot more.
How?
It's already messed up.
It's sticky.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my god.
I'm so scared.
No, I can't.
I'm so tired.
I'm just moving slowly like this.
I can't do it.
I'm going crazy.
I'm going to die soon.
It's so weird.
I just put it in a little.
It's totally different from
the medicine before.
It can't be the same.
Oh, no.
I love you.
I love you so much.
You haven't been licked yet.
I haven't been licked yet.
I want you to be licked a lot.
I feel sorry for you.
I'm doing my best to take care of you.
About the house?
What was it? Your husband.
My husband?
Which one was it?
Was I there?
Forget about it now.
I want to go.
Let's go.
Let's go there.
Ah...
I can't do it!
I can't do it! I'll do it.
I want you to be kissed by me.
Uhh….
I want to be kissed by you.
I want you to be kissed by me.
Your skin is very sticky.
Your skin is sticky.
You have to remove your chakras properly.
Oh, I forgot.
It hurts.
Why are you doing
this to me? It's all right.
I'm going to take care of you.
Please take care of me.
Wow.
It feels good.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry I'm sorry.
I feel good.
I'm going to go.
Oh, it feels so good.
It's going, it's going,
it's going, it's going.
Oh, it's going.
What a way of life.
I can't do it anymore.
I want you to do something for me tomorrow.
Come on.
Get up.
Rub your face.
Rub your tongue.
I can't do it.
※I'm sorry.
It feels good.
I hate you!
Oh, no! I'm so nervous.
I'm so nervous.
No, please continue.
Oh, my! I can't do it.
You are good at playing with it.
I want to play with it.
Do you want to
see it? Yes, I do.
Let me see it.
OK.
My husband is not here.
Who is he?
Is he your boyfriend?
I don't think so.
I'm so happy to see you, Ochinchi.
Wow, you are shining.
You are hard.
You are really hard.
You are beautiful, so I became hard.
I'm glad.
The day you made it hard.
You smell so bad.
You're a pervert.
Wow, you're licking a ball.
You're licking a gold ball.
Wow, wow, wow.
Ah, something is coming out.
It's the same as you.
When I listen to the sound of the
wind, it comes out more and more.
Then, I'll make it more sound.
It smells good.
It's very good.
You like to lick your penis.
Do you like licking
your feet? Yes, I do.
If you don't like it,
you can't lick it so well.
When did you lick your feet?
When was it?
I think it was a month or two ago.
You don't remember? No, I don't.
Did you want to lick your feet?
Did you want to eat a lot?
Yes, I wanted to eat a lot.
It feels good.
Ah...
Wow...
That's a nice sound.
Wow... Crackle, crackle.
I'm glad.
Wow...
You have a lot of pus in your mouth.
That's amazing.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
ーOh, my god.
ーI'm coming.
It's no good.
If you do it too hard, it'll come out.
You've got a lot.
It's been a long time.
30 minutes left until my
daughter goes back to school.
Until then, I go back
to being a serious mom.
I go back to my daily
life from my non-daily life.
I have to go back to my daily life,
but the remaining days of pleasure
bring me back to my non-daily life.
Bring me back.
Come on, Dopa Dopa.
That's right.
It's a medicine to wake up your instincts.
Instincts? That's right.
After all, you're an animal.
I can't believe you're doing this.
I don't have a PTA, so I don't
know much about Aoi's husband.
Besides, we are animals, aren't we?
If we have a chance, we
will give a treat anywhere.
A treat?
Yes.
A treat.
It's the best.
It's so sticky.
But we need to add some medicine.
Medicine?
Yes.
I think so.
I think it's getting worse.
Right?
It'll be great if we add it.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
Wow.
Yes.
Oh, but it feels good.
The instinct you have now
will turn around smoothly.
What? Turn around smoothly?
Yes.
Turn around smoothly?
Turn around smoothly.
Drink this and you'll feel better.
I'll feel better...
In 30 seconds, right?
Yes.
If you drink this for 30 seconds,
you'll feel great.
I was scared.
Do you want to put it in?
I can't stand it.
It's a little dark.
No, no, not yet.
Ten seconds left.
No, I can't.
Then try putting it in yourself.
Five seconds left.
I can't.
I can't put it in.
It's been 30 minutes.
Wait a minute.
I didn't put it in.
Why?
It's hot.
I'll put it in.
I'm sorry.
AHHHHHHHHH!!!!!
UGHHHHHHH!!!!
%$!&$$!!
censored
I'm covered in bruises!
You can't even tell
if I'm alive or dead Ahhhhhh
UGHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!
Then I'll do this
AHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!
Gahhhh UGHHHH!!!!
UGHHHH!!!!!
UGHHHHHHH!!!
I still have a lot
to do Oh, my God.
I can't move at all.
I'm drooling.
It's strange.
You remember it on your own.
I want to move by myself.
No! Don't touch
me! Then I'll stop.
I want you to touch me.
I want you to touch me a lot.
A lot? I want to go.
I pulled it too much and it came off.
Put it in without using your hands.
I can't use my hands.
Come on, put it in with just one.
aaahhh I have to run!
ueahhhh aahhh
aaahhh ooohhh aahhh eeehh
ahh aahhh
eeehh
aahhh aahhh
oooh
What's wrong? I'm cold.
Then I'll stop.
I don't want to move.
You move by yourself.
It's cold.
It's cold again.
It's amazing.
It's very tight.
You are amazing.
Ouch! I can't do it.
Let me do it.
I can't do it.
Oh, my God.
I want more.
One more time.
Raise your leg.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
Ouch! Ouch! It hurts.
I'll move your neck.
Show me your beautiful boobies.
I'm going to poke you deeply.
Don't be angry.
Don't go.
〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔
〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔
〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔
〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 〔 I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't move my hips.
I don't know what to do.
I'm so sorry.
It feels so good.
Are you okay?
Well, I am fine, thank you...
Ahh!
Watermelon?
No.
After pill.
You'll be excited again when you transform.
The scenery that I have never
seen, the daily life that is fading away.
Until yesterday, my husband
didn't have any complaints.
He accepted my forced
sex once every few months.
I accepted it.
But now that I know
that pleasure, I can't
imagine getting along
with this person anymore.
I want to be loved.
What's wrong?
I wonder if I can't stop my next plan.
You'll be addicted.
Next, I want to be with another daddy.
It's Dekachin.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Then, let's play
rock-paper-scissors and decide
what to give to Dekachin
and Aoi as a pair.
Oh, I see.
After all, it's great sex.
When I'm tired, I feel
like I'm going to faint.
I'm getting goosebumps.
It's an hour earlier than the navigation.
That's amazing.
Didn't you get
drunk? I was fine.
I was drinking a lot.
That's different.
Do you have it? It's too much.
It's called Maserati.
It's stylish.
It's a Nagoyaki cat.
Everyone is riding it.
It's a Ferrari.
It's a little old.
I can't ride it.
It's too fast.
But you couldn't say it was
fast, could you? It was amazing.
I don't think so.
If you work a little harder, you'll
be able to do it in 30 seconds.
It's been a while since I've done it.
What should we do with
the first combination?
Let's do it as usual.
Let's do it with four people.
One, two, three.
Good bye.
I forgot.
Oh, I forgot.
I'm glad.
It's not good if it's like this.
I prepared a new one today,
so you can see a different world.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go.
What is it? Here you are.
Call me if you need anything.
OK.
New brand.
What?
What will it be?
Do you want to try?
SOSORITATSU
SOSORITATSU?
SOSORITATSU Right?
It's my first time.
Let's get into the stimulation.
Follow me.
I feel something strange.
I'm getting a little nervous.
Right?
What's wrong? It's so fast.
It's getting warmer.
It's getting hotter.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
Wow, what is this?
My tongue is getting hotter and hotter.
I'm getting very sensitive.
It's so hot.
I just touched it.
What is this?
I'm starting to feel sick.
My boobs are sticking out.
I haven't been touched yet.
What's this?
I want you to touch me.
Why are you touching
me? I don't know.
This is the first time.
You are so cute.
What should I do? I don't know.
I can feel it very much.
Hey, look.
Oh, no.
Look at me.
I'm just playing with you.
Can I go? I can't.
You can't? I can't.
You can't?
I can't, I can't.
I can't.
If you make me cry
like that, I'm going to cry.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Show me more erotic figure.
Mom, please help me.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I can't believe it.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
I can't speak any more.
Please help me.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
【【Shout】】 【【Shout】】
【【Shout】】 Oh, oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Ouch!
Oh, it's so cold!
Oh, no!
The water's dripping.
Oh my God!
No.
What's wrong? Oh, no.
Not yet, not yet.
Wait a minute.
No, no, no.
I haven't hit you yet.
What's going on?
What's going on? Koko.
..
Koko...
What's going on?
Oh, no!
Oh, it's cold! Oh, it's cold.
It's cold, isn't it? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
I'm so wet.
You got dirty.
My underwear got dirty.
I know.
I'm so wet.
I want you to do more.
I won't be found out.
Are you okay? I'm okay.
I want to go home.
Then, you should be more careful.
I'm so nervous.
No, no, no.
One more time.
I can't do it.
It's okay.
I'll get it dirty.
Oh, it's cold.
It's getting warmer.
Look at me.
What do you want?
I want a pair of scarves.
Scarves.
I want a scarf to put my skin on.
I want an ointment.
Don't worry.
Whoops, I wanted to say thank
you, but my Korean is not perfect...
Don't cry, it's gonna be just for today.
Thank you.
Oh, it's so hot.
It's so hot.
It's very hard.
I like to spit it out.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious? It's delicious.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Are you excited?
Are you even more excited?
Look, you're bleeding.
Oh, I see.
We are going to get our hair cut.
What's happening?
Where are we going?
Good!
Wow!
Awesome! A little more.
How do you feel? It hurts.
It hurts.
How does it work? I don't know.
If it gets bigger than
this, it will explode.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Does it feel good?
You're so small.
I'm not ready yet.
My husband and I bought a new cat
tower for the first time in a long time.
It is a cat tower that can
be used for a long time.
Pocky is very hard.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm so happy.
Look at me from above.
With you?
Your breasts are the best.
Do you love me? Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, my tongue is dirty.
Oh, my tongue is getting bigger.
Oh, my tongue is getting worse.
Thank you.
Oh, my head.
Oh, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Wow.
Oh, it feels good.
Open your mouth.
〈The sound of a baby crying.
〉 I'm sweating a lot.
〉 He is very excited.
He is very excited.
He is sticking out his tongue.
Wow, you have a big belly.
Yes, you do.
Let me go.
Give me a lot.
Do you like shark? Yes, I do.
Please give me a lot of jam.
Give me a lot of jam.
You got a lot of jam!
Wow! It feels good.
It's good.
It's delicious.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm a little sleepy.
Is this good for whitening?
It might get bigger.
I want more if it gets bigger.
You want more? I want more.
She's not answering.
Where the hell is she at this hour?
If she doesn't answer, it'll be a problem.
I can't help it.
I didn't even do the laundry.
Let's try something else this time.
What is it?
It may sound a little different.
It's so green.
Let go of your tongue.
I'm going to ask you in 30 seconds.
I'm getting hot.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's getting hot.
There, too.
Here, too.
You want to touch it, don't you?
You want to touch
it, but you can't help it.
If you want, you can touch it yourself.
You can go to heaven.
Heaven?
Yes.
Come on, show me.
I can't touch you.
I just touched the air.
You're trembling.
Look, you're trembling so much.
I didn't touch you, but
you're trembling so much.
No, you can't touch me.
I can't touch you?
No.
What?
You want to touch
it, but you can't help it.
I can't stand it.
Let me see.
Do you like it? Yes, I do.
I love it.
Let me see.
Let me touch it.
I can't help but feel that my body is cold.
Where do you feel cold? Here.
I can't stand it.
My nose is running.
Ouch!
What have I been doing all this time?
I want a lot more.
Oh, my God! It's so hot.
It's so hot.
Can I take off my pants?
No.
No?
This is a video taken on
the day of the earthquake.
The video was taken
on the day of the quake.
It smells good.
I think it's enough for you.
No, it's not.
It stinks.
This one is big, too.
What do you want to do?
I want to lick you.
Are you going to lick me? Okay.
Your back is so soft.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't
it? It's delicious.
You are so happy.
You love me so much, don't you?
I won't run away from you.
You are so happy.
I love you so much.
You are so hard.
It's hot.
I was able to sleep well tonight.
I'm glad I slept well.
I'm going to make a video of
the process of making this video.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
Good morning.
It's all done.
There you go.
Let me see your tongue.
It's delicious.
Hoshi
Hoshi Give it to me.
Oh, it feels good.
Can I put your tongue out?
Are you ready?
I want you to make me feel better.
Welcome back.
Did you drink?
Yes.
There was a gathering of friends.
You haven't moved recently.
Miu was worried about your mother.
Miu? She's asleep.
What do you mean?
Are you giving up your child?
Even if I get married and have
a child, you didn't help me at all.
Can't I just grow my wings?
No, I just said it's okay once in a while.
Once in a while?
You're always looking around.
As Miki said, it's
true that if you rebel
against your strength,
you won't be cheated.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying.
I'm not sure if it's a baby
crying or a baby's crying.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Are you okay?
Are you okay?
What?
Can't you come today? I'm sorry.
My husband is very suspicious.
No.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What?
What's that?
What kind of man?
App Matching?
Yeah, today too.
Are you young?
I'm a college student.
Aren't you hot? I know.
But
You're always bored with
your dad, aren't you? Hi, I'm Aji.
What's it like to be a college student?
Unlike you, I know I'm getting serious.
Scary.
30 seconds.
It's getting hot.
20 seconds.
Wow, I'm getting hungry.
10 seconds.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Do you want to drink some herbal medicine?
I don't want to.
I don't want to mix it.
Then, I'll take this.
What should I do? It's okay.
I'm so sad.
What are you sad about?
This is a video of me
practicing my English.
I'm nervous about this video.
I'm nervous about my English.
It's so dirty.
I can see that you're enjoying it.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Today, I have something more fun.
What is it?
Do you want to fly?
You'll be a baby.
What? A baby?
It'll be a big deal.
What's that? What's going to happen?
What's going to happen?
You can look forward to it.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I feel so good.
I feel so good.
ーWhat's wrong?
ーYour sticker is...
ーI can't die.
ーI'm gonna die.
It smells so good.
I'm going to sleep.
Don't play with me.
Ah!
Sis! What happened to you? Sis!
How is it?
Is it okay?
Are you okay?
Don't move your hip.
I'm going to clean your hip.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't cry.
I'm sorry.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a thing.
I've never seen such a thing.
ーHow do you feel? ーI'm fine.
ーDo you want to have a break? ーNo.
ーYou are strong.
ーYou can't get up.
Are you satisfied only with your mouth?
I can't be satisfied only with my mouth.
Let me see.
I put it in.
Show me your butt.
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
※This is the sound of a baby swallowing.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm going to do it.
Do you want more? I want more.
Look at this.
I put the cat food in the bowl.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
〔Crying〕
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Oh my god!
What should I do?
※This is not a sound effect.
Oh, it's hard.
Let's do it again.
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
I want to go to the bathroom, but
my stomach hurts more and more.
I'm going to sleep.
I feel so good.
How do you feel? I feel so good.
Good.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a baby crying in front of a camera.
I was surprised to see a baby
crying in front of a camera.
Hurry up.
My stomach hurts.
Do you like me? I like you.
Oh, it's so hot.
Mom, I'm going to sleep.
You have a very gentle face.
You look like a real animal.
I'm going to sleep.
Not yet.
Not yet?
May I go to bed?
I'm going to sleep.
I feel good.
It's broken.
Oh my, oh my!
消えた。 涙出た。
嗚呼、水。
涙痛い。 痛い。 It's a lie.
It's a lie.
I'm sorry.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
I don't know what I said.
Oh my god.
I'm going to take a bath.
〔Yuko's mother is crying.
〕 You're dead.
It's not over yet.
〔Yuko's mother is crying.
〕 Are you satisfied?
I want to help you.
〔Yuko's mother is crying.
〕 What are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
Which one?
I can't hear anything.
私の声はあまりにも小さくなく、 しみじみにしています。
私の声がより小さくなるまで気をつけましょう。
私は非常に熱いです。 私は本当に怪我をしていた。
K.Y.M.Nは私にとってのとても悲しいことです。
私は原因としてそれをやめられない。
I finally got the monthly salary for the
month and a half of raising my daughter.
I was wondering how she
would react when she heard
that her daughter not
received the monthly salary.
But she loved the word she had received.
Oh, my God!
Are you all right?
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm so happy.
Ah!
Ah! Welcome back.
You look a bit pale.
I had a bad smell of tobacco in the
bar, so I'm going to take a shower.
I'll go to bed first.
Good night.
I'm going to watch it on
LINE while waiting for it.
I'm so busy.
What is this video?