I wonder if Yuzuriha will come.
I'm sure they will.
They have a meeting with the PTA.
It's a two-day trip to the
hot springs with Akazuma.
You should stay away for a while.
Chairman, don't say that.
Please don't say that.
You are hated by Yuuzuriha, aren't you?
Mr. Horii, please don't stalk me.
Are you still a member of PTA?
But the president is also
hated, isn't he? My son.
..
He's a good boy.
Your son, Kazumasa-kun,
was the first one to do it.
My son is not a bad boy.
He's desperate.
He wants to be recognized as a good boy.
It's raining, but I'm looking
forward to the hot spring.
It's been a long time since
I've been to a hot spring.
What do you mean your wife can't come?
I participated in the story because my
husband and I were in the same class.
The girl below me had a fever.
It can't be helped.
I have a child, too.
And your husband doesn't
want to come, either.
It's the same thing.
My husband was called to work suddenly.
But he will come in the evening.
Will he come?
I'm sorry that my wife can't come.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
I have all the staff,
so there's no problem.
That's right. Please get on quickly.
I'll cut the meeting early.
Please spend the night with your
husband and your wife without water.
Izuihon's husband is running a
cafe in front of the station, right?
The owner of the
building and I are friends.
The owner of the building
put a claim in the cafe.
As expected, the president
of a real estate company.
There are collaborators in various places.
Well, but I made some money.
Hello.
Is this your husband?
I can smell coffee.
I don't think so.
He's taking good care of himself.
I hope he doesn't regret it.
Is this really the Akane 3rd floor?
It's very different from
the picture on the website.
It's a business, so it's a little bad.
But it's true, it's the Akane 3rd floor.
It's a premonition that
Showa literature loved.
Is that so? Welcome.
You are a PTA staff, aren't you?
I'll show you your room,
so please follow me.
I'll take your luggage.
Thank you.
Here you are.
It's delicious.
I can't get enough of it.
It's good.
I'm so happy.
Stop it.
Excuse me.
We haven't had a meeting for a while.
Well, well. We're on a trip after all.
How about a drink, Mr.
Yuzuriha? He doesn't want to.
Stop it!
Well, I'll take it.
Excuse me.
What?
I told you, it's a wedding ceremony.
But, I think Atsushi doesn't like it.
I think it will change
if we hold a ceremony.
I don't think so. I don't feel it now
that Karen has become a mother.
I don't know.
A little.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm fine.
Oh, there she is.
It's a woman. It's a woman at this time.
Actually, I have something
important to tell you.
What is it?
It's Atsushi's fault.
It's about last month.
Atsushi drove around my car and
crashed into the car in front of me.
I was drunk.
I was drinking alcohol
without a driver's license.
It's a lie.
It's true.
My daughter was also in the car.
But don't worry.
I paid the tax and wiped it off.
How much?
What do you mean?
I have to pay the repair fee.
It's not about the money.
It's your responsibility.
Am I wrong? You're right.
Please come here.
I'm glad you understand.
Please spare my body.
Are you stupid?
You only have a body and no bones.
Please, if this becomes public, my
daughter will be expelled from school.
Please.
Sakuma, help her.
Do you think you can
stay calm in this body?
I'll lick your body.
I'll lick your eyes.
That's right.
I'm like this.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a scene in
my life, and I'm very happy
that I was able to do it.
I'm very happy that I was able to do it.
Did you really
do it? Yes, I did.
What are you doing?
You can't just do it.
You have to throw mine properly.
Takuma, you have to make it in time.
I can't do anything.
I have a chance evidence.
Just for now, just for now.
If you bear it, it will be solved.
You never lick my shoulder compared
to the future of your child, do you?
No, you have to do it properly.
You have to pull my
armpit and lick it properly.
You did it well. I'll reward you properly.
If it's a finger, it's still a low hurdle.
Takuma, are you licking it properly?
Not only Tetsu-san, but
Tetsu-san also licks it firmly.
You licked it properly.
You licked it well.
Look, look.
Are you OK?
The future of your
precious son is at stake.
You shouldn't just feel good.
Look at me.
Please lick my neck.
You don't have to lick my neck yet.
Satsuma.
How do you feel about
Yuzuriya's back? I feel better.
Oh, you feel better.
No, no, no.
You feel better.
It's no good.
Let's lick it in this state next time.
You have to do it properly.
Sakuma, look, here too.
Let's do our best for the child.
Let Maoko lick a lot and live.
Sakuma, you did your best.
You did your best.
Yulia, you felt good, didn't you?
Then, you have to serve me more.
I'll turn my butt to you.
This time, you lick my butt.
I have a video of the accident.
I'll shake your butt.
Do you want me to rub your back?
You are a good boy.
Do you do this to your
husband? Yes, I do.
Good boy.
You can lick my back.
This time, I will rub your belly.
You are a good boy.
It's the best.
If you don't wash properly,
I don't know what will happen to you.
Sakuma's daughter's future is at stake.
So you have to wash properly.
You're doing well.
Hey, Sakuma.
You want me to wash you, don't you?
Sakuma wants me to wash his hands.
He is crouching.
Sakuma, wash his hands.
He is rubbing his hands.
Sakuma, wash your hands.
Sakuma, do you like bread?
I think my bread is better.
I'll wash my hands, too.
This is Sakuma's.
And this is mine.
OK.
Come closer to me.
Let's lick together.
It's fun.
Yuzuriha-san.
How do you feel?
You don't say anything.
This is my shampoo.
I'll finish it tomorrow.
Oh!
I don't know about that.
If you don't take good care of her,
I can't delete that video.
Please do your best.
Oops! It's dangerous.
You ate this big.
You did well.
Sakuma, sit here.
You have to eat this.
I'm sorry.
You are sorry?
You're not a child anymore, so
there's no excuse for this, right?
Please stop that.
No, no, no.
Oh, you're attacking the entrance.
If you're going to be so rough,
I'm going to stab you in the butt.
Don't do that.
You are already in the Showa era.
No, I'm not.
Hold on a little more.
Rubber...
Rubber is not narrow.
I'm a Showa man.
There is no such thing as a condom.
Why?
Why? Why?
It's too intense.
Too intense? It's too hot.
I want to throw you in the water.
No, no, no.
It's too cold.
Wait, I'll do it.
I'm going to lick your
nipples, not just your nipples.
Let me see your feet.
Look at your feet.
I'm going to lick your nipples.
Mom, I can't do it.
You've done your best so
far, so let's do a little more.
You're doing a good job.
This is the real mother figure.
Can I be fierce?
I might say it later.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ahhhhhhh!
What? Why are you trying to run?
Let me hold you, Otomi.
Ahhhhhhh!
Ahhhh!
Oh, my!
Ahhhhhhh!
You want to get in the water, don't you?
You don't have to get in the water.
Are you ready?
You shouldn't do that.
What's going on?
You are amazing.
Do you feel good?
I'm glad you feel better
thanks to miso soup.
I'm glad.
Asakuma, you feel better, don't you?
Now, let's get you on my back.
「Hey, let's go home.
」 「No, I can't go
home. I can't go home.
」 「Hey, you shouldn't
be with me and Sakema.
」 「Shake your hip for
your son. You've grown up.
」 「Are you watching
Sakema? You're a good woman.
」 Don't look at me so much.
I wish I had come out of this cocoon.
You are the worst.
But I feel better now.
What's wrong?
Are you waiting to go again?
Put your hand here.
Well, I'll do it.
Let me move more.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You can wear it.
I want to do it more.
You can wear it wherever you like.
Show me your teeth.
You are cute.
This is also hot.
I feel so good.
I can't stand it anymore.
No, no, no.
Let's take her inside.
Please, no.
Listen, it's an order.
I'll take you inside.
No, no, no.
Please, no.
I'll take you inside.
It's dangerous.
Please, no.
There was no choice but to do this.
It's amazing.
It's completely exposed.
But it's still not enough.
It's over there.
It's going to be horizontal over there.
I'll put it in.
Can I put this
in too? I'm sorry.
Please, don't cry.
I'm sorry.
Can you do it? Please.
What?
You were good at it.
No, I'm not.
I'm not kidding.
I can do it.
What can you do?
Tell me what you can do.
What can I do?
What can you do? I don't know.
You don't know what you can do.
It's so cold.
I think I'm dying... I'll be OK.
I'll be OK.
Oh!
You may be in love.
If you know you can't
escape, I'll let you go.
Then, I'll do it with my mouth.
Come here.
Will you really erase it?
I'll do my best.
Wait a minute.
Look, Chinchin doesn't just lick
his tail, he licks his balls as well.
He licks his balls as well.
He doesn't just lick his balls,
he licks his mouth as well.
You know it well.
When you lick a ball, you have
to squeeze it with your hand.
Like this?
You have to squeeze it more slowly.
Let me enjoy eating for a long time.
Do you want to eat a lot of salmon?
You still have to eat it with your mouth.
Try to eat it with your mouth this time.
Did you eat it well?
If you eat it,
this will touch your nipples.
Don't touch me.
Touch me and move your mouth slowly.
Izuya-san,
You have such a nice boob.
Can you pinch my
boob? Pinch my boob.
You can do this much,
can't you? It's okay.
Then, can I hold the video
all the time? That's right.
Like this? That's right.
That's right.
Can you put a toothpick
on my dick while pinching it?
Yuzuha-san, do you know
how to make me feel better?
Like this? That's right.
Yuzuha-san, this feels good, doesn't it?
I'll show you how to make me feel better.
I'll show you how to do it.
I'm going to stick my
nipple on your nipple.
You can do it, right? Oh, yeah.
It's a little slippery.
I'm going to stick my
nipple on your nipple.
Did you do it?
Now you feel good,
don't you? The other side.
That's right.
Squeeze it.
Oh, it's coming out.
I'm getting confused.
Let's eat again.
You've gotten much better.
Did you get confused because I pinched you?
I'll give you a reward if you slurp.
I'll give it to you.
Swallow it well.
Oh, no.
Oh, I'm almost there.
All right.
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
How is it?
Let me see the sesame seeds in your mouth.
Oh, you've received it well.
You've done a good job.
Look, I've erased it.
I'll come again.
Hello?
You?
Are you Kallen? I called you many times.
By the way, when are you coming here?
I'm already here. It's the
third floor, isn't it? Yes, but.
..
But it's a great inn.
The whole room is an ocean
view, and the golf course is closed.
It's expensive.
What do you mean?
There's no beach or golf course here.
There's no way there isn't.
I'm sorry, I'm hanging up.
Karen?
Excuse me, is anyone there?
Please help me! Karen.
..
Let me go.
What?
If I stay here, I'll...
I stole the black key.
Let's go.
I'm sorry about the hot spring.
I was threatened.
Let's forget about it.
I don't think I can forget it.
Can I ask you one last time?
What are you talking about?
I'm betting on my daughter and the scales.
If she finds out that I'm
the one who let her go,
I don't know what kind of
harassment she'll do to my daughter.
I don't know if I can do it, but if I have
a memory with Kanetsu, I'll give up.
If you refuse,
I can't get out of the car.
Kotoko, if you ask me, I'll do it.
Please bear with me.
I'm sorry to make you do it every week.
Double life?
Isn't it a double life to give birth to a
body to do something? Please stop.
No, I can't.
Oh, my God.
You are wet.
I'm sorry.
I became a PTA because you left.
I've always liked you.
Please go.
Can you love me now?
I have a son, too.
He's alive.
Can I take him
out? No, you can't.
I'll take responsibility.
That's not the problem.
I'm tired, aren't I? You can sleep.
Karen, we've arrived.
I'm sorry.
I don't want this guy!
No, I don't want it.
Chairman.
She can't stand it.
Let me wear this.
Is this OK?
I'm begging you.
Wow! Look at me.
You are looking at me.
Wow!
What's wrong?
You feel good, don't
you? I'll show you.
Look at me.
Look at my tongue.
You're not honest.
This is...
...Sakuma's.
You should be honest.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Even if you're his mother...
Hatsushi-kun won't admit it.
I've been asked what I
should do to get you out of here.
So I told him to worry about you.
Well, if you drink alcohol and
drive a car, you'll be in trouble.
Well, if you do that, you'll
be able to get out of it.
But I didn't think it
would cause an accident.
I didn't think it would be like this.
Dig!
No! No! Wait! No!
No!
I don't like this guy.
You were abandoned by a child.
Your mother is disqualified.
Mom, you should stop it.
It feels good, doesn't
it? Yes, it does.
Well said.
It's all right.
That's right.
You are abandoned by your son.
I'll give you a good treat.
I'll treat you well.
Do you understand?
I'll lick you.
I've seen it in my dream.
This is Yuzuruha's pussy.
Great.
Pussy.
It's so flabby.
What are you doing?
Don't open your eyes too much.
I'll burn it on your eyes.
I can't stand it.
I'm glad you got a lot
of attention from me.
I'm so moved.
May I?
Of course, it's okay.
Please lick me a lot.
Please.
Don't be in a hurry.
Enjoy it slowly.
You have to taste more.
We are on your side from now on.
Let's do it.
It's getting very edgy.
Do you feel it?
Do you feel being licked
like this? Answer me.
It feels good.
It's good, isn't it?
You shouldn't just feel good.
Don't lick me.
You have to lick me.
You are the best.
You licked me.
You look great.
I want to do this.
I want to lick you more and more.
You look good.
I'm going to put a bandage on your back.
Oh, my God.
You are eating so much.
Good boy.
You are wonderful.
You are amazing.
You look sleepy, even
though I prepared it for you.
Do you want me to
pet you? You look good.
Do you want me to pet you?
As I expected, you want me to pet you.
Let me touch your belly.
You have loved me for
a long time, haven't you?
Do you want to be touched by everyone?
You are so sleepy.
Do you want me to give you a kiss?
Then, I will give you
a kiss with my finger.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it.
Please don't attack me with three people.
What's wrong with
you? It's intense.
Three people.
I'm being bullied.
Boss!
You are so messy.
I'm so happy.
You've been like this since a while ago.
I'm going to tickle you
while looking at your wife.
I love you!
She's finally getting the hang of it.
You're the only one I can rely on.
She finally understands.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Please enjoy this video.
Are you okay?
You've had a hard time,
but you're still drooling.
You are so kind.
You have a good heart.
It's like a dream.
This is... Yuzuriha-san's
mouth is...
I'd like you to lick me, but...
No, no, no, not the penis.
This one first.
Oh!
Ah!
You can swallow more.
How does it taste?
Is it good? It's good.
You can taste a lot.
I'm going to put both
your hips on your chest.
I'm going to do the same.
Look at me.
I'm so happy to have you do this for me.
I know.
This is great, isn't it?
This is the best.
This is all thanks to you, Natsushi.
Do you want me to lick you?
Ah…
Ah... Ah...
Oh...
Ah...
Oh, it feels good.
You are so happy.
You can do things like this with
the boobs of a home-cooked meal.
I can't believe you did this to me.
I'm going to be eaten.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
This is a video of the process
of making a baby's first baby.
Baby's first baby will
be born in a few weeks.
Baby's first baby is a
baby with a lot of hair.
Wait a minute.
Let's start.
Oh, it's hot.
I won't let you go.
Don't choke on it so much.
You're going to die soon.
It's delicious.
How do you feel? Good girl.
Good girl.
Look, look.
Don't let go.
I did it too hard.
You haven't done it too hard yet.
I'm going to die.
I can't. I can't.
It's amazing.
It's so smooth and warm.
Is it like this?
Then, I'll put you in the box I dreamed of.
Yes.
May I? Of course.
Are you going to sleep?
This is a dream.
Let me taste it slowly.
If you do it quickly, you will go soon.
No, you will go soon.
She says she feels very good.
I want to see her face.
It hurts.
Oh, I see.
You are so cute.
Look at me.
You are having sex with
Izumiha-san, aren't you?
You are so cute.
I'm so happy.
You should eat mine, too.
You move a lot.
What should I do? It's tight.
You are eating well.
The baby is crying.
You are very strong.
You are strong.
I feel good.
〔Crying〕
Hey, you two, hold on to this.
Yes.
Wow, what a view.
You are a good boy.
You ate one.
Can you see it? You ate two.
Can I taste a lot?
Can I?
No, I don't want to eat.
It's delicious.
Change the bowl.
You have to put it in by yourself.
You have to taste my shape.
I'm so happy that I can't do anything.
I also feel very good.
It's good.
You can see it.
It's connected well.
How about this? It feels great.
You shouldn't hold it like this.
Then, I'll hold it like this.
Let me see.
I'm touching you properly.
I'm so happy.
I feel so good.
I'm so tired.
Yuzuru-san, how
is it? It's delicious.
It's really, really delicious.
You can taste a lot.
It's not bad to be so slow.
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
I won't stop you.
Your ears are turning red.
It must feel good.
Can you see?
Wow!
You two get along well.
I feel sick.
Go! Go! Go!
I've had it out.
You've had it out?
Ah, it feels good.
No way.
Now, the other side.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to sleep.
It's better to sleep like this.
I don't want to sleep.
Oh, no! Hey, wait.
This way.
It feels good, doesn't
it? It feels good.
You are a failure as a mother,
but you are the best as a woman.
It's okay.
It's the best.
I can't do it anymore.
Oh, you can walk now.
I'm getting bigger.
Yes, you are.
I'm so tired. Help me.
You are used to it, right?
Yes, but I won't let you go.
Hey, Atsushi, come here.
I'll leave you here.
President, let me do it too.
Ask the woman.
Hey, what do you think?
Is it okay not to say anything?
I wonder if that's what it means.
It's dirty.
You put out too much.
You have to clean it up.
No, I'll get drunk.
You're noisy.
I'll clean it up.
No, no.
I can't drink alcohol.
What?
You can't?
Then I'll suck you up.
Are you clean now?
You're drunk too, aren't you?
The bowl is good.
I'm so excited about tomorrow.
You can't do that.
I can't wait.
I'm going to drink more.
You're always enthusiastic.
What are you doing?
You want to drink, don't you?
I'll make you drink a lot.
It was delicious.
You are the sweetest in this body.
You're licking again.
Come on.
To the back.
Did you drink a lot? Yes, yes.
Does it feel good?
How do you feel? It feels good.
Really?
You're really good at it.
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't do that.
Let me see.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey.
You came back a little while
ago, didn't you? Look at this.
Look, look, look.
Oh, you have a lot of hair and it's loose.
From here, the grass...
It's coming out more and more.
That's great.
How much did you put out?
You can't help it, can you?
Because it's a very good book.
Is it here?
I'll give you more reactions.
What's wrong?
I can't take it anymore.
No, no, no, no!
You're not like you.
I knew it.
I'm too bad for you.
You got married and you're a guy.
I know.
Why don't you come out
when it's my turn? I'm sorry.
I can't help it. My arms are tired.
Do you really think it's bad?
Then you have to show
me with your attitude.
You have to show it to me with your body.
If you do it to me, you
have to do it properly.
I'm going to kiss you.
Look at my eyes.
I'm going to give you a massage.
I can't stand it.
You are taking a rest.
You are really a grumpy woman.
I think so.
It takes a little time to do this.
Is it okay to lick only the nipples?
It's wrong, isn't it?
Hey, you have to shovel properly.
Yes.
You have to not only
shovel but also taste properly.
Yes.
This is the first time I've
had a baby, so I'm a little
nervous, but I'm sure it's
going to be a good baby.
I'm sure it's going to be a good baby.
I'm going to have a bath.
※This is the sound of a baby eating.
You can't eat it all?
Oh, you really love it.
Come here.
Like this? That's right.
Ah...
You're talking and making a mess.
I'm so tired.
And I'm drunk.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
You've been poked in the front and back.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Oh, it feels good.
「It's delicious!」
「No, no, please, no!」
「No, no, please,
no!」 I'm so scared.
Calm down, calm down.
I'm going to put it in.
Try putting it in yourself.
Yes.
Ah, it feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
I feel so good.
You have a nice waist.
You must be lonely.
Yes, I am.
Here you are.
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm so happy.
Ah!
What's this?
It feels so good.
Did you really do it? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Did you leave
already? I'm sorry.
I was in a bad mood.
I want to do it more.
Do you want to do it more?
If you want to take a bath,
you have to take your butt out.
You can't help it.
Here we go.
How much do you have to take your butt out?
I can't take it out at all.
It hurts!
I'm not fully back yet.
You have to speak properly, Sakuma.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
If you are hungry, you should eat properly.
I'm going to take a bath.
Yes.
Be a good bath.
I'm sorry.
It seems that the place where
I stay is not Ganysan Temple.
No, you don't have to come.
Go home and take a rest.
OK.
Well, I have a long meeting.
I'll go home when it's over.
See you.
OK.
Good night.