I have a temperament. I love
to be turned around by women.
I love to be turned around by various men,
and I love to be worn out and consumed.
If you want to add more excitement,
it is a great pleasure to have a wife.
A wife is a person's
wife and a person's thing.
That wife is in a place where
her husband doesn't know.
I just think about it,
This time, I would like to show
you a video with such my personality.
I would like to show you a
video with a lot of scenes.
Just in time for the mid-autumn
festival, my wife came in.
Are you all here? Yes, I'm fine.
This time, not only the training trip,
but also Mr. Oshima's welcome party.
Mr. Oshima, please enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
Also, we'll hold a party at night.
Let's do it!
But before that, we need you to study hard.
Let's go to a tourist spot
and take pictures together.
It's a nice place,
isn't it? It's beautiful.
It's good, isn't it?
I'll bring your luggage.
You can use that room.
Thank you very much.
Your luggage is over there.
It's good, isn't it?
The owner here has been
my friend for a long time.
Thank you very much.
He takes good care of me.
I'm sweating.
You're sweating,
aren't you? I'm tired.
You're tired, aren't you?
Then, let's take a bath.
Let's go right away.
I don't care about the bath.
Let's take a short break before the party.
Let's do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a practice.
What?
Thank you very much.
I'll do my best.
You're late.
How do I look?
Do I look cool? You look good.
Do I look good? You look good.
Let me ask you.
Is the meal good? It's good.
Did you like the hot
spring? It was good.
Did you have a great
trip? It was good.
Today is a welcome party for Oshima-san.
The star of the day is always Oshima-san.
Let's have a good time today.
Oshima-san, you are the star of the day.
Can I be the star of the day?
Can I steal the star of
the day? No, you can't.
Oshima-san, please steal
the star of the day from me.
Wait a minute.
I've prepared a game for you.
What is it? You'll see.
But, Oshima-san, are you
okay with this outfit? It's not good.
So, I've prepared an outfit that
will make you look better than me.
Come here.
Let's go.
I've prepared it.
Good luck!
Please look forward to it!
Are you ready?
Everyone, it seems
that Oshima-san is ready.
Finally, Oshima-san is here!
There's something on it.
There's something cute on it.
It's cute.
Oshawa-san, this is not all.
Oshawa-san.
Let's open it!
Let's go!
Open!
Oshawa-san, it looks good on you.
Let's buy it.
It's cute.
It looks good on you.
Everyone, let's play the game!
The name of the
game is... Ta-dah!
Manpo-kei!
Put it on your waist and shake it!
The rules are simple.
Put this manpo-kei on your waist.
And you can shake your waist
as much as you want in a minute.
OK!
I'll do my best!
OK, I set it to zero.
Here you go.
Put this on your waist.
It's OK around here.
It's a private house, so I'm
sure you'll shake your waist a lot.
Shinohara-san, you are going to lose.
No, no, no. I'm not going to lose.
I'm going to judge you in a minute.
Shinohara-san, please.
OK, leave it to me.
This is a serious game.
If I lose, I'm going to work
overtime for 5 hours every day.
If I lose, you'll have a penalty game.
Shinohara-san, please
think about what to do.
I'll think about it.
Are you ready?
3,2,1, Start!
More! More!
30 seconds have passed.
15 seconds left.
You can do it!
Winner!
You did your best!
How was the result? Thank you.
The king was strong.
I see.
The result is... 136 to 116.
The winner is HIMORI!
Thank you! I did my best.
The loser is Oshima-san.
It's a penalty game.
What is it?
What's the penalty game?
The penalty game
is... Retirement!
It's a counterattack!
Oshima-san, please
strike a counterattack pose.
This is a serious game.
Please strike a pose of M-shape.
That's good, Oshima-san.
Don't hide it!
You can't hide it! It's a
penalty game! Ok, Maeda-san.
Let's start with a rolling pose.
Roll your waist.
President, next pose, please.
Show me your butt!
I want to see your butt!
President! President!
It's here! It's here!
Beautiful!
Cute!
Yūko Toshiba!
President!
What's the next request?
I want to see something cat-like.
That's good!
Please look at the camera.
The pose of the cat.
Look at the camera.
What do you say? Meow.
Wow.
Cute.
Cat walks with two legs.
Yes.
It's so cute!
It's wonderful!
It's beautiful!
I'm so jealous of you!
All right!
The game is over now.
Thank you very much, Oshio-san!
Let's give a big hand to Oshio-san!
Awesome!
Thank you very much, Oshio-san!
It was great! No, no.
Everyone, the game time is over.
Enjoy the rest of the simple time.
I can't stand it if you
show me such a thing.
What?
You were also excited, weren't you?
No, wait a minute.
What's wrong?
What if I do that?
Is it bad for your husband?
It's okay, isn't it?
You were so excited that your legs
were shaking, weren't they? That's.
..
You came to the game expecting
this, didn't you? No, I didn't.
You don't look like a bad girl at all.
You want me to comfort
you, don't you? Please.
Why? I'm tired.
I'm tired.
It's okay.
Be quiet.
How is it? Is it hot?
Is it hard? I'm sorry.
I'm going to use my tongue.
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do that.
I want you to move.
Please.
It's over. It's over.
It's over.
Please.
It's getting worse.
I'm here.
No.
I'm in the middle of something.
Go away.
Shut up.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
I'll be found out.
Don't worry.
He's a good talker.
No, I'm not.
I told you not to say it.
Don't worry.
I'm asking you if you can quit here.
I'm asking if you're okay.
I'll leave you alone for a while.
You'll hear me if I speak.
How do you feel?
How about this one? I'm done.
I'm done.
You have to make a sound.
Do it like this.
Close your eyes.
Hold me tight.
Good.
More.
I can't.
Why? I can't.
You can't? I can't.
Stop.
More.
Don't worry.
I've never been able to do it.
Good luck from now on.
Thank you very much.
I'll give you a bonus.
Oshima-san, you're late.
Hurry up and sit down.
I'm sorry.
There's no alcohol for the president.
Come on.
Sit down.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Come on.
I'm not a man. I don't like this salmon.
It's so good.
You have to drink it.
It's good for your health.
He's right.
You have to drink it.
It's good for your health.
Open it. Open it.
You have to drink it.
I don't know.
Hey, Kiyoshi.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Me, too.
I'm sorry.
You're overdoing it.
Drink up.
Hey,
Kiyoshi is definitely talking.
Don't say that to me.
Don't you want to take a bath?
What?
If you don't wash properly,
you may get pregnant.
I'm going to take a bath.
You have a good body.
It's the best.
President!
Oh! Hey! I'm sorry.
Hey! I'm sorry.
You're not doing what you should be doing.
What?
Well,
It's such a good body.
It's a waste to enjoy it alone.
I'm sorry.
You were pretending to be nice just now.
I saw it just now.
I'm fine, too.
President!
I don't like it.
The president says it's good.
Enjoy it.
This is also part of the training.
It's fluffy.
Oshima-san, please enjoy it.
Today is a holiday, so you
should do a lot of things.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, it's hot.
Is it really okay for such
a good woman? It's so hot.
You have a sharp body.
Your nipples are getting longer.
Can I go this way?
Do as you like.
I can't get used to it.
You can't get used to it.
Let me see.
What? What? This is.
..
Excuse me.
I don't want to.
Oh! You are so big.
Excuse me.
Don't lick me.
OK.
Oh!
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Oh!
How do you feel?
Tell me if you feel good.
You feel good, don't you?
I feel good every time.
Look, you are sweating.
Yes, I am.
You are sweating a lot.
Great.
It's easy to put it in.
It's thick.
Oshima-san, do you usually
ask your husband to do this?
You can enjoy it.
Tell him you'll go when you go.
Beer came out from here.
Beer came out.
What are you going
to do? I don't know.
You are drunk.
I'm getting drunk.
Then, I'll do it.
I'm going to use your hotel room.
What are you doing?
Let me feed you.
Can you feed me?
How does it taste?
Is it good? Kimori.
Yes.
I'm glad you joined us.
It was the right decision to come here.
It feels good in my mouth.
It's going to come out.
How erotic are you dressing up?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
The baby's inside is amazing.
I didn't know the baby's
inside was this colorful.
She was crying a lot, wasn't she?
Oh, no! Oh, no! Yes, yes, yes.
Wow, she's crying a lot.
She was crying a lot, wasn't she?
He's still sticking his tongue out.
How do you feel about your husband?
Does your husband look down on you?
I'm glad he doesn't.
I thought you couldn't get
your hands off your husband.
Thank you very much.
Your mouth looks like a dumpling.
It's like a baby.
Great!
You are very good at it.
It's so creamy, isn't it?
How creamy it is!
Wow!
I can hear the sound of the bath.
This is a place where everyone gets tired.
I have to be quiet.
Then, I'll take off my socks.
Wow!
There was no reason for me to come here.
As expected.
I can't wait to cast her.
Me, too.
Our company is the best.
It's the best.
The girls who work at our company say,
she's a nasty girl.
I can't stand her.
This is our company's trademark, a scarf.
I'll do my best.
You are so cute.
Boss, let's do it together.
Me, too?
Yes, let's do it together.
You use your teeth so well.
You are so patient.
So, we are doing this for your welfare.
Yes, for our welfare.
We are the only ones who can do this.
Yes, we are.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oshima-san, in order.
I'm sorry, but I can't
help but want to release it.
Because you are young.
I have a request.
What is it?
Can I take a bath?
Do you want to take a bath?
Yes.
Then, ask Oshima-san.
Oshima-san, can I hit your pussy?
How is it?
It's good, isn't it?
Then, stand up.
Stand up.
Come on, come on.
Stick out your butt.
Come on.
Come here.
I want you to put it in.
Can I put it in?
Can I put it in? Yes, you can.
Thank you very much.
You like the back, don't you?
I'll put it in with my young heart.
What's this?
It's all wrapped up.
Go on.
Kill it with your dick.
Can you feel it with your dick
other than your husband's?
You have to report it to your husband.
Please do not feel it.
Please do not squeeze so much.
This is not good.
Next, I will do it.
Woooo!
They are in the sauna now.
Uwu…
Chin, you should breathe in.
Yes, I can breathe.
Please be quiet.
Wow…
What?
Are you taking a bath?
Aha!
Oh my…
Please sit down, Chinko.
How do you feel? It's strange.
It's amazing.
How do you feel?
You don't feel like taking a bath.
It's OK.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm going to tie you up.
Your butt is floating.
I'm sorry.
I don't think you're using any strength.
Please don't drown.
This is the first time I have
ever seen such a scene.
I was surprised to see a scene
where I couldn't do anything.
Oh, my God!
Mr.Konjima, you are wearing
a very embarrassing outfit.
Your clothes are really
fantastic, Mr.Shachio.
You sure, you have a
lot of influence on me.
Thank you.
Mr.Konjima, can I see
the sex senior? Don't move.
Sit properly.
Tighten more.
You have to feel the president's feelings.
How do you feel, president?
Enjoy it, Chiba-san.
You still have two steps to go.
That's right.
You can do whatever you want.
You really like to play
with the water, don't you?
You don't care about your husband.
You can put your butt on the water.
It feels good all over the body.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Tighten your belly button more.
How is it?
The president's waist is heavy.
It's powerful.
To the back.
This side, too.
The sound of a baby crying The sound of
a baby crying The sound of a baby crying
I'm tired because I haven't
washed my hands yet.
Show me the taste of a veteran.
You look good in hot springs.
Oshima-san, you've been looking forward
to this kind of training, haven't you?
Yes, I have.
It's scary.
I'm so jealous of you.
It's not a big deal.
Then, let's do chin-up.
Which one do you
prefer? It feels good.
I don't think I can beat you.
I can do it in 10 seconds.
In 10 seconds? That's right.
It's a competition.
It's hard.
It's always fun.
It's different when you shake it.
It's like this, isn't it?
You can do it harder.
You are short of breath now.
Can I do more?
Let her do more.
I can't do it anymore.
Do it with double motion.
Let her do more.
Show your manliness.
You did it.
I can't stand it anymore.
Look at him.
Hold him tight.
Can you rub him? Rub him more.
Please break the window.
Please break it.
Do you want a tissue? Yes, I do.
Please hold this.
Thank you.
What kind of person are you?
I won't let you go.
Don't do that.
Listen to me, let's go together.
I can go with you,
can't I? Don't go.
I don't want to go.
No, I don't want to.
I'm not going to.
Come on.
No, please.
I don't want to.
Please.
Oh!
Oh! Here you are.
Here you are.
You are great.
You are soaked.
Please clean your body.
I feel sick because my body is soaked.
Oh, my God!
Oshima-san, please take her inside.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come on, lift her up.
No, no, no.
Please, dad.
Why are you making
her cry? Please, dad.
Hang in there.
No, no, no.
She will come out soon.
Please, dad.
It's impossible.
Please, no! Slowly, slowly.
No, no, no!
Oh!
No!
Ok, let's sleep now.
Let's enjoy a little more
and then sleep again.
Please go back to me.
You are shaking your hips a lot.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
I'll follow you to the car all my life.
Hey, Oshima-san, you
can't sleep in a place like this.
I think I drank too much.
I'm going to sleep.
Then you guys pull
the futon and take it out.
I'll do it.
Hey, take it out.
I can't help it.
You can't do that.
Give it to me.
Mr. Oshima.
Mr. Oshima, look.
Are you OK?
Mr. President.
Mr. Oshima, you're OK.
What's the matter?
You're idiots.
Mr. Oshima wants it.
Don't you know that?
You can't? That's why you can't
participate in the competition.
That's right.
You should learn from the president.
What are you doing?
Your eyes are open.
You should forgive him.
Don't do that.
Don't worry.
Let him sleep.
President! Don't worry.
You should go to bed.
What are you doing? Join us.
I can't let you sleep.
Don't worry.
You're so mean.
Women are pitiful if they
don't make you laugh.
Look at this panty.
What's this? Look closer.
Why is there so much blood in it?
Did you draw this?
What's this? Look at this.
It's so erotic.
No, no, no.
It's OK.
Are you smoking? No, I'm not.
President!
It smells so good.
President! It smells good.
I think it's good.
Touch it.
It smells so good.
You should kiss it.
It's your wife's lips.
It's good.
You can lick him.
He is asking for it.
If you don't understand
it, you can't be promoted.
I'm telling you, you can't do that.
Kyoryu, you can't bend it.
Go, go.
I can do it, too.
You can lick it.
You lick it, too.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Look at his face.
If you are hungry, you should eat more.
Oh, no.
You are hungry, so lick it.
Lick your toes, too.
Lick everything.
Lick your father, too.
Don't give me more.
It's delicious.
You can have sex with everyone.
Men and women are the same.
What do you want to do if
you are beaten by five women?
What do you want to do if you are beaten?
I want to be beaten badly.
You want to be licked badly, don't you?
You want to be touched badly, don't you?
Go! Go! Go! Excuse me.
Your nipples are open.
I feel sorry for her.
She is excited.
She is standing up.
She is happy.
Give her more.
Do you want more?
Do you want more? I want more.
I told you.
I want more.
What's going on?
What do you want
me to do? I'm scared.
I'm going to lick you.
What are you doing?
Oh, my boss' hand.
Oh, my boss.
What's wrong? Do you want more?
It's your thought party.
This is a present for you, Oshima-san.
Can I? Of course.
Oshima-san.
You want me, don't you?
I can't face you.
I'm sorry.
I'm giving you a break.
Oshima-san.
I'm going to lick you.
You are coming.
Please lick my face.
Please lick my head.
Give it to me.
This one, too.
Hey! That one, too.
I want that one, too.
You wanted it so much, didn't you?
Right?
That's the way you are.
Give me more.
Oshima-san, you're such a hard worker.
I'm serious.
Do you really love
Chimpo? Yes, I do.
I love Chimpo.
It's so much fun.
You're doing this even
though your husband is here.
It's so exciting,
isn't it? You're right.
She looks so erotic.
She wants Chimpo other than her husband.
If you don't understand
her heart, you can't work.
I can't do it.
When will you do it?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
You're about to do it.
You're out of luck.
I'm in a hurry.
I'm so excited.
He is licking his mouth.
He is licking his mouth deliciously.
Here is another one.
He is licking his mouth.
There is also a welcome party.
Let's welcome everyone with a small step.
Then I will also participate.
Please lick me in order.
Then next is me.
That's right.
Look, look.
He is very happy.
It feels good.
Please lick me too.
He is crying.
He is busy.
There is another one over there.
He looks happy.
It's hard to do this, isn't it?
I'm going to use all of this.
Which one do you want to put in?
I'm going to put it in.
Do you like this?
Did you put in your
underwear? No, it's mine.
It's mine.
I wanted to do
it for a long time.
Do it.
Which one do you want to put in?
He's hesitating.
What do you think?
Oh, this is good.
Put it in.
Let him lie down.
Oshima-san, lie down.
Spread your legs.
You spread your legs and bend your legs.
Good boy.
It's good that you choose the biggest one.
Is it OK?
Now, you are going to have a baby.
I will put it in your mouth.
Wow! It's so slimy.
I want to put it in your mouth.
I will put it in your mouth.
It feels good.
You like it, don't
you? It feels good.
There are many.
I don't know if I can do it with one
hand, but I can't do it with both hands.
This big baby is strong.
You're doing a pretty good job.
How do you feel? It's the best.
It's the best? That's good.
It's the best.
Oh, my God.
What? Are you going to
give birth soon? Yes, I am.
What? You can't do that yet.
I feel so bad.
You can't do that yet.
You have to give birth
after all the babies are born.
You can't do that.
You have to give birth
after all the babies are born.
Oh, I feel good.
It's been a long time since
I've done this, so I was nervous.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
I feel great.
I feel great just by touching her feet.
I'll do the same.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel good?
Look!
She is in a mess.
You are crying, aren't you?
She is in pain because
her legs are entangled.
He moved his two legs and
raised his head to the sky.
Oh, he is the most
careful and cuddly of all.
Oh, he is just a baby.
He began to shake his hips from there.
He likes the way to
make him shake his hips.
He is the best at shaking his hips.
It's so good.
It's really good.
I'll have one more.
I'll have one, too.
I can't stop.
It's hot.
Oshima-san, let's make a good music video.
Let's welcome him.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry.
You can move around.
We'll move around.
I'll put it here.
I'm sorry.
Look, there is a pacifier next to you.
Look, there is a gap.
It's a pacifier.
Look, there is a pacifier next to you.
I'm sorry.
You want to go home, don't you?
Now, hit your back.
It's not over yet.
No!
You are amazing.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
You are a man, aren't
you? Yes, you are.
No.1 No.2 No.3 No.
4 No.5 No.
6 No.7 No.
8 No.
10 Wow!
You like this flat bed,
don't you? I like it, too.
Wow!
Manko, you look so happy.
Here you are.
I'm glad you like it.
How do you feel? It's the best.
It's the best? That's good.
Let's go deeper.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Do you want more? More.
It seems that there are two pussies.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a big one.
It's amazing.
It's amazing that such
a big one was killed.
It's amazing.
Are you okay, Oshima-san?
I don't have any strength.
You haven't been home for a while.
I'm so sad.
You've been out so much.
Don't take a rest, Oshima-san.
I'll take care of it.
It's the president's turn.
It's a different feeling.
The president's rolling is amazing.
Don't lick my nipples.
Stop it! I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I can do it in 3 seconds.
Don't look at me.
Who is the fastest?
How do you feel?
I feel great!
I feel like I'm going to have a baby.
You feel great all over.
I'm going to sleep.
You're mumbling.
I'm going to put you in the cage.
You are not allowed to be in the cage.
I'll do it.
I don't want to do it.
Then, take it off by yourself.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
I'll take it off.
President!
You can feel it in your
stomach, can't you? No, I can't.
What's that?
You have a special ability.
President!
The president made it.
That's our president.
We are also Hideshi.
It's perfect.
Let's go get the cake together.
Please stop doing that.
Stop the inside.
It's not a problem.
I can't do it anymore.
It's not good.
I can't do that anymore.
You are pregnant.
That's right.
I am so sorry.
I will do it.
Please don't make a baby sound.
No, please don't.
Please don't.
I am so sorry.
We are looking for a person
who can give birth to a baby.
Why are you giving birth to such a baby?
I'm going to give birth to a baby.
I'm going to give birth to a baby, too.
I want to say that it's terrible.
This way.
Wow.
What's going on? I'll push you.
I'll put your hand
in your stomach.
Oh, no!
Please, don't!
Don't pull it out.
I'll pull it out.
Pull it out.
Put it on the back of the head.
Yes, yes, yes, like this.
OK, look.
One, two, three.
Did you put out too much?
Your legs came out, too.
Wow.
More, more, more.
Lift your legs.
Lift your legs more.
Wow.
Don't cry.
You are crying a lot.
You have a beautiful face.
No, I don't.
I don't do that.
You can cry.
More, more.
I was so excited.
I want to poop, too.
Everyone is pooping. Poop more.
Ms. Oshima, do you
want to poop? Yes, I do.
Do you? Yes, I do.
Please poop more.
I want to poop a lot.
If you ask me to do so, I
have no choice but to do it.
Here we go.
I can't stop.
You are amazing.
You are squeezing.
I'm used to it.
You are amazing.
I like it so much.
They are going to be pregnant.
I will be pregnant.
They will be pregnant.
Ah, ah.
Wow, wow, wow.
OK, let's drink again and meet again later.
Yes, sir.
Today is a meeting of Oshima.
So, we'll have a drink later.
I'll be back.
I was a little lonely.
What are you doing?
This is a good view.
This is the first time.
Study hard.
I'll study hard.
OK.
Today is the day to welcome
Mr. Oshima until the morning.
I want to do it next.
I want to do it.
Mr. Oshima, please wait.
It's a good employee trip.
Everyone, how was the
video full of my personality?
I can't stand the sight
of my wife spending
all her money on men
other than her husband.
By the way, my wife doesn't quit her job.
So, I leave it to your imagination.
What is going on in the company?