The story of the wife and the
husband Oh, your husband is watching.
Look at him.
Tsubaki...
You're so excited.
The wife, who is the most
important person in the world,
is being used and played
by men who are greedy.
I wanted to be treated like a toy
used only for sexual exploitation.
If I do that, I...
Well, I'm leaving soon.
OK.
Oh, your tie is bent.
Oh, is it? Oh, my.
It's important for a
salesperson to look good.
Here you are.
Thank you.
By the way, do you
know there is a restaurant
that specializes in
delicious egg dishes nearby?
No.
The other day, there was no egg in
the Negitoro bowl or the Seafood bowl.
Then I wanted to eat eggs.
That restaurant has a lot of
delicious dishes, including Bulgarian
specialty dishes, such as
mishmash, Oyakodon, and omelette.
There are a lot of things that
look delicious, such as ice cream.
Do you want to eat it?
I don't want to say it
myself, but I'm an ace in
the nutrition department
at an advertising agency.
I have a lot of money, and
I'm happy every day with
Tsumugi, the beautiful wife
of the former receptionist.
I love Tsumugi from the bottom of my heart.
I love you.
Yes, I love you.
That's why I want to make
other men wear a tsumugi.
It's been two years
since I got married this fall.
I decided to confess
my distorted genitalia.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You're back early.
Yeah.
I had a meeting today, so I didn't go out.
I see.
Do you want to go eat something?
Before that, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I want you to listen to me calmly.
I'm sure you'll be confused.
But it's hard to keep it a secret.
We're not a couple, so tell me anything.
We're a couple, aren't we?
We love each other from the
bottom of our hearts, don't we?
So I'll tell you.
I have a personality of sleepwalking.
Do you know what sleepwalking is?
I've heard of it.
I have a question.
Does it mean that my lover and my
wife will be taken by someone else?
Yes, that's right.
What do you mean by that?
I mean I want you to be taken by someone.
I want to see you having
sex with another man.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Tell me.
I'm so frustrated and disappointed
to see you being beaten by someone.
I'm so excited to see you
being so important to me.
That's what makes me so excited.
So you're excited to see me
having sex with other people?
What's that?
I'm honestly shocked.
I wish you hadn't told me.
I hope you understand.
Good evening, this is the
first time I've seen you in a
long time, so I'm looking
forward to working with you.
This is my first time to write a letter.
I've been a fan of yours for a long time,
and I've always wanted to participate.
This time, I came out to my wife
with my personality and desire.
I'd like you to put us in your circle.
I'm going to follow
the rules of this bulletin
board and put my
wife's picture on it.
Here you go.
Excuse me.
Please have a seat.
I'm Akari. Nice to meet you.
Don't be nervous.
The people who put your wife
on that board are all our friends.
Thank you.
Would you like a
drink? Drink this.
Thank you.
What is this? It's very delicious.
This is an egg drink
made with the eggs of the
Ucock family that I bought
at my parents' house.
The eggs of the Ucock
family are rich in nutrition
and are a necessary
supplement for our activities.
I like egg dishes, but this is
the first time I've eaten them.
Is that so?
Well, let's take a look at
the records of our activities.
It's amazing.
This is actually my wife.
What?
He's so into me that
he's doing it in secret.
Is that so?
But at first he really didn't like it.
But all the guys in this
circle are like beasts.
As soon as I saw Kami, I did it by force.
I don't know what to do with myself.
Hey, Akari.
Are you really prepared to be
treated like this by your wife?
What? Oh, I'm sorry.
What is it? No, no.
It seems you're the real deal.
You can always introduce your wife to me.
I don't know if my wife will understand.
Well, then, I can say that I'm
the person who makes the deal.
It's a part of a relationship,
so why don't we meet once?
No, that's a lie.
If you really want to
make your wish come true,
it's not the time to choose a means.
In this way, I finally stepped
into the sleeping swapping circle,
deceived Tsumugi Nakaba,
and finally succeeded
in meeting Mr. Takimoto.
It's really starting.
My heart and my pelvis
were full of anticipation.
I really love Tsumugi.
Because I love Tsumugi.
Are you okay,
Tsumugi? I'm not okay.
I was suddenly brought here.
I see.
But you're not a bad person.
Really.
I didn't know there were
people like this at your dealings.
Oh, I see.
In fact, it seems to be quite a lot.
Is that so?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, no.
I'm Kanai.
Nice to meet you. I'm Tsumugi, my wife.
As I heard, you are a beautiful wife.
Well, please sit down.
But you are also a happy man.
You have such a beautiful wife.
Well, I'm not proud of it, but
my wife is also quite beautiful.
I'm sorry, but with my wife, it's more fun
to watch other people than to do it myself.
Yes, so I want to practice
that feeling as soon as possible.
What are you talking
about? I'm sorry.
But you met Takemoto-san.
What are you talking about?
Well, well, my wife.
First, let me explain our activities.
Please look.
Please understand that we
are more interested in what
other people are doing than
what our partner is doing.
The woman in the
picture is actually my wife.
This is my wife.
At first, she didn't like it.
But now she's so confused.
What do you think?
What if she imagined
herself in this video? Tsumugi.
..
Tsumugi, this is amazing.
Would you like to try it right away?
Mr. Takemoto came in time.
You can't ignore it.
Hey, Tsumugi.
Hana-chan.
As you feel.
Hey, it's okay.
Mr. Takemoto.
Tsumugi.
Tsumugi, are you all right?
Why are you so wet?
Why?
Are you excited?
You look so beautiful.
You must be happy.
You have a nasty voice again.
Please help me.
Hello.
They are members of our club.
They are wonderful people.
They are beautiful.
Please come in.
Please be careful.
Hello.
It's a good view.
What are you talking
about? I don't know.
I've never heard of it.
But...
Let's have fun.
This is what you want, isn't it?
It's a little rude in front of your master.
The baby's neck is beautiful.
How are you?
You have a good skin.
Show me your face.
You have a beautiful skin.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry.
You have a good skin.
Do you want me to pull your hair?
I'll pull your hair.
When you get pregnant,
your face will be like this.
It's wonderful.
It's very wonderful.
You have beautiful legs.
You have a good style.
Look at this.
Oh, my wife.
You have a good appetite.
You are excited.
You can see inside.
Did you know that? Excuse me.
You are a big boy.
I want to make you meet
such a beautiful person.
Are you ready, Saki? Go ahead.
Are you interested in penises
other than your husband?
Um, I didn't mean to do that.
What are you saying?
Are you okay? Look at this.
This is a penis other than your own.
Please taste it.
Here you are.
Don't be shy.
You can come closer to me.
Mango tastes good.
You have beautiful cheeks.
Please push me out and talk more.
Let's enjoy.
This is the place.
Come on.
I want you to hold it.
It feels good.
It's wet, isn't
it? Yes, it's wet.
That's good.
Well, let me excuse you.
Come here.
Here you are.
Let me excuse you.
Already?
First, you have to put it in.
Well, let me excuse you.
If I hadn't done that, I wouldn't have been
able to do it with the person I just met.
That's right.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'm sorry for doing this all of a sudden.
That's right.
I'm sorry for being a gentleman.
Mr. Nakata, let's go over
there and have a drink.
Tsumugi, are you okay?
But it was very beautiful.
No way.
Hey, Tsumugi, look at this.
What?
Wow, when did you take it?
I don't want to.
This is a video, isn't it?
Many people will see it.
Don't worry.
I can't see your face clearly.
Wow.
I can't believe I'm on
this board with Tsumugi.
Are you all right? I know.
You must be dizzy.
What are you going to do?
Takemoto-san's wife also
said it was the same at first.
Hey, don't you really hate
to see me with another man?
I don't like it.
But I can confirm that I love you only
when you say you really don't like it.
I see.
Tsumugi?
If you say so, I'll do it, too.
Really? Then I'll see you again.
Not often, but occasionally.
Well, I'll let you meet the
members of the circle today.
You don't have to force yourself to start.
You don't have to worry about it.
Please wait here.
Good morning.
You are late.
We were drinking together.
I see.
You can drink here.
I thought you would start drinking first.
You are a beautiful wife.
It's been a while, isn't it?
Do you remember me?
Nagata-san, she is afraid of you.
That's terrible.
We just met the other day.
By the way, do you like
to be licked? Like this.
TAKIMOTO Mr. Takimoto,
are you going to start so soon?
Well, if a woman is okay.
We are all energetic people.
Tsumugi, are you okay?
If you don't like it, please tell me.
This is the first time for you, and
you may not be able to concentrate.
Please wait in the other room.
What? Don't worry.
I can monitor you.
Please come in.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please come this way.
I can check everything in
the city with this monitor.
Please take your time.
You have a nice body.
Your husband has gone over there.
I'm so glad that you are here.
I know.
You look nervous.
Let's get started!
Otsu-san, your husband is gone.
Let's relax.
Put your head down.
You can't be so stiff.
You have a nice body.
You can open your legs.
Did you come here to be teased?
Maybe you were sleeping.
Let's take off the button.
It's okay.
Look at this beautiful face.
Please push me up.
Your legs are beautiful, too.
You have such a beautiful tongue.
Are you trying to seduce us?
Let's take a look at the upper teeth.
How do you feel? I feel better.
You're not feeling quiet, are you?
I don't mean to do such a thing.
I don't know what to do.
Don't worry.
If you don't like it, just say no.
Look at this.
He is taking off his clothes.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
How do you feel? You are in front of
men you don't know, but you are naked.
You have a beautiful body.
I told you. You can put your hands down.
I will look at you.
Chirara
You have a beautiful neck.
You don't hate it, do you?
You don't hate it, do
you? You are naked.
Are you shy?
It is important to be shy.
I can see that your nipples
are getting harder and harder.
Let me see.
Please smell it.
Oh, it smells good.
I can smell it, so I can smell it.
It's small.
The baby's nipples look comfortable.
Which one do you feel comfortable?
What are you doing?
Are you going to show me your butt?
You have a nice butt.
You have a nice back.
Are you going to do that?
You say you're not going to do that.
What is this?
It's already like that.
It's shining.
Can you see it?
If you don't see it, I'll see it.
I want you to show me.
It's so shiny.
I can see the stains on my pants.
It's true.
It's amazing.
When I put my dry
fingers on it, it shines.
It's so shiny.
I didn't mean to do this.
You like it, don't you?
Your body is happy, isn't it?
How do you feel?
You are touched by the man you love,
and you show your important part.
Like this?
Or like this?
Or like this? I'm sorry.
You are so mean.
I'm sorry.
You are licking my panties.
You are so mean.
You have a bad taste.
You are getting harder and harder.
You are so mean.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
How do you feel? It's good.
I'm so happy.
I'd like to see what's going on.
The pants are dirty, so I'll take it off.
I'll take off the pants you're wearing.
What is this? I'll open it.
This is the bedroom of my husband.
He usually sleeps in this room.
But his bedroom is not enough.
He wants to sleep in the
bedroom of a man he doesn't know.
You want to put your hand in it, don't you?
Good reaction!
Your body is trembling.
You are sleeping.
You are feeling better.
You are patient.
Let's enjoy together.
This side.
Go Futo, Futo.
I can not stand it any more.
Do you mind?
We did our best, Futo.
Futo, come over here.
I'm worried.
You have been looking for this for a
long time, haven't you? Yes, yes, yes.
This side, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
How do you feel?
This is the first time for you, isn't it?
I heard a strange sound.
You are wetting your face
while you are chit-chatting.
Are you worried?
How is it?
How do you like it?
It is better to taste
different kinds of chinchin.
Is it good?
Compared to your husband.
I still have some.
Can I have some?
Do you like it? Yes, I do.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Please open your mouth wide.
Don't be shy.
Yes, yes, yes.
More, more.
You can taste various flavors.
Yes, yes.
Isn't it great? Yes, yes.
The third one.
It feels good.
Here you are.
Here is the third one.
You are a good boy.
Please don't make me feel sad.
Give me a hug.
Here you are.
You are a good boy.
How do you like it? Which one do you like?
This one, right?
It's a four-leaf clover.
Yes, yes, yes.
You are a good boy.
I wanted to lick you from
behind while you were whining.
Good girl.
Oh!
You do it yourself.
Here you are.
Do you lick it?
Yes.
Don't be shy.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
I'm sure it's a nasty sound.
I won't let go of your head.
I love you.
Let's go back to your room.
You don't have to go to bed.
I don't have anything.
I'm a wolf, too.
I'm a wolf, too. Please go home.
Please look at me.
You are wonderful.
I'm going to do it a little hard.
How is it? Is it hard?
Wife, please lie down.
Please lie down.
You know what to do, don't you?
What's the matter?
You are moving your hands slowly.
You are moving your hands one by one.
Do you feel good?
You are moving your hands now.
You are moving your hands slowly.
You are opening your mouth.
The baby is crying.
Don't hold back.
Hold the baby's hand.
Good boy.
I'm so happy!
She is so happy!
How do you feel, Masato-san?
She is the best!
How do you feel?
Look!
Look! Please relax.
Please relax.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wow!
I feel it while I'm eating.
Oh!
Please put your hand on the top.
Look!
Ah!
Oh, my! Yes, yes, yes.
I can see your belly button clearly.
Like this.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
I was surprised that he was crying.
He was crying because he was stiff.
He is a very good boy.
He has a good reaction.
He is a good boy.
How do you feel?
Can I do it?
Let me do it first.
Please enjoy the video.
Let's sit down and take a look.
The sound is different from
the previous one, isn't it?
You don't feel anything, do you?
You have a good face.
Does that mean you feel good?
You have a voice.
Is this it?
You look like you're in a good mood.
You have a good face and a good voice.
Here you are.
I'm going to sleep.
How do you feel?
Are you OK?
You don't want to let go of her, do you?
You are a good boy.
You don't want to let go of her.
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on.
One more time.
You have a big belly.
Baby crying Baby
crying Baby crying
Baby crying
You have a stomachache all the time.
You have a stomachache and tongue pain.
You are really a hard-working wife.
Wife, when you feel good, you
feel good while eating chinko.
Wow, that's great.
Please be careful.
It's going deep.
Yes, it's going deep.
Now, I'm going to massage your back.
Here.
And here.
Good.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to massage your back slowly.
More, madam.
This side is better.
And then...
Here.
Yes.
The baby is crying.
You have a beautiful face.
Can you speak, wife?
Can you speak? I'm gonna cry.
..
I'm gonna cry...
I'm gonna cry... My
wife, can I help you?
Are you ready?
Say yes!
Yes!
I'm going to give you a massage.
Next, I'm going to give you a massage.
Please lie down on your back.
It's so hot.
I'll put it in slowly.
If you tighten it so
much, it will be gone soon.
You tighten it so much.
Ma'am.
I'll do it, too.
Please be patient.
I can't stand it anymore.
Ouch!
I think I have a lot, too.
Look at this.
I'm going to do it now.
Oh my god!
What's wrong with
you? It's terrible.
I can't believe how
much I've been harassed.
My wife... It's terrible.
Oh, my wife, it feels really good.
My wife seems to be enjoying it.
Oh, my wife, I'm going to go.
I can't stand it any more.
Ouch! I'm sorry.
It felt good.
Please don't do this to me.
Tsumugi, I'm sorry I
made you do that today.
But, it was really wonderful.
Tsumugi was embraced by various men.
It was really beautiful.
And, I was also very excited.
Tsumugi, do you want to have sex today?
What's wrong?
I haven't invited you for a long time.
I don't know why, but
maybe I don't feel it.
Hey, be honest with me.
Did you feel better when you were turned
around by those people? Hey, tell me.
What did you
write? I don't know.
Welcome.
Hey, welcome.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't get a room in
the previous hotel today.
I like that place.
When I can't get a room,
I use my house like this.
Oh, my wife.
If you can come here, you're one of us.
Oh, no.
First of all, take a shower.
The towel is in the laundry room.
Shower?
Well, if you like, you don't
have to take a shower.
Some people like that.
I don't want to take a shower.
I want to smell the sweat.
What are you talking
about? You're drunk.
What are you doing?
My husband is also in the bathroom today.
Are you going to take a bath?
Let's take a bath.
There is no one in this house who is
embarrassed to show their naked face.
Don't be shy.
I don't know.
Dad, come on.
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for you.
I'll wash you.
I'm going to take a bath.
It's a little hot.
Here you are.
Wow! Great! Let's wash it.
This time, like this.
I'm going to wash it.
Did I tell you?
It's good to have a wide body.
It's wonderful.
I haven't used it yet.
The water is so hot that I
can't see the back of my head.
I'm so happy.
I'll wash your face.
You have a big finger.
You have a big face.
You have a big mouth.
This is the first time I've ever seen
such a large number of fish in my life.
I'm going to catch more.
There are still a lot of fish.
That's right.
There are a lot of fish.
Let's bring it here.
Please relax.
I also want to relax.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby eating a baby's food.
The baby is eating a baby's food.
It's not a bath, is it?
I have to wash my face.
I'm going to wash my face.
I'm shaking because I
haven't taken a shower yet.
It's wonderful.
I have to wash my wife's hair carefully.
I have to wash her hair properly.
I have to open the important
part of her hair and wash it.
Are you a little excited
about this situation? It's good.
This bath is more exciting than
the bath of the master, isn't it?
Don't you think so?
Do you want to wash your body?
I will wash your body
with a hot spring bath.
It's good, isn't it?
If you wash your nails like
this, your nails will be hard.
Please wash your hair, wife.
I'm washing my hair.
Gacha-no-yaki is ready.
Oh, excuse me.
It's coming.
This is also a seabass.
Please wash it cleanly with a net.
You see, it's clean.
I want to talk to you.
It's better to take a bath, isn't it?
Look, the baby is coming.
Come on, come on, come on.
No, no, no.
Come on, come on.
What do you think?
You like this painting of
your master, don't you?
You came here because you can't
satisfy your master's desire, don't you?
That's right.
You came here because you can't
satisfy your master's desire, don't you?
Say, you can't satisfy
your master's desire.
I can't satisfy my master's desire.
I'm not satisfied.
You said it with your true heart.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Wow!
You're speaking so politely.
Open your legs as you are.
Oh, you're moving your butt.
That's right.
Let's make her feel better here.
Put your hands on the back
Wow!
Look at this! It's so smooth.
It's so smooth.
It's thicker and bigger
than your husband's, isn't it?
The top and the bottom will rot.
I'm going to wash you.
Here you are.
What's going on?
Oh, my wife, you are
sweating a lot, and you
sound like you are in a
good mood, don't you?
How do you feel? You are a kind wife.
I'm sorry.
Keep your mouth shut and say,
You feel better than the master.
That's right.
Finally, you're being honest.
That's good.
You're not being told,
but you're being honest.
It's hot, isn't it?
This time, I'll do it.
OK.
OK, here we go.
Oh, my.
Your wife is beautiful,
so I'm getting dizzy.
I'm in trouble.
Everyone is excited because of your wife.
Your wife is also excited.
Everyone is excited.
Oh, it's hot.
Hey, I won't stop.
Stand up.
Stand up firmly.
I can't do anything.
Here it is.
Thank you.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's the best.
It's okay if you feel disgusted here.
It's okay.
Your legs are shaking.
The baby is in a good mood.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
As you fall in love,
you start to ask for
something from yourself,
and when you realize it...
You look good.
I've been telling you.
You're the best woman I've ever met.
I'm so glad for you.
Tsumugi seems to be looking
forward to moving in with everyone.
Is that so?
Looking forward to?
We've been doing this for a long time.
I know.
It's a woman who woke up in a mess.
Well, Wife, Tell me.
I like to be played by old
men in front of my husband.
I like to be loved.
Let's show him a lot and have fun.
You are beautiful today.
Master is looking at you.
Look at him.
Your husband is also excited.
Please let him hear a pleasant
voice so that he can hear his husband.
So sexy.
I can't stop.
It's so sexy.
It's like this on the top.
Show me.
Did your husband choose this or
your wife made this? Don't be shy.
It's good that you don't
have to worry about it.
I taught you how to make a sword.
You chose it yourself, didn't you?
Is that so?
Is that so, wife?
Yes.
We've been dressed like
this to be fooled by you.
Oh, let me hear a more disgusting voice.
Let me see.
Good.
Let's do a bold pose
and provoke your master.
Come on.
Can you sleep?
Master is watching you.
What?
Come close to me.
Wonderful.
Master is already so wet in front of you.
Why are you so wet?
Master is watching you.
Let's show you a more sexy figure.
Come this way.
Oh, you are sexy.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm going to massage your knees.
Yes, here.
Oh, I can see it well.
Oh, you look sexy.
Look, your master is
looking at you from behind.
Your butt.
You have a good face.
I want you to taste my manko.
Now, please tell us.
Please taste my manko
in front of my husband.
I understand.
Excuse me.
You are a good girl.
You are shiny.
Let me see your face.
You are being licked in a nasty way.
I'm watching you, master.
Oh, you are slow.
Hold this.
Oh, I can't stop.
I want to see your face.
Please hold this.
Please hold her.
Look at her.
Can you see her?
This juice is coming out of her puss.
It's coming out from here.
You are so wet in front of your husband.
You are a bad wife.
I'm sorry.
It's because you are
in front of your husband.
Oh, it's round.
It's even more wet.
You can hear the sound of the body.
Let your husband hear it.
It's time for the master to
see what his wife is feeling.
Show your wife how you feel.
Please show it to him.
Can you hear it?
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
He is shaking.
I'm so embarrassed.
Your face is so embarrassing.
Give me all the soup.
I can't stand it.
Come to me.
Are you standing up? Come to me.
Come to my face, please.
Look at me.
Yes, look at me.
Yes, yes.
Stretch your arms.
You are wearing a strange costume.
Your hair is a little tangled.
Your favorite food has arrived.
This is your favorite chicken.
I'm sorry.
You look like you're
enjoying the shabu-shabu.
You look much better now.
Now, please talk a lot
in front of your master.
Come on, this way.
Bend your knees.
Your master is watching you closely.
Come on.
Please look at her.
Let's look at her spitting disgustingly.
Let's be honest with her.
She says, she is a more
delicious chimpanzee than you are.
Did you hear that, boss?
She knows that one is not enough.
I know you don't like it.
Give me your hand.
Oh, your legs hurt.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're talking and your legs hurt.
I don't like to see you talking.
Oh, now this side too.
Gently, gently.
This is your hand.
How do you feel?
You are getting worse.
You like to be touched.
You don't have to look at me so closely.
I want you to look at me properly.
You look at me properly.
Let me see your belly.
This side, too.
That's right, that's right.
Oh!
What is it?
Lick this side, too.
Oh!
Where are you
licking? This side.
Raku-san.
Lie down on your back.
Lie down on your back slowly.
That's right.
Stretch your arms.
Can you reach out your
hand and rub it? That's right.
Master is watching over you.
I was beaten by a cunning wife.
I get excited just by watching.
I don't think he would have
thought of doing such a thing.
You've never done anything like
this to your husband, have you?
Your husband is jealous.
Ma'am, I can't lick yours, but
I can lick your uncle's anus.
Please tell your husband.
If you don't lick me, I can't lick you.
She licks you deliciously.
But, please let me lick you again.
Please lower your head.
This is a good view.
I'll do it.
I think it's better to lower your head.
What's this?
I'm sorry for you.
You are so naughty.
You are so happy to be licked by Manko.
Give him more.
Open your mouth.
Oh-san, is it okay to be licked like this?
You want it, don't you?
You are not sick, are you?
You are very healthy.
I'm going to take you to the vet.
Great! Great!
Yes.
Your pussy is the best.
Please lie down.
Please lie down more.
Like this.
I'm sorry.
You look good.
Here?
I'm going to put the
baby in the baby carrier.
There is still a little space.
Spread your legs.
Spread your knees.
I'm going to put the
baby in the baby carrier.
Who is next?
Is it me? Of course.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my dear, come here.
Look at me.
Come here.
I'll show you my face.
Excuse me.
Come here.
You are so mean.
More.
The baby is crying.
You have a good voice.
You have a beautiful voice.
Come here.
Excuse me.
Let's do more.
Let's take a break.
Raise your face a little.
Please look up.
He is moving up and down.
He is looking at you so closely.
Please look up.
I'm sorry.
Let's have your husband look at you.
Look at me.
Ahhhh!
Ah, she's sleeping soundly.
Ah, it's my turn.
It's my turn.
I can't stop.
Ah, I can't stop.
I can't stop, You
are so stubborn.
You are so stubborn.
You are so kind.
Ma'am, are you here?
Are you here?
Please tell me that you
feel good in your house.
Come on, go to your master.
Turn around.
Come here, my dear.
I'll pull you.
Look at your husband.
You have been scolded by a lot of old men.
I'm so hungry.
Me, too.
It's coming out.
I wanted to see my wife, who is more important
than anything else in this world, being teased
and played by men who are greedy, and treated
like a toy used only for sexual desire treatment.
I wanted to see it treated
like a sword, so that I could
feel that I loved the sword
from the bottom of my heart.
So, even though I feel so frustrated,
these perverted days will continue forever.