Good morning, everyone.
Did you enjoy the sex at the inn yesterday?
Let's enjoy the wonderful sex that will
remain in our memories today as well.
Before that, we will have two
more actresses participate today.
I'm Sayuri Hayama from Yuuka Oshima.
Please introduce yourself
and tell us your enthusiasm.
I'm Yuuka Oshima.
I couldn't participate in the audition
yesterday, but I'll do my best today.
Thank you.
I'm Sayuri Hayama.
It's my first time to perform with
other actresses, so I'm very nervous.
But I'll do my best, so thank you.
Thank you for your enthusiasm, both of you.
You are in Team B, and Ms.
Oshima is in Team D.
I'm sure it will be even more
exciting with the two of you together.
That's right.
Let's make fun memories together today.
Oh!
Now, there's a little
time until the next corner,
so I'd like to set up a
5-minute talk time here.
It's good to talk in the team.
It's good to talk to an actress
you don't usually talk to.
It's good to talk to actresses,
so let's deepen your bonds here.
Yeah! Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shiraishi.
Nice to meet you, too.
You were pretty rough yesterday.
I was in a good mood.
I bought a lot of things.
It was so good that I can't speak anymore.
How about today?
Let's take a rest.
Yes, I want to take a rest.
Yes, me too.
It's fun to be a teacher, isn't it?
It's really fun.
Do you like it? Yes, I love it.
Do you like to teach boys?
Do you like to live alone?
I like it a lot.
I love it.
Do you?
I woke up in Madonna.
I see.
What are you going to do today?
I'm thinking of going
to a open-air bathhouse.
Open-air bathhouse?
I've never been there.
Me neither.
What is it?
What is it? Thank you.
That's Aya-sama.
That's amazing.
That's a game.
What?
I've never heard of it.
How do you do it?
Hey, who's the king?
Recently, there are many
young actors I don't know.
I want to teach them.
That's good.
Let's do it.
Cheers!
Let's have fun
today! Hey, wake up.
It's hot, isn't it?
Let's take this off.
Your body is getting hot.
You are sweating.
What's wrong?
Are you excited? You are cute.
You are sweating a lot.
I'm going to give you a lot of love.
You have a cute neck, too.
How about here?
You're surprised.
You're so surprised.
Do you want me to
lick you? No, I don't.
Give me a hug.
It feels good,
doesn't it? No, I don't.
Is it hard over
there? It looks hard.
Do you want me to lick you?
But...
It's embarrassing.
You're shy.
It's not embarrassing.
I want to lick you, too.
Let's lick together.
I see.
You are very sensitive.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
He is a typical adult male, but
he has a soft, gentle personality.
He has a soft and gentle personality.
He is a gentle and cute boy.
Are you tired?
You are excited because it's your homework.
Be more excited.
You like big boobs, don't you?
How is it?
You like it, don't you?
More? It's okay.
You want to touch it, don't you?
You like it, don't you?
You can drink more.
Is it soft?
Do you want to see more?
There are so many.
Do you want to see everyone's boobs?
Do you want to see?
Oh, you like it.
This side is good, too.
Then I'll do it, too.
I'm going to touch your ears.
I want you to touch me directly.
I want you to touch me more.
I'm going to give you a massage
from the bottom of my hand.
You're sweating a lot,
but it's good, isn't it?
I'll make you feel good with my breast.
Do you feel good?
Do you know I'm
touching you? Yes, I do.
I'm touching you a lot.
Yes, I do.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
I can't help it.
You're so cute.
I'll give you some medicine.
It's for your neck and neck.
I want to do it, too.
It feels good.
You're so cute.
It's tickling.
You feel it, don't you?
You feel it with your
whole body, don't you?
It's scary, isn't
it? It's scary.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
I was surprised to see a baby cry.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to tickle you a little more.
You look so happy.
I'm going to rub you.
With that nasty boob.
Let's rub together.
Let's rub.
I'm going to show you how to
get rid of pimples on your face.
Can I look at you?
Yes.
Show me, show me.
I'll look at you with everyone.
I'm embarrassed.
Here we go.
One, two.
You're so pretty.
I'm scared.
Are you embarrassed? I'm sorry.
Why? Did you miss
me? You're so cute.
You're pouting.
Are you waiting for me?
I'll give you a lot of love.
You're amazing.
Today is a video from the morning
of the second day of the rescue.
I am going to show you how to do it.
First, open your eyes.
Close your eyes and open your mouth.
Do not open your mouth wide.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
with such a cute expression on its face.
I'm going to lick your face.
How do you feel? It's too hot.
You should make it harder.
It's too hot.
Are you getting hot?
Do you know you're getting hot?
Do you want to see more?
Let me show you.
Oh...
I'm all muddy.
Look, I'll spread the bread for you.
Come on, take your tongue out.
Oh, it's so good.
It's so good, isn't it?
My legs are shaking.
I'm going to cry.
I'm so happy.
You're so good at it.
I want you to feel good.
You want me to stroke you, don't you?
Are you ready?
Are you sleepy?
I'm going to stroke you.
Smell me.
You like my smell, don't you?
You like my smell,
don't you? Good boy.
You like it, don't you?
It feels good,
doesn't it? Good boy.
You know it's good,
don't you? It feels good.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
I've never seen a cat like this before,
and I've never seen a cat like this before.
I love you so much, I love you so much
so much, I love you so much
love you so much, I love you so much
I love it.
You are good.
You are very good.
It felt good.
You were surprised when I said it.
I'm sorry. I'm getting slimy, too.
Lick me, too.
How did you lick
me? Lick me, too.
I'm glad to hear
that you like it.
I'm glad to hear that you like it.
I'm going to move my head.
My back is going to move.
I'm going to move my body.
It feels good.
Can I stay like this?
Can I stay like this? I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
You're so delicious.
You're amazing.
You're so chubby.
You're a sassy little baby.
It's hot!
I'm going to pinch your
cheek with my cheeks.
Look at me.
I can't see it.
You have soft cheeks, don't you?
You like it, don't you?
You love it, don't you?
I'll rub it for you.
Wow!
You're drooling.
Give me a hug.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm glad I was able to film it.
I'm glad to hear the sound
of the baby's heartbeat.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm not sure if it's
because I've never seen
a cat like this before,
but it's amazing.
I'm so happy just to play with you.
I hope you feel better.
Hold my hand.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're doing well.
You're crying a lot.
Thank you, Emi-san.
You're full of energy.
Maybe I should do something like this.
How is it? It feels good.
You're purring.
You can't, right?
Not yet, right?
I'm not done yet.
More, right? I want more.
Next, Marina.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
Are you enjoying it?
Are you wrapped in a blanket?
You are so cute. I love you.
It's warm, isn't it?
You are so warm.
You are purring.
How do you feel?
You have a lot of teeth.
We want to be more comfortable.
I want you.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want you. I want you.
If you want to take a
bath, can I do it for you?
It's hard, isn't it?
I'll take a bath first.
It's uncomfortable just to take a bath.
Oh, it's in.
It's in.
It's still in.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, thank you.
Can you see it?
Momoka's mother
mother Momoka's mother
Oh, it's hard to breathe.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's amazing.
I can't move any more.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm so happy.
I'm sorry.
No, don't do that.
Show me.
Please show me.
Let me see.
You are so fluffly.
Oh, you are fluffy.
You are so cute.
You are so cool.
I can't do it anymore.
Let me lick your teeth.
I want you to catch me next time, too.
I want you to catch me.
From the back?
I like it from the back.
Open your mouth.
I just pulled it out.
Wow, you're going in so deep.
Don't move.
I have to move.
Give her more attention.
Let her feel good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to love me more.
It feels so good!
Does it feel good?
I'm going to get a cold.
I'm getting a cold.
I'm glad you're doing well.
You have a lot of hair.
It's good, isn't it?
Let's see your belly.
It's amazing, isn't it?
What?
It's after you went to the
second floor, isn't it? It's amazing.
I can't believe it.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, wow.
I love you.
You're so nice.
It really feels good.
I'm going to make it more intense.
Don't cry.
I'm about to cry.
You'll feel better.
You'll feel much better.
Wow! I'm going.
Together!
It's a video of me and my
husband's cat and our cat's voice.
And we also recorded a video of the cat's
voice that was recorded on a mobile phone.
I'm glad you're enjoying it.
How do you feel?
Did you feel good? I'm glad.
Let's do it again.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Frank Lutheis.
How do you feel about this shooting?
This shooting is really fun.
Are you enjoying it? Yes, I am.
You're not satisfied, are you?
Satisfied?
Yes.
I want to do more.
I see.
I'll think about it.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Wow, it's amazing!
Wow, it's salty!
It's cold, isn't it?
I want to hug you more.
It's cold.
Please close your face more.
Oh!
I want to lick you.
Lick me.
You want to lick my feet,
don't you? Lick me more.
You are happy, aren't you?
Let me lick your feet more.
You look so miserable.
Lick me more.
Lick me all.
Let me lick your feet.
Wow!
You want to lick here, don't you?
Look at this!
Ryo-san, look at this!
Wow!
Look at this!
He looks so happy!
Look at this eyebrow! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
It's hot!
You have a scar on your neck.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to take a deep breath.
You have a scar on your neck.
It's hot!
I'm going to take a deep breath.
I'm going to lick you.
Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's
mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's
mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother
Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's
Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
Oh, my...
Wow, you're being hugged.
You're growing up!
You're eating the branches, too.
Mom, I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
Are you happy to be bitten?
I feel tingling when you touch my feet.
Thank you very much.
You are a pervert.
I love you.
I love it.
I put out so much, but I put out so much.
I'm really a pervert.
I'm a little nervous.
Really?
I think it's going to come out.
I put it out.
Where are you going?
Where are you going to put it out?
Where is hope?
I think it's okay to put
it out in your mouth.
I think it's worth putting
Oh, it feels good.
It was great.
Please let me out.
Please let me out more loudly.
You are being strangled.
Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's
mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's
mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's
mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother
Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother
Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's mother Momoka's It was so big.
It's really big.
Opanpanko.
What's that? It's English.
What's it?
Opanpanko chinko.
Don't make me hungry.
I can't do it.
Hurry up.
Thank you for letting me go.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Where are you going?
More! More! More!
Great! Great!
Alice, you can't run away.
Wait a minute, wait a minute!
Hold on, hold on!
Wait a minute!
You can't run away.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Not yet?
It still hurts a lot.
Yuka, you can do it.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a baby crying in front of me, and
I've never seen a baby crying in
front of me, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous
because I've never seen a
baby crying in front of
me, but I'm so happy.
Tama Zoo, Chimpanzee
What are you doing?
Can you do it?
Can you do it? Yes, I can.
One more time?
I want to see how you do it.
I want to see it.
Oh, my God.
Will it come out? Oh, my God.
I want to see it.
Oh, my God.
I was shivering.
I can't go out.
You can't go out.
They are just starting to eat.
They are still eating.
It's a perverted baby.
Ryo, what rank of Jinko is it?
It's A5 rank, Shimofuri Jinko.
A5 rank is delicious.
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
I'll put it in your mouth, too.
It's big.
Really? It's big.
Really?
Can I taste it?
Can I?
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
Do you feel good?
Does your neck feel good?
1. Try not to cry.
2. Crying.
3. Crying.
4. Crying.
7. Crying.
8. Crying.
9. Crying.
Oh, my God!
It's gone again!
Again?
Wow!
You said that earlier.
I wonder if it's gone again.
How much is the perverted friend?
Oh, my God!
It's gone again!
It's still coming out.
Because we haven't put it in yet.
No, no, no.
We haven't even started yet.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Come on.
You can still get out, right?
Hey, you got hit.
You poor thing.
Next is Nami-san.
Nami-san, make her feel better.
You can make her feel
better, right? I can't do it.
You can do it, right? I can't.
You can't? I can't.
I can't do it.
You said you can't do it.
You can do it.
You can do it, right?
You can still do it.
You can go up here.
You can do it, right?
You said you can't do it.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
You can do it.
Wow, you can do it!
You're doing great!
Wow!
It's huge! It's OK.
He did it!
Wow!
There are not many people
around to take this situation
seriously, but we can't
help but cry for them.
The children are just
waiting for their turn.
This is a video of a child
crying for her first time.
Show me!
Wow, it's growing!
It's growing!
Wow!
You all can't run away!
Ouch!
Wow, it's going to burst!
More! More!
It's so natural here.
Lots of greenery,
and very pretty.
At a place like this,
a 20th anniversary event is being held.
I'm looking forward to it because
it's a very luxurious project.
There are more than 20 actresses, more
than 20 actors, and more than 100 staff.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Good morning.
He is a staff member and an actor.
I'm Tato.
I'm doing my best.
He is a gorgeous staff member.
Wow, amazing.
It's amazing.
The sign of the 20th anniversary of
the Onsen Bus Tour is shining brightly.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I think it's more than Moody's bus.
It's amazing.
It's even attached to the air conditioner.
It's gorgeous.
And look at this pond.
It's moving.
I'm happy to be able to
stay in such a gorgeous inn.
I don't know when I'll
quit being an actor, but I'd
like to come to such a
gorgeous inn when I get married.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's beautiful.
The hydrangea is beautiful, too.
Wow, is that where
you're turning the camera?
Oh, it's Samoari.
You've come on the second day.
Oh, my God.
I'm turning the camera firmly.
I think you'll turn a good camera today.
Director Dai, Mr. Mamezawa is not here.
Wow, this is amazing, this
corridor, this stone pavement, isn't it?
This inn has become a
demolition site, hasn't it?
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Oh, there's a samurai again.
Samurai are really after fishing.
It's been a long time
since I've been to Samoari.
Huh? Oh, it's Mr.
Mamisawa! It's Mr.
Aizawa! I'm Mr.
Aizawa, the great director.
What are you shooting?
Mr. Samoari said he wanted
to do something sharp,
so he made me walk around the inn.
What do you think?
I think it's good.
Can I raise the gallery?
I don't think it's at that level yet.
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
I'm sorry.
Mr.Makai, did you hit your head recently?
I hit my head hard.
Mr.Makai, please do your best.
I'll do my best, too.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Oh, this is...
Isn't this the big
producer of this eye ball?
Hello, I'm the producer of
MADONNA, and I'm always in your care.
Wow, look at the hoodie.
The beginning of the
20th anniversary shoot!
Wow.
As expected.
I don't think we've ever
had a project like this before.
I don't think it's a good
idea to skip this project.
I think it would be bad if I won.
No, no, no. Don't be mean.
By the way, how much is the budget?
Well, it's only a four-digit amount.
Oh, wow.
Thank you for inviting
me to a great project.
Thank you very much.
Please sell me more beer.
Let's do our best today.
Let's buy a mountain at the camp.
I'll buy a mountain.
Thank you very much.
I was so nervous I was nervous.
But I'm still a newbie, so I'll do my best.
I'll do my best at the hot spring.
It feels good.
I've been wearing it for a long time.
I've never worn a ring like this before.
I think it's a good
idea to put a net on it.
I think so, too.
I want a real one.
I want to get married.
I want to go home.
I don't like the word.
It's a bit erotic, isn't it?
The tempo is good, isn't it?
We're doing it,
aren't we? It's true.
We do it every time,
but... It's usually recorded.
It's every time.
What did you do today?
What did you do? I don't know.
I like Hachule.
Hachule?
Hachule? It's a 9-key.
It's a 9-key.
Do you like it? Yes, I do.
Do you have a secret
today? No, I don't.
I know it, too.
Do you? No, I don't.
Are you bullying
Shirofuku? No, I'm not.
I'm not.
This is it.
What's this?
Happy birthday? No, it's not.
It's a crocodile.
Crocodile?
I'm going to be a crocodile today.
I'll do my best.
Are you going to be a crocodile today?
I'm going to be a crocodile today.
I was given a role that doesn't make sense.
Today is our 20th anniversary.
Why is it called WANI?
There is a translation.
The man who comes to the
woman's world is called WANI.
But we are the opposite of that today.
It's different.
So the man should come in.
I've been waiting for this.
We just have to wait until he comes.
So, the moment you come
here, the crocodile will bite you.
Wow!
This is a prey town.
Yes, this is the hot spring.
Surprisingly,
it is said that there are legendary
crocodiles in the Tochigi hot spring.
What is a crocodile?
Does a crocodile really
exist in a hot spring?
What?
I can hear the cry of a crocodile.
Is that a crocodile?
What? Oh, no.
Is this a crocodile that
lives in Tochigi Prefecture?
Is that a crocodile that says that
it will be a year-end celebration?
What?
What kind of 20th anniversary is this?
Is it okay to do such a ridiculous thing?
Oh, no!
Oh, no! It's a fierce battle!
What? What? What?
Oh, no!
It's a fierce battle!
Hello!
I'm Ai Akabane, but...
Hae-san!
Do you know?
Crocodiles kill prey very slowly.
So, they do it suddenly.
Slowly, slowly.
I see.
They do it slowly.
I've seen it on TV.
Really?
It's a good lesson.
Let's do it slowly today.
Slowly, slowly.
It's so painful.
It's strange to say that
we're going to get rid of it.
But I'm glad.
It's very popular these days.
Oh, really?
I was tired yesterday, too.
I want to do it freely.
I'm tired now.
I'm tired, so let us do what we want today.
It's not good.
I'm being teased.
Wait a minute.
I heard you can make a cherry blossom tree.
Please.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Do you like the
string? This is good.
It looks delicious.
It's cute.
I've never been treated
so badly by an old man.
I can't help it because
my partner is a crocodile.
I can't help it because it's my first time.
Oh, no!
Itadakimasu!
Here we go!
Can you show me how to lick it?
Wow! You are great!
Come on, everyone!
Cut it in half.
Don't drop it.
Don't drop it, Ichigo.
Can I eat your butt?
I like spicy food.
It looks delicious.
It's feeding time.
It's delicious, isn't it?
What does it taste like?
It tastes like smoke.
I don't like smoke.
It's a cat, isn't it?
I've always had a lot of fun,
but I'm having a lot of fun today.
Can I tickle you?
Wow!
Don't go!
Let me go!
Do you want to go?
Yes, I do!
Great!
Well, she is flawless.
She is a genius.
I hate you!
She is a genius!
You are a genius!
What are you doing?
She is a genius! I'm a teacher.
I'm learning.
It's painful.
Let me go, please.
Don't push me.
I'll go if you push me continuously.
If you don't want to go, I'll go.
Wow, amazing!
Oh, my God!
Do you want to go?
I want to go!
Well, I'll count to ten, so
you can start from zero.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
8, 7, 6, 5, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4,
3, 2, 1 Can I do it? Of course.
Can I?
I'll do it quickly.
Oh, my goodness! I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
I want to go to the top.
I want to go.
Let me do it.
Let's do it again.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
We did it.
Thank you.
Good job!
Thank you!
One, two, three!
I can't bear it.
Can you bear it?
Then, I'll give you a present
for your 20th anniversary.
Oh, really?
Thank you!
Oh, is that the plan?
What are you talking
about? I'm sorry.
You're a bad boy.
Sit over there.
Hurry up.
Let me have a drink.
I'll have a drink.
Wow! Slowly, slowly.
Wow!
Congratulations!
Do you feel good?
She is concentrating.
Show me your eyes.
So cute!
What should I do? Move more.
Move more.
Good boy.
It's good, isn't
it? I'm so nervous.
I'm so excited.
I'm so nervous.
You can't go yet.
I'll do my best.
You can go.
You can't go yet.
Not yet? Not yet.
Really?
Really? Not yet.
Just a little bit.
No, not yet.
Halfway through.
Not yet.
Just a little bit.
No, not yet.
What is it? It's deep.
It feels good.
It's deep.
It's very deep.
I took it out a while ago.
If I take it out now, it will be very deep.
No, not yet.
OK, but not yet... No
doing it to me! OK, not yet.
Not yet.
OK.
Oh, it feels good.
OK, OK.
OK.
No, no, no.
OK, OK.
I said no! OK, OK.
Oh, OK.
OK, OK.
What's this?
Hey, look here!
He's a little bit of inside.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Oh, oh, me too!
Oh, that's good!
It's still big, isn't it?
It's standing back.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I eat a lot of kimchi.
More.
Can you open your mouth wider?
More!
I want more! I'm so happy.
I want more!
One more!
How is it? I'm happy.
How is it?
A little bit more.
It's getting more painful.
It's not good to have
an emergency like this.
Take a deep breath.
Good, good, good.
I want to go there again.
You've been there many times.
I've been there many times.
I want to go there again.
I can't stand this person
at all, so I'm going to go.
I brought a warm one.
What is a warm one?
What is this?
Well,
What is this? I'm sorry.
I just put it in my mouth.
I'm sorry.
I'll punish you.
I didn't stop you at all,
so I'll punish you.
I'm going to have a meal.
Oh, my god! I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
I don't want to move.
It's the 20th anniversary of Madonna.
It's the best.
I'm going to buy a bra.
Thank you for your hard work.
I felt good.
I'm glad I had a good memory.
I'm strong.
I'll get better soon.
That's good.
Everyone, let's have a drink.
Let's have a drink.
Let's have a toast.
I want to drink a lot.
Are you ready? Thank you.
Cheers! It's good.
It's good.
It's good to drink with
such a beautiful woman.
Let's play a game.
It's easy to play.
Let's play.
This is what you taught me.
Oh, that's it.
No way.
Let's play.
There are a lot.
Please pick one by one.
Ladies first.
Which one?
What should we do?
It doesn't matter.
All of us? Yes, all of us.
Hurry up!
Pick one!
One, two, three!
Who is it?
Who is the king? That's fast.
That's fast.
What is it? The king.
I'm sure it's the king.
I'm going to do it like
Madonna's 20th anniversary.
No.4 is... No.7 is...
Super...
Super...chubby...
Super...chubby... Super...chubby...
Who is No.4 and No.
7? Who is it? Number 7.
Number 4.
It's a man's shirt.
I hate this kind of picture.
I'm sorry.
This? Excuse me.
Let's start.
Wow!
What?
You are eating a lot.
You are licking.
What?
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a cute baby.
I'm so happy.
Ummmm Hot hot hot
Hot hot hot
Wow Ummmm
Umm
What do you like?
Osama?
Do you wanna do it again?
Next Let's do it
again Okay, let's do it.
Let's do it.
Ready, set, go!
Who is the king?
Wow!
It's a little dangerous, isn't it?
What kind of question is this?
I think it's better to attack
more than Velociraptor.
What? The king is.
..
The king is... The king is...
What are you doing? The king is.
..
The king is... Number 4's
sensitive nipples check!
Wait, wait, wait.
The king's nipples are good.
Who is number 4? Number 4.
Alright, alright.
Please come to the front.
Here you are.
King, please check it.
How can I check it?
Please leave it to me.
Here?
Please sit down.
It's the same as before.
Where is it on the yukata?
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, it's a human!
Can you put your chest up more?
I can't check your chest.
Put your arms back.
I'll do it seriously this time.
No, not yet.
What's this? Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
What? What? I don't know.
I don't know.
Isn't he the prince's son-in-law?
What?
Which one?
Wait, wait, wait.
Under the yukata, he might not be.
I'll hide it.
What?
Then, please raise your face.
Look at the prince's eyes.
Wait, wait.
Oh, my goodness.
Wow! A little more.
Wait a minute.
Please look this way.
I'm sweating in my chest.
Look up.
She is very sensitive.
Is it long?
It's so hot!
It's the best!
Thank you for your hard work!
Let's go!
Is it over?
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Which one is the king?
Yes.
Oh! I see.
What's coming?
Well, I have a good idea.
What?
What is it?
No.2 licks No.6's sensitive
part with his tongue.
Oh!
You like the tongue, don't you?
With his tongue.
It's heavy.
Who is No.
6? Who is No.2 and No.
6? Who is it?
Who is it?
Don't say your name.
Oh, he's here.
Oh, good.
If I were you, I would have
done it the other way around.
What?
Number 2, Number 2, Number 2.
Wow.
Well, well, well.
Come forward.
Yes, yes.
I'm glad I'm not a man.
What? It's dangerous.
I have to do it with my bare hands.
I have to take it off.
You should take it off.
Wow!
Are you ready?
I'm looking forward to it.
What's going on?
Is there something in it?
No, there isn't.
What's going to happen?
This is what happened in the process.
Is there something in it?
No, there isn't.
Let's take it off.
Take it off.
I'm not the king.
What are you talking about?
What? Take it off.
I want to see it.
What did you do?
I peed my pants.
You peed your pants?
Well, let me see.
Oh, no.
No, you can't do that.
Everyone can't do that.
Can you lick more?
Next is Asuke.
His tongue is beautiful.
Amazing.
He is showing his teeth.
If he shows his teeth, it's over.
I'm not the king.
Next is Asuke.
Are you going?
No, you can't go.
If you go, I'll go home.
This is dangerous.
Oh! I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
You look like you're
going to stick to the floor.
I can't do this anymore.
Is this OK?
OK!
Let's do it again.
OK.
Ready?
Who is this?
Yes!
Oh!
What is she doing?
Well,
Can I do what I want to do?
Oh! I am I'm No.
3, and I'm single.
No.3!
I'm behind you!
I can't believe it!
I've never done this before.
Can I do this?
Can I?
Is that so?
Where am I? Here.
From the top.
It's embarrassing.
It's a great picture.
May I? Yes, you may.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's embarrassing.
Oh, it's wet.
Is it really your first time?
I think you like it.
It's good.
Your butt.
Oh, my! That's warm.
You are being petted.
He is sucking his face.
I have to teach him.
I have to make him feel good.
He is feeling good.
He is sucking his face.
He is so strong.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it.
It's getting fun.
It's fun.
It looks fun.
If you don't use your hands,
just use your mouth.
Just my mouth?
Only the mouth?
Yes, only the mouth.
When I release it, it goes like this.
It's fun!
I hope he's happy.
The king.
The king seems to be enjoying it.
It's embarrassing.
Oh, no.
It's good.
The king is having fun.
I can do it.
No, no, no.
Not yet.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Awesome.
I can't stop.
Mr. Oshiro, your butt.
My butt.
Your butt.
It's OK.
It's too long.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'll do it next time.
One, two, three.
I'll do what I want to do.
Osamu, Osamu.
What should I do?
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I just did a single grip, so I
want to do a mangrove grip.
It's the other way around.
The king will do a mangrove grip.
Who is number two?
Number two? That was close.
Watch out! Watch out!
Let's do it! Up, up.
And this way.
It was turned over just now.
It's yellow, isn't
it? It's great.
Thank you very much.
Do you want an emoji?
Do you want a normal emoji?
It's not coming out.
Are you OK? Oh, it's coming out.
The king is nervous.
You look like a virgin.
What?
What? Go, go, go.
Hey, hey, hey.
Is that all you've got?
More?
More? Go, go, go.
Masato, you're overdoing it.
「Ai-chan, it's cool!」
I will set the table.
Do you like Kun? Yes, I do.
She said she likes you, Kun.
Thank you for the meal.
Are you listening?
I'm the king now.
Don't be selfish.
Are you listening? Continue.
I'm going to do it.
What are you doing?
Hey!
I thought you were quiet.
What's the matter?
I think it's good.
It's good.
The game is over.
That's good.
Tama Zoo, Chimpanzee Great.
It feels good.
Someone is touching my big hand.
What are you doing?
Is it fun?
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Ah!
Puppies! We are going
to pet them! Oh, that's hot.
Oh, that's hot.
Oh, really? Here you go.
It's cold.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I was surprised to see
a baby crying like this.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I was surprised to see
a baby crying like this.
【Whimpering】
Are you ok? I'm breathless.
Are you breathless?
【Laughter】 Ah, it feels good.
【Laughter】 I want to do it more.
【Laughter】 【Groaning】
Ah, ah, I'm going to go.
Hey!
You sure?
I'm in the middle of it.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Did you fall down?
The front of the baby is crying.
The baby is crying.
Oh my god!
Oh my god! Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Oh, it's hot!
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Oh, it's hot!
Don't leave me!
What? What? What?
I'm calling my new co-workers.
Today, we, the Jukujo, are going
to show you how to make this.
Today, I'd like to teach
you something erotic.
Yes, yes.
Hey, you.
Yes?
Do you know what's erotic and feels good?
Which part do you think
you feel the most? Well.
..
Your pussy? Oh, I'm sorry.
You're so cute.
You're so simple.
There's more to it.
Oh, yes.
Actually, we have to learn
about these things ourselves.
But today, we're going to teach you a lot
of things that are weak and easy to feel.
I'm looking forward to it.
So cute!
Who would like to go first?
There are so many of you!
What are you going to do?
Oh, it's you!
Come here!
Welcome, welcome.
So, we are going to teach
you about erotic things.
So cute.
Wow.
So, first of all, we are going to
teach you about the feeling of boobs.
I'm going to tell you
what I like about you.
Are you looking forward to it?
Yes.
Oh, you, with the glasses.
Come here.
Yes.
In my case,
if you tickle my nipples with
your feather touch, I can feel it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Come on, stretch your arms, Boku-chan.
You don't have to be afraid.
Come on, smile.
Be more gentle.
Don't be too strong.
Yes, be gentle.
Be gentle.
Be gentle, Feather Touch.
You are so cute.
I feel so good.
Now, it's your turn.
In my case, I want you to twist it harder.
No, I don't want to.
I want you to squeeze my
big nipples a little harder.
I want you to pinch me.
No!
Is it like this?
You look at me at such a close distance.
You are my sister.
Don't be shy. Come here.
Come on.
Come on?
How is it?
Not good at all.
Harder.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
More firmly.
Oh, it hurts.
Roll me back more.
It feels good.
Feel it more.
You're getting
better! Good girl.
Today is a special lesson of practice.
Let's have a study session.
I'm sad.
This chest, too.
Welcome.
Both hands.
You have a talent.
You look sexy.
You have to practice more.
Don't be shy.
Touch the feather more.
You can turn it over.
Oh, no.
Your nipple is sticking out of the hole.
It's a double-breasted
cat, so it's hard on
this side and feather-touched
on the other side.
Oh, yes.
It feels good,
doesn't it? Oh, wow.
You're amazing.
You're the best.
Oh, more.
You're making me feel better.
Oh, yes.
It's getting better.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm getting wet.
I'm going to get wet with my nipples.
This baby is good.
I'm getting wet with my nipples.
Oh, I'm getting wet with my nipples.
Yucchi, I'm sorry.
I don't want to do this anymore.
I can feel it.
Yucchi.
I'll teach you more.
I'll hold your hand.
I'll keep teaching you.
I'm sorry.
They haven't given birth
yet and he's losing his breath.
He may be satisfied with only pumps
when he croises with his mother.
Their father, Naruniyo, who is a carpenter,
is waiting for his mother to give birth.
I love it.
Let's eat it.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm getting hot.
It feels good.
I'll tell you how I feel now.
I'll teach you how to do it.
I'll start from your boobs.
You want to touch it as soon
as possible, don't you? It's OK.
Welcome.
Don't be shy.
Where do you feel good?
Stretch your arms.
I'll start from here.
Oh, I'm so happy!
I'm so happy!
It's getting hot.
I can't believe I can see you so close.
I want you to touch me here.
Come here, Maki.
Oh, you're embarrassed in the middle.
I will teach you how to do it.
Come here.
Where was it? Don't be shy.
Wow!
You are so good.
You can do it.
Wow!
You can do that, too?
Great! Be gentle.
Be gentle.
Take care of yourself.
Sleep well.
Kuri-chan is moving.
She turned pink.
Really? She looks cute.
Her fingers are wet.
I'm sad.
Wow!
It's so shiny!
You came so close!
Mr. Greedy!
You want to lick it, don't you?
No!
Do you want to lick it?
Wow!
It's hot, isn't it? It feels good.
I'm getting jealous.
Oh, you brought a mango.
May I? Yes, you may.
Come to the center.
I have a different mango.
Nice to meet you, Lingerie.
You're so sexy.
How do you like to be touched?
Which side do you like?
I'll do this side.
Nice to meet you.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a cute cat.
I'm so happy to see such a cute cat.
Hello.
Please touch her.
Yes.
But I won't tell you how
to make her feel good.
But you already know, don't you?
I'll look for it.
You'll look for it.
Where is it?
How is it?
Wow.
It came to me.
Was it correct?
Oh.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
Good job.
There, there, there.
You're good at it.
But you know what?
You have to look at Guri's face properly.
I see.
From now on,
you have to touch her gently and slowly.
Can you do it?
Be gentle, be gentle.
Oh, she's lowering her head.
She's lowering her head.
You're good.
Next time, touch from below and trace.
Is it right? There, there.
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
The stars are
moving! Yes, yes, yes.
And now you're going to spin.
Guri-chan, you're going to spin.
Yes, yes, yes.
Your fingers are wet, Yoroshiku
onegaishimasu! No, no, no.
Yes, yes, you're doing great.
Wow, it feels so good!
I wonder if I can make you laugh.
I wonder if you can do it.
You can do it.
You don't have to be patient.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
It is a derivative work
of the Touhou Project.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
It's been a while since I've seen a cat
I'm sorry.
Chiho I want you too.
Do you want me, too? Welcome.
Today, I'm going to
tell you a story about a
cat that I met for the
first time in my life.
I'm going to tell you a story about a cat
that I met for the first time in my life.
Today is a special day.
If you look up, you'll see something bad.
You're right. It's something bad.
It's a nice view.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
It's coming. It's coming.
Can I use a toy to
attack? It's coming.
It's coming.
It's good.
I'm over there!
I'm over here!
Wow, you're so good at this!
Look, I have a toy!
You and Chikubin are
attacking at the same time!
You all have talent.
That's right.
You want to grow up more, don't you?
If I make you feel good, you will grow up.
Don't be shy.
You can think of it as a practice table.
You are great.
You brought a great one.
He's coming back.
A little more.
Be gentle.
Aim at his neck.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
Wow, wow, wow.
I can feel it everywhere.
I know where you can feel it.
He's coming back.
Rub, rub.
Oh, wow.
Oh, wow, wow.
Oh, good, good.
I'm going to fall.
Hurry up.
Help me.
I can't stand it anymore.
Please.
Come here.
This way.
Wow, it's big.
Let's see where you can get in.
Does it feel good?
Do you feel good?
You move so well.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What's going on? I don't know.
Do you know what's good about it?
Are you shaking?
Are you fighting?
Wow!
Are you angry? I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Look at the angle.
You are so kind.
I want it, too.
I envy you.
I'm so happy.
Please do it more comfortably.
Come on, do it.
Wow.
It's done.
Oh, it's gone.
It's gone.
A lot of it came out.
I'm so happy.
It's so rich.
As expected of young people.
Who's going to give me a kiss?
Me!
Me, too!
I want you to give me a kiss, too.
Tokoroto-kun, come here.
What are you doing?
You already know how to do it, don't you?
You're really doing it.
It's almost ready.
It's big.
Oh, it's stiff.
Oh, I am relieved.
Oh, feels good.
Feels good.
It's great.
Oh, I am relieved.
It feels great.
I am relieved.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm so touched.
It feels so good!
It's so hot!
Wow!
I love it!
Please eat more.
Don't stop eating.
Please lick my hand.
Please do more.
Does it feel good?
Oh, it feels so good.
Let's get better.
I want to come here more and more.
Oh, it feels so good.
It's so hot!
I can't stand it anymore.
Are you okay?
It's so hot!
Let me feel more comfortable.
Let me hug you.
Give me a hug.
Hold my hand.
You are getting better.
Shake your hips more.
Sit down.
Go inside.
The red tank top is so cute!
It's so cute, isn't it?
It feels so good!
You're good at it!
Oh my god, oh my god.
It's so great.
Ah, more! More! Oh, great.
Oh, great.
You did a great job on the
two-day trip to the hot springs.
That's close.
It's so close.
I was wondering what would happen if I
was surrounded by MADAME and TATSUMI,
but I had a lot of new experiences
from the beginning to the end.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm glad I moved here.
Thank you.
I'm Yumi Kazama.
I had a lot of fun in no time.
It was fun. I don't know how many
times I've said it, but I feel so good.
I still have a lot of things to do,
so I want to do something erotic.
Thank you very much. It was fun.
Hi, I'm Marina Shiraishi.
It was a two-day hot spring trip, but
I was able to meet a lot of actresses.
I was able to meet a lot of actresses, and I was able to
get along with a lot of actresses, so I would be happy if
I could have the opportunity to shoot and have an event
where actresses from MADONNA will gather again this time.
Everyone, please pull out a lot.
Thank you very much.
I was able to participate
in a special project
for the 20th anniversary,
and it was very fun.
It was fun. I got tired of
the hot spring. I would like to
come here again if I have a
chance. Thank you very much.
Thank you for the two-day stay. I was
able to perform with many actresses.
It was very exciting and fun. I will
never forget it. Thank you very much.
I did it!
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm Aoi Ichino.
It was my first time to perform today.
I was very nervous
among the seniors, but I
was able to show
myself, so it was very fun.
If I have a chance, I would
like to challenge again.
Thank you very much.
Hi, I'm Reihaya.
I had a quick toast and drank it.
Thank you for the meal.
I was very impressed by this movie.
It was a lot of fun.
It's a very erotic scene.
It's rare.
I think I took a lot of
scenes that I can't show you.
I hope you'll enjoy it.
Congratulations on your 20th anniversary.
Thank you very much.
I had a great experience.
I still have a long way to go.
What?
You still have a long
way to go? Yes, I do.
I told you before.
I still have a long way to go.
I want to appear in your dreams.
I can't get out of it.
You can't get out of it?
No.
Oh, really?
Is it because of me?
I was thinking about it.
It was fun.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard work.
There is a camera.
Thank you for the two days.
It was fun.
I'm so happy to meet you all.
Thank you.
I'm so happy to meet various
actresses and get along with them.
Thank you so much.
Please watch our movie a lot.
I've learned a lot.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I had a lot of fun.
How was it?
I became the sexiest person in the world.
Me, too.
Thank you for your hard work.
Cheers!
It was rough, but I overcame it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ms. Madonna, congratulations
on your 20th anniversary.
Thank you very much.
Today, I was able to
collaborate with 21 actresses.
I learned a lot.
I was able to collaborate with a legend.
Is this the second time?
No, it's the third time.
I learned a lot.
I saw the episode up close.
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy it.
Cheers! I'm Yuka Tadai.
I'm Haruka Rukawa.
Thanks to all of you,
I was able to participate
in this great event.
And the party was over safely.
I'm really grateful.
We look forward to working
with you in the future as well.
It was fun.
It was really fun.
We got drunk.
It was too fun.
We got carried away.
It was great to be able to
participate in such an event.
I'm the newest member.
I'm a newcomer, but I had a lot of fun.
Thank you for inviting me.
I'll do my best from now on.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Are you kidding me?
I don't know how to end this.
Are you going to run away?
I'm going to do it.
You're still not enough, are you?
Oh, my God!
It's amazing!
I can smell the sweat.
It's coming out!
Wow! It's coming out!
Wow! It's coming out a lot!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Can I put it on my chest?
Put it on your
chest? Look at this.
Let's go.
Let's go together.
Can you see it?
Thank you to all the cast and crew.
Thank you very much.
It is the 20th anniversary of MADONNA.
We will continue to do a lot of
erotic things, so please support us.