Good morning, everyone!
Good morning!
It's the 20th anniversary of HITOZUMA
JUKUJO's No.1 maker, Madonna!
It's all thanks to the fans who supported
Madonna and the cast and crew.
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
To celebrate the 20th anniversary,
the legendary school
bus tour has been revived!
Yeah!
But it's not just a revival.
This time, not only men,
but also actresses from
Madonna will feel good.
Yeah!
Let's get on the bus!
Let's go!
Now, I would like to divide
the actresses into four teams.
We will be divided into four
teams, and we will go, go, and go.
Please enjoy a lot of places where
you can make men go and make men go.
Then I would like to
draw a lottery right away.
Please introduce yourself
when you draw a lottery.
Actually, I don't have one.
I don't know which team
I'm in, but I'm Maki Komoda.
I'm sorry for the noise
in this 20th anniversary
commemoration work, but I'd
like to do a lot of erotic things.
I'm Marina Shiraishi,
who played the red A team.
This time, I'm very honored to be
the host of such a special project.
I'd like to interact with a
lot of actresses and actors.
I'll do my best to interact with everyone.
Thank you.
I'm Ryo Ayumi, a member
of Team C, the green team.
I was chosen to be a hostess with Marilyn.
I'm very nervous.
I'll do my best until the end.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm Yumi Kazama, a member of Team B.
I want to be erotic, fun,
and have a lot of feelings.
I'm Nami Okime from Team D.
I'm probably the most novice, so I'd
like to meet everyone and have fun.
I'm Mariko Sata from Team
B, who played the blue ball.
I'm Riko Sata from Team B.
I'm honored to be here for the
20th anniversary of Madonna.
I'll do my best, so thank you.
I'm Rio Kuriyama from Team B.
I'm nervous since my debut, but I'll
do my best not to be overwhelmed.
Thank you.
My name is Momoko Isshiki.
I chose the green team, Team C.
Congratulations on your 20th
anniversary, Madonna-sama.
I'm wearing glasses.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Mito, from Team D.
I'm going to be sexy with everyone today.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm Kanna Fujii from Team C.
I'm looking forward to meeting
a lot of actresses from Madonna.
I'll do my best.
Hi, I'm Ai Mukai from Team D.
Today is Madonna's 20th anniversary.
I'm very happy to be
involved in this project.
With this opportunity, I would
like to do a lot of fun and erotic
things with the actresses in
charge of Madonna, so thank you.
I'm Yuki Takeuchi, who drew green.
I'm really happy to be able
to come to the hot spring
with the sisters who smell so
erotic and good to Madonna.
I'm so happy.
Today... Today?
Today...
I'm going to have a lot of fun.
I think I can do something erotic.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you in advance.
I'm Aoi Ichino, who played a blue ball.
I'm so nervous that I'm
losing my vocabulary.
I love erotic things.
I'll do my best today.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, I'm Yuka Tada,
a high-heeled fetishist
of the D team, who
played the yellow ball.
I'm very honored to be here.
I enjoyed the game and did my best.
I'm Ririko Kinoshita of the A team.
I'm already excited.
I've been looking forward to it.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your 20th anniversary.
I'm Ueha Aya, a member
of the Takayaka team.
I'm a little stupid, but I'll do
my best not to bother you.
Thank you very much.
It's the best to finish right
before entering the tunnel.
I'm Haruka Rukawa, a
member of the Red Ball A Team.
I'm very grateful to be able to participate
in such a wonderful opportunity.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best to take wonderful
and various works with you.
I'll do my best and have a lot of fun!
Thank you!
I'm Yuka Mizuno from Team A.
It's my 20th anniversary this year.
Congratulations, Madonna!
I'm looking forward to the bus tour.
I'll be sexy and happy.
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
I'm YUNA KASHIINA.
Congratulations on your 20th anniversary.
I like to play with MO.
Thank you for your cooperation today.
Are you ready to enjoy EDGE?
Are you ready?
Yes!
Please pay attention to
the balls you have received.
Balls.
Red balls and blue balls
can do erotic things at once.
Wow!
Isn't it good?
So, the red team and the blue
team, please stay here for a
while, and the rest of the
team, please relax at the inn.
And the blue team will
move to the bus over there.
Everyone, please move.
Please enjoy it!
I'll dance at the end.
Really?
I'll dance.
I'm so excited!
We're going to do a lot of
naughty things in this bus.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Let's call them.
Welcome, Chinko!
Hurry up!
This way!
Thank you!
Can I take a bath in the bus?
We can't wait any longer.
I can't wait any longer.
It's twitching.
Wow.
It's starting.
It's so cute.
I'm so excited.
Please touch it.
This way, too.
He's coming down.
It's hot, isn't it?
Hello.
Are you single?
Yes.
We're also single.
You look happy.
I'm so happy to see you happy.
I'm happy, too.
Can I touch you a little bit?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I think you've grown up.
I think so, too.
You have a great tongue.
It's amazing.
You are quite sensitive.
I think so.
It's getting very hard.
It's getting hard.
It's amazing.
It's a waste to touch it so soon.
How big is it?
I don't know its shape.
It's amazing.
Where does it come from?
Is it small?
I don't know because it's too big.
What's going on?
It's amazing.
It has a small neck.
I'm going to die.
Oh, my God.
I can't do it anymore.
It's too big.
I'm surprised.
Come here.
It's too big.
This is a good one.
From here.
I'm going to die.
I'm so happy.
He's crying.
It hurts.
He has a big face.
You can't put it on your boobs.
I can't put it on my boobs.
It's coming out well.
It's beautiful.
It's so soft.
It's stained.
It's painful.
I want to see what happens.
I want to see it.
She is kind.
Do you want to see it?
I want to see it.
Yes, I do.
Show it to me.
It's big.
This one is also big.
Let me show you.
It's amazing.
I didn't know it was like this.
It's hard.
Can you bend it?
Can you see it?
I want to see it.
Here we go.
One, two.
It's amazing.
It's thick.
It's so big.
It's so hard.
It's your 20th anniversary.
20th anniversary.
It's so big.
She is so cute.
Her head is bouncing.
What are you going to do with her?
I don't know.
Maybe I should cut her hair.
I don't know what to do with her.
Please.
Please stop.
It's so cute!
It's so good!
I can't put my mouth in.
Really?
It's so big that I can't get in.
It's really big.
It's amazing.
It's so big.
It's really big.
No matter how big it is, I can't get in.
He looks like he's in a good mood.
Do you feel good?
He's so cute.
He's getting better.
What's he doing?
He's licking me.
He's licking you, so you
are bigger than before.
He's licking you!
Wow!
It feels good to play with you.
It's amazing.
It's a goldfish.
I'll have one, too.
Do you like it?
It's amazing.
You're so good.
He's so good.
Don't do that.
It tastes like pepper.
How does it taste?
It's good.
Itadakimasu.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's so cute.
It keeps wiggling its tail.
It's pushing it.
Even a small one can get fat.
It's so sexy.
It's getting bigger again.
How big will it get?
It's a good boy.
Do you want a strong one?
Do you want a gentle one?
Which one do you want?
Both?
What a good boy!
No, no, no!
You have to have more fun!
He's out of breath.
He's surprised.
No, no!
You can't!
You really can't do it!
You did well!
You are amazing!
You are so cute!
You are so nice.
It's amazing.
It's not as big as I thought.
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Wow, seriously.
This is incredible.
There'scedant!
Just kidding.
No, no!
You're so cute!
You're all grown up.
She's gotten so tough.
She makes you happy.
I like this.
You like this.
This is good.
I didn't know we'd end up like this.
I'm sorry.
Is this it?
It's amazing.
It's really you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It's you?
Excuse me.
Ah.
You couldn't do it.
Wow!
It's so cute!
It's Pane-chan!
It's so good!
It's so cute!
I'm sorry, I couldn't resist.
I'm so happy to have you all here.
It's so good!
I want to give it to her.
Give it to her.
Oh, really?
You're so cute.
You haven't given it to her yet.
You're so sweet.
Why are you so sweet?
You're so cute!
Thank you!
It's so nice to see you!
I love you!
It's huge!
It's eating!
Oh my gosh!
It feels good!
It's amazing!
What is it, Zaki-kun?
It's holding it in!
It's so nice!
It's so cute!
It's falling!
Wow!
It's so cute!
I can't believe everyone is watching us.
This is embarrassing.
I can't do it either.
This is amazing.
Can I lick it?
It's so good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's amazing.
I'm so happy!
Can I go home?
I wonder if I can meet her.
You are amazing, Chinchin.
You are great.
I'll give you a drink.
You are great, Chinchin.
You are great.
It's hard.
It's so hard.
It's gross.
I'm so happy.
I can't help but feel happy.
I feel good.
My body is getting warmer.
I'm sweating.
I feel good.
I'm scared I'm scared.
No, no, no, no No,
no, no, no No no no no.
No!
No no no no.
There is no place to sleep.
No!
I want to sleep.
How can you fall?
Oh, my god!
What's going on?
Go, go, go!
Oh, my god!
Don't spill it!
It's hot!
Oh, my god!
It's amazing!
Everyone is here.
It smells like ecstasy.
Did you enjoy the welcome trip?
We enjoyed it!
Let's do a lot of
ecstasy things after this!
Yes, that's right.
Hello.
You are here.
Is it OK?
Have you started?
It's been a while since we've done this.
It's been a while.
I was told that I could do something nice.
You can do something really nice.
I'm so happy.
It's been a while since we've done this.
It's been a while.
How do you feel?
Good.
The chocolate has hardened.
Did you feel the heat?
The neck.
Is your neck hard?
It's so good.
Is that so?
I feel good.
Do you feel good, Chimpanzee?
Why do you feel so good?
Are you okay?
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
It's so warm.
It feels good.
Ah, it feels so good.
Wow, it's so hard.
It's a little bit hot.
It's so hot.
It's scary.
I can't do it anymore.
It's so hard.
I can't do it.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel sick.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's do it again.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm going to finish it.
My neck is stiff.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm so tired.
It's so warm.
Are you okay?
I can't do it.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God.
I feel so bad.
I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
I'm thirsty.
Oh, it's bitter.
How about me?
Let's Go sister!
Ouch ouch!
Ah!
Ouch!
Already, already.
No more?
No more.
It's so hot!
Now, we've arrived at the inn.
Let's play the game!
The game we're going to
play is... Breast-sucking game!
Breast-sucking game!
That's right.
I'll explain the rules.
First of all, each team will
select one representative.
The representative will cover her
eyes and bite the person's boobs.
The game is to guess whose boobs it is.
If you guess whose boobs it is, you win.
If you don't, you lose.
If you win, you can enjoy
3 different hot Springs.
Choose your favorite course and enjoy!
If you lose, you have to
play a punishment game.
It's an erotic punishment game.
Let's do a 10-second countdown.
Ready, go!
10.
9.
8.
7.
Time's up!
Okay, then.
Please tell us the answer.
Um...
It's Aoi Ichino!
Please take off your blindfolds.
I made a mistake.
She's cute.
The actress who made a
mistake will be standing like this.
So, I want you to sit as long as you can.
Let's get excited for the second match.
Okay, let's get excited!
Ready?
Time's up!
Please give us the answer.
It was pretty big.
Right, Haya-San?
Please take off your blindfolds.
Ah, no, I'm not.
I'm not.
Another member, JOYO
Kiyosuke, was born.
Let's continue the game.
The third game.
Ready, go.
10, 9, 8,
7, 6,
5, 4,
3, 2, This is amazing.
Time's up!
This is amazing.
Please tell us your answer.
I don't remember anything.
Kazama Yuichi.
Please take off your blindfold.
I did it!
This is amazing.
She's beautiful.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
Well, then...
Are you really going to stand up, Yomi-San?
Thank you very much.
Now, let's move on to the next round.
Ready, set... 10, 9,
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up!
It smelled so good.
No, it's the cheek.
Please tell us the answer.
I think I know what it is.
It's Tadayuka-San.
Tadayuka-San.
Please take off your blindfold.
Please take off your shoes.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
10 seconds left.
We have 2,000 seconds left.
Let's get excited.
Ready?
Time's up!
Please give us your answer.
I'll go with Momoko Ishiki.
Please cover your eyes.
I'll go with Kiyosuke.
Welcome.
This is the last game!
Let's cheer up with a
loud voice until the end!
Ready?
Time's up!
I knew it!
Please give us the answer.
This is Ai Mukai.
Please take off your blindfold.
I knew it.
Congratulations.
I was a bit excited.
I felt good.
Thank you.
It's frustrating, but I'll do my best.
Congratulations.
I want to ask you to do it.
Now, the lucky chance
has come to Kiyotsuke team.
Yes.
You've been standing there carefully.
But one of the actresses who
is standing right now will have
to play rock-paper-scissors to
decide who will be on this team!
So, let's start the game!
Can I ask you to call out your name?
Let's start with Kuu.
After that, I'm going to go all out!
Psychological warfare!
I'm going to go all out, too!
I'm going to go all out, too.
Here we go.
Rock, paper, scissors!
That's how it is.
I'm going to go all out, too.
Yes.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ichiro-San, Ichiro-San!
Ichiro-San!
Ichiro-San, what's going on?
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Ichiro-San!
It's been a while since I've been here.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful.
So, Kazama-San, are you okay?
Are you okay?
We've decided how we're
going to spend our time.
Everyone, please enjoy as much as you want.
It's nice.
Right?
It's comforting.
They are so cute.
Because we won the game.
Excuse me.
May I join you?
May I?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
It's a nice bath, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
It was a pleasure.
It's fast.
Oh, it's raining.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
Is it salty?
It's salty.
It's so soft.
Oh, my God.
Amazing.
That's great.
I can't stop moving.
The river is amazing.
The river is so beautiful.
I'm on the edge of the river.
Ahhh.
Ahh It's so sweet.
Amazing.
You are going to have a baby.
What are you doing?
Wow.
The water is cold.
I'm afraid if I jump.
Look at that.
The water is cold.
It's cold.
It's hot.
I'll do my best.
Oh, my gosh.
It's hot.
Thank you for the meal.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
It's refreshing.
It feels so good.
I feel so happy.
I'm going to wash my face too.
Will you?
I'm not good at it.
I see.
I want to do that too.
Your face.
I'm not good at it.
I see.
It's so hot.
Kiss me.
It's so cool.
I feel sick.
Ah...
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to live an old life.
That's right.
oh.
ah.
oh oh.
oh.
oh oh oh oh It's warm.
It feels good.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
Oh, it's cold.
Oh, it's hot.
It's good.
Do you want to drink?
Does it hurt?
Does it feel like a butt?
Ma-kun, let me touch you.
More.
I will protect you.
Thank you.
Ah, I fell down.
Oh, great.
Here, here.
Feeling good.
Oh, no.
I will keep going down.
It's hot.
I want to do more.
Yeah, you two do it.
Isn't it hot?
It's hot.
I can't believe it's over!
I'm so happy!
Oh, my God!
This is great!
Good job.
Good, good, good!
You did it, you did it, you did it!
I'm at a loss for words...
I'm here to save him.
I can't believe he's still in my arms.
I'm so happy my sister's going to save him.
I'm so happy I'm going to cry right now.
I can't believe I made it through.
I'm terrified I'll die in this place.
I can't believe I can't move.
I don't know if I can make it through.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I'll put it in, too.
I feel good, too.
Have more!
More!
I can't do this anymore.
One more!
No, one more!
Let's wait.
It feels so good.
It's hot.
I feel sick.
Oh, no.
Thank you so much.
I want to go to the hot spring.
It's amazing.
What are they doing?
What should we do?
Can we go there?
It's amazing.
It's really fun.
Wait a minute.
I'm sure it's fun.
Let's go.
It's amazing.
It's different.
I'm going to take it off.
What?
Really?
Look.
I'm nervous.
I'll go first.
Wait for me.
Let's go.
I can't help it.
Let's go together.
I can't go alone.
I'm shy.
I feel so embarassed.
I feel so embarrassed.
Let's get back in the game.
Still don't want to play?
Just a second.
I will get back in the game.
Oh, well.
Please go back.
Feels good.
I'm nervous.
Here we go.
I don't want to go back.
It's hot.
It's deep?
It seems to be a good way.
Let's try it!
It's a great weather, isn't it?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Let's do it together, everyone.
Let's do it together!
Let's do it.
It's getting bigger.
It's amazing.
The mother is grumbling.
She is grumbling a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's so hot.
I can't get up.
I feel so hot.
I'm so hot.
Let's all stand in a line and put
our hands in each other's mouths.
I'm so happy.
This is great!
Do you feel good?
You have grown up.
It's so warm.
I feel so good.
Oh, that way.
Oh, no.
I love you.
No, no.
I feel so good.
Hey, hey, hey.
You're cheating on your boy friends.
We want to try it too.
I want to try it too.
Me too.
Can I try it?
It's embarrassing.
I don't like it. Look at me more.
Look at me properly.
It's embarrassing, but it's okay.
I'm so happy!
It feels so good!
Amazing!
I'm scared.
Go! Go! Go!
Let's go!
Go! Go!
She is out.
Did she run away?
Did she run away from inside?
You can do it.
Oh!
You were in the water.
How is the oil?
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Please close your eyes.
It feels good.
Please relax.
Yes.
Where are you now?
My lower back.
Your lower back?
Yes.
Oh, that's...
What's that crackling sound?
It's the sound of a bell.
It's a good sound.
Oh, is that so? Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I'm going to use some loofah.
Loofah is good.
I'm going to massage your back.
No, I don't want to.
I want to do so.
I'm going to massage the flowy part.
Okay.
I'm going to stretch a little.
Please inhale and exhale lightly.
Inhale... Take a deep
breath in and out slowly.
One more time.
Take a deep breath in and out slowly.
The other side.
Are you okay?
Yes.
It's hard.
It's hard It's super hard Relax.
It's hard around scapula.
It's hard there too.
Yes, it's hard here.
It's hard here It's not good
there, it's weak I can't do it.
There are many people who can do it.
It's easy to move the muscles.
It's okay.
I will massage here.
I will massage the upper
part of the pancreas.
Is it pleasant?
Yes, it's pleasant.
I am doing pleasant things.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Please let me know if you need anything.
I can't speak well.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I can't speak well.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
She is a member of the team.
Is she a nurse?
Yes, she is a nurse.
She is a nurse.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
Good girl, good girl.
It's okay.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
It's so good.
I think it's time to get up.
I'm sorry.
It's so hot.
Oh, it's hot.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's good, isn't it?
It's so good.
Oh, my.
Please come here.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
It hurts.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to cry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
They both keep staring at the baby.
Ahhh...
Baby barely stands up...
Baby keeps looking up...
Baby keeps looking down...
Looking up again...
Baby keeps looking up...
The baby wants to stand up...
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
Nice!
That's it!
That feels so good!
Uh-huh.
Ah.
Eh?
It looks painful.
Ah.
Does this hurt?
I'm starting to sweat.
It's almost done.
It's bleeding a lot.
It's amazing.
I want to go further and go on.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Don't do that.
It's cold.
It's dangerous.
I think I can do it.
I can do it.
Oh, no.
I'm going to die.
I'm going to die, too.
I'm so weak!
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Give me a lot of energy.
What should I do?
I can't breathe.
I'm going to have a hard time
if I don't go to the bathroom.
I'm not going to go to the bathroom.
I'm getting tired.
After a while, the women
are going to the bathroom.
I'm back.
I'm Rio. Nice to meet you.
I'm Yumi. Nice to meet you.
I'm Momoyakko. Nice to meet you.
I'm Haruka. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ikki. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ai. Nice to meet you.
I'm Yuka Dosue. Nice to meet you.
Thank you very much.
Here you are.
Thank you very much for today.
Please drink a lot.
Thank you very much.
President.
Great.
Thank you very much.
Amazing!
You drink quite a lot, don't you?
No, I don't drink much.
But it's easy to drink.
How is it?
It's good.
Wait, wait, wait.
Give it to me.
It's delicious, right?
Your lips are so soft.
I'm so excited.
Mini cheese.
My boobs are going to explode.
I'm going to cry.
My boobs are going
to explode Oh, it's hot.
Wow, it's getting harder and harder.
Oh, no.
I can't see anything
with my eyes and mouth.
I can't see anything.
It's a miracle.
Give me another kiss.
Kenji-San Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
Good boy.
You shouldn't be patient.
Drink it.
Drink it all at once.
He is a doer.
Is he a doer?
Oh, no.
He looks so cute.
He is so cute.
He looks like a baby.
He looks so cute.
Do you want me to pet him?
Let me do it.
Let's drink it.
It's hot.
Who is special?
This is a big one.
I wonder if it's a plane?
Here is the plane.
Oh my god... It
looks like a pilot.
Oh my god... She's so cute.
She's really cute.
You guys are so cute!
Let's lick together.
Oh, it's hot.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I want you to lick me.
I don't want that.
You can't do that.
You're cute.
It looks delicious.
I'm sorry.
Let's take a look at the photo of the baby.
She is so cute.
She is very comfortable.
She is very gentle.
She is very good.
She looks like she was born.
Do you want me to hold you?
Look at me.
Wow.
Do you want me to hold you?
It feels good.
You are so big.
Please go ahead.
Oruchan Are you
covering your eyes?
Did you cover your eyes?
You covered your eyes, didn't you.
Oh my! She's going out.
You can't follow her.
Don't go there.
She is going there.
Don't do that.
She is taking a rest.
I feel so good.
Open your chest.
Where is your chest?
Here?
Yes, here.
There is a lot of chest.
I'm going to lick you.
Does it feel good?
Frankfurt is good.
It's like a cake.
This is a special one for you.
Thank you.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm nervous.
It's a special one.
It's delicious.
Drink it with a cup.
It feels good.
He is calm.
That's scary.
It's like a zombie.
It's a zombie.
A zombie.
But, I can make a different kind of face.
You can make a different kind of face.
It's coming out.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Don't do that.
Do you have a cold?
I am fine.
This is our special sake.
Thank you very much.
I feel sorry for you.
This is our special sake.
Please try it.
What is it?
It's cute.
It's so cute.
Don't give it.
Put it in.
Wow, you're amazing.
Then I'll put it in my mouth.
It's not fair!
I'm happy.
No, no.
I can't do this!
I want to put it in, too.
I'll put it in.
I'm sorry.
Ahhhhhhhhhh!!!!
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!!!!
Ah, it feels so good!
Oh, my God!
I'm scared!
No!
I almost died!
Please let me go!
No!
Oh, my child The other side
Oh, my child Oh, my child.
Oh, my child Oh, my
child What a shame.
Oh, my child Oh, no!
Let's do it one more time.
What should I do?
This is for Ai-chan.
This is for me.
It feels good.
I feel sick.
I'm sick.
I'm sorry.
This is great.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yes, that's it!
Yes.
It feels great.
It's hard.
I feel sick.
I'm tired.
Let's push him over there!
Push him more!
More! More!
Oh, no!
I want you to follow me more.
Come here.
Hello.
Wow, amazing.
What's next?
Thank you very much.
Wow, now I will... I'm so happy.
Ah, she's coming in!
Ah, how nice!
So nice!
She's so nice!
This is so nice!
Would you like to have me in there too?
I want to be in there too!
I'm so happy.
When dad is at work,
I feel like I can go back
to my old haunted house.
I'm so happy.
I feel so good.
It's a joke.
I'm sweating.
It's wrong. It's wrong.
It's right.
Don't go out.
Oh, it stung!
Give him some water.
Oh, gosh.
Oh.
Ah!
I'll give him some water.
Oh.
Stop!
Stop, Stop, Stop!
I'll give him some water.
Oh.
Stop, Stop, Stop!
Thank you very much.
What's going on?
This is the biggest fight yet!
It's so fast!
Oh, it hurts.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh yeah a male
Oh, my goodness.
Please line up in a row.
Look at this.
Oh, my God!
Oh, I'm so happy!
You're so cute!
You're so cute.
Oh, my God.
It's hot.
It's so hot.
Oh, my God.
Let's go together.
I'm going to fall.
I can't take it anymore.
It's so hard!
Are you going to do it again?
However, I miss Mimmy's voice very much.
You are OK?
We can bring out as much as we need.
My life is full of stress.
Why is it so hard to make a video?
Oh my, oh my!
The baby is coming out.
There are many of baby in the baby body!
There are many baby in the baby body!
Wow!
Lots and lots!
I'm so happy!
I missed you!
I missed you... I
missed you... Kano-chan!
Kano-chan!
Oh my! Oh...
I'm going to throw up!
This is not good! I can't take it anymore!
Not good!
One more time!
Kano-chan is amazing!
He's very chubby!
Wow!
Thank you!
Thank you for loving me!
I'm so happy!
This is so nice!
Thank you!
She's having fun, so let's go.
It's so cute.
Come in.
Let's go in together.
It's so cute.
Let's take a picture together.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm going to imitate you.
It looks delicious.
Please call me again.
Let's have a drink together.
I'm a baby farmer.
I'm still here.
I want to join you.
and so, with that... The BAAM
project has come to an end.
Thank you very much!
Good job!!
STAFF How was it?
I wish I had another opportunity!!
STAFF Like the magical bar... All I
have to do is go in and out of Dylan.
I wanted to have one though!
The water is so cold!!
Why are you taking a bath?
You don't have to do this... You
don't have to do this... No way!
No way!
This is unbelievable!
Can you hear me?
Everyone! Let's take a bath together!
It's so good!
It's so cool!
The zookeeper is very kind.
This is the first time I've ever seen
such a large number of children.
I was surprised to see so many children.
It's a lot of fun!
I can't do it.
Kana-chan!
Take this slice for me!!!!
Ohhhhhh Oh, it's going to break.
Oh, it's going to break.
Daddy, I'm going to eat it!
Can I put it inside?
I'll put it inside.
Wait, wait, wait.
I can't hold it anymore.
Not yet.
Not yet?
How is it?
I can't do it!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God!
I can't do it!
It was very good.
Oh, it hurts.
Oh, it feels good.
It's so hot.
Oh, it's hot.
I'm so happy!
Both hands.
I want more.
...
... ... ...
I'm so sorry.
I feel...
I feel so weird!
I don't know what to do!
Are they connected?
Yes, they are.
I feel like... I'm
getting used to it.
It's the first time for me to touch it.
It's the first time for me to do it.
It's open! It's open!
More?
Wow!
It's too much!
I'm scared.
Hello.
I'm so happy to see you all here.
Ai.
Wow.
It's awesome.
Ai.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
I'm so marvelous.
I'm so wonderful.
I was surprised to see how
many times I had to do it.
It was hard for me to see the next step.
I was surprised to see
how many times I had to do
it, and I was looking
forward to the next step.
9.5 times.
I was surprised to see that I was
doing it for the first time in my life.
Oh!
You did it!
You are a pervert.
You can do it!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I am going to do it.
I did it!
Leave it to me, Mr. Motodana!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
I'm so excited.
It feels so good.
I want to kiss you.
Oh, my God.
I love it, so please do a lot.
I'm doing it.
It feels good.
Oh, my God.
Wow!
You're so cool!
Thank you.
One more time!
Ouch!
Ah, it's hot.
Thank you.
It's cold.
It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
Congratulations!
Thank you so much!
I'm going to cry.
So cool!
I'm going to play
with you I'm scared.
It's so good!
Feels good!
Thank you very much.
I feel so good.
Wait a minute.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
Hurry up!
Did you do it on your own?
Yes!
Wait a minute!
Oh, my God.
What's going on?
More, more.
Madonna is the best!
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I want you to hold Genki.
I feel good.
Move Genki.
Let's move a lot.
Do you want it?
Congratulations on the
20th anniversary of Madonna!
I got a neck sprain.
Can I hold it?
Oh my god.
Did you go to many places?
Did you have fun?
Yes!
We will continue tomorrow!
Are you ready?
Yes!
We will start now!
Let's go!
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
Are you hurt?
Do you still have pain?
It's okay?
It's okay, I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
It's coming out.
What are you doing?
Are you OK?
Are you going to sleep?
No, I was sleeping.
It's enough.
It's delicious.
She's a good girl.
She's smiling.
She's so cute.
It's so cute!
It's so good!
Is it good?
Let's eat!
They can't stop laughing and playing.
I'm going to take care of him.
I want to take care of your grandpa, too.
Ah!
Grandpa is alive!
How is it?
It's good.
Let's eat together.
It's so good.
I want to eat this.
Nani, do you want to do it?
Do you want to do it?
Come here.
You're so cute.
You can do it now, can't you?
So cute!
Whose mouth is it?
It's everyone's mouth.
Let's take care of each other.
It's like an elevator.
It's like a Kintama elevator.
It's going up and down.
Which one do you like?
I'm so happy!
It's so good!
You're so cute!
Don't lick me.
You're so nice.
I'll hold you.
I'll hold you tight.
You're so nice.
It's so good.
I'll have the joint.
Thank you.
It looks so good.
Let's try the flavor.
Which one do you like?
I'll try this one.
Is it good?
How is it?
It's so good.
What does it taste like?
It's amazing!
It's coming out!
I want that one too!
I'm shaking.
What does it taste like?
It's like...
Expensive.
It's expensive.
I'll have the expensive one.
Wow!
Is it English-ranked?
Is it okay because there
are a lot of younger sisters?
No, you can't eat this.
Look, it's an English-ranked team.
English-ranked?
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
It's too expensive.
Oh, it's so good!
Can I have an English lamp?
I want you to light it up.
Do you want me to light it up for you?
No, I'm scared.
I don't have one.
I don't think so.
What's wrong?
He's frowning.
Really.
Wow, he's shaking.
His tail is shaking.
Let's do it together.
From there.
It looks fun.
Wow!
The high-class Chimp is delicious!
The Egoranke was delicious!
I want to eat it!
Really?
Wow!
It's a million yen!
I'm so full.
Wait, how about this?
You are so big.
The biggest one in the world.
It's so tasty.
It's so good.
I'll give you some more!
This is the taste of wild!
How does it taste?
You are a good boy.
Wow!
You are eating well.
You are eating until your fingers are gone.
Wow!
Come closer.
Smile.
Great.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to go blank.
What should I do?
Is it going to come out?
Let's see if it comes out.
I want to see it!
It's sad.
Come here.
Yoroshiku.
You are great.
Come here.
You are like an angel.
Yoroshiku.
You are great.
Come here.
It's amazing!
What is it?
It hurts!
It's delicious!
It's dangerous.
It tastes like wild.
It's coming out.
I'm so happy.
It's moving.
It's moving a lot.
I don't think it's digital.
I'm so happy.
Let's go with you.
Enough! Let's go to our room next door.
The little ones go to bed.
Shall we go?
Let's go to my room.
We're going!
I can't sleep.
I can't sleep anymore.
I'm afraid she'll come again.
Thank you for the meal.
I've been drinking a lot.
It was amazing today.
There were a lot of people.
There were a lot of people, and everyone
was so erotic that I was quite satisfied.
Are you satisfied?
Is it your first time?
It's the largest number of
people I've ever been to.
That's right.
There were a lot of people on the bus.
A lot of faces came out and changed a lot.
Aya-San has a lot of things
to do, and Gou-kun has
a lot of things to do, but
I don't know what to do.
I still have a lot of adrenaline.
But it's not enough yet.
I said it wasn't enough.
But I still have tomorrow,
so I'm looking forward to it.
But I'm glad today.
It reminds me of something.
Reminds you of what?
Reminds you of something.
I'm getting excited.
Don't you have any?
Reminds me of something.
There was such a wonderful actress.
I could understand the feelings of a man.
I understand.
It's like an eye massage.
I know.
Everyone is naked.
I want to feel good.
In front of us.
I want to make everyone a side dish.
I understand the feelings of the fans.
I want to see it as a side dish.
That's right.
I want to touch it.
It's amazing.
If I touch it now...
It's hot, isn't it?
Oh, wait a minute.
It's really hot.
It's a souvenir.
This is hot with alcohol.
I'm already hot.
I'm quite satisfied today.
By the way,
What is it?
Something.
The story changes a lot.
Do you do it yourself?
quite.
I do.
I want to hear about that.
How often do you do it?
I want to know how often you do it.
I'm interested in that too.
I do it once a week.
That's so mean.
I'll finish it at once.
It's a little hot.
My tongue is tingling.
Is there such a word
as an important meeting?
No, there isn't.
What is important?
If I think about it, I'll take a little.
What are you going to do?
I think it's good to have a girl's skin.
I thought it would be
nice if I could do that, too.
I want to see beautiful things.
That's great.
I've seen the works of the
same actress, Madonna.
I've bought a lot of Don Pichon's works.
Do you use them as side dishes?
Yes, I do.
I do that a lot.
When do you want to do it?
On a rainy day.
When it's raining at night.
The sound of rain is so good.
It makes me feel sexy.
It's like a sensual novel.
With your ears.
With your ears?
Yes, with my ears.
But it's kind of moist.
I can hear the sound of water.
But when I look sideways,
there's no one there.
I'm like, should I do it?
It's a little higher.
It's the sex I used to do in the past.
It's a great thing.
Play it in my brain.
I'm going to do it.
There's a lot.
That's why I love it in the rainy season.
I like it too.
You do it every day.
That's great.
That's amazing.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I can't say it.
If you say it, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
That's cool.
It's so cool.
That's how it is.
I see.
It's so different.
It's so opposite.
On my day off,
I eat first.
I eat snacks first.
I eat late-night snacks first.
So I don't want to eat first.
I don't think so.
I think it's because you
have three big needs.
You want to eat well, and
you want to sleep well after that.
I don't think so.
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm not wearing white today.
Do you all take a bath?
I do.
I don't!
Do you wear a yukata?
I do.
Do you wear a yukata and underwear?
I don't, but... Do you
wear it to save yourself?
I put it on just in case.
Let's just put it on for now.
Is that so? What should I do?
Let's take a peek.
Is it real?
It's no bra.
Oh no.
Can I stand up?
Stand up a little.
I'm so excited.
I can't do it.
What?
I saw it.
This is terrible.
This is... I won't die.
It was hard to put on underwear.
You don't put on underwear, do you?
It looks like an armor.
I see.
I'm the only one who didn't come in.
The most erotic.
I'm so excited.
Terrible.
Oh, it's in.
It's in.
It's white, right?
Wait, wait, wait.
I was just... I
was just talking.
What?
This finger... This
is the only one.
This is the only one.
I'm still saying it.
I still have a lot of work to do.
Can I say something weird?
Can I do something weird now?
Of course.
Can I?
I want to see you.
I don't think I can sleep.
Can I do something weird now?
I want to see you.
I'm hot.
It's hard to take it off.
Please take it off.
It's taken off.
It's painful.
It's really hot.
Oh no, it's been washed away.
Oh no, oh no.
I'm surrounded by such a beautiful woman.
Look at this.
This is really bad.
Oh no.
If you take the top part,
you have to wash it away.
Eh? No way.
Wait a minute.
Why am I being attacked like this?
Is this a prank?
Wait a minute.
Amazing.
What is this?
I'm so happy, but I'm a little embarrassed.
No!
Eh?
Wait a minute.
Am I the only one who is strange?
Don't you think it's weird?
I think it's going to go in soon.
Take it off!
Panties!
Give me panties!
Please take off your underpants.
If you don't mind, let's
take off your underpants.
I don't want to take them off.
Let's take them off and go outside.
If we are wearing the same
clothes, I will be relieved.
I don't want to wear them.
That's right.
Let's change the clothes.
Change the clothes?
It's hard to see.
It was amazing just now,
so I can't see it slowly.
I can't see it at all.
It's a big deal.
What did I do?
It's the best position, isn't it?
Wait a minute.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you prefer the middle or the neck?
Both feel good.
I can't take it anymore.
I can feel your passion.
I know.
I don't care about anything.
It feels good.
It's short.
Only four of us.
You were the quietest.
I was.
It's true, but there are so
many things to worry about.
We don't have enough time.
It's weird to say, let's sleep as it is.
It was amazing.
We're doing something great, aren't we?
You're amazing.
You're drinking alcohol.
I want to borrow the power of alcohol.
I want to concentrate on this too.
Let's get everyone to
look at the hot place.
I want to have sex again.
I want sex again.
I want to have sex.
I'm so happy.
It feels really good, doesn't it?
It's the best.
It's very luxurious.
I'm so happy.
It feels so good.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to die.
Ai-kun!
Ah!
Wow, amazing!
This is a good girl.
Ah!
I can't stop crying.
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.