P.S. This is P.P.K System.
In Ginpachi,
they say that what anyone has it is a
My wife's precious mouth and manko are covered with a penis.
It looks like a skewer.
My wife is treated as a scoundrel.
It looks like a Dutch wife.
I'm so excited.
What's wrong with you?
Actually, I've been hiding something.
What is it?
Actually, I have a special sexual habit.
Sexual habit?
Do you know what a sexual habit is?
A sexual habit?
It means being cheated on?
Yes.
It's close to that.
My wife gets excited when she sees another man being cheated on.
Are you getting excited?
Yes.
If I cheat on someone, am I getting excited?
I think she gets jealous.
No, I'm not jealous.
I'm just a pervert.
I see.
You don't like me anymore?
I don't like you.
I was surprised.
That's right.
Why did you say that?
I wish you could keep quiet.
I think so, but it's not good to hide it between couples.
I was surprised.
What do you think if I ask you to have sex with another man?
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
That's impossible.
We only have sex once every three months.
Are you satisfied with that?
It's none of your business.
That's right.
I'm suffering because I don't want to do it.
Then, why don't you do it for me every day?
I can't.
Why?
I can't get excited without you.
I don't know what you mean.
Can you have sex with another man?
I want to hug you.
I'm thirsty.
What do you want?
Water.
You're upset.
Yes.
I want to take back what's important to me.
That's how I feel.
I don't want to take away Kana.
Please understand my feelings.
Men are complicated.
It's not easy to understand.
I'll try to understand.
I see.
That's all for today.
I have to pack the laundry.
Please take a look.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Osaki.
This is Kanae.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome.
Do you want coffee?
How about you?
Same.
Thank you.
I saw him several times on the Internet.
He understands our situation.
Don't worry.
I understand your feelings.
At first, my wife was just a child.
If I brought my wife today,
she would be relieved.
But now she's pregnant.
I see.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
Do you often go shopping with your wife?
Not really.
I see.
When you go shopping,
you become more and more friendly.
Is that so?
There aren't many stores
that sell orange-colored bags like this.
I see.
Let's have a drink.
Let's have a toast.
Here you are.
Sit in the middle.
Let's have a toast.
Actually,
I didn't show you this picture.
This is a picture of Chiba.
Wow.
Isn't it amazing?
Can I be like this?
That's right.
I don't know who you are.
Oh, right.
There's a DVD, too.
I'll bring it.
Let's watch it together.
DVD.
Wow.
This is amazing.
Come here.
It's pretty lively.
That's right.
This is my wife.
This is amazing.
Isn't it nice?
Yes.
It's amazing.
This face is amazing.
This is amazing.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Please use whatever you have in this room freely.
If you are hungry, there is a kitchen in the back.
There are many things in the fridge.
There are many beds in the futon.
There is a bed in the back.
Please use it freely.
Thank you.
There is a bath.
It is always open.
You can use it anytime.
It's not a hot spring, but it feels good to take a bath in the afternoon.
Thank you.
It's free time until dinner time.
Please relax.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Hello.
Thank you.
You are very good at it.
I see.
Let's take a bath.
Okay.
Let's go.
It feels good.
I wonder how it will be.
It's a great place.
I agree.
Thank you.
The weather is good today.
Let's go.
May I come in?
Yes.
Let's go.
It's fresh.
It's clean.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
It's okay
Don't worry
Come on, come here
Come here
Here
It's okay
OK
I want to touch you
Here
It may be that Silence paths may die in, but even a person who knows the meaning of seeing YouTube,
I can't put it on my table, so...
Come here
Don't get scared.
She's here!
What do you mean?
Come on...
I'm sorry.
It's not enough.
Let's continue.
I'm sorry.
Hey, madam.
I was surprised that it suddenly rolled over.
I see.
I can't stand it now.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hey, look.
It's yours.
What?
What is this?
This is definitely yours.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to get a drink.
Here you are.
It's an edgy costume.
That's right.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
I enjoyed the bath right away.
This is the best result for us.
I can't stand it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It hurts too much, this place.
I'm sorry.
Hoshikawa, I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
She's very excited.
She's a good girl.
She's wonderful.
Hoshikawa, you're beautiful.
Her costume is wonderful.
You did it with your husband last night, didn't you?
Yes.
You must have been excited to do it.
It looks like this.
There's nothing in here, but this villa is fun, isn't it?
Please be satisfied.
Madam, I can feel it.
It's amazing.
Look at her.
It's hot inside.
Madam, it's getting hot.
Madam, you're such a good girl.
It's amazing that it's hot inside.
Madam, it's getting hot inside.
She doesn't like it.
It's getting hotter.
Look at your husband's face.
He's smiling.
Madam, it's getting hotter.
It's getting hotter.
Madam, you're teaching Sado, aren't you?
Yes.
What are you teaching your students?
What?
Madam, please tell them.
I'm teaching them how to make tea.
How to make tea.
Poem.
Help.
Please help.
Not bad.
Love.
Don't tease me like that.
What's going on?
What's wrong?
I can't do it anymore.