The first day of
the trip It's so big.
It's about the size of a human.
It's so big.
It's amazing.
It's so fast.
It's so big.
It's really big.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
The first time I saw
him, he was 4 years old.
He was 10 years old at that time.
This is his first time in the water.
I have never seen him in the water before.
But he still finds new things.
I wonder what kind of fish it is.
I'm curious.
It looks like a carnivorous fish.
I wonder what kind of fish it is.
It's been a long
time since I've had a bath, but I feel
like I've been
bathed for the first time in a long time.
It's been a long
time since I've had a bath, but I feel
like I've been
bathed for the first time in a long time.
I'm going to take a bath.
How was your work today?
It's going well.
If it goes like this, it's a knuckleball.
How about you,
Misao? I'm doing well.
How about you, Kodomo?
I'm not good at this.
How many
times do you play this month? Next.
Ah, that's it.
Here's your hot water.
Thank you.
What? You're already
drinking? That's fast.
That's not fair. We're drinking too.
Is this okay?
Excuse me, can I have
some sake? You're fast.
Let's drink.
Cheers! It smells good.
It's good, isn't it?
Do you feel
refreshed? Yes, I do.
It's been a while since
I went to a hot spring.
It's good.
It's been a while since I went to a hot
spring, so I took a bath with my brother.
How many have grown?
Stop it!
How long have you not taken a bath?
I haven't taken a bath for about a year.
I went on a trip last year.
You are still growing.
I was just talking about that with Akiyo.
About boobs?
I want to talk about men's boobs.
It's not fun to talk about men's boobs.
I haven't done it recently.
Is that so?
My daughter
is amazing, isn't she? No, she is not.
My daughter is amazing, isn't she?
She is not normal.
Really?
You are amazing.
We are communicating.
What? Are you
Italian? No, I am not.
It is strange that you
don't speak Italian.
When I work, I speak Spanish.
Yes, yes, yes.
In the middle of the summer.
Because the work is getting late.
It doesn't matter.
It's better to do it when I'm tired.
When I'm tired.
What?
Our promise after marriage is like a
slogan.
One shot when I wake up.
What?
Get up in the morning and get on the bus.
My sister is like that.
What?
One shot at the station.
Really?
From the first
thing in the morning? Yes, yes, yes.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
No, I'm not that strong.
Hey, Aki-kun.
What kind of sex are you going to have?
What kind of sex?
Don't make me say that.
I'm curious.
You don't have to.
But I don't know anyone else.
It's been a while since I've
seen you, so I'm a little nervous.
Is that so?
It's my first time.
It's a little different from Ipe-san.
Wait a minute, Misa's
blood is flowing, right?
Well, the DNA is the same, but my
sister is also flying, so it's amazing.
I feel like it's empty, but what about the
action mode?
You're looking at this,
aren't you? Look at this.
I can't imagine from this body.
It's pretty amazing.
Is it that amazing?
What you have.
What I have.
Really?
Is it that amazing?
It's amazing.
I've never seen other people.
I don't know.
Show me.
Wait a minute.
You're not
a cutting board, are you? No, I'm not.
I'm not a cutting board.
It's OK.
I'm sorry.
I was nervous.
You suddenly came to me.
I'm so worried.
You have such a fine thing.
I don't say like I'm a secretary.
That's not true.
You have a fine thing, too.
But it may be more amazing than that.
It's more amazing than it looks.
You're laughing and saying.
Just a little bit is fine.
Just a little.
You're a family.
It's heavy, so I can't take it off.
Please take off the belt.
I can't take it off.
You can't take it off?
Yes, I can't take it off.
We don't have that many people.
Don't say that.
It's early in the morning.
What's early in the morning?
You don't have to.
Show me.
I can't see it.
Because... Hey, hey.
Hey, look at this.
I can't see anything.
Can you see anything? No, no.
It's real.
It's real?
Really? It's this wide.
It's so wide.
I have one like this.
Can you show it to me?
I'm not looking at the whole thing yet.
Hey, you can't see anything.
It looks like a fish sausage.
No, it's not.
It looks like a squab.
It looks like a fish sausage.
It looks like a grilled fish.
No, no, no.
It's amazing.
I touched it, but it's okay.
Let's eat from the top.
Wait a little longer.
It's amazing.
What?
You know what?
What are you talking about?
We are brothers.
What?
You know, when
we are married, we get bored easily.
It's
not like we're going to sleep all night.
We're doing it every day.
The pattern is set.
But we're not that bored.
It's important to be energetic.
So... Have you ever heard of it?
I thought it was only about overseas.
I don't think that's going
to happen in Japan.
There are places like that.
You mean there is a place?
Since we are
here, let's change it once in a while.
What?
Are you doing such a thing?
Once in a while?
It's good to change it once in a while.
It's exciting.
But you should stop it.
It's exciting to be seen,
isn't it? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
You should stop it.
He is eating very well.
What's wrong, Misato-san?
Why are your nipples so swollen?
What's wrong with you?
What happened to you?
I'm so embarrassed.
I've never done such a thing in my life.
Why is Misato's nipple so big?
It's as big as a bear.
It's big as a bear.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Tell me honestly.
Misato.
What are you doing?
Your belly is wet.
Your belly is getting bigger and bigger.
Your belly
is getting bigger and bigger, Misato-san.
It's not good.
I can't stop it! Give me more.
Give me more.
I can't stop it!
You can't stop it.
Do you like it?
Have you ever
been blamed by a woman like this?
No, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
I've blamed you so many times.
I'm the only one who knows.
Then you have
to teach her the different tastes of women.
Hey!
Sometimes, Misano
has different tastes of men.
Really?
Which one
do you like more, this one or this one?
Sometimes you are
so nervous that your lower body is shaking.
I can't do it.
You have to do it to be brave.
Wait a minute.
Misato, you can't stop crying.
I'm sorry.
It's been 15 minutes.
Oh, my sister.
Why? Look at this.
Look at this.
It's a lot.
Let me see.
What are you
doing? Don't do that.
How do you feel? I feel good.
You should be more aggressive.
You are not aggressive.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to drink it?
What?
I'm going to drink it.
Oh, come on.
Just do it.
It doesn't matter whether
you drink it or not.
Are you excited?
No.
I'm excited.
But I can't drink it.
Why are you in such a hurry?
You are so kind.
You are so shy in front of your husband.
You are a pervert.
You are, aren't you?
If you weren't a pervert,
you wouldn't be so shy.
Look at yourself.
It's so big.
Look at this, Misato.
It looks delicious.
Why did you rub it so much?
I rubbed it from the top of my panties.
Really?
Look at this, Misato.
If I rub it directly like this,
will I be able to see it? That's right.
It looks delicious as usual.
It's different from time to time.
That's right. If I
don't taste it, I'll forget your goodness.
That's right.
In order to know your goodness.
If I rub it a lot, I think you'll see it.
She is crying.
Look, Akio Kumara.
She is shaking her body.
She is shaking.
Akio Kumara is shaking.
She is crying.
You look so cute.
You are so slimy.
Do you want me to do something
for you, Misato? Rub your boobs.
It feels good,
doesn't it? I'm hungry.
What's wrong, Misato?
My stomach is full.
Full? I'm hungry.
You're amazing, Akirin.
Your dick is harder than mine.
Is it hard?
It's small but hard, isn't it?
It's really hard.
It's hard.
But when you do it, it's harder.
Really? I'm glad.
Can I do more?
You are good at it.
You are my sister.
Is it always hard?
How much do you
have in your head? Here.
Tell me how much you have in your head.
If you don't, you have a lot in your head.
You can see it, can't you?
I'll squeeze out all of it for you.
Misato, this is a dry golden egg.
You did it today, didn't you?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Why don't you eat this?
You are so energetic.
She is still a virgin.
Oh my god!
I feel sick, too.
What?
Hey,
Do you see a doggy?
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
But the smell is the same.
I smell it, too.
No, you don't.
The shape is different.
It's been a long time.
Honey.
Yes?
Can I come in?
Ura-chan!
You got in!
Great!
Big!
You have a great body shape!
Do you feel good?
I feel good!
You have a lot of body fat!
I know!
You have a lot of this!
I have!
What's wrong?
Do you want me to
help you? Yes, I do.
What's wrong?
It's been a long time.
It's been a
long time since I had such a hard time.
You're not crying, are you?
You're crying a lot.
You're hungry, aren't you?
You're eating a lot.
What are you going to do with this?
You can't help it.
Come here.
What is it? You have so many.
What's wrong with you?
You're crying all of a sudden.
Come here.
I'm too excited.
I'm so happy.
I'm crying.
I'm too excited.
I'm so happy.
I can't get up.
Misato, get up and look.
She's sleeping.
Look at her.
She's so dirty.
Please look at me from over there.
Momoko, look at me.
I'm in the solitude.
Your tears are falling into me.
I'm going to cry.
Please feel good in my chest.
Misaki, please look at me.
Oh, no!
Oh, I was surprised.
I don't know if I can go in.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, my God.
Mi-san, wake up.
Can I dig out a heart full of love?
Oh, no!
It's been a while.
It's been a long time
since we met last time.
We'll meet again tonight.
I heard that!
But for a while, I'll be with you.
Sounds like fun.
You don't have to go to HAPPIFY.
Of course.
We can eat together.
We usually eat at TAKEOFF.
We are tired of eating out.
We eat at TAKEOFF.
I'm hungry.
How do you like it?
It's really good.
It's good, isn't it? It's good.
This is scary.
I want to eat half of it.
You were eating at that time.
No, I wasn't.
I didn't eat at all.
I ate a lot.
Let's stop it.
I'm in a hurry.
Thank you very much.
The soup is more than I expected.
Do you drink it? Yes, I do.
I can't drink it.
What are you shooting?
The boss told me to shoot it.
You all have nice Yukata.
Are you really
drunk? Just a little.
Oh my god.
..
I need to weigh it.
Is it OK?
OK.
Wait a moment.
You look gorgeous.
Let me check the weight of this.
No, wait.
You also weight the meat with the lid.
This is the
first time for me to eat this kind of food.
Huh?
This is the
first time for me to eat this kind of food.
It's a bit stinky.
This is the
first time for me to eat this kind of food.
It's good, isn't it?
Cheers!
Cheers! It's good.
It's good.
It's hot.
I'm full.
Please eat all the cheese.
It's fun.
Let's go for a run.
We've been shooting for a long time.
Let's have a drink.
Where is the glass? It's broken.
It's OK.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm OK.
Next.
Please wear the dress stand.
OK.
I'll put it in.
You look cute when you get dirty.
It's hot.
My face is getting red.
It's not red.
It's hot.
Take a picture over there.
Please take a picture of me.
It's embarrassing.
I'll take a picture of you.
Cute girls only take
pictures of their faces.
I'm not taking pictures of my face.
You are.
Go ahead.
What? I'm hungry.
Don't call it hungry.
It's an act of drunkenness.
It's a joke.
It's like anything.
My body is hot.
I'm drinking Kacchou.
Kacchou?
Kacchou is good.
Kacchou has a big breast.
What?
It has a big breast.
I don't have it.
It's terrible.
It's not natural.
It's natural.
I don't know because it's a uniform.
I don't know at all.
I made a mistake.
Let's drink a lot today.
Let's drink a lot.
I think so.
I'm thirsty.
I'm thirsty, too.
This is the toilet.
He is so dark.
This is purple.
His beard is missing.
What?
He is saying to pee.
That's not true.
What are you doing?
He is saying to pee.
He is not saying.
Let's go to the toilet together.
Let's go to the toilet.
OK.
Don't film this.
Can you go to the toilet?
Why are we going to the toilet together?
Everyone is drinking too much today.
Everyone is drunk.
I'm enjoying it.
I want to go to the toilet.
I can pee.
Where are you going? Toilet.
Where are you going?
Isn't it suspicious to go to the toilet?
Isn't it suspicious?
You are drunk.
Kato-san, you are drunk.
You should go alone.
It's lonely to go alone.
I'm a little lonely.
You are alone.
I'm lonely.
I want to take you to the toilet.
Toilet.
Toilet is on the right.
It's hot.
Why are you pulling me?
I was just about to put my hand on you.
Then I'll take it off.
Oh, I shouldn't take it off.
Oh, it's the other way around.
Purple.
Pants? Do you like
purple? It's slippery.
What is this?
This?
No, it's a shimmy.
I like it.
Is there a shimmy?
Are you a girl?
You are so erotic.
Yes, I am.
Yes, you are.
You are wearing a white one.
I am a girl.
Really? Let me try it.
I am wearing a white one.
You are wearing a white one.
Who are you going to fight?
I am going to fight Kagari-chan.
Are you going to fight me?
Are you going to fight with me?
Then I'll kiss you first.
What do you think?
Why are you here?
It's just right here.
That's right.
I'm embarrassed.
We usually work together.
I don't know what you're going to do
from tomorrow.
I'm an adult.
I don't know anything.
I'm embarrassed.
It's okay. Don't tell anyone.
What if the head of the club finds out?
I've been filming you
as the head of the club.
I'm the head of the club now.
With whom? I don't know.
I want to see you.
I left earlier than you.
I don't care.
I don't know.
Are you a troublemaker?
Troublemaker?
Troublemaker? Don't say that.
It's hot.
Haru-chan, it's hot.
I'm laughing.
It's hot.
You're sweating.
You're sweating a lot.
I don't want to sweat.
Do you want me to
lick you? Lick me.
How did you do
this? I don't know.
How did you do this?
My boss did it for me.
Is that so?
I'll look at you.
Take it off.
I can't do it.
It's short.
It's easy to cut.
It's easy.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it? It's hot.
Your belly is hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's beautiful.
You have a good body.
You have a good shape.
It's beautiful.
It's good.
Purple.
Purple? Purple.
It's really purple.
Purple is a fancy color.
Fancy color?
Do you have a bank
account? No, it's not.
It's just a plain color.
It's the color of dissatisfaction.
Yes, yes, yes.
When did you get this stain?
When did I get this stain?
You guys always wear sexy clothes.
It's so colorful.
Well, I'm just confused
because of the alcohol.
You're really beautiful.
It's stained.
Stained? You're alive.
It's purple, so it stands out.
Oh, it stands out?
Do you have
any stains? No, I don't.
No, you don't.
Is it a shadow?
Isn't it a shadow?
Is it a shadow? It's a shadow.
No, it's not.
But if you touch the
stained part, it's the tip.
It's not a shadow.
Look at this.
Oh, it's true.
It's moist.
Really?
It's like a hot spring.
I was in a hot spring before having a meal.
While saying,
Why? You were drinking so much.
It doesn't matter to me.
I drink alcohol.
It's good.
You said it's bad.
No way. It's good.
You're a virgin.
You are good at it.
You are sweating a lot.
It's hot.
You are good at it.
Do you usually do that?
I don't do that because I'm a virgin.
She's always like a little girl.
She's a little girl, but she's amazing.
She is a girl who was born for the world.
Look at her eyes.
Yes.
It's embarrassing to see her like this.
See? She is closing her eyes.
She is smiling.
What are you smiling at?
Is that a bomb?
She is saying, Ah.
No, that's not it.
Here you are.
Oh, wait.
It's ticklish.
I can't do that.
Oh, there.
Look!
This is not the place.
You look like you actually like it.
I don't want to be eaten.
I'm drunk.
Wait a minute.
Here you are.
Oh, you are a good boy.
Wow, you are a great boy.
You are a naughty boy.
What? Your pose.
Why are you getting used to it?
I'm not getting used to it.
What is the pose? Oh, nice.
Oh, it's big.
Wow!
You are so beautiful.
You have a big butt.
Actually, it's this side.
This side? Oh, buttocks?
I'm embarrassed.
I went to the bathroom, so I'm embarrassed.
What are you doing?
What are you doing with seaweed?
Seaweed?
Raw seaweed?
Tuna?
It's my first time to eat it.
It's tuna.
I ate a lot of tuna today.
It looks like raw.
What? It looks like raw.
It's warm and breathable.
I'm sorry.
You too.
Is it cold?
Is it good?
No?
Is it cold? It's cold.
I want to hug you.
Let me hug you.
It's a throw.
Do you feel it?
Yes.
My fingers are weak.
I can hear the sound of a baby crying.
I'll put the medicine on your neck.
Do you want to lick my neck?
Do you want me to hold your neck?
I'll hold your neck.
Don't do that, please.
Please take a shot and give it back to me.
No, no, no, that's not good.
Put it on.
Like this?
Everyone is doing that.
It looks good on you.
Does it look good on me?
Like this? Oh, no.
Do you have earwax? It's salty.
It's eel.
It's good.
It's my first time.
You like it, don't you?
You are so clever.
Because it's my first time to have sex.
Are you sure?
Yes.
You are careful.
You can't have
sex with your boyfriend? No, I can't.
Why?
I can't do it for some reason.
Really?
You are so erotic.
What is this?
I can't hold it.
Really? I can hold it.
What is this?
Wow, you lick it all the time.
How long do
you lick it? 3 seconds.
What? All the time?
It's coming off.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
No, no, no.
It's too late.
It'll fall off.
Oh!
Oh! It's too late.
It'll fall off.
Oh!
It feels good, but it's embarrassing.
You used to be like this.
You used to move like this.
Why?
Because you looked like this.
You look so happy.
You don't like it, do you?
No.
Why?
Because you are excited.
I'm not excited.
Why are you excited? No reason.
Because you are on the bed.
Yes.
Because you
are doing something you should not.
Yes, I am doing something I should not.
You are narrow.
Great!
Look at her mouth.
She has a big mouth.
What's up?
Wow, you are great.
You don't pull out.
Great.
You are great.
I'm sorry.
Are you sleepy?
You're sleepy, aren't you?
I want to sleep.
You can't. You'll get a bruise.
I'm fine.
You can't.
You can't do that.
You slept a lot.
You don't want to go to your mom.
It's OK.
Do you want to go
to your mom? It's too small.
How do you feel? It feels good.
It's a miracle.
It's hard.
It's cold.
You are a good girl, aren't you?
You are a good girl,
aren't you? I'm nervous.
Are you nervous?
What are you doing?
Where have you been?
I didn't do anything.
You didn't do
anything? I didn't.
You didn't do anything?
No.
You feel good, don't you?
Do you like the bag? Yes, I do.
You like it, don't you?
Oh, no!
Look!
Don't spread it! I'm sorry.
Do you want me to put you on my lap?
Oh, it feels good.
It's good.
I can't get enough of this meat.
It feels so good.
You're doing a good job.
Are you okay?
Your knees are stuck.
Oh, it's stuck.
You are very good at it.
No, no, no.
Are you a girl?
What?
You are not a girl, right?
Are you a girl? You are coming.
I feel sick.
You are amazing.
No.
You are a girl.
You are mean.
You are moving a lot, aren't you?
Do you feel good?
Do you want me to take it out?
Ouch!
Oh, my God! I'm so nervous.
It's all out, isn't it?
I feel like it's all out.
The amount of rice is... It's not a meal,
but it's like alcohol.
Did you pee?
No, I didn't pee.
I didn't pee. I'm clean.
Let's go to bed.
I'm going to eat.
I'm sweating.
I'm going to sleep on the futon.
Who's going to sleep here?
I'm going to sleep here.
Really?
Yes.
What about here?
The one next to you?
This is the manager.
Why are you looking at my futon so much?
I'm going to be scolded.
It's OK.
Are you tired?
I feel like I'm still sleeping.
If you wash your feet, you'll be fine.
I want to go home soon.
It's cold! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I want to go home soon.
It's OK.
I'll be back soon.
Are you okay? It's hot.
Can I take off your obi?
Which one?
It looks painful.
Please raise your hips.
How do you feel?
Are you ok? Yes, I'm fine.
Do you want some
water? Yes, please.
Where is the water?
I don't have any.
Are you ok? Yes, I'm fine.
Are you going to sleep soon?
Yes.
Are you ok? Yes, I'm fine.
It was really fun today.
Yes, it was fun.
I'm drunk, too.
Can I sleep here for a while?
Do you want to sleep together?
Can I sleep together?
Everyone will come.
I took a bath, so it's okay.
Did you take
a bath? I took a bath.
Why did you take a
bath when you were drunk?
I'll make you drink.
Is it painful here?
You touched me a lot a while
ago, didn't you? Don't touch me.
I can't?
What are you doing?
You are limping.
What do you think I'm doing?
You can't do it because you're naked.
Are you okay?
Is this part weak? Yes, it is.
Here?
Don't touch here.
What? You are strong.
What is this?
I'm going to fall asleep.
Kacchan is going to fall asleep, too.
Hey, everyone's taking a bath.
I'm going to sleep.
We're taking a bath, so...
I'm going to fall asleep.
It's okay, right?
Are you ready?
Then, I'll kiss you.
What are you
doing? I'll kiss you.
Like this.
I'll kiss you.
I want to stand on this side, too.
It's hard.
You have a weak neck.
I have a weak neck.
I want to stand on this side, too.
What's wrong?
I can't open my mouth.
Let me see.
It's too early.
I raised my hips by myself.
Where do you feel good?
I feel good all over.
All over? You are greedy.
It's hot.
Oh, it's hot.
I'm glad I'm not sweating.
It's hot.
I was suffering when I was eating.
I was suffering.
Can I take it off? Let me see.
It's beautiful.
It's cool.
I'm going to sleep a little longer.
You are beautiful.
Am I beautiful?
I'm sweating a lot.
What is it?
Maybe he got drunk and passed out.
Oh, I rubbed it.
Are you okay? I rubbed it.
I can't stand it anymore.
I rubbed it.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I see.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good,
doesn't it? It tickles.
It tickles.
It tickles, doesn't it?
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay.
As it is.
It's open.
I put it in my mouth.
Because I can't do it anymore.
It feels good.
Oh my god.
What's going on? Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
The sound is good.
I feel like I'm in space.
Oh, it's great.
It's hot.
They did it!
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry.
Give me a hug.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
The baby is crying.
Please come to me.
What are you doing?
Did you come in? Not yet.
Not yet? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Bitten by a Black
Maggots Bitten by a Black Maggots
Rattling
Rattling It's creepy.
What's wrong? I'm scared.
It feels so good.
It's tight.
Oh, my God!
Is it better if I
turn it off? Turn it off.
Turn it off.
Thank you very much.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
It hurts.
It's cold.
Oh, my god!
My skin is peeling off.
It's disgusting.
You have black spots on your eyes.
Oh, no! I'm scared.
If I wear something thick, I am scared.
You have a lot of dark spots.
Oh, my god.
I'm so full.
I see.
I'm going to take a bath.
Did you drink a lot? Yes, I did.
You just drank a lot.
I think it's over after this.
Do you want to go somewhere to drink?
Are you OK?
We don't have enough time.
You want to drink, don't you?
Maybe I want to drink a little.
You are drunk.
Do you want
to go to a shop or go shopping? Let's go.
I'm really drunk.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
I'm fine.
This way.
A few days later Are
you OK? Yes, I'm OK.
You were sleeping.
Yes, I was sleeping.
I was about to fall asleep, but I didn't.
I hope no one will come today.
It's so quiet here.
Yes, it is.
What would you like to drink?
I'll have a lemon tea.
Lemon tea?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Me, too.
This is the first time to go
on a business trip, isn't it? Yes, it is.
I'm so excited.
I drank too much yesterday.
Everyone drinks too much today.
It's not like work, is it?
It's fun, isn't it? Yes, it is.
I'm glad I came here.
I'm glad to hear that.
You look like a girl who wears a yukata.
Yes, I do.
I'm wearing a
yukata because the tree is falling down.
You don't have
a boyfriend now, do you? No, I don't.
I don't have a boyfriend for a long time.
You don't have
a boyfriend for a long time? Yes, I do.
I had a boyfriend until two months ago.
You don't have a boyfriend.
You are getting drunk.
I am.
It's just two of us.
Are you okay? Are you drunk?
Are you drunk? Yes, I am.
You should drink more.
You are weak.
I am weak.
Koko-chan is cute!
She kept laughing a while ago.
Was she laughing?
She was laughing and making fun of me.
That was funny.
It's your first time, isn't it?
I don't think so.
You startled me.
You're not good.
I'm not good.
It's a lie.
But you won't tell anyone,
will you? No, I won't.
You can work.
You're fashionable.
I don't know
if it's safe, but you have a big chest.
What cup is that? Green cup.
Green cup.
I can't do it.
I'll be seen by
everyone, won't I?
I was conscious of it.
You know what?
I've been thinking about it all day today.
About the banquet?
The president asked me to shoot it,
but it's noisy.
I'm going to shoot it now.
You said you wanted
to take a picture of me.
I was lying.
I said I wanted to take a picture of you.
I don't like this.
You are cute.
Do you look at me?
I don't look at you.
Don't you look at me?
You are warm.
You drank a lot.
I drank a lot.
You drank a lot, didn't you?
Your face is so red.
I always show my face.
You are fine. You are cute.
It's hot.
You are so cute.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
Why so suddenly?
Why? Is it bad?
It's not bad, but I was surprised.
It's warm.
I'm hot, too.
It's so hot.
It's cute.
You don't want to come back, do you?
Where did everyone
go? It's warm.
Are you going to take off your sweater?
I don't want to.
I want to take a picture of a cute girl.
You're not cute. You're red.
You're just a red person.
I'm sorry.
Really?
What should I do?
Why?
Because of this
distance? It's dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Do you like it?
I'll take you to the vet soon.
Are you sick? No, I'm not.
Wait.
My face is getting red.
You're not at home, are you?
I'm not at home, but
I said I wasn't at home.
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
Why do you ask such
a question? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I was going to do that.
No?
I didn't notice.
I was going to do that.
What's going on?
Let me see.
Wow.
You drink a lot.
You drank too much.
Are you cold? No, I'm fine.
You didn't
touch the room, did you? No, I didn't.
I was just reflecting.
I was in front of you.
I'm having a lot of fun.
Are you drunk?
Huh?
I feel like you're drunk.
If no one comes... I don't know what
you're doing.
I don't know what you're doing.
You are good at it.
You should go home.
Everyone is drinking.
It's funny to talk about it.
Everyone is funny.
I feel like I'm going to come back.
It's OK.
You will be sleepy when you come back.
I haven't slept yet.
I haven't.
Did you drink too much?
Yes.
I haven't slept yet.
You are great.
You ate too much.
Did it hurt? Oh my god.
It's so big.
You don't remember when you
get drunk in the morning, do you?
I don't know if I'm not that drunk.
But it's embarrassing to
remember when we're all together.
I don't know if I'll keep it a secret.
What's wrong? Long time no see?
Yeah, it's been a while.
It's warm. Your hands are very warm.
You are energetic even if you drink water.
Thank you.
You are amazing.
You are warming up.
You have a very erotic face.
What?
Have I changed from before?
Why are you doing that?
Because I like it.
I feel good.
You are so sexy.
Your lips are too big.
I think you will get cold.
Really?
I got caught.
Oh, it's cold.
I'm crying.
I don't like such a bright place.
I feel so good.
I'm crying.
Wow, it's so warm.
Wow, it feels so good.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to kill you.
Oh, it's so warm.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, it feels good.
Hi guys! Welcome back to my channel.
Today, I'm gonna eat
Bburinkle chicken feet.
Please enjoy watching it!
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe and like.
It feels good.
It feels good here.
It's around the back of my back.
It's tickling.
You are going to sleep.
You have a lot of hair.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
It's amazing
that you can feel the back of my neck.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's like a gori gori.
Is it hard? It's very hard.
It's hard and gori gori.
Oh, it feels good.
I can hear the sound.
I can't believe it.
Are you okay?
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
It's painful.
It's great.
I can't do anything.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to go.
I don't wanna go.
Oh, my God!
Please subscribe to my channel.