This is the end of the video.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Please subscribe to my channel and give it a high rating.
Thank you for your viewing.
This is the end of the video.
See you in the next video.
Thank you for your viewing.
This is the end of the video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Hello everyone, I'm Waito Okoyama.
Today, I woke up at 7am and ate breakfast, toast and scrambled eggs.
I had a scramble egg.
Today is the second day of shooting.
I'm very nervous.
I couldn't eat breakfast as much as usual.
That's why my belly is swollen.
Like always, I bought some gummies.
This is my first time eating gummies.
I'm going to try it.
It's sour.
It's sour, but it's delicious.
I'm going to eat while the rain is going down.
I came here by train today.
After all, when I ride a bicycle in the morning, the wind feels good, so it makes me feel good.
It was going to rain, but it hasn't rained yet.
Maybe she is a hale girl.
I think it's time to go to sleep.
Thank you very much.
It's been a while since the last time I filmed a video, so I'm a little nervous, but I'm sure I'll be able to do it again.
From now on, it's the first day of the first half. I'm still a little nervous.
The room is 2013.
Where is it?
What kind of people are there?
I still have a long way to go, so I have a lot of things to do.
Are you also wondering about the
wardrobes that that this is
uh ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah 3
I'm going to sleep.
Hello.
Please come in.
There is a sofa over there.
Oh, you took a picture.
Yes, I took a picture.
This is your first time with me, isn't it?
Yes.
Please introduce yourself.
Yes, please.
What is your name?
First of all, my name is Koiwa Ito.
I'm 19 years old and I'm going to university.
Really?
Yes.
Is school fun?
School is fun.
I see.
What about today?
Today is summer vacation.
Oh, now.
Yes.
I see.
Can you study?
No, I'm not good at it.
I'm just good at it.
How was the shooting last time?
I was very nervous last time.
But it was fun.
Really?
Yes.
I see.
It was your first time.
Yes.
You were interested in the world of English, weren't you?
Yes, that's right.
I didn't have much confidence in myself,
so I wanted to be confident.
I saw actresses on SNS.
You mean actresses on TV?
Yes, I was interested in them.
I see.
Do you like girls?
Do you like watching cute girls?
I like watching cute girls.
You don't like race?
No, I like watching cute girls in videos and pictures.
I see.
Do you mean that most of the actresses are cute?
Yes, they are very cute.
I see.
There are a lot of people who are on TV.
Are you interested in that?
I haven't thought about it yet.
You haven't thought about it yet?
Do you have any dreams in the future?
I haven't decided yet.
I want to decide something in college.
While studying.
I see.
You still have a long way to go.
Do you know what you're going to do today?
Today...
I'm going to do something erotic.
What kind of erotic thing?
I don't know much about it.
You didn't come here because you love erotic things, did you?
That's right.
What do you mean?
It's not that I like blood, but I don't feel like I'm feeling good about it.
I don't know if I'm feeling good about it, but I'm not sure if I'm feeling good about it.
That's what I thought.
After we broke up, I thought I'd try it on my own.
Did you want to try it on your own?
Yes.
But I didn't really know how to do it.
What did you think when you tried it on your own?
I didn't really know how to do it.
Which do you prefer, S or M?
Do you know S or M?
I do.
What is S?
What?
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
What is S?
Sa...
I don't know.
Sa?
Sa...
What? I don't know.
Sa-do.
It's not a name.
That's how it is.
That's not true.
It's a difference.
What about M?
M is...
I think so.
I understand.
Which one do you think it is?
I think it's M.
I don't think it's S.
I think so.
I'm going to check the tube for the first time.
It's big.
Do you think it's big?
Yes.
Am I wrong?
Have you ever used this?
It's similar to the first one, but it was smaller.
Oh, there's a bigger one.
This one.
It's this big.
Please look at it a lot.
Please watch it a lot.
Is it good for you?
It's good for me, thank you.
Let me see.
Do you like it?
It's getting hot
It smells a little
It smells sour
I'm going to the bathroom, so come here.
It's getting bigger.
How is it?
It's okay.
I'll wipe it off.
It's so cute.
Have you ever been touched on the buttocks?
I haven't
Why?
You're eating a little more
It was like you were waiting for me
Wow, you're so cute
Look at your hips.
Open your hips with your left hand.
Open your hips more.
Where are you looking now?
Look at your hips.
You don't like it?
Look at your face in the mirror
It's beautiful over there
It's a beautiful pink color
I'm going to give you an itchy smell.
I'm sorry I made you cry.
I can't help it.
I'm going to take a bath.
You have a big body.
What do you like about your body?
I don't know.
You have a good neck.
Do you want a bath?
But I don't have any confidence.
What?
For example, do you like the shape of boobs?
Yes.
You're standing still, aren't you?
Do you have anything to do with love?
No, I don't.
I'm scared.
It's good, isn't it?
Move your shoulders a little.
Can you do it more?
Can you do it again?
Please do it again
I'm sorry.
You look weird.
I know you're not feeling well.
I made a really good book.
Let's read it together.
Have you ever taken your man's underwear off?
I haven't.
You haven't?
How is this bath?
It's very slippery.
Please touch it.
This is lotion.
Have you ever taken a bath like this?
No.
This is the first time I've taken a bath like this.
This is a whole body bath.
It hurts.
Don't you take a bath with a man?
I don't take a bath.
You don't take a bath with your boyfriend?
I've never taken a bath.
I see.
You took a bath with your father, didn't you?
I took a bath with my father.
How old were you?
When I was little, I was about 3 or 4 years old.
You don't take a bath with your father?
I don't.
Why?
Why? I don't know.
I see.
How many people have you had so far?
One person.
Only one person?
How many people have you had so far?
Only one person.
I see.
Don't you have a lot of etchings?
No.
How many times have you done it?
Not once or twice, right?
I don't know.
Really?
Then, you haven't done it yet.
I'll do it again.
It's too much.
It's been a long time since I've had a body bath, hasn't it?
That's right, that's right.
It feels good to be able to apply lotion, doesn't it?
Yes, it feels good.
You're so beautiful when you're shining.
Look this way and put your buttocks together.
I'm supporting you.
I'm going to massage your buttocks.
I'm sorry.
Please help me.
I'm so tired
Can you do it a little bit more?
Yes
How is it?
It feels weird
It's hard even with just one
Are you okay?
I feel good
I can't help it anymore.
This is the most important thing.
I'll give you the medicine for that.
I'm sorry.
All right.
That's all.
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting for you.
It's not over yet.
Look at me.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
It's not over yet.
I'm going to wipe it off.
I'm going to wash it off.
Thank you.
Do you want me to wipe your face?
I'll wipe your face.
How is it?
It's good.
What?
It feels good.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Yes, it's hot.
This is a carp.
Wow, it's moving a lot.
What kind of fish is this?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's big or small.
You don't know?
You can't do that.
Are you tired?
How do you feel?
I feel good.
If you feel good, say you feel good.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
If you feel good, say you feel good.
Look at me.
Come here.
Put your feet here.
Open your mouth.
Like you did before.
Say, please lick me.
Please lick me.
Look at me and say it.
I want you to lick me a lot.
Where do you want me to lick?
Buttocks.
What? Buttocks?
Do you want me to lick your buttocks?
No, I want you to lick my buttocks.
Which one?
Please lick my buttocks.
It's dirty.
Do you want me to give you more?
Do you understand?
Yes
What are you doing?
I'm going to massage your butt
I'm going to massage your beautiful butt
I'm going to spread it
I can tell by the amount of salt.
Look at me
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm okay.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Do you want to eat this?
This is for you
What does it taste like?
It tastes like...
Please lie down on your knees.
Are you okay?
You look good.
Is it good?
Make a good sound.
I'm going to take a nap.
I'm sorry.
You're so kind.
You're not doing your job.
You should do your job.
how does it feel?
eww
how do you feel?
feel like
eww
how do you feel?
What are you going to do?
No.
You're wet like this.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Spread it out.
Don't look at me when I'm sleeping.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sleepy.
Come on, touch me.
What's wrong?
I'm shaking.
What are you going to do?
I want you to touch me.
Is it good?
It's okay, it's okay
Are you okay?
You're okay.
You're in a good mood.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
You feel good, right?
Are you okay?
It's a mess.
Can I drop it?
Look.
It's a mess.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It feels so good.
ーAre you okay?ー
ーHow are you?ー
ーI'm okayー
ーYou're okay?ー
ーWhy?ー
ーI need to see my family.ー
ーI have to see my parents.ー
ーI have to look after them.ー
ーYou are good at this.ー
ーI'm not a good daughterー
ーAre you okay?ー
I want to go to the bathroom, but I don't want to go to the bathroom, so I'm going to take off my clothes.
Where are you going to take it off?
I'm sick.
Look over here.
Do you like it?
Where are you going to stand?
Let's do the other side, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can relax now.
Good.
I want you to relax
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
What?
What is it?
It's tickling
Look at me
I'm going to sleep
Give me a cup of water
Let's go, let's go
Let's go
Oh, no
Oh, your mouth
Close your eyes.
How do I put this on?
You can just put water on it.
It's cute.
I thought it would look good in yellow.
What? Here?
Please tie it there.
This is a micro bikini.
Have you ever worn something like this?
No, I haven't.
Really?
I don't know how to wear it.
But you wear bikinis and go to the beach, right?
No, no.
But I don't wear such a small bikini.
Really?
It's cool, isn't it?
Is it done?
It's good if it dries out.
Is it good?
It's the same.
Well then,
I'm going to close this.
How does it feel?
What are you going to do?
Do you want to go outside?
No
No?
It's embarrassing
That's right. You'll get caught.
The clothes you were wearing earlier.
Here.
Yes.
Try it on.
It's more comfortable than the first one.
But I think it's gotten a lot better than the first one.
Say it in words.
Yes.
If you want to kiss, kiss.
If you feel good, feel good.
There is still a long way to go.
From now on, this is the key.
Hold this.
There are other men on the top.
This.
Can you hold this?
I understand.
Do something nice with that person next time.
Yes.
Hold this camera.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Excuse me.
This is a thread.
A thread?
Yes, please.
Please.
This way, please.
You're a college student, aren't you?
Yes.
How is school?
It's fun.
Really?
Why did you apply for AV?
I'm interested in it.
And I didn't have much confidence in myself.
Why? You're cute.
I didn't think I'd be confident.
You're popular, aren't you?
No, not at all.
Really?
I see.
I heard that you want to fall in love with sex.
Yes.
I didn't know much about it.
So I want to fall in love with it.
That means you want to be in love with it.
That's right.
Please put your bag here.
I see.
That's right.
Could you please put this away for a moment?
Please take off your shoes.
I want to smell it, but I can't hear it.
You're motivated.
I'm motivated.
What are you doing?
I'm just doing what I feel like doing.
What? You look upset.
You just bit your lips.
What are you trying to do?
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
It's better to be embarrassed.
It's fun to do something embarrassing.
Shall we do it?
I'm going to do something embarrassing for you, so that you won't have any mistakes in your life.
Get on the chair.
I'm going to take a nap.
It was hot today, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It smells good.
What's that?
You like that kind of person?
I'm sorry.
Don't put your hands in a circle.
Sex is not about wanting to be in love.
You don't like it anymore, do you?
It's like you're a dog.
Thank you for your viewing.