The hole in the butt is sticking out to the ceiling, isn't it?
It's a little close, isn't it?
You have a beautiful skin.
I want to touch you.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it.
What should I do? I'm getting goosebumps.
What kind of face are you making?
I'm embarrassed.
Next time, it will be an M-shape.
The M-shape is not beautiful at all.
It's wet.
It's soaked.
It's not in your underwear.
It's in there.
Yes.
Is there a place where it can get in?
What is it?
What do you call it?
Manco.
I wonder if it will be in the movie.
I can see something.
Show me.
Put your hand behind your head and stick out your thumb.
How long has it been since you got out of the hospital?
How long has it been since I got out of the hospital?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Please lick it.
It tastes like Mito-chan.
The taste of mango is different depending on the woman.
The taste of Hito-chan is rich.
Don't move your legs.
Spread your legs more.
Stretch your back.
Do you know that you've come all the way to the entrance?
Tell me that you'll be born when you get out of here.
That's how much fun it is.
I'll be born.
You'll be born.
I'm going to be born.
Not yet.
You're going to be born from a manhole.
I'm going to be born from a mango.
You've done a lot of things you've never done before.
It feels so good.
Come here.
Let's go to bed.
Which one do you prefer?
The round one or the straight one?
Show me your right hand.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I'm going to pat you on the back
Don't hide your face.
Where is your boobs?
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
You're filming it, aren't you?
I want to see how you feel, Mito-chan.
Show it to me.
Roll it up a little.
Push it up a little.
I want to see how you feel.
I feel good.
Take it easy.
You'll be fine.
Don't say anything.
I feel good.
I feel so good.
It's not a big deal.
Don't cry.
What is this?
Give me some candy.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so small?
You're big.
What's the matter?
Will you come in?
What's in there?
What?
Your father's.
Father's?
Ok, your father's in there.
I'm going to the bathroom.
A lot of men are watching this.
It's raining.
I'm giving you a massage now.
What kind of massage?
Big one.
Mito-chan, you are not a college student, you are a senior high school student.
I'm sorry.
Which one do you want to do?
Don't speak with your face
It's okay, just the tongue
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll give you a kiss.
Please eat while looking at the camera.
I'm sorry.
It's not in your mouth.
I'm going to eat a little more.
I'm going to do the most embarrassing thing from now on.
What do you think it is?
What? What are you going to do?
I'll put your blood in your belly.
Please give me your blood.
Where?
It feels good.
Feels good?
I'm not sure what to say, but I'm a little bit sad.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing now?
It hurts.
I feel like I'm in a hospital.
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
I love you.
Where are you?
Tell me
I'm inside
Where are you?
It hurts.
How deep is it?
Just a little more.
It feels good...
How do you feel?
I felt good.
Do you feel different from before?
How do you feel?
It was a strange feeling, but it felt good.
Are you starting to like it?
Yes.
I'll change this.
Do you want to see?
What do you usually do?
I don't do this at all.
What color do you wear?
White.
You don't wear this?
I can't.
I don't like it.
Show me.
I wonder if it was cut properly
In the back
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I'll do more nasty things for you.
I'm going to lie down on the floor and lie down on the floor and lie down on the floor and lie down on the floor.
You know what sound it is, don't you?
The next man will come and feel good alone.
I will be with you.
Let's wait until you feel better alone.
Wait a minute.
You have a good body.
Your skin is clean.
That's right.
But it's okay, isn't it?
You're licking your face.
Don't cry.
You want to cry more, don't you?
What's wrong?
Please look at this
What is this?
It's the same, isn't it?
You want me to wet you?
You have a flat neck
I'm sorry for what I said.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're being sucked in, aren't you?
What?
What are you saying?
My neck is being pulled.
Do you know what this is?
What is this?
I don't know.
Open your eyes.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to give you a hint?
No.
It's the one from the West.
The one where a man does this.
What's this?
I'll give you two hints.
You're moving your hands, aren't you?
It's the same day, isn't it?
Tell me.
Are you small?
What's wrong?
Don't lick it yet.
Is it okay to just lick it?
I want to lick you.
I'll do it.
Leave me alone, please.
Yes, yes.
Do you want to see how big it is?
Open your eyes.
How big is it?
It's big, big, big.
It's the same size as your face.
You can't run away from me, can you?
It's okay.
It's really important.
Relax.
What's wrong with you?
Yes.
Do you want to feel good?
You don't feel good?
No.
Are you interested?
I'm going to attack you.
Sit down.
It's morning.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
?
I want to go.
You want to go?
Open your eyes and see yourself.
Come back tomorrow.
I told you to come back.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Please let me go
Look at me more
What happened?
What happened to your finger?
It's in there
Are you okay?
I'm sorry I shook you.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Show me.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's amazing.
What is this?
Look at this.
Let me see your eyes.
Let me see.
You have a good eye.
The taste has changed.
You are so kind.
I want to kiss you.
You're doing this to your ex-girlfriend?
You've gained some experience.
Does it feel good?
Are you enjoying it?
Yeah.
Come here.
Sit down.
Let's do it one more time.
It's okay.
It's warm.
You want me to put it in?
Are you okay?
Looks like you don't come back...
You can go back to graduate school
for 1 month
and does your homework
luxury drama
for about 3 months
I've been doing that all the time
Can you put your feet in?
I feel like I'm about to cry.
How do you feel?
It hurts.
I want to get out of here.
Oh, it feels good.
I want to sleep from the back.
I'm going to push you out.
I'm sorry.
I found a good one.
Wait a minute.
Have you ever done that before?
No.
I'm sorry.
Close your eyes.
What are you doing?
Look at me.
What are you doing with the first person you met?
I'm doing it with Tetsu.
It's the first time I've ever seen my own face.
What's wrong with you?
Let's get out of here.
Oh, my God.
Look at your face.
It's okay.
Oh, it's good.
Come here.
Please look at me.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Look over there.
What's wrong with you?
Are you okay?
ah
It feels good
Hmm?
What happened?
It's so hot in here.
Kuro inside the house
After the shooting, I came out of the hotel.
I'm a little dizzy.
In the last shooting, I was in a state that I didn't understand well.
This time, I was able to get a lot of food from the actors and actresses, and I was able to have a good time.
I was hungry and wanted to eat something, but I was so hungry that I fell asleep right away when I got home.
I think I got used to this place.
Thank you.
Good night!
Thank you for watching!