Please introduce yourself.
I'm Tomoko Naedan. I'm 25 years old.
I'm Kazuki. I'm 35 years old.
How many years have you been married?
It's been 3 years.
About a year.
About a year ago,
I was doing diving as a hobby.
In Miyakojima?
Yes, in Miyakojima.
We met at Miyakojima.
He used to be my diving buddy.
He was very quiet.
He was quiet and I was a little worried
about what kind of person he was.
He invited me to dinner.
I got used to him and I could talk to him.
I thought he was a beautiful
person from the beginning.
It's embarrassing.
But you pretended not to look at me.
Oh, did I?
Yes, you pretended not to look at me.
Then we got along well.
We started to like each other naturally.
And now we are married.
Why did you want to swap this time?
Why did you apply for this job?
Well, to be honest,
I'm interested in this job.
Did you apply because your wife
was dissatisfied with your husband?
Did you apply because you have
something you want to do? Of course not.
Of course I love diving
and I have no complaints.
I don't have a hobby.
However, I like diving,
skydiving, surfing and
other marine sports.
I also like mountain climbing.
I like adventures.
I like her a lot. Even if she
wears a pink mask, I don't like it.
I'm told that I'm the
opposite of my appearance.
I'm told that I'm more active,
but in fact, she's very active.
I prefer to stay at home.
I'd like to talk about sex.
What kind of sex do you usually have?
I don't know if it's normal.
I don't think it's normal.
I don't know much about people's sex.
I don't know.
What is it? I don't know.
I think it's normal.
It's normal.
How many times a month do you get
married in the third year of marriage?
It was a little less than the first time.
The number of times has
gradually calmed down.
What kind of couple do you want
to have when you do swapping?
Well, the computer chooses, but if there
is hope I feel that the type is different
I see I wonder what
What do you think of me?
I'm like this, so I want you to go out.
Go out?
Do you want to pull me?
Yes.
I don't know.
You look cheerful.
Ichiro, 32 years old.
Misato, 26 years old.
I used to work as an
instructor in a team called 〇〇.
At that time, there was a yoga
instructor, and that's where we met.
How many years have you been married?
How long have you
been doing this? 2 years.
Oh, 2 years.
2 years.
Yes, 2 years.
I'm a bit older now,
so I'm in the business.
Now, I'm doing a salon business.
Is it yoga?
Isn't it yoga?
What do you do? Nail salon.
Oh, you do nail salon?
What are you doing? You suddenly
changed again, didn't you? Yes, I did.
I see.
You look quite clean.
Do you like to take a picture
of your face? Yes, I do.
You are beautiful.
You are a good man, too.
Yes, I am.
It's a shame that I can't talk to you.
I thought you were cute.
Your first impression of me was cute.
I didn't think about marriage at all.
I just wanted to have fun.
I wasn't serious at all.
I had a girlfriend, too.
I'm a straight-A student.
A straight-A
student? No, I'm not.
I'm almost a straight-A student.
I'm a straight-A student.
I'm really tall.
What?
Are you bragging? No, I'm not.
How do you feel? I feel good.
Do you have a lot of sexual desire?
I don't think so.
I think I have a lot of sexual desire.
It's amazing.
What is amazing? Today.
..
What?
I did it earlier today.
Is it amazing?
But isn't it normal?
How many times do you do it?
I do it five times a day.
Do you still do
it? I still do it.
You've known each other
for a long time, haven't you?
Yes, we've known each
other for a long time.
I've heard that you've known each other
for 2 or 3 years before you got married.
Yes, I have.
I feel like I'm stronger than I am now.
Do you?
Yes.
Especially since I decided to do swapping,
I've been getting a lot of requests.
I don't know why, but I've
been getting a lot of requests.
Do you have any wishes?
Do you have any couple
guides or anything like that?
Well, I don't like people who are fat.
I'm not good at it. If I can, I'll do it.
I like clean people,
but I'm not good at it.
You're nervous, aren't you?
This is the best matching
that the computer chose.
The matching rate is 93%.
It's a pretty good one.
It's a pretty good one if it's over 90%.
Now, everyone is wearing a mask,
but at this point, please take off
your mask if it is okay to look at
each other in the first impression.
If not, you can go home on the spot.
Yes, please.
Yes, then, everyone, please say hello.
My name is Ueda.
What's your name?
My name is Maeda.
Nice to meet you, Maeda.
Nice to meet you, too.
What do you think of me?
What do you think
of me? You're cute.
You're cute, aren't
you? I touched you.
Are you sure? I'm Togo.
Nice to meet you.
You're beautiful.
I'm so nervous.
Hi, I'm Kazuki Maezawa.
I'm Kazuki Maezawa.
I'm an employee of this company.
What we have in front of
you is… I think you've noticed,
but we have many items in front of you.
We're going to lend to you for free.
Please take what you like.
Please take a look.
There are various things.
This is a part of me.
There are a lot of things in the warehouse.
Please take home what
you like and play with them.
What do you think? I don't know.
Can I cut this?
What is that?
Oh, it looks like a soap.
Is it a soap?
The contents are...
There are many more wonderful things.
There are so many small things.
Please take a look.
What is this? I like this.
What is this? This is.
..
This is...
It's different.
You know what it is, don't you?
It's all different.
We have good news for you.
Since it's our one-year anniversary,
we have more than 10,000 subscribers.
This time,
we are giving away a
lottery for a hot spring trip.
We also have a lottery
where you can win a
lottery ticket, so if
you like it, please try it.
I'd love to see it.
And, well, is it okay if we
say it's okay for both of us?
Yes.
I like it.
If that's the case, I'd like you to have
sex in front of each other's partners.
Are you ready?
I think it's difficult to swap suddenly.
First of all, let's have sex in front of
each other's partners and get used to it.
After that, let's take various steps.
What do you think?
I'm totally fine.
Are you okay?
Are you looking at me?
Yes.
How close is it?
There is a bed, and a chair
is prepared right next to it.
It's from there.
Do I have to look at it?
I don't know what it is.
But is it okay?
Don't you want to see it?
In the first place,
swapping is meaningless.
I see.
I think it will take some time to get
used to it, so let's move away a little.
Yes, there are people like that.
Then, let's start from a little away.
Is it okay? Yes, it's okay.
Is your wife okay
with that? It's okay.
Is your wife okay with that?
Oh, we can go in as much as we want.
Okay, let's get started.
Do your best.
I'm a man who does it when I do it.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Mi-chan, do your best.
I'm embarrassed.
Why? It's all right.
I'm sorry.
Let's drink tea.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! It's small.
※Because this video is taken
at the hospital, it was very
cold, so there may be a slight
difference in the sound quality.
※ I apologize to all the viewers who have
been waiting for this video to be released.
I'm not a person who cries easily.
I'm not a person who gets emotional easily.
I'm not a person who gets depressed easily.
It feels good.
Wow, it's great.
It really feels good.
I'm sorry.
I'm excited.
I can't.
Can I? Yes, you can.
Ah!! I'm sleepy.
What? You can't sleep?
I can't take it off.
Turn your hips.
Don't laugh, I'm sorry.
Don't cry, I'm so sorry.
Come on, don't cry.
Are you feeling good? Yes, I am.
Oh, it's hot.
Welcome to the 좋아요 &
グッドボタン If you like this video,
please like this video and
subscribe to my channel.
He is breathing heavily.
Are you all right?
You have a lot of blood.
How is it? Can you
go in? It's all right.
Can I look at you from here?
From here?
Yes.
OK, but don't you want to
look at me from close? It's OK.
Everyone is looking at you from close.
Yes.
Well, if you are interested,
please come inside.
OK.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, no.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let's start.
May I? Of course.
May I?
Your husband is a little far away.
Oh, really?
Is he that far?
Is it okay?
Well, he was saying
that from the beginning.
It's really hard.
It's okay.
You don't have to be shy.
It's hot.
Oh, oh, oh.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's amazing.
The cat's voice is amazing.
Oh, is that so? It's amazing.
I was surprised.
It's amazing.
Good evening.
May I come in? It's amazing.
It looks fun.
Please come in.
It's okay.
Let's go in together.
Please come in.
Your husband is here.
Which one do you like
better, this one or this one?
I like this one.
Which one?
This is the first time I've ever seen
a baby drinking milk from a bottle.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
It's smaller than you.
I'm sorry.
You are a dinosaur.
It's okay.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while,
hasn't it? It's heavy.
Can you let me
touch it? Oh, I see.
Wow, you are wearing a very cute pants.
Do you like it? Yes, I do.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
The baby is crying.
I'm sorry.
You are so mean.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with
you? Hit my butt.
What? Hit my butt.
Your butt?
Yes.
More.
I love you.
I love you, too.
You are here.
It's good. It feels so good.
I'm so happy.
And you are so good at it.
You are so messy.
Turn your back to me.
Look at the face of Tama-san.
Hey, what are you
doing? I'm so excited.
You are excited, aren't you?
Yes.
Oh, it's hard.
Can I throw it away?
I'll throw it away.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
I'm so happy.
Hey, you.
It's fun.
Let's have fun until you get sad.
You have a strong body.
I understand.
I'm scared.
This is my house.
You are strong.
You are small.
You are great.
More, more.
More?
Really?
Do you want to
drink? That's good.
You're getting bigger.
I'm so happy.
If you're happy, that's good.
You must be tired.
It was fun, but I'm tired.
How do you feel?
Do you want to
try it? It felt good.
We did it.
Yes, we did.
Yes.
Then, the next step is to take this camera.
Oh, yes.
Take this camera, go on a
date, and do a lot of things.
Yes.
Please record it.
Record it?
Yes.
We will record it and release it as a DVD.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
How was your day today?
I'm glad I did it.
You had a lot of fun, didn't you?
How about you?
I wish she was really happy.
But it's hard.
I'm going to take this camera
and ask you to take a picture of me.
I'm going to put the picture on the
DVD and exchange it with the couple.
Sorry, I made you wait.
It's been a while.
How are you? I'm fine.
I haven't been to
the beach recently.
How have you been?
I haven't been to the beach recently.
You haven't been to the beach recently.
Then, your body has become numb.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
I want to move my body.
Do you have anything you
want to do? I don't know.
I have no idea.
I'm so excited.
Then, let's move your body.
Let's play baseball.
How about baseball?
Baseball?
Have you ever played baseball?
I'm not good at it.
Really?
But you just have to move your body.
You can change your mood.
You can hit the ball.
You can shake the ball.
I can relieve my stress.
You can relieve your stress.
Are you going to play baseball?
Are your nails okay?
I think your nails are okay.
It's amazing.
I want to have sex.
Don't you have sex? Yes, I do.
You do, don't you?
I have a lot of sex.
It's amazing since then.
I know half of it.
It's 80km.
What? It's 80km.
It's fast.
Is it the slowest?
Well, let's see.
Oh, where is it? It says 70 kilograms.
Oh, what should I do?
It says 70 kilograms and 10 kilograms.
Well, let's do the slowest one.
The slowest one?
The slowest one.
Wait a minute.
Let's go in together.
Be careful.
Go inside.
What should I do with your bag?
Should I carry it?
What should I
do? It's dangerous.
No, no, no.
Carry it, carry it.
Thank you.
Like this? Yes, yes.
Put it in.
Have you ever shaken it?
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit? When you were a kid?
Yes.
Then this is the lightest.
This? This is light.
Is this heavy?
How is it?
Yes.
It doesn't go up at all.
It doesn't go up at all?
The ball comes from there.
I'm going to throw it.
Don't swing it.
I'm scared.
I'll put money in it.
Wait a minute.
Be careful.
Are you scared?
I'm afraid that the ball will hit me.
The ball will hit you.
How many times? About 20 times.
I can't swing it that much.
You don't have to hit it.
Let's go.
Get ready.
Be careful.
Don't worry. It won't come from there.
Let's go.
It's coming.
I'm coming!
Wait a minute!
I hit it!
I'm scared!
It's fast!
It's fast?
I'm scared!
It's a nice fight.
I'm not good at it.
What should I do?
Are you sleeping? Let's hit 9.
Let's guess what it is.
If you get it right,
I'll give you a reward.
I'll give you a real bat.
A golden bat.
Wow!
You got a good one.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's the first time.
It's still cold.
Isn't it enough?
What's this?
There's something inside.
It's an LCD.
It's amazing.
What's this?
I wonder what it is.
Shall we do it?
Shall we?
What's this?
What does it say? Gold? Gold.
Gold.
I can't do it at all.
What should I do?
Should I lift it up?
Oh, I couldn't do it at all.
It's cute.
It's just the right size.
Right? Oh, no.
There is only one table.
No way.
I messed it up.
It's OK.
Here?
Yes.
Like this.
A hint?
You are good at it.
Do you want to
try it? No, I'm good.
It's so fine.
It's good.
It's not crispy.
It's sticky.
It's thick.
No, it's good.
You can eat it.
He ate it.
Let's go in.
Let's go this way.
Let's go.
It looks fancy.
It looks expensive.
Not at all.
Isn't it expensive? No, it's OK.
Is it OK? It's OK.
I have a lot of money.
I have a lot of money, so it's OK.
Then, I'll treat you.
Say anything you want.
Take a break?
Break?
In a white place.
What floor?
302.
I didn't press it.
Why? Oh, no.
This is not a maid.
Did you play such
a game? No, I didn't.
I'm worn out.
Here it is.
Let's get in.
Can I go in? Yes, you can.
The moment you press the
button, the door will open.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's OK.
Get in.
It's a good room.
How do you feel?
Can I look around first?
Lady first? Lady first.
The room is big.
It's good.
I found something strange.
What is it? It's hot.
Are you OK? Cool me down.
Cool you down?
I'll cool you down.
Really? Then get hot.
I'm happy even in my mouth.
I can't do it.
Unlike my husband, I can't do it.
That's a secret.
Really.
My husband does it normally.
Normally?
Do you like it?
Yes.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm going to wash my face with the sponge.
My face will be washed with
the condition that it is warm.
I'm wearing a very sullen outfit.
I want you to show me a little more.
I'll put it in for you.
Raise your legs.
It hurts.
It's coming.
It's over.
What's wrong? It's over.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for my baby.
I'm so hungry.
I feel so good.
It's too hot.
I don't want to be in such a box.
You are in a box.
You are very much in a box.
No, I don't want to die.
You are in a box.
Do you understand? Listen to me.
I don't want to die.
She is crying.
Please rub your belly.
Rub your belly.
I like that.
I'm watching you.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I feel sick.
I'm so sorry.
Please close the door.
I think I'm going to forget everything.
I can't stop crying.
Ouch! I'm so scared.
There is a statue of Godzilla
on the top of the building.
Is it a statue of
Godzilla? Yes, it is.
It is a famous statue of
Godzilla on the top of the building.
Godzilla is on the top of the mountain.
Are you scared? I'm scared.
You are doing various things.
Is this your 50th first kiss?
Let's kiss 50 times here.
No.
Let's watch a movie.
Oh, we're going to see a movie.
We're going to see a movie.
That's right.
Let's go.
Here it is.
Buy a ticket here.
Ticket
This Here you are.
It looks delicious.
What do you usually play with?
What do I usually
play with? I can't drink.
I can't drink, but I like to drink.
Do you like the atmosphere?
Yes.
Are you alone?
No, I'm with a friend.
Are you his friend?
Is he a man? He is a man.
I see.
Do you have a lot of friends?
Yes.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
The movie was interesting,
wasn't it? Yes, it was.
How was it?
It was cute, wasn't it?
By the way, I'm a surfer.
Is that so?
I like you, too.
Really?
Yes.
Actually, I haven't told anyone about this,
but there was no one in the sea at dusk.
So I went to the beach
for about 30 minutes
with my boyfriend I
was dating at that time.
Not your current husband?
No.
I was bleeding.
Ah!
Do you still have it?
I did it in a cable car.
What?
In a cable car?
Yes.
How was it?
Well, when no one was holding it,
I don't know if there
was a security camera.
There must be a camera.
I wonder if there is.
I think so.
I did it in that.
You did it? Until the end?
Yes.
Were you naked?
No, I wasn't naked.
You were naked.
Yes, I was naked there, too.
Because I was shaking.
You were shaking a lot.
I'm not that kind of
person, but when I talked
to him, I felt like I
was getting dizzy.
I'm not that kind of person.
Where should we go?
Let's go over there.
Let's go.
I'm going to the hotel.
Can I eat here? Oh, I can't.
It's 3,000 yen.
I'm at the hotel.
Love ho!
Love ho! 5,4,3,2,1.
5,4,3,2,1.
Here you go.
Oh, it's the 7th floor.
This hotel uses an automatic system.
Please put your members, cards,
and your belongings in the card slot.
When you leave, please press the doorbell
at the front door and pay your fee.
Please put your hands on your waist.
You are so sexy.
Let's breathe.
【The sound of a baby eating.
】 Wow!
You always attack me like this.
Do you want me to do it?
Wow!
Great!
Great! It's too bad.
It's too bad.
It's on the side and the back.
I have to go to the bathroom.
The water is boiling.
I'm gonna fall.
No!
I'm going to fall.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
She is a cat that is very sensitive
to the sound of a vacuum cleaner.
I'm sorry for the noise.
Oh my god!
Oh my god! It is made of silk.
Look!
※This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
Hurry up,Ten.
I feel good.
now I feel good
Oh, it feels good.
You don't have to put up with it.
You don't have to be stupid.
You are so distracted.
Show me your true self.
I'm sorry.
You're lying.
You're selfish.
You're amazing.
It's disgusting.
「」「」 I'll give you a massage.
I'll give you a massage.
It feels good.
You can spit it out.
A lot.
We are going to
have a party! I drank it.
I drank it.
Yeah!
We are going to have a party!
Cheers! I'm so happy.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
How do you like it?
It's like a hot spring.
It's good.
We went to hot springs three times.
Yes, we did.
It's delicious.
We did good things.
What did you eat?
Abalone and sea urchin.
I want to eat abalone.
I'm sorry.
We are going to do swapping.
Today, we're going to play a game.
Are you ready? Yes, I am.
I brought this from the countryside.
From the countryside?
Oh, this is the one you can
see in Love4, right? Yes, it is.
You can use it as much as you want.
You don't have to be shy.
There's no time limit.
You can use it as much as you want.
I'm so excited.
Oh, my gosh.
I think it's too big for me.
Are you OK? It's big.
Let's compare the face.
It's shuffle time.
We have to shuffle.
Maru-san looks so energetic.
Did it pop?
What's going on? Look, look.
I'm having fun.
Which one?
What was that?
You're too drunk.
Let's start.
Go ahead, everyone.
Here you are.
It's easy to eat,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
It's easy to eat.
Look at this.
It's wonderful,
isn't it? Look at this.
It's wonderful.
Look at this.
It's amazing.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
I can't stop laughing.
Let's start the
video! You are so big.
I envy you.
What?
You are so cute.
You are so shy.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Do you feel good?
You are a brave girl.
Look at this.
This is her pillow.
I'm going to tell you that
you can sleep next to me.
Do you feel good? Look at me.
The baby is crying.
This is a video of a baby
who was born in the morning.
The baby's mother, who is a
mother of three, is the first child.
The baby's mother, who is the
second child, is the first child.
The baby's mother, who is
the third child, is the first child.
What?
How can you say such
a thing? Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, no, no, no.
What's the matter?
You're crying again, aren't you?
A little? No, no, no.
Look.
A little.
In the past, Kuronoko used to tell
us that she loves us so much, and she
loves us so much, that she and
Kuronoko want to give everything to her.
So no matter what, I
want to be with Kuronoko.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Which one is the fraud?
Which one is the
fraud? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
The day when I first saw
the baby, I thought it was
a baby who was in the
hospital, but I was wrong.
The baby was crying, but I was worried
that the baby was in a bad condition.
I was worried that he was sick,
but I was relieved that he was fine.
You were very gentle.
You are getting sensitive.
Let's see how wet you are.
How wet are you? You are wet.
You are wet, aren't you? Great.
You are so wet.
I've never been so wet.
What's wrong?
Did you spill it?
Huh?
Is it our baby?
We haven't opened it yet.
The sound is coming out.
Right?
Oh, it's amazing.
The sound is loud.
It's amazing.
It's the same as before.
That's right.
Do you want to play it?
Where is the red one?
The one you were eating.
Do you want to go to the lower house?
You want to go to the
lower house? Let's go.
Do you want to go to the abbey?
Do you want to go?
I'm going to put a cream on his head.
Look at him.
I put a cream on his head.
Can I put it on your head?
I'm going to put it on your head.
Do you feel good?
Do you want me to give you a massage?
I'll give you a massage.
Look!
Oh!
I was surprised!
You are not there!
It's already like this.
Then, look! I will.
..
I will leave this a little.
Wow! You look happy.
Yes, it is.
You are smiling.
Aiko, you look like a cherry blossom.
Your face is bigger.
I can't move.
Your wife is very fat.
How do you feel?
My voice is gone.
It's about time.
I see.
What do you mean?
Actually, we are not in that
kind of relationship anymore.
We are not dating anymore.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Are you two a
couple? Yes, we are.
If so, we are.
..
May I? Yes, please.
You are too impatient.
No!
Look at my nipples.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
It's hard for me to watch.
I'm sorry.
What's this?
I thought it was my wife's hand.
It's my hand.
You grabbed your husband's hand.
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
You are getting heavier.
You can't take it out, can you?
The baby is crying.
I was injured and my finger was cut.
I took medicine, but
I couldn't stop crying.
I got a lot of workout,
so I couldn't stop crying.
Let's taste it.
One by one.
You can do it because you are alive.
Is it okay?
I'm sorry.
Can I take this out?
I'll take it out.
Ouch!
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't stand it either.
Lie down.
We look forward to your
comments in the summary section!
We look forward to your comments
in the summary section! It's cold.
It's cold. It's cold.
Thank you.