Steaming
It's this good
Is your Inner Box mostly used?
I'm going to pour the sauce on top of the rice
This is a souvenir
Oh, a souvenir?
That's good
I didn't think it would taste good
It's really good
I have a good sake
Do you want to drink?
I want to drink
I'm going to taste it now
It's not hot at all
It looks delicious
It's easy to melt
What is this?
I think it's already melted.
What?
It's already melted.
That's right.
Do you guys usually do this?
You're a pervert.
I'm sorry.
Don't do sex with me.
You're the only one doing it, aren't you?
I don't like it.
Don't do sex with me.
I love you, I love you.
No, no.
It feels good.
I don't know what to do.
I see.
By the way,
did you say you wanted to ask me something?
Yeah.
What is it?
If it's something other than money,
I'll ask you anything.
Kuroko, I have something I want to try.
What?
What do you want to try?
I'm sorry for making you eat so much food.
It's okay.
You can eat as much as you want.
So, how are you doing recently?
What?
Aren't you going to make a child?
Well, I've been thinking about it a lot, but I don't know if I can do it.
I can't make a child because my parents are strict.
That's right.
My parents say, make it, make it, but it's noisy.
By the way, where are Yasu-kun and the others?
Huh?
Sutan went to the bathroom.
Both of you?
Yeah.
The bathroom?
Is she a girl?
Hahaha.
I wonder why.
Right?
I wonder why she's doing that.
Hahaha.
I wonder if it's okay if we only talk to each other.
I don't like it.
Hahaha.
Hey.
Let's not talk about it.
I mean,
you're not serious, are you?
Hey.
What are you talking about?
No, I don't think so.
You were staring at Yuu, weren't you?
You're so mean.
No, no, no.
I can hear you.
You can hear me, right?
While you're here,
Please stop it.
I don't have anything to do with you anyway.
You're tired of me, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
Your wife and my wife.
Which one is better?
Let's exchange.
No, I don't think so.
I can't do it anymore.
At that time, I couldn't resist the words of my childhood friend, SHINODA.
I don't want to see his wife, Yuu-chan, and me, but I want to see it.
I want to see it.
In this way, the childhood dream and the childhood dream
are going to stay in my house for 4 days.
It's a little embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
You're taking a break?
How are you?
It's so painful.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
She's just a child.
No...
I'm sorry...
YASUKE, no...
No...
I'm sorry...
Let's do it again.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
It's been a while since I've done it, so I'd like to exchange it for a while.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to say it now.
Hey.
What do you mean by exchange?
It's obvious.
It's him, right?
He's a real man.
I'm an adult.
Yasu-kun...
So...
I'll do what Sumire-chan does...
So you're going to do it with Shinji?
Sounds fun, right?
You're in trouble.
No, it's fun.
I'm sorry.
I was surprised.
You don't have to say it now.
I don't know.
I was surprised.
Mom.
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Well...
Well, it's okay.
We talked about this before.
Yeah.
What?
Really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey,
I want to talk to you alone.
What?
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
Let's go.
I wonder if he's okay.
Didn't he catch a cold?
Sumire-chan.
I don't think he's okay.
Yeah, I think so.
I was going to tell you something.
What?
Well, that's what happened.
What do you mean?
No, I'm not talking about that.
You told me about our vanilla ice cream before, didn't you?
I may have told you, but that and this...
So I was wondering if it would be better to do something like that.
But...
If that's the case, I'll have to do it with Yasu-kun, so is that okay?
It's not good, but it's not something you don't know.
That will make our friendship even better. I think that's better.
Just once.
Just once is enough.
I'm begging you.
Just like this.
Sumire, I'm begging you.
Let's do it.
Okay, let's do it.
We've been talking.
Who's going to do it?
What should I do?
I'm dying more than I am.
You're dying more than you are.
What should I do?
Close your eyes.
Good.
Now close your eyes.
Ok.
Let's start from Shinji.
You're okay, aren't you?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I've never done this before.
But everyone does it, right?
One day.
It's cold.
I can't take it off.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
You don't kiss often, do you?
Kiss?
Are you cold?
Are you okay?
It's embarrassing.
What are you talking about?
How long are you going to keep it in your hand?
Or do you want to hug each other?
Or do you want to kiss each other?
Kiss me.
Really?
Like this?
It's not bad, isn't it?
Is it okay?
Only us?
Not only us.
We'll do it later.
I see.
Yes, that's right.
Do you want to kiss me?
Yes, I do.
Do you want to?
That's right.
Do you want me to kiss you?
I'm so embarrassed.
Are you going home?
Yes.
Don't be shy.
I'm embarrassed.
People are staring at me.
Don't worry about me.
I'm worried about you.
Let's take a picture.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't look at me like that when you look at me like this.
It's like a curtain.
What's wrong?
Can I sit down?
It's hard to do, isn't it?
No.
Like this?
Yes.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
What should I do?
Feels good.
Yeah.
You know...
Hey,
you should lick the chair too.
Don't lick it too much.
This way?
It's your favorite place.
Can I take it off?
Wow!
It's okay.
It's really standing.
Wow, you look strong.
Can I really lick you?
You really want to lick me, don't you?
Wow, look.
It's like this.
It's strong.
It's harder than mine.
You're lying.
I thought you weren't going to eat it.
It's delicious.
It's a fresh taste.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
I want to see your face.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I feel like I'm doing something bad.
It's not bad at all.
Really?
Really.
It's the first time you're licking me in front of people like this.
Look.
You're curious about our politics, aren't you?
It's really intense.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about me.
It's embarrassing to do it.
What about me?
It's okay.
You're already wet.
I'm not.
It's okay.
I want you to be embarrassed.
I'm not embarrassed.
I'll close the door.
No.
Can I have a look?
Don't spread it out. It's embarrassing.
I want to take a look.
Oh no.
It's in the bubble.
It's not coming?
It's a little embarrassing.
It's jealous.
It's soaked in blood.
I don't like this. It's embarrassing.
Don't touch it like that.
I can't do it anymore.
It's embarrassing.
It's close.
What are you doing?
You don't have to lick it.
You don't like it?
You lick it.
It's embarrassing.
Don't look at me like that.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Shien-chan, come here.
Come here.
What?
Put it in.
I want to put it in.
What do you mean?
I like it when you hit me from the back.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
Really?
Wait a minute.
Sorry.
Here you go.
What are you doing?
Don't you put on the rubber?
It feels good.
It looks easy, but...
I'm doing it live.
Are you sure?
I'm fine with it.
Then I'm fine with it.
I'm fine with it if you're fine with it.
You want to do it in person, don't you?
Are you sure?
Yes.
I want to do it in person.
I'll do it.
Are you sure?
Oh, it's cold.
It's hard.
Shin-chan's...
It's amazing.
Oh, it's gross.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
Amazing.
You're amazing.
It feels bad.
It's bad.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm dying.
This is amazing.
This feels so good.
Let's go.
It's so hard.
I'm dying.
Why is it so hard?
I'm sorry.
Please do it again.
Is it okay to do this?
Is it okay, Sumie?
Don't worry about it.
It's really big.
Amazing.
I want to do more.
Can I get on it?
Yes.
I feel like I'm doing something bad.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm going to sleep.
What should I do?
I can't see my body.
I'm so nervous.
I'm scared.
What should I do? I have coke in my mouth.
You can see it well.
Is it okay to do this?
I don't know what to do.
I'm in trouble.
Should I give up?
I told you.
I'm not good at it.
I'll do a little more.
No, no.
Just a little more.
What?
How is it?
It's dirty.
Is it okay to do this?
It's all wet.
I'll wipe it a little more.
Is it okay?
It's not messy.
Shin-chan, you're amazing.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I feel good.
Shhh.
Here.
Sen-chan.
Don't be shy.
It's better to lie down.
Like this.
Like this?
Yes.
I can see Sen-chan's face well.
It's scary.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
If you're about to die,
I'll get you out of there.
What?
I want to see you get out of there.
What are you talking about?
That's not good.
I don't care.
I'll get you out of there.
Isn't it dangerous if I release it inside?
I feel like I'm going to die.
I'm in trouble.
I'm going to die.
Ah!!
Shin-chan!!
Shuu!
He's moving!!
Oh!
He's getting out!!
What should I do?
Ouch!!
Shin-chan!!
What should I do!?
Are you okay?
What should I do?
It was good, wasn't it?
It was good, but
I wonder if it's okay.
It was really good.
What should I do?
It can't be helped.
Let's all have fun together, okay?
I'm not bad at anything.
Shin-chan is good too, but if you give it a try,
you'll get used to it.
Okay?
I don't care about Shinta, but I want to try it once.
You're fast.
No, it doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Right?
I'm sorry.
I knew it.
Just in time, the
I'm sorry.
It's not good for the couple to get wet.
We decided to stay here today.
It's ok.
You should take a shower.
Since we're here, let's do it together.
Okay.
Bye.
Did you feel good?
I'm listening to you.
I was nervous.
I was nervous, but it felt good.
Really?
I forgot.
Hehehe
It's warm.
This is how I embraced my childhood friend's dream.
I couldn't tell my wife that I was so excited that I was embarrassed.
And after that, a surprising sight was waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
It's amazing.
Don't look at me.
My dream came true when I got out of the bath.
Moreover,
while I was being filmed,
I was drooling with an expression that I had never seen before.
Jealousy?
Excitement?
On that day, I was so excited that I woke up in the morning.
In the end, I couldn't sleep at all.
I was busy with Shinoda's dream.
Of course, Sumire also went to Shinodani.
You're good at cooking.
The more we were in a rush to get dressed,
the more naturally we headed for the morning.
I'm looking forward to it.
Do I?
Do I look like that?
No, you don't look like that.
Oh, right.
Mr. Kurokawa.
Do you want to see what we took yesterday?
It's okay.
You took a good picture.
Let's see it.
It's embarrassing.
Let's see it here.
Let's see it together.
I'm ready.
It's hard to sit down.
It's hot.
Amazing.
It's fun.
It's amazing.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
I'm tired.
You feel good?
Yes.
Are you happy?
Did you feel good?
What?
Yes
That's good
I'll show you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're strange.
Do you want to drop it?
I don't want to drop it.
I want to get used to it.
Put it here.
Put it in.
It feels good.
I want to lie down and stretch.
I'm so sorry.
You're sleeping a lot.
You can sleep like this when you're sleeping.
Did you sleep?
I slept.
I'm afraid you will get up.
Who?
It's embarrassing to do this.
I'm afraid you will get up.
But I can't do anything about it.
I'm so tired.
I want to go home.
I want to go to the hospital.
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat like this in my life.
I've never seen a cat like this in my life.
I have to put up with it
I'm so hungry
Well, I'll choose this one first.
No, I can't.
I have 13.
What? You have more?
Yes, I have more.
You have more?
I have more.
I haven't seen it.
Hey, I have more.
You have more.
I have more.
Oh, 9 again.
Oh, it's close.
7? I've never seen 7.
9.
You just said 9.
I saw something around here.
It's totally different.
Where are you going?
Amazing!
You're a genius.
I haven't taken a single picture yet.
I've seen it before.
No, I haven't taken a single picture yet.
Really?
Oh, it's amazing.
Amazing, amazing.
A gun?
I have one.
You have a good memory.
Amazing.
I have one.
What about this one?
I haven't found anything in this area.
Huh?
I haven't found anything yet.
Wait, I don't know what it is.
I saw it around here.
It looks like me, though.
I came up with an interesting game.
What is it?
Can I try it?
Can I?
What is it?
I'm getting tired of this game.
I think so, too.
It's like a game where two people are blindfolded and one of them gets the right answer.
What is it?
It's a little funny, isn't it?
It's easy, isn't it?
It's easy.
It's 1 in 2.
It's obvious.
Don't you have anything to write?
I have.
Let me see.
It's easy.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Why are you so confident?
What's that?
You can use it when you go to bed.
Is it a plane?
You can use it.
This is the one that can be given to you.
Let's do it one by one.
One by one?
It's a referee.
I can't see it at all.
Are you going to start already?
Let's start.
Let's get started.
I'm so motivated.
Let's do it quickly.
Come a little closer.
Wait, wait.
Isn't it too early to make eye contact?
Where?
Can't you see?
I can't see.
It's okay.
Hurry up.
I'm thinking.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
If you lose, do you have a punishment game?
You look like you have a bad feeling about this.
Someone's already here, right?
Oh, I'm sorry. I screamed.
I was a little scared.
Wait, is it good?
It's warm. Here we go.
Oh, It's so good.
Okay, next
I'm going to take a bite of this.
I got it.
Really?
I just have to hit it gradually.
At first.
Can I take this off?
Is it right?
I did it!
I knew it!
It's the correct answer with the first try!
I can't see anything.
I see.
Please.
I was surprised.
I was really surprised.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
Wow
What?
Is it good?
I was surprised again.
Oh, I see.
What? You don't get it?
What? Is it the beginning?
No.
You got it right!
Really?
No way!
You're a good girl.
You know what you're doing.
You're my husband.
I'm going to take it off.
What?
No, no, no.
I was surprised.
I took it off.
What?
I don't know if it was a coincidence.
I'll do it again.
It's still a little bit...
It's okay.
Leave it to me.
Actually, men are full-time.
Stick together a little more.
About this.
Like this?
Yes, there are men.
Are you ready?
My heart is pounding.
It's a heart.
Hmm?
I know
I don't know
It's hard, isn't it?
Hmm?
It's 그때
It's hot.
It's totally different
Mmm!
Mmm?
It's getting harder.
I don't know.
It's harder than the last one.
Yeah.
There is a pattern that has not been replaced, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know.
I can't see it.
Hm?
What?
Oh, it's not there.
I don't know what it is.
Impossible.
What?
Are you looking at Japan?
Yes.
That's great.
I'll give you a hint.
I haven't answered yet.
What?
You're so cute.
Where are you going?
What?
What are you doing?
Is there something on your forehead?
It's so sweet.
It's delicious.
delivery
Your mouth is very sharp.
Say something.
It's hot.
Are you sweating?
Who's talking right now?
You know what I'm talking about, don't you?
Of course I do.
Oh, I knew it.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's easy.
What?
I said, what?
You made a mistake.
I think I made a mistake.
Really?
It's so good.
It's different from usual.
It's amazing.
Really?
It's good.
It's really good.
It's amazing.
Really?
You taught me.
Let's change it a little bit.
What?
Mitsubi is doing it.
Why do you talk like that?
You don't use the technique I don't do.
I'm using it.
Is it different?
Yes.
Yes, it's different.
Is it the same taste as before?
Yes.
It's the same taste as before.
You really didn't make a mistake, did you?
It's delicious.
Is it?
I think it's really delicious.
I got used to eating this.
Not at all.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
Oh, my!
No, it's coming out.
Why don't you want to do it?
I've done it many times.
You've done it many times.
I'm sorry.
Is it good?
Did you spit it out?
It's so good
I'm going to eat a lot today.
It's spicy.
You're spitting out a lot.
Can I spit it out?
Wow!
It's amazing!
It's so clear!
Wow!
It's thick!
It seems to be thin.
I didn't say that.
It's really thick!
Why did you hold it in your hand?
It's important.
What were you going to do?
I'm sorry.
I hate you two.
That was great.
That was fun.
It was fun.
This is nice.
So, what do you think?
What do you mean?
In the end...
My dream and yours...
Which one do you want?
I don't know even if you say that.
Which one?
Are you going home tomorrow?
Oh, I see.
What should I do?
You don't hate my voice anymore, do you?
Thank you so much for smile.
Are you ready?
You are?
Yes!
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you ready to go home?
Yes!
Today is our last day of school.
Yeah.
It was fun.
There's still time until the plane, right?
Yeah.
There is.
Hey,
since we're here,
Let's do it together.
Together.
You are getting taller.
It's okay.
You're sleeping.
I'm happy.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Oh, it's hot.
It's hot.
I don't want to do it anymore.
It's not over yet?
It's not over yet. It's not over yet.
Are you okay?
What is it?
Amazing.
Are you going to take a shower again?
Just a little.
Just a little?
What?
What are you doing?
I want to kiss you.
Kiss?
It's embarrassing.
What?
It's hot.
You're standing on your own.
I'm sleepy.
No, I can't.
It's too early. You're already trying to lick it.
Just line up your butt.
Is it good?
Close your eyes.
What is it?
I'm enjoying my kiss.
Ah!
I can't see.
I'm pulling out my nails.
I want it.
Eat it.
Do you like it?
No
Both of you are doing great
Because
Do you feel good?
Yes
Serina is relaxed
He is very serious.
He is pulling the string.
What are you doing?
He is licking.
Do you want to wet yourself?
I can see that they are licking each other a lot.
Let me see.
Let me touch you a little bit more.
Really?
Wow, you're touching me.
You're trying to do something great.
What?
What? I can't see you.
I can't see you.
I want to eat it.
What are you doing?
It's delicious.
I want to eat it.
Cool, cool.
It's amazing.
Sumire, you should learn this technique.
I'm not doing anything.
I'm sorry.
Cheers.
Your hands stink.
Really?
What are you doing?
You always do this.
What is it?
I don't know.
His voice was pleasant.
Yes.
That's what I thought.
Why do you always move like this?
Are you licking me?
You are moving a lot.
Look at her.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
I told you to lick it.
Let's learn, let's learn.
There's no such thing.
You're the best.
Wow!
I can remember it right away.
Don't you want to compare the two?
What?
It's embarrassing.
Let's go to the bed.
Over there?
It's a round table.
Turn your back to me.
In such a bright place.
Open it yourself.
It's a plate.
It's not embarrassing to sleep on the stone.
Like this?
I can't lose to you.
It's difficult.
Can you do both hands?
Both hands?
I'm embarrassed.
It's a shame.
It's great.
Can't you cancel the flight?
What are you talking about?
What?
You thought it was good, didn't you?
No, it's true.
Forgive me.
It's very beautiful.
It's very wet.
It's wet, isn't it?
It's embarrassing.
Why is it so wet?
No, don't do it.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no.
Are you breathing?
Why?
No.
Stop it.
1,2,3
It's embarrassing
It's a little hard to tell
This
Huh?
Is it this?
The one on the top
Do you like it?
Is it this?
Yeah
I'm embarrassed
What do you want to do?
It's embarrassing.
It's a wet tissue.
What do you want to do?
What are you doing?
I can't go.
What is he doing?
Did he go inside?
I'm sorry.
I was looking forward to it.
Look at this.
Amazing.
Is this your body?
I'm sorry.
It's a little weird.
It's amazing.
It's licking here.
It feels good.
Wow.
Shacho.
What are you enjoying?
What?
Nothing.
I see.
I'll pet you.
You can't take it out.
What should I do?
I'm going to use this.
What is it?
It looks lonely.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
I'm so tired.
I feel so good.
I can't believe it.
It feels so good.
It's so hard.
Wait.
I'm scared.
I'm going.
You're sweating.
Amazing.
You are really doing it.
Do you like it?
I like black
I was surprised.
It's amazing.
I don't know if I can do it.
Let's try again.
I feel so good.
Amazing.
I am about to cry.
I am scared.
It's cold.
Go.
I am scared.
I'm going to put it on me.
I'm going to put it on you.
Wow, that's amazing.
You were shaking your hips a lot.
I was shaking like that?
Don't you feel like a wife?
Oh, no.
Oh, that's not it.
That's not it.
It feels so good.
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
It's all over the place.
You're so kind.
Study hard.
It's cold.
Almiya Etci.
Oh, it feels good.
Her hip is moving.
Can you do this?
I can't.
Really?
Oh, great.
Her hip is moving.
Watch carefully.
Oh, my!
Please, help me!
Show me.
I want to touch your butt.
It feels good.
Can you touch it?
I can't touch it.
Amazing.
It tickles!
How is it?
Can I touch it?
No, you can't.
Does it tickle?
Amazing!
There are a lot of itchiness.
Here?
Wow, it's so messy.
It feels so good.
I feel like I'm going to fall into a pool.
I'm tired.
Let's go.
Next to me.
Next to me?
Yes.
Are you ready?
Come on.
I'm tired.
I'm here!!
I'm going to have to go to the bathroom.
Me too.
I'm so nervous.
Are you okay?
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I can do it.
Oh, I'm nervous.
Oh, did you go in?
Are you okay?
How many times did you go out?
I'm getting goosebumps.
I'm so happy.
Are you in pain?
Oh, no.
It's because you're in pain.
Well, that's true.
I'm getting a lot of pain.
I'm so happy.
I feel so good
I'm going to go
Give me a good one!
Ouch!
Wow!
Did you get hurt?
I'm so tired.
I'm so tired today.
Did you take it out?
Did you really take it out?
This is bad.
Well, it's okay.
It's not good.
I feel good.
Is the time okay?
The time is okay.
Can you do it again?
It's amazing.
It's amazing. I can still do it.
Even though I just did it.
No, no.
It feels good.
Wait.
It's okay, it's okay.
One more time.
Amazing.
Ah!
What happened to everyone?
I'm so tired.
What's wrong?
I can't do it. It feels so good.
Aaaaaah!
It's too painful!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Ah, ah, ah!
I'm going!
Uh, uh, ah!
Ah, ah, ah!
Ah!
Ah, it's painful!
Ah, ah!
Ah, ah, ah!
I'm so tired.
Look at me.
Please help me.
You are too small.
I'm not.
Look.
It's amazing.
It's a little bit.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm getting semen.
It feels good.
It's really hard.
Oh, no.
I'm going to die.
Are you OK?
I'm so tired.
No way.
Are you okay?
Ah, it's so cold.
Did you put it out?
Did you put it out for Riri-chan too?
I put it out.
You put it out for a crazy person's wife?
It's so messy.
I was so scared.
Is it okay?
I feel like I did something wrong.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
It's gross.
Stop it.
Ouch!
I can't do it anymore.
This is too much.
This is Sen-chan's.
I'm sorry.
Oh my god.
It's amazing.
It's coming out.
Both of you are amazing.
It's the second time.
Amazing.
Wow, it's so strong.
It's still warm.
It's amazing.
I don't have much time left.
I'm glad I was able to do it before I left.
I have to go to the airport.
I'm going to go home now.
You should rest a little.
I have to hurry.
It's good.
Yes, it's good.