It's been two years since I got married.
My husband, Yosuke, had
left the company a year ago.
Then he started an investment
business in oil and gas development.
He kept trying to get close to the company.
However, he found out that the
investment company was working on fraud.
The company disappeared before he knew it.
The manager also disappeared.
Yosuke, who had been pulling
investment funds from many customers,
has left tens of millions of yen in debt.
Even if I wanted to break up with him,
if he did such a thing,
I would have a bad reputation.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
What is it?
Yosuke...
You've changed, haven't you?
Most of the investment
funds Yosuke collected
came from a man named Nakae,
who runs a venture company.
It was a gift from God.
I'll pay you back someday.
You think you can pay me back?
How?
I'll think about it.
It's impossible.
I had more than 50 million yen.
I was stupid.
I was stupid, too.
Why didn't I notice this Ponzi scheme?
I'll make it easy for you this
time, including your repentance.
Of course, there are conditions.
Can you work for me for 50 million yen?
I'll do anything.
Please let me work.
Please let me go!
Huh?
It's not you.
The one who works for me is your wife.
Me?
Your wife has been...
What was her name again?
Tsumugi.
Tsumugi-San, as a
private secretary, will follow
my orders unconditionally,
no matter what.
No matter what?
You won't do anything weird, right?
I said, no matter what.
If you don't like it,
let's not talk about it.
If you refuse me even once in
this month, I'll cancel the contract.
That's right. I'll get 50 million yen back.
That's all.
I'll answer you by 22nd.
I've made up my mind.
I knew it.
You've decided to go.
But there's no other way
to get the money back.
You don't have to worry about it.
But...
If Tsumugi does something to her...
It can't be helped.
You have to be prepared.
It's all your fault.
You've been patient for a month.
I can't stand it anymore.
The next day, I went to Nakae's house.
Yosuke followed me because
he was worried about me.
Why did you come here?
I thought I could do something for you.
No.
Go home.
But...
Yosuke, go home.
You can do whatever you want.
I don't know how long I can stay.
Tsumugi, I'm looking forward
to working with you for a month.
Yes, I'm looking forward
to working with you.
Well, let's get naked.
Why don't you become my wife?
Wh...what do you mean?
I mean...
I'm going to take off my
clothes and underwear here.
Wait a minute.
Why would you do that?
I thought you were
going to ask me anything.
Or... You don't want to do it?
But...how much is it?
I got it.
Okay, go home now.
I'll give you 50 million yen next week.
Wait a minute.
I'll do anything for you.
Please don't kill me.
What can I do for you?
This is the only angle.
I can't do it so easily.
You know that, right?
Go home.
I understand.
I just need to listen to
you for a month, right?
I see.
Tsumugi has a better
understanding of you than me.
And she has more courage than you.
That's right.
It's only been a month.
I'm just going to use it.
Tsumugi...
It's only been a month, so...
Hey, you sit there too.
Then I'll have you naked.
But you have to hurry.
Tsumugi, you don't have to.
What are you going to do?
Tsumugi...
Let's go home.
You can go home.
What are you going to do?
You have a beautiful body.
Take off your clothes.
Please stop.
I told you to stop.
Your wife is working hard for you.
This is for you.
This is your underwear.
Stop it, Tsumugi.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to stop?
Don't hide it.
This is your tongue.
Show me.
Turn around slowly.
What?
Look.
It's good, isn't it?
First of all, I'd like you
to clean up in this outfit.
What?
You have to squeeze your genitals well.
I'd like you to clean it up.
Look, it's dirty there.
Yes, put your hips in.
It's dirty there, too.
If it's dirty, you have to put it
in water and squeeze it again.
It's dirty here, too.
If you don't put your hips in
and wipe it, it won't get dirty.
Squeeze it again.
You have to water it properly.
It's beautiful.
Tsumugi, thank you.
You're tired because I cleaned
up all of a sudden, right?
I'll give you a massage.
Sit here.
Don't hesitate to come over here.
Hey, move over there.
You must be tired.
I'll give you a massage.
It's okay.
I'm fine.
You don't have to be shy.
Tsunugi, please don't do that.
You must be tired because
you have a lot of hair.
I'm really fine.
So don't be shy.
Don't move.
This is a massage.
Oh, it's hot.
What's wrong?
Massage my thighs, too.
Oh, it's hot.
I have to massage your thighs.
Natsumi, come on.
I'll give you a foot massage.
I'm going to give you a
good massage, so come on.
What's wrong? You're just giving me a
weird voice and giving me a massage.
Then look at me again.
Come on, put your tongue out.
Hurry up.
Your tongue.
Come on.
Take it out more.
It's so soft.
What are you doing?
You have a nice tongue.
Look at what your wife is doing.
Look at it with your own eyes.
Look at it carefully.
Lick it.
Look at me.
Are you looking at me?
Do you feel better?
You feel better because
your husband is gone, right?
Let's continue the
massage Let's continue.
You wanted me to touch
you like this, didn't you?
Look at me.
Come on, your body is honest, so come on.
I fell.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You look like you're in a good mood.
Or do you like this better?
Tsumugi, what's this?
It's a mess.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
You're feeling better.
You can't do it on your own.
Come on Please
Give me a kiss.
Look, I'm going to take out your tongue.
Just like before.
What?
What time is it?
Please lick me.
That's right.
Ah!
Hmm... Ah!
This side too.
Ah!
Look closely.
Does it feel good?
Hmm!
Ah...
It feels good, right?
It feels so good.
Did you want to go now?
You were about to go, weren't you?
When you were about to go,
you said you were about to go.
It's hot.
Please.
What's wrong?
Why are you so irritated?
You can't stand it, can you?
What's wrong with you?
Does it feel good?
Answer me.
I can't.
I won't forgive you.
Don't say anything.
Do you want me to go?
You don't want to go?
I don't want to go.
What do you say when you want to go?
What do you say?
Let me go.
Say it louder What is it?
See?
You want to go, don't you?
Please let me go.
I said you can go.
Let me lick you.
What is this?
Massage me, please.
Lick me more.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Let me lick you.
I'm gonna lick you.
You can eat it all the way to the back.
I don't want to!
Come on!
You can't do it anymore, can you?
Look at me.
Open your legs.
Manko, open your legs.
I'm begging you.
I'm begging you to put me in a stroller.
Stroller...
Please put me in a stroller.
I'll say it again.
Stroller...
Please put me in a stroller.
Good girl.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I can't take it anymore.
AHhhhhhhh.
AHhahahhahhahhahh.
Urghhh.
Urghhhh Urrgghhh Urghhh
Do you feel that good?
Urrghhh Ahhhhh Urgghh
Urrgh Surly you do Urrghhh Urghhh
I'll make you do something else Urrrgh.
Urgh Uwah Urrghh
Urrgghh.
※ waves ※ I have a
bad feeling about this.
※ I have a feeling that this is also good.
※ My head is clearly visible.
What are you doing?
Oh.
Oh Oh.
Oh Oh Oh.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to see?
Do you want me to put it on you?
Here you are.
It feels good.
You can move on your own.
You can move on your own, right?
Do you want me to put a lot on you?
Which one do you want?
Please.
What is it?
Please... Please...
Let go of me...
Over there...
One... KUIKUIKUIKUIKUI.
I'm sorry.
Ahhhhhhhhhhh
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh Now
let me touch your body.
Oh no.
I'll make you feel better.
Ahhhhh.
I can't do this anymore.
Ahhhhhh.
Why are you crying?
I've never felt like this before.
I had sex with Nakae many times that day.
Despite the situation, I kept
feeling like I was forgetting myself.
Are you still awake?
What have you been doing since then?
Do I have to tell you?
You've been doing things
you can't say anyway.
You've been doing a
lot of things, haven't you?
I'm tired, so I'm going to take a shower.
You've been doing a
lot of things, haven't you?
You were happy to do a
lot of things, weren't you?
Do you really want to know?
It's a month's patience.
I know I can't do it with my
head, but when I remember
the love I received from Nakae,
my body reacts on its own.
Nyaaah!
It feels so good!
Ah!
Ah, I'm scared!
I'm scared!
Nyaaah!
After that, every day.
I would get drunk.
I drowned in the play with Nakae.
Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah...
Eventually, the request
from Nakae was escalated.
Tsumugi-San.
This is Kobayashi-kun,
Nice to meet you.
What...
Kobayashi-kun, you're always
doing your best, aren't you?
Today, my private secretary,
Tsumugi-San, will make you feel good.
Thank you very much.
Tsumugi-San will do anything if you ask.
Then, please.
First, put your clothes on.
What are you doing?
Look at her face and do it.
Take off all your clothes.
Don't be nervous.
I won't.
Enjoy it.
Kiss me gently.
Look at me.
Look at me more.
I kissed you because you are
young, but you have a lot of pimples.
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Then make me feel better.
Ask me if I feel good.
Do you feel good?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm glad. I should have licked you more.
You're so slow.
Look at me.
What's going on?
What are you going to do?
Can I touch you?
I don't feel anything.
Let me touch you.
You're drooling.
Let me lick you.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'm not a god.
It's not what you think it is.
What did he do to you?
What did he do to make you feel good?
Listen to me.
Make him feel good.
What should I do?
I don't know.
Try to provoke him more.
Be nice to him.
Does it feel good?
I'm going to eat it all.
Do you want me to kiss you?
I'll kiss you.
Hello?
The door is open, so you can come in.
I'm watching you here.
Look, Tsumugi.
I'll do it while looking at you.
Look, I'll do it.
Look, I'll do it while looking at you.
Take a good look at it.
You're so excited to be
seen by your husband.
It's good.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
I'm sorry.
Oratsumi-San.
Give me a deep kiss.
Wrap your tongue around me.
Look at me.
Give me a strong kiss.
Make me feel good.
I can't do this
anymore It's that hard?
Then I'll end it here.
I'll give you one last chance.
If you can't keep the contract, you
have to pay back the debt several times.
Which one do you choose?
I'll do it.
Please.
Listen.
Don't look away.
If you can't keep the contract,
You don't have to do anything, but
you have to pay me back the damage.
OK?
I'm watching you.
I'm watching you while kissing you.
Look at this.
This side, too.
Your neck is already swollen.
Do you feel good?
I'll lick you.
You have to remove
the gallbladder properly.
I'm going to take it off.
It's coming off nicely.
I'm going to support you from behind.
I'm going to take it off.
Look, it's so slimy.
Show it to him.
You're excited to be seen by your husband.
You want him to see you, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Come on, you can do it.
I want you to look at all of them.
Look at all of them.
I'm telling you to go when you're going.
You're a good girl, aren't you?
Look at this.
Does it feel good?
Open your butt.
Turn your butt this way.
That's right.
Open your butt so that
you can see it clearly.
Look at me when I'm embarrassed.
Please.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It's been a long time
since I saw you last time.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
You're crazy.
Look at your husband.
I'm gonna touch your ear.
Your ear is wet.
I'm listening to you.
Answer me.
You're so pretty.
Look at me.
What do you want to do?
I want to drink
You want to drink?
Is it good?
You're going to be all right.
You can't sleep?
Wake up.
Come here.
Please sleep.
I have a favorite chimpanzee.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll massage your lower body.
It's hot.
You're happy to be in Japan, right?
You love it, don't you?
It's so delicious.
I don't like it because it's so small.
Ahhhh.
Ahhhhh.
Ahhhhh Ahhhhh Yeah, I
know I know I'm sick Ahhhhh.
Ahhhhh Ahhhhh Ahhhhh Ahhhhh.
I'm sick Hahahahaha.
No, I saw it a lot because
my kids are eating so well.
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind...
I was so happy to eat my
favorite meat and water.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy... I'm
happy... Don't cry.
Look at me.
What do you say when you
go to the maternity hospital?
Please give me a baby.
Where do you want a baby?
I'm sure you'll feel
better in a few minutes.
Keep going.
Oww!
Oww!!!
Oh!
Do you feel better?
Oww!
You feel better?
Do you feel better?
What's wrong?
You gotta get up!
Ahhhhh!
Ahhhh!
Oh!
so good feels good
ah ah ah ah ah ah.
look at it ah.
ah.
ah feels good.
ah ah feels good.
ah.
Yes!
Once more Well done.
My legs are so
painful My back hurts.
Oh, my God!
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do it anymore.
I'm gonna give you a massage.
If you get a massage
from me, you'll be okay.
I'm gonna give you a massage.
Do you want a massage?
Please put your hands on my waist.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels so good!
Come here.
It doesn't matter if you do this or that.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, it's disgusting.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ah, it's gross.
ahhh Tilt your head Ahh!
Ahhh.
Ah!
Ahhh ahhh.
It's the last one, isn't it?
Is it good?
It's cold.
I want to die.
You look so tired.
Look at this.
Don't cry.
It's okay.
I can't stand it anymore.
I know it hurts.
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, okay.
I'm going to die.
Why is it so hot?
Let me have a drink.
OMG.
I can't let you drink it.
How can you drink it?
I can't open my eyes!
You're bleeding a lot.
Come on.
Come here.
Why are you whining?
Does it feel good?
What?
Do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
One shot, two shots, it doesn't change.
I'll get you out of here.
No, no, no, no.
We were released from Nakae.
After that, Yosuke didn't
come back for a while.
I suddenly remembered the time with Nakae
and called her, but Nakae didn't answer.
Even though my body is aching so much.