What a big house!
Isn't it nice? It's a guest house.
This kind of house is going to be popular.
My husband, Mr. Shusuke,
runs a company in Tokyo.
As a housewife, I lived
in an apartment in Tokyo.
He was living a carefree life.
He heard that his company's
business was booming,
so he decided to start a
guest house as a new business.
You're going to be the hostess here.
How's that? You're excited, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Mr. Shusuke is the type of person
who does whatever comes to his mind.
I'm the type of person who acts
on impulse, and I just found out
that I was going to start this
guest house just the other day.
I'm excited and nervous
about what's going to happen
next, even though I'm being
swayed by Shusuke-San.
I'm having a fun married life.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think I need a little cleaning.
Oh, I see.
The interior work is done, so I'll do
the rest of the work for the opening.
I want you to do the cleaning.
Oh, I got it.
But isn't it hard for you to
do both work and cleaning?
What?
Oh, well, it's hard, but it's okay.
All right, let's get started.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's go in.
How is it?
Wow!
It's amazing!
I'm going to bring the
documents to the pharmacy.
Okay. Be careful.
I'll be back soon.
See you.
I found you.
Futaba Shunsuke.
The persimmon is delicious.
I don't know if it's a girl or a man.
But I'm going to go see for myself.
Excuse me?
Oh, hello.
I got lost on the road.
Could you get me a glass of water?
Oh, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, but I can't let you
stay in a woman's house.
Don't worry about it.
It's not open yet, but
this is a guest house.
So, please take your time.
My husband hasn't gone out yet.
Please come in.
Thank you.
The water is delicious.
So, you're opening a guest house in Gokufu?
Yes, I am.
I said it before, but it's not open yet.
It's a good place.
It's a really good place.
I was born and raised in Tokyo.
I've never been to a
place like this in the
mountains, but it's a
really nice place, isn't it?
The air is delicious, it's very
peaceful, and it's comfortable to live in.
I don't usually do this, so I don't enjoy
this kind of nature, so I feel really good.
Did you come here for a tour?
Well, I had a little business.
We have a guest house.
I didn't know that.
It's good to have a lot
of nature around here.
My husband and I have a guest house.
We moved here from Tokyo recently.
I see.
Tokyo?
Yes.
My husband told me
that he has a guest house.
I didn't know that.
Did your husband quit his job?
No, he has a company in Tokyo.
It seems that his company is doing well.
So I came here again.
Is that so?
It's going well.
Is something wrong?
No, no.
I thought that your husband
was a person who could work.
I thought you were a good person.
You're like a hard worker.
I see.
Well, I have to go.
Can you go now?
If you don't mind, you
can stay a little longer.
No, I'm busy.
Don't worry about me.
I see.
Please come again if you like.
I'll come again.
Yes.
I'll stay at your place next time.
If you come here.
Thank you very much.
I hope I can come here soon.
Hello, I'm Matsuzaki.
Thank you for your request.
I'll make a reservation.
I'll take care of the rest.
Yes, I understand.
But, is it true?
You let a woman go and get a reward.
Do you really have money?
Of course.
Revenge for the president who
ran away from the employees.
And...
My wife died.
It's time for that man to pay for it.
The time has come for you to do it.
I know. I believe in your words.
Then I'll do it.
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me.
Yes, sir.
Is this real?
It's real, isn't it?
Are you serious?
You can do anything.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's good.
Really? I'm glad.
I'm glad.
You ate a lot, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
By the way, there was a visitor at noon.
A visitor? What kind of visitor?
What do you want me to do?
Well, there was a customer
who got lost on the street.
He was just talking to you.
And he said he'd come
back when the store is open.
Oh, I see.
I'll just...
Well, whatever.
Just...
But I think you should advertise
this comic book store more.
On the Internet.
No, you can't do that.
I mean, you can't do that.
You know, this kind of place is far away
from the hustle and bustle of the city.
So, don't advertise it.
It's like getting to know someone you know.
I see.
But there are a lot of people who
collect information on SNS these days.
Oh, yeah.
I'm making a website now.
Oh, you're right.
So, only people who want to stay
can search, come here and stay.
Oh, I see.
Oh, there's a reservation.
What? Oh, you're right.
There's a reservation for two
nights and three days on the first day.
Wow!
You're amazing!
Actually, I told my friends about the guest
house in the apartment I used to live in.
Maybe that's why they made a reservation.
What?
I'm sorry.
I told you it's a secret, but I told you.
It's okay. I can tell my friends.
I can talk to you.
Really?
I'm glad.
I have to do my best.
I'm looking forward to it.
Me, too.
I wonder how it will be.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What are you laughing at?
I'm looking forward to it.
We have to start cleaning from tomorrow.
That's right.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best, too.
Let's do our best together.
And we split up our roles.
While sharing the burden,
we organized this small
house, and welcomed the
opening day of the guest house.
Here it is.
We have a guest.
What?
Guest?
I'm the guest?
We're ready.
This is a good place.
I'm in charge of the reservation.
I'll make a reservation for 3 people.
The customers are amazing.
You know what?
Today is the grand opening.
I hope the first day won't come.
That's a bad thing.
What are you talking about?
Don't get me wrong!
I'm sorry.
I've lost so many times.
It's the first day.
I'm sorry.
Then, this way, please.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to the room later.
Later?
What did you do to him?
Come on!
Zamanu.
Where is he?
Zamanu, I'll prepare it.
Hurry up, Gijin!
Where is Mom?
... ...
...
What are you doing?
Cheers!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
It's amazing.
We are so great.
We are.
It's over.
Thank you very much.
Eat, eat.
Eat.
What?
Wow.
You can eat.
You are great.
One more time.
Eat.
Well,
I'm not that strong.
I can do it.
Here you go, ma'am.
I have work to do.
I'll drink this.
Don't drink too much.
I'm fine.
Here you go, ma'am.
Show your manliness.
Please stop.
Can you do it for me?
Skinship?
I'm not a skinship.
I'm a skinship.
Hug.
Are you okay?
A little.
He fell asleep.
It's dangerous.
I'm not strong.
It doesn't matter.
I have a lot of work to do.
Here you are.
Take a picture of your husband.
I'll wipe it off.
Here it comes.
It's going to smell even worse.
Here you are.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
Thank you Cheers.
This is good
Please stop.
Service is bad I don't
want to go to Ginza.
Ginza is lonely.
It's not that kind of place.
It's not Ginza.
No, it's not.
I don't want to go there.
There's no such place.
You're so cute.
Wait.
Please don't.
No.
Come here.
Please stop it.
I have to go back to work.
I got it.
I won't push you.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Hey, I won.
Stop it.
No, no, no.
You've been playing
rock-paper-scissors for a long time.
If you win, it's a reward.
That's right.
Hey.
Stop it.
Please stop.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
It smells good.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Please stop it!
She wants you to stop it.
No!
Don't go wild.
You'll get drunk.
No!
Stop it!
Please eat this.
No, no, no.
Let's enjoy it.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
You are so soft.
Good girl.
I'll do a good thing.
What is it?
I'll soak you in water.
Good.
The water will splash.
I'll do it.
Don't cry.
Be careful.
Is it good?
Ah.
She is crying.
It's hard.
Don't cry Don't cry.
It's hard Thank you
for your hard work.
Did you eat my nose?
Please sit here.
Do you see this?
How do you feel when you stand?
This is a misunderstanding.
Please wake up.
Give it to me.
No, no, no.
You're going wild.
You have a good spirit.
It's hot.
Please stop.
Stop.
Stop it!
Oh, it's broken.
It's broken.
Come on, come on.
Eh?
I'll take it off.
I'm scared.
Don't be aggressive.
I can't feel anything.
I'm scared.
Don't do that.
Come on, come on, come on.
Isn't it shining?
What is this?
It's not broken.
Hey, it's broken.
Ah!
Don't do that.
It smells so good.
She is wearing a very dirty underwear.
What is this?
It's a guest house, isn't it?
There's a housekeeper.
Put your butt here.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
Full service.
What's wrong?
No!
You're wearing a nice hat, aren't you?
You're wearing such a sexy hat.
This is good.
You're eating a lot.
It's comfortable, isn't it?
Good boy.
You have a good butt.
You are a good host.
A lot of guests will come.
Do you feel good?
Let go of me!
Stretch your legs.
What are you doing?
Please stop.
I don't want to see it,
I don't want to see it.
Then, do you want to have a drink?
I want to drink wakame sake.
Wakame sake.
Do you allow it?
I don't want to see it.
Close it properly.
I can't do it anymore.
Stop it.
Hey, Kuro-chan.
Oh, no!
She has become so wet.
Let me help you.
Come on, Kuro-chan.
Come on, come on.
I beg you.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's too early.
My wife is...
My wife is so heavy.
So...
I beg you.
Let me go.
I have work to do.
It's okay.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's good.
Give me more.
I'm sorry.
A little more.
Let's add more water.
Mrs.
Koyama is calmer when she makes a voice.
That's good.
Come on, Mrs. Koyama.
Come on, get up.
What's wrong? Why are you lying down?
You're just like me.
The sound of the tree has changed.
I don't know if it's the
sound of the grass.
To the back.
It's shaking.
Good, good, good.
It's coming out.
I think it's stuck in your stomach.
Oh, it's coming out.
More, more.
Sit down, sit down.
Let's go to the room.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, ma'am.
Stop it.
It's slippery.
Come on!
Relax!
It's starting!
Slowly!
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Wow!
Put your legs down.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Did she go?
She went, didn't she?
Didn't she go?
Then,
I'll let you go.
Here.
I'm going to let you go.
If you don't go, I'll keep doing this.
You don't go?
Then, until you go,
I'll finish if you go.
It feels good.
You're round.
You look like you're in pain.
I think she's biting.
What are you doing?
Yes, that's a good girl.
I think she was in a bad mood earlier.
I'll do it.
Are you going?
I'm going.
You have to go.
Are you going?
You are so stubborn.
Oh, no.
Don't cry.
Stand up.
You can see your feet.
Can you see your feet?
Step on your feet.
What?
Are you a newborn baby?
No, I'm not.
Your husband is close to you.
You are a big girl.
Don't make a sound.
Go quietly.
You can go up to the front.
Don't make a face.
Don't make a sound.
If you make a sound, you'll be found out.
You'll wake up.
What are you going to do?
That's not good.
Chikkun, you can't do that.
He's gone.
You don't have to go.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Chikurin, you're sweating so much.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
Ah!
I went.
That's right.
Did you go?
Yes.
No!
Why?
You can't leave me!
No!
I can't take it anymore.
Here you are.
Take it.
I took it out.
It's clean.
You are so beautiful.
Here you are.
I'll give you a medicine.
You got out of the box.
You are so beautiful.
Here you are.
What's wrong?
I'm hurt.
It's hurt.
Are you alive?
She is in a critical condition.
She is stuck.
You guys are helpless.
What's wrong?
It's okay.
You two are out, so you can watch TV.
Why are there so many people?
What?
Are you going to wake them up?
I don't want to.
No one is coming.
It's okay.
You feel better?
You don't want to do it.
You're next to your husband.
You're going to get dizzy.
Look over there.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Are you comfortable?
Soda-San, wait a minute.
You have a bad temper.
Please don't kill me.
I beg you.
I don't want money.
What?
Stop it.
That's just an act.
Baby.
She's wearing a diaper.
She's coming out.
One more time.
Good girl.
What?
What's that?
You're a good girl, you know
that, don't you, Aoki-San?
You're a good girl.
Don't tell anyone.
You'll be exposed.
Let's drink again.
Let's drink.
Thank you, thank you.
Today's sake is good, isn't it?
I'm full.
What time is it now?
You scared me.
Where is the guest?
He went back to his room and took a rest.
I see.
You should go to bed now.
Yes.
Then I'll go to bed too.
I have to go to work early in the
morning tomorrow, so wake me up early.
Good night.
Good morning, ma'am.
What's for breakfast today?
I haven't told anyone.
I don't have any money left.
I can't take it anymore.
Please.
You don't have to go through all this.
It's not that bad.
You've got 3,000,000 yen, right?
Do you want to do it again
until tomorrow morning?
Stop it.
I'm so sorry.
Just pretend to be normal.
You'll understand if I
talk to you strangely.
Yes, I understand.
Hello.
I saw a sign that said open.
What's wrong?
A man...
A man is coming.
My husband is coming.
Please.
Please, please, please.
Oh, looks like you're doing well.
Come here, come here.
No, no, no.
These people, these people.
They're going to hurt me.
Let me see.
What?
Hey, ma'am.
What? Why?
No, no, no.
This guy, you know... He
betrayed us by letting his wife go.
What? Why?
Why?
Calm down.
I was surprised when I talked to you.
The company is doing well.
You haven't been told anything.
You went bankrupt due to debt.
You abandoned your family and employees.
What's wrong with you, the
president of the company?
Because... All he said was
that the company is doing well.
I'm an ex-employee who used to work there.
He's a bastard who threw
everything away and ran away.
No way...
It's so bad...
That's right, that's
right... I know... Stop!
Stop!
I want to see it!
Now...
How's your abalone today?
Is it better than yesterday?
You're acting like you're in pain.
I'm in pain.
Who would come to this kind of place?
What's this?
She's scared and getting scared.
Oh, no.
We can't do anything about it.
She's been running around for 5 years.
She's got a headache.
You're not going to get any better.
Look at her.
She's fast.
She's talking to me.
It's cold!
You're in shock, aren't you?
Oh, no!
You hid your underwear!
Pon-chan's Polaroid camera hid it.
You have a beautiful body.
I'm sorry.
I know.
Let's give up.
Here.
Dirty.
No!
I'll put it in the morning.
Let me go.
More.
Is it better to wet it?
Yes.
How can I wet more?
No!
Let me go.
It's so cute.
You're so beautiful.
You're so beautiful You're so beautiful
So pretty It's so cold You look so pretty.
Stand up.
Show me.
Be honest.
I'll do something pleasant for you.
No!
Stand up.
Stop it!
I'll do something pleasant for you.
She is crying.
She is very lively.
She is more lively than yesterday.
Because she is a raw abalone.
Because she is a living creature.
I'll give her a lot of water.
You're so strong.
I promise you that.
Smile.
You're bleeding.
It must have been disgusting.
Don't cry.
Ok, let's go.
I prepared a bed for you.
Come here.
Ok, Rami.
Good.
Ok, let's start.
Ok, Rami.
You are such a good boy.
Come on.
First, let's go to the back of the throat.
Let's go all the way to
the back of your throat.
It's best to go all the way to the
back of your throat in the morning.
More, more.
Here, here, here.
Sit down.
Hold her tight.
Give her a warm welcome.
Don't let go of it.
I'll do it with just my mouth.
That's a good voice.
It's not over yet.
Give me your hand.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
You're surrounded by so many things.
It's disgusting.
Come on, come on.
You're becoming more and more quiet.
You've become so big.
Yes, yes, yes.
You've got a lot of fat.
Here you are.
You're so big.
Oh, yes.
You're getting bigger.
You're breathing heavily.
Yes.
Good.
You're so big.
Wow!
You're not going to do it?
Do it properly.
You have to do it properly.
You have to get up.
Open your legs wider.
I'm scared!
Come here.
I'll give you a sock.
I'm sorry.
Good girl.
You three are customers.
I'm sorry.
Is it still warm?
How do you feel?
It's a mess.
It's almost ready.
Here it comes.
Are you going to die?
Are you OK?
Are you alive?
You look like a skeleton.
Are you OK?
Did you lose weight?
Did you get it?
Here you go.
Don't put it in your butt.
Oh, it's melting.
It's melting.
You've grown up.
It's in your mouth.
Stop it!
Why?
I don't want to!
Ouch!
Oh, you ate the help.
Let's give you a foot massage.
I won't let you rest, wife.
I won't help you.
Show me your face.
I can't move my mouth.
You don't have much energy left, do you?
You've been put in a cage.
You're crying.
Come on.
You're a good girl.
Get on my back.
You're on my back.
Come on.
Kokichi, you have to
hold on a little longer.
Hang in there for another day.
You can do it.
Give her a hand.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Matsuzaki!
What are you doing?
Ema, what are you doing?
So you're going to take care
of the employees who quit?
Will you kill me?
Will you give me back my dead wife?
Look at me.
Do you know what she looks like now?
Tell me.
She looks sad.
Why?
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill you.
Don't do that.
It's meaningless.
Wait.
Look at me.
I'm going to kill you.
Don't do that.
But my wife is dead.
I don't care.
Oh oh oh.
So can I get out?
No no no Stop?
No Alright, I'm getting out.
Here.
Here you go
She's holding her head up.
Here.
Oh.
Oh oh oh Do you want it, Seishi?
Ouch!
What's that?
Show it to me.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stand up.
Stand up, stand up.
Put your hands on your head.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stand up.
You have to look at your wife.
Hey.
Hey, wife.
What are you looking at?
Look at your face.
Look at your wife.
You too.
You're a woman.
Say the truth.
Say the truth to your wife.
Say you're sorry you lied.
Come on, say it.
I was angry.
I'm sorry.
You stole the company, didn't you?
I was angry.
Say it with your own mouth.
Say it.
Say it!
I'm telling you to say it!
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
Here you are.
I'll give it back to you.
I'll crush you.
I'm used to it.
Here you are.
Do you want to have a drink?
I'll buy it for you.
I'll wait for you.
Here you are.
Don't lie to me.
I'll punish you.
Let me kiss you.
Don't look at me.
You can do it!
I'm sorry.
They're out.
Damn it.
That's enough.
Come on, let's hug.
Hey, come on.
You should have seen it.
You should apologize.
You shouldn't have.
I'm sorry.
You should have been a bigger girl.
What's going on?
You're starting to cry.
You should take care of your husband.
Haru-chan, look at him.
You should look at each other.
You are getting along with him.
He is going away.
He went away.
I'm sorry.
Don't say sorry.
My dead wife won't come back.
She'll be upset.
Your wife will come back.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry to make you feel bad.
I'm sorry.
No, I don't.
Look at her.
What's that?
Are you going to show her?
I'm sorry.
He's just a normal guy.
You don't have any grudge against him.
But you made a mistake in your marriage.
You made a mistake in your life.
That's a sin.
But if you feel so good
because of this sex,
at least you're saved.
I'm sorry.
Come on, ma'am.
You're all scared, aren't you?
Let's forget all the
bad things with a kiss.
Open your legs.
I'm glad to hear that.
But it's your fault for arresting that man.
How was it, Osamu?
It was a good job. Thank you.
I'll pay you back.
Of course.
But...
It's still good, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
It can't be helped.
How long has it been since then?
The sun has set, and I don't
know if this is a dream or reality.
Even so, the men continued
to eat away at my body.
Do you want to go?
Isn't it a little early?
Let's go to the broth.
I'm sorry.
What?
The first round has just begun.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
It hurts.
Don't be so violent.
This is a theme park.
You did a good job.
Hey, look at me.
I told you to go away.
My wife.
Do you feel good?
If you want to pee more,
you have to change your clothes.
I don't feel good.
You have to change your clothes.
What do you want to pee?
I want to pee.
You have to change your clothes.
Really?
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a hand.
Move your brother.
Are you looking at me?
Do you want to do it?
If you want to do it, you can do it.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Say something
like, Can I do it, too?
What do you think?
Can I do it?
Here you are.
Oh, you got a big one.
There's a lot of toys over there.
It's good, isn't it?
This toy looks good.
Eat more.
Don't eat so much.
I think it's better to eat
the real thing than this.
I'll break this one, too.
I'll break that one, too.
Your husband is looking
at you with a great face.
What are you looking at?
You're still eating.
It's delicious.
I'll give you more.
Put it on your face.
Rub it on your face.
It feels good.
You have to drink it all.
Drink it all.
You are standing up.
What are you going to do?
Here, if you want to
lick the doggy, move it.
Please lick it.
Open your mouth and lick it.
This is...
Oh!
Oh, good!
Good!
Let's wash your hands and mouth.
Yes, yes.
Let's wash your face, too.
Let's wash your face.
I'm sorry.
I'll put my butt out.
You have a good butt.
How do you feel?
Are you fine?
I'm fine.
How about glible Man-ko?
She's still sucking on the لound.
Put it in your mouth.
I'll do it myself.
Here it comes.
Try moving it.
Move it yourself.
You like this, don't you?
I'll make you feel better,
so move it yourself.
You feel better than
your husband, don't you?
I'm scared.
What?
You just said you felt good.
You said you felt good.
I'm scared.
Ah...
Ah, I feel sick.
I can't breathe.
Oh... I feel sick...
Ah... I feel sick...
I feel sick... Oh!
Oh!
You broke it.
Here you are.
Hold it.
Open your legs.
Put your hands behind your head.
Here we go.
Here you are.
You can do it.
It's so comfortable.
Go.
Put your hands behind your back.
You can do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
Let's go. Let's go.
Go to your husband's room.
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
Are you okay?
Oh, it feels good.
I'll watch you.
That's it.
Tighten it properly.
It's too loose.
It's broken.
It's in.
I'm so happy!
What's wrong?
You want more, don't you?
I'm so hungry.
You're hungry?
You're eating a lot.
It's dark even if you look this way.
It's dark.
I don't feel good at all.
I want money.
Please give me money.
I'll put it on your back.
I want to see your whole body.
It hurts.
You can do it.
It's long.
You are tired.
You can do it.
It's over.
OK!
I'm sorry.
You are very strong.
I give you an egg.
You are cute.
You can do it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Do you want it?
Yes, I do.
Let me go inside.
Please.
What are you going to do?
Let me go inside.
Take it.
Inside!
Here we go.
Move, move.
Go deeper.
Let go.
Let me go.
How do you feel?
Come on, come on.
Come here.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, come here.
Your wife's manko is
open, and the manko is here.
Hey, hey, show me. Where is it?
Mr. Matsuzaki, my wife's manko is here.
Masuzuki-San, your wife Mac is here.
Here?
Where?
Your wife Mac is here.
Let me see your right arm.
You did a good job.
I'm so sorry.
I'm surprised, too.
You look like a newborn baby.
My belly is getting bigger!
Your belly is getting smaller!
I'm moving!
I feel good!
You feel good!
I'm sorry!
I feel good!
Which one is better?
Your husband's or mine?
This one is better!
I feel good!
It's disgusting!
Let go! Let go! Let go!
Here we go!
Wow!
You scared me!
Let go, darling!
It's disgusting!
I'm going to throw up!
You're so slow!
Don't look at me.
I'm going to kill you.
It's coming out.
I'm sorry.
Are you still licking me?
I'm petting you!
It feels good, doesn't it?