Curry Tube
Thank you for your presents.
Thank you.
After this, let's take a rest at the inn.
OK.
Well... Hey, Hayashi.
Are we there yet? Well.
..
I think we'll be there soon.
It's been a long time since
I've been to a hot spring.
Do you have a open-air
bath, Hayashi-kun? Yes, I do.
Yay!
Let's go in together.
I want to go in.
We're going on a business
trip, so don't miss it.
Okay.
We're going on a business
trip, so don't miss it.
What's going on?
It's strange that there are only two rooms.
We are four people in one room,
but Hayashi is in a single room.
The balance is bad.
I'm sorry.
If I told you the budget and
the number, it would be like this.
I'm sorry.
Well, it can't be helped.
It doesn't seem to be
so narrow, so this is fine.
Or do you want to be with Hayashi?
Do you want to stay
with me? No, no, no.
You don't, do you? OK, then.
Let's have dinner together after this.
OK.
Shall we go to the hotel
room? What? Let's go.
Let's go.
Let's go to the room with Hayashi.
What? Don't go.
I'll see you at the meeting.
Oh, I see.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is a man's room.
Are you OK? I'm OK.
Oh, I'm sorry.
See you later.
OK.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see you.
Oh, I see.
It's small, isn't
it? Yes, it is.
Hey, why are you coming this way?
What?
Because I'm a man.
No way.
I told you so.
I'm a man.
Please get out of here.
Wait a minute.
What?
Oh, wait a minute.
This is a men's room.
Oh, is it? Yes, it is.
Oh, it's a men's room.
So, please get out of here.
So, it's a men's room, isn't it?
No, it's a men's room.
What is it?
What is it? Oh, yes.
What?
Hey, hey, it's a problem.
I told you I'm a man.
What? You're right.
Why do you make a mistake?
Do you want to come in with me?
What? No, I'm fine.
Just kidding. See you.
What's going on?
Are you sure you're okay?
Wow, it looks so delicious.
It looks so delicious.
Thank you for your present today.
Thank you.
Hayashi, say cheers.
Me?
Thank you for your present.
Thank you very much.
The presentation went well and...
I'm so full.
I want to drink sake.
Let's toast.
Let's drink.
Cheers!
You drink so fast.
I want to drink sake.
I see.
You drink so fast.
Were you thirsty? I love sake.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Yes.
You look like a fool.
I'm sorry.
You can see my face.
Well, then.
You are great.
I'm sorry.
You look like a fool.
I'll take it.
I'm sorry.
What?
Is he the director?
He is a little polite.
No, no, no.
What?
Is he a fool? No, he is not.
What are you doing?
I want to eat it.
I'll do it.
Will you do it?
You are too late.
Thank you.
It looks delicious.
Is it a squid?
Is it a salmon? It's a scallop.
It's a scallop.
It's delicious.
It's fresh.
It's soft.
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's good.
I can't stop drinking.
I'm going to change.
You're fast.
You're too fast.
I used to drink a lot when I was a student.
Here you are.
I think it's almost gone.
Yeah, it's amazing.
You should eat more.
Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
Are you eating nutritious food?
No, I usually eat cup noodles.
At a convenience store?
That's why you can't work.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Eat a lot.
I'm sorry I pulled my legs today.
You were biting a lot.
You have to get used to it.
Yes.
Are you nervous about work?
I'm not good at talking in front of people.
Excuse me.
Are you okay? It's amazing.
It's amazing.
I have Japanese sake.
Japanese sake?
It's a big deal.
I'll change it to Japanese sake.
I'll have a drink.
Don't spill it.
Here we go.
Oh, no.
Hey, there's more here.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
What are you doing? I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
You can't even wear it.
I'm really sorry.
We ate a lot.
It's good to eat like this once in a while.
It's fun.
It refreshes me.
I have to eat.
I can't help it.
I ran out of sake.
I don't have beer, so
I'll have Japanese sake.
I see.
That's right.
You should have noticed it earlier.
Don't spill it.
You spilled it.
This is not good.
It's good.
Let's pour some for everyone.
Yeah, pour some for them.
Then I'll pour some for you.
Excuse me.
I want to drink.
It's a Japanese sake party.
You're pouring it properly.
My legs are numb.
Do you want some Japanese sake?
Are you sure?
I want to drink it.
I want to drink it, too.
I see.
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
I spilled the tea.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, sorry.
You're late.
Excuse me.
Oh?
Oh, you're here.
You've grown up.
Why are you sitting there?
What's wrong?
No, I don't think so.
I don't know.
You don't have to ask.
Hey, it's gone.
See, it's gone.
Give it to him.
Thank you.
Did you grab it?
I'm grabbing it.
Don't worry, everyone.
Hey, it's me.
Do you drink a lot?
Yes.
Are you weak?
I can't drink it at all.
It's okay.
It's delicious.
One more time.
I'm going to drink it.
Wow.
Drink it.
Put it on your lips.
Hurry up.
It's getting wet!
It's getting wet! It's OK.
I'm going to drink it.
I can't drink that much.
It's getting wet.
It's because of your shoulders.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll do it for you.
I have a shoulder.
Shoulder? I see.
Like this? Harder.
Wow.
I'll do it next.
Hayashi, are you good at it?
Yes.
You just touched it.
Don't push too hard.
I did it.
Push more.
There, there, push more.
Yes, yes, yes.
Not bad.
Yes, there.
It's wrinkled, isn't
it? Loosen it more.
Yes, yes, it feels good.
You did it.
I was praised.
Yes.
How is it?
Is it good?
Hayashi, are you angry?
Me? No, I'm not.
Do you want me to
massage you? No, I'm fine.
Why? No, no, no.
Do you want to see? No, I don't.
What?
Why?
Where are you angry?
What? Where?
Where are you angry? My feet.
Your feet?
What's wrong? It looks painful.
No, no, no.
A little, a little.
You're a couple.
You're going out today.
Yes, I'm okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
What? Wait.
What?
What is this?
Who is he?
What's wrong?
What?
What are you playing?
It's a different thing.
What's different?
What's this?
What?
What are you doing?
What made you so
excited? It's so shaped.
Isn't it big? It's big.
But it smells.
It was in the bathroom, wasn't it?
No.
I didn't bring my underwear.
You didn't bring your underwear?
You don't have
underwear? It's dirty.
Oh, dirty.
Take off your dirty underwear.
Take it off?
Why not?
Take off? It's dirty.
It's stinky.
This is a smelly underwear.
Take it off.
Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off! Take it off!
Hurry up!
Are you ready?
Take it off! Take it
off! Take it off! I got it.
Wow!
I've never seen such a thing!
It's amazing!
I've never seen such a thing.
It's so big.
Everyone told me to take it off.
Why did you make it
so big? Hey, touch it.
What? Touch it.
Why? It's a freebie.
Touch it.
No, no, no.
I don't have a handkerchief.
No, you don't.
Why?
The one who lost the
rock-paper-scissors touch it.
The one who lost?
Rock-paper-scissors!
What? What?
What? What? What? Wait.
Your hand.
..
What?
Wow!
What is this?
What is this? Please stop it.
Is this a YouTube
video? No, it's not.
I was surprised.
Oh, my God.
It's moving.
What is this?
It's a little bit small.
Don't open your eyes!
I lost to the second time, so I'm sorry.
One more time.
Wait a minute.
Look at this.
Calm down.
He moved a lot.
How did he do that?
Wow! Wait a minute.
Wow!
It's huge!
It's moving!
Let it stand more.
Look!
It's moving!
Is it reacting?
Wow!
Let me take it off.
What is it? Imagine it.
How is it?
It's moving!
The blood vessels are amazing.
It's alive.
Amazing.
I didn't know there was a mole here.
It's true!
Isn't it slanted?
Isn't it big?
Can you put it in?
This is the only way
to do it! Please try it.
It moved!
Hold it! Hold it! I will try it.
It's upside down!
Let me see! Here too.
Wow!
I got a good one.
Let me see!
I'll borrow a good one.
What?
Wow!
It's a good one.
It's dirty.
Wow!
If this was Uekura...
You have to clean it.
Do you want to try wrapping it?
Do you wrap it?
You can touch it directly.
If you tear one sheet...
It looks like a living thing.
Wow!
How is it?
It's hot!
Hot?
It's getting hot.
Let me stand up.
How many percent
is it? It's 30%.
30%?
It's not hot at all.
Let me stand up quickly.
Quickly.
Oh, it's the butt.
Let me see.
What is it? It's the butt.
Which one do you like?
The butt or the boobs?
Which one?
Which one do you like?
Which one? Pick one.
Not wow.
What are you looking
at? What? Hurry up.
Which one do you like? Pick one.
I can't choose.
You can't?
I don't think so.
Let's decide who to touch.
Rock-paper-scissors again?
Rock-paper-scissors?
Our team will lose again.
No, we won't.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Oh!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You lost!
OK!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yeah!
What?
Does it mean we change?
It's a 30% chance!
30%?
100%?
Hurry up!
Does it feel good?
How do you feel? Well.
..
It feels good a little bit.
What are you talking about?
It doesn't feel good.
It feels good.
See?
Hurry up!
Is Sate coming?
Can't I sit here?
You don't like this part?
You like this part.
She likes her nipples.
Look at her nipples.
Her nipples are getting bigger.
Wow.
It's so hard.
It's twitching.
It's wrapped.
It's sealed, so you
can lick it as it is, right?
Oh?
Really? Wait a minute.
Why?
It's not your fault.
It's not my fault.
It's your fault.
Yeah.
It's getting bigger.
How is it?
What does it taste like?
It's full of juice.
It's too big.
It's bigger than my boyfriend's.
What is this? It's so big.
It's so hard.
What is this? It's so sticky.
Is it hot? Yes, it is.
Wow, it's hard.
I can't get it in.
You're moving your hips,
aren't you? No, I'm not.
Really? No, I'm not.
You're shaking.
You're moving your hips.
Wow, you're shaking, too.
That's right.
Look, it's getting bigger.
It's hard.
What's wrong with you?
You made it so hard.
Let's eat.
How is it?
It's like a wrap.
It doesn't go in at all.
I want to see it.
Let's see.
Wow.
It's black.
Wow, that's amazing.
Rapping is tough.
It's really tough.
Wow.
Do you play Sanju Game?
Sanju Game?
Do you know what that is?
I know what it is.
You cut it with your hands.
I've heard of it.
1, 2, 3.
The loser of this game
will get a ferrari like this?
How about that?
This is a match that can't be lost.
It's huge.
Go to sleep.
I'm sleepy.
Let's go to sleep.
Let's go around the clock.
Let's go clockwise.
1, 2, 3!
What are you doing?
What's next?
Clockwise? Me? This way.
How long?
Yes, think about it.
4, 5, 6.
You're attacking.
7.
Sexy.
How to touch.
Nine.
Ten.
Eleven.
Twelve.
How is it?
Stop at twelve? From thirteen.
Do you feel good, Hayashi?
Yes.
Stop at 14!
What?
What is it?
You can't say it!
How do I do that? I can't go on.
20, 21, 22.
..
You are getting closer and closer.
Go on, go on! Twenty.
..three! Twenty.
..four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-five?
It's almost there!
Oh no!
It's in my mouth!
What should I do? 26, 27, 28.
What was it?
29.
It's 29.
Here we go.
9 9 You win.
We've opened the souvenir book.
What's this? Can I
lick it? Yes, you can.
You said it yourself.
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm going to lick it.
Look at me, Hayashi.
Look at me.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14.
Don't move your hip.
I am not moving.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14.
Wow, that's amazing.
Wow, that's a great sound.
It's getting more intense.
It's dripping.
That's how you usually lick it.
It's embarrassing.
It smells good.
Let's eat it properly.
Wow, it's amazing.
You're taking a lot.
You like to eat blood, don't you?
Wow, it's amazing.
It became hard.
It's getting smaller!
Look!
Look here!
The gap is huge!
Amazing!
What kind of room do you usually live in?
Show us!
Are you going to show us?
Show us your daily life.
How do you manage it?
What? I'm curious.
Who is it?
Well, I guess it's Sefure.
I'm curious.
Well, show me.
Show me.
Well, first of all,
Well, first of all, I'll
start from the bottom.
I'll start from the bottom.
Wow.
I like the way you touch it.
Wow!
Is it a pitch pipe?
Are you purring?
Wow!
Wow! It feels good.
It feels good.
You didn't make such a voice when I did it.
No, I didn't.
Are you good at it?
You are better than me.
You have a very erotic face.
I didn't know you have such a face.
You look like you were put in a safe.
I think it will be bigger.
It's not like this yet.
I'm going to show you my boobs.
I'm not going to let you touch it yet.
You want to touch it, don't you?
It's soft, so imagine it.
What's wrong, Tachibana-san?
Tachibana-san, you have a nice boob.
You must be envious.
You're always daydreaming, aren't you?
I'm not daydreaming.
You're just glancing around.
I'm not glancing around.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Icchan, you can't do that!
Wait a minute!
Too fast! I can't do it.
Why are you so fast?
You should work faster.
I can't do it.
Why are you so fast?
You can't do it, Icchan.
I can't do it.
Next!
Show us!
I'm under a lot of pressure!
I'll make the best voice!
That's good!
He's the type to do it from the bottom.
Haruka!
Wow, you are so sexy!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Eat it!
What's the matter?
Wow, you are so sexy!
You are so sexy!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Wow! It's amazing!
It's touching!
What are you touching?
What is it?
I can't believe it.
What are you so happy about?
I want to touch it, too.
Wow!
Wow! What is
this? It's so erotic.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
No, no, no!
No? No? No?
Ah!
He can't get it out.
Did you try to get it out?
I can't get it out.
I don't think so.
I haven't seen it.
You haven't?
I want to see it.
Excuse me.
You are so mean.
How can you remember that?
Wow!
It's a big one!
It's amazing!
How is it?
Wow!
Oh, no!
Why?
Hold on!
Oh, no!
What's coming out?
Oh, no! It's hot.
Do you want to lick it?
Do you want to lick it together?
You are so erotic.
It's not easy to lick
because you two are big.
It's easy to lick.
Touch her breast.
I'm just touching you.
How do you feel?
You are amazing!
You don't have time to rest.
Look!
Look at Shino's boobs!
It's soft, isn't it?
How do you feel? It's soft.
It's soft?
Why are you acting
like a child? It's true.
Don't touch it.
Touch it a lot.
It's cool.
No, no, no.
You can't! You can't!
Becca, no!
You can't!
You can't, right?
Did you put up with it?
What about you, Becca?
What about your boobs?
You're so flirty!
Wow!
It's a big one!
It's big! Yes, yes.
Touch this side, too.
Wow!
It's so plump!
It's so plump! It feels good.
It's stuck in your boob.
It's already stuck.
Wow!
It's a bubble wrap!
Do you like bubble wrap?
Can you feel softness?
Wow!
You like bubble wrap! Oh, I see.
You are a country boy.
But you don't let go of your boobs.
You love boobs.
You are a boob-adventurer.
Really?
Wow!
You are like a baby.
I want to do it, too.
Which one do you want to do?
This one?
Let's do this one.
Do you want to
lick it? Like this.
Wow!
You look so happy.
It's a baby.
I feel so good.
It's like a baby.
It's so painful.
I'm so happy to see you.
Did you try it on?
You love it, don't you?
How do you like it?
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Wow, it's really tight.
I think I'm going to suffocate.
Wow, amazing!
Teimo, I love your boobs!
You're still pooping.
Oh, no.
It's still hard.
It's hard.
It's gross.
What?
Do you want more? Oh, no.
Do you want more? No, no, no.
No, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
I want to show you the talents of the
organizers of this sun dance ceremony!
This is the eve of the event.
Let's dance together!
I want to do it, too.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Not yet, not yet, not yet.
Wow!
It's dirty!
What's this?
It's all over the place.
What's going on?
Wow!
What? What? What?
What? It's not coming out?
It's not coming out?
It's already out!
It's so ugly!
Wow! It's the worst.
It's not strong enough.
It's too early.
Let's drink again.
Don't you go to bed yet?
We don't go to bed.
We are going to sleep.
Are you trying to
sleep? I drank a lot.
You are sleepy because you went to bed.
No, no, no.
You didn't look like that.
You did.
Does Hayashi have a girlfriend?
A girlfriend?
He doesn't have a girlfriend anymore.
That's true.
I heard that.
Why is Hayashi so unpopular?
I don't think so.
Why?
It's because it smells like money.
Isn't it too much?
Don't you rely on her?
No.
I don't rely on her.
I see.
Have you ever been in a relationship?
Well, maybe a little bit.
You're strong.
How much do you rely on her?
That's a secret.
What?
What do you mean?
Are you hiding it? No, no, no.
Wow! No, I'm not.
You're a magician.
No, I'm not.
Are you a magician? No, I'm not.
Then, you're not.
You're not yet.
Well, I'm not.
Why do you feel
like that? That's right.
It doesn't make sense.
It's suspicious.
What?
Well, it's okay.
Why? I'm curious.
Why?
We got along so well.
Yes.
Are you drinking? Yes, I am.
Drink up! Yes, I am.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
You are sleeping with
your penis on your pillow.
I want to sleep with my penis on my pillow.
I feel like I want to do that.
What? Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
Are you in love with me?
What? No, no, no.
No, I'm not.
You're right.
My boyfriend's eyes are big.
Is that so?
What?
You like big eyes.
No, no, no.
What? What? What?
Wait, wait, wait.
Can't you listen to
your senpai? Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
What are you doing?
Why aren't you wearing
your panties? No, no, no.
Why?
Why aren't you wearing your panties?
Were you expecting
something? No, I wasn't.
I'm sorry.
No?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
What are you
doing? Wait a minute.
What? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
What?
What are you waiting
for? It's rubbing.
It's rubbing.
It's rubbing?
What are you
doing? I got a chair.
Is it OK?
Is it really a chair?
It's comfortable to sit on.
Can I touch it?
Has it started?
No, it hasn't started yet.
What's going on?
I can't move my hips.
It's different.
It's a chair.
A chair? Yes, yes, yes.
Hey, hey, hey.
What? What?
Are you really just
sitting? Yes, I am.
I'm just sitting.
Really?
Yes.
Hey.
Wow!
It's in there!
What? You found out?
No way!
How can it fit in there?
It's so big!
Wow!
How did it get in there?
How did it get in
there? I didn't know.
Look!
It's in there!
It's so big!
Wow!
What's the name? No, I don't.
You don't? No, I don't.
Are you sure?
I don't want to put him
in such a big house.
What?
You don't?
He's my boyfriend.
He's your boyfriend.
I love him.
Let him move.
Wow, you look so much better.
Young people are amazing.
You're right.
You're so strong.
How many times can you do it in a day?
I can do it as many times as I want.
Let's see how many
times you can do it today.
You haven't had a
girlfriend for a long time.
That's right.
It's been a while since we've seen you.
You look like a treasure hunter.
I'm so happy.
I can see your face.
What are you doing?
I'm changing my clothes.
What?
You're in the way.
Are you going back to the castle?
Are you sure?
Hurry up!
Don't make a girl wait.
Don't look at me like that.
What is it? It's a scab.
It's a scab.
It's a scab, isn't it?
I can feel the pressure.
I can see your shoulders.
I can see them.
Wow, amazing.
I can see your chest.
Your shoulders are amazing.
It feels good.
You look so happy.
You have to move more.
Oh, no.
You have to move faster.
It doesn't feel good.
Oh, no.
It feels good.
You are moving so fast.
Oh, no.
I can see your eyes.
I feel good.
I feel good, too.
Wait a minute.
I feel good.
Only Ayashi doesn't feel good.
Wow!
I've never reached this far.
Wow! It feels good.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good?
It's been a long time.
Look this way.
Oh, I see.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
What?
What? What? What?
What is this?
Wow!
Can you see it?
It's so big!
I can barely see it.
I'm sorry, but you are crying a lot.
It's OK.
Do you want to
cry? I want to cry.
It's OK.
Wow!
It feels good!
Does it feel good?
Wow!
It's like a push and pull game!
It's amazing!
We're all on it!
Wow!
It feels so good!
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
I want to see your face.
Your face?
It's not fair.
You'll get bored if you only
play with cabbage, won't you?
I think the big one is better.
The big one feels good,
doesn't it? Yes, it does.
Does it feel good?
How do you feel?
It feels really good.
It feels good.
Wow, there are a lot of them.
They are so big.
Can you see them?
Can you see them? Oh, no.
What is it?
What is it? Wow, amazing.
Wow, amazing.
Wow!
I'm in the water.
It feels good!
I'm so happy!
Wow!
Ai-chan!
It feels good!
Ai-chan! It's freezing.
So creepy.
Ouch, my stomach hurts.
Oh, it feels good.
What's wrong? Why did you get up?
What is it?
Do you want me to touch you?
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's great.
I'm sorry.
You are so busy.
You don't have time to rest.
Move him more.
You can do it faster,
can't you? More, more.
It feels good.
Hayashi, do you
feel good? Yes, I do.
It's been a long time since you
had a bath, so you feel good.
Yes, I do.
Wow, you feel good.
Hayashi, more, more, more, more.
It's getting intense.
It's coming out!
It's so cute!
It's so cute! I'm so nervous.
Don't worry.
I'm so nervous.
You are sweating a lot.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm going to lick you.
Wait a minute.
It's still wet, isn't it?
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
It's still a long way to go.
It's going in.
Are you looking at it?
Look at where it's going in.
Can you see it? It's big.
It's big.
It's in.
It's too big.
It's the first time I've ever
seen something like this.
It's too big.
Is it big?
It's not moving at all.
I'm afraid I'm going to die.
It's not moving yet.
It's too big.
I'm so happy.
You're so happy, aren't you?
You must be happy.
I'm going to cry.
I'm so happy.
You're so cute.
Ah, it's scary.
How do you feel,
Hayashi? It's scary.
Hayashi? Calm down.
How do you feel?
Which one do you feel better, Hayashi?
Why are you asking me?
Which one?
It's me, isn't it?
Do you want me to be
more violent? I'm scared.
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! I feel sick.
I feel sick.
You are too big.
You have a big body.
I have a cramp in my back.
How can you remember that?
I don't remember at all.
That's because you are old.
I'm so happy!
How is it?
You cleaned up and
put it in the box, Hayashi.
How is it?
How does your juice taste?
Are you a baby?
You are so cute!
It feels so good!
You are the best!
I am going to fall down.
You have white eyes!
Look at his mouth.
He has a big mouth.
It feels good.
Which one do you
like? I feel good.
Which one do you like?
I like this one.
You don't mind? I'm so sorry.
How do you feel?
Do you want me to stretch
your neck more? I'm sorry.
How do you feel? I feel good.
I feel good.
Can we see that?
Wow!
OMG!
Go, go!
Wow!
She's crying!
OMG!
She's really crying!
That was too much!
That was really
intense! You are crying.
You are still crying.
Just this one.
You are crying a lot.
Oh, you are crying! I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm crying.
I'm happy.
Do you want me to
put it in? Yes, put it in.
OK, I'll put it in.
Do you want to
put it in? It's big.
Wow, it's so big.
It's huge, isn't it?
Amazing!
It's so big!
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! It's too big!
Oh, it's intense!
I'm going to cry.
What's wrong with you?
You have a lot of hair on your waist.
Look behind you.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay? It's no edge.
You're so good at moving.
Oh, my God.
You're shaking.
How far are you in?
Are you in? You're shaking.
Wow, she is strong! I feel good.
You are grombling.
Oh, awesome!
Yes!
Oh!
Oh! He's moving.
He's moving twice! It's amazing.
It's amazing.
Hayashi, you should move too.
Come here.
She is crying.
Oh, my God.
She is cold.
Did you get a cold, too?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Well, that's great.
That's a good feeling.
I feel so good.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
Oh, she's gone.
Where is she?
She's coming out.
It's coming out so much!
How many times?
Are you okay?
It's coming out so much!
It's so sticky!
It's so sticky! I'm going to.
..
I'm going to go last!
You're a bird!
It's a bird, isn't it?
It's a bird, so I'm going
to put it on my eyes.
What are you going to show me?
Don't expect too much.
I'm scared.
I'm going to give you a heart.
Did you find out?
I'm going to take it off.
It's in your ear.
Is it in my ear? Let me see.
I'm going to push myself down
and show you my strongest Kijoi.
Senpai, please show us.
I'm not your senpai at all.
Here I go.
Here we go.
It's so big.
It's big, isn't it?
Wow.
How do you feel?
I can't believe it.
Wow.
It feels so good.
Oh, it's great.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, my God!
Wow!
I'm going to throw up.
I feel great.
Ah, it's so nice.
It feels so good.
I'm going to throw up.
It feels so good!
Aoi-chan!
Yes!
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it feels so good.
Oh, it feels so good when I rub my back.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
Oh, it's cool.
Oh, it's cold.
I'm going to cry.
It's ticklish.
You have a very good face.
You have a big heart.
It's ticklish.
I'm sick.
Wow, it feels so good.
I feel so good.
I love you.
How do you feel?
How do you feel? I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Go, go, go!
Oh, no! It came out again!
Did it come out again?
It's so big!
What?
Which one is it?
Wow!
There are so many!
So many!
It's overflowing!
It's overflowing! I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Can you still do it?
I can't do it yet.
It's amazing.
The taste of the spirit of the spirit.
I'm so happy.
It's unfair.
I can't do it anymore.
Well, we sweat a lot.
Let's take a bath together.
I agree.
Let's go.
It's OK. Let's take a bath.
Which way? Hurry up.
It's been a long time since I've been here.
It's so dirty here.
You have to clean it up.
It's so noisy.
It's not good.
How do you feel?
I was washed by my senior.
Thank you so much for washing me.
You should be grateful.
That's right.
Great.
How do you feel? Great.
What's up?
He's getting bigger.
Wow, he's standing up.
He's really energetic.
Wow, amazing.
How do you feel? Good.
Great.
It's getting warmer.
How do you feel? Great.
How do you feel?
Can you feel it?
Wow!
I'm going to get up.
What?
You are so luxurious.
You are so cute.
I'm washing you like this.
There is no senior like you.
You are so kind.
You are right.
It's true.
It's soft, isn't it?
Does it feel good? It's warm.
It's standing well.
It's so smooth.
It's rubbing.
It's standing well.
Wow, it's amazing.
Wow, it's a luxury.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It's really sandwiched.
It's amazing.
Oh, it's amazing.
Wow, amazing!
Feels good!
How old are you?
Do you wanna do it?
Wow! You are so big!
You are so great!
Wow, awesome!
That's awesome, Mom!
It feels so good!
Wow, it feels so
good! I feel so good.
I'm going to wash your face with you.
Wow!
I'm going to wash your mouth, too.
I'm going to wash your breasts, too.
Oh, no.
It's so tight.
It feels good outside.
It's amazing here.
It's a pampan.
It's amazing.
Can I wash my
hair? Yes, you can.
Can you do it by
yourself? Yes, I can.
Really?
I'm going to wash my hair.
Can you do it?
I'm going to put a lot
of powder on my hair.
Is it hot? Yes, it's hot.
Really? It's so big.
Wow!
Do you like it?
Wow! It's very hard.
Wow!
It's good, isn't it?
My butt is shaking.
It's amazing.
Whose butt is it?
My butt?
What's the next butt?
Oh!
Do you want to go?
Wow!
Oh!
This butt feels good.
Do you feel good?
Do you feel your buttocks?
Yes, I feel good.
You feel great.
Everything feels good.
Wow, you are so sexy.
You are so sexy.
I didn't know you liked
your buttocks so much.
It's so cool.
You still have a butt.
Is it OK?
It's everyone's butt.
Everyone's butt.
Is it OK?
Can you do it?
Wow.
How do you feel?
You look so comfortable.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Thank you so much.
It was beautiful,
wasn't it? Yes, it was.
It's so nice!
Look at this!
Wow!
It's so big!
I can't reach it, so I'll put it here.
Let's go to the next one!
Let's go!
Come on!
It feels so good.
It's the best.
It's worth working hard.
It's true.
I don't know why Hayashi is doing his best.
It's tough.
I'm not doing my best.
I'm sorry.
It's true.
Do your best more.
Yes.
It's true.
I have to do my best.
Why don't you take a bath?
What?
Oh, I made him drink the water.
Did you?
Yes.
Wow, he is smiling.
Why did you make him
drink the water? I know.
He was sensitive.
I know.
He is still sensitive.
He is getting up.
He is getting up a lot.
He couldn't get up a while ago.
He couldn't get up.
They are doing it together.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It's clean now.
Yes, it is.
It doesn't smell.
I was surprised.
It's true. It's hard.
Yes, it is.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It's amazing.
Do you feel good?
It feels good, doesn't it?
I want to lick it, too.
Oh, it feels good.
The sound is erotic, isn't it?
It's dripping, isn't
it? It's amazing.
It's amazing.
Who feels the best? I do.
Who is it?
It's been a long time.
I don't want to decide.
Why?
I don't want to.
Decide.
Saki-chan.
Does it feel good?
Do you like
Saki-chan? I don't know.
You don't know?
You like all of them, don't you?
So you feel all of them.
I'm so sorry, I got too
emotional and went crazy.
Really? What does that mean?
What does that mean?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Are your boobs being patted?
Your nipples are curled up.
You feel it, don't
you? I can feel it.
How do you feel? I feel great.
It's amazing, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
It's a little scary.
It's a little hard, isn't it, Naoko?
It's a little hard, isn't it?
It's already full.
It's full.
It's fast.
It's about to burst.
Ah!
Wow!
It's amazing!
What are you doing there?
Wow!
It's amazing!
It's amazing, really.
It makes me feel good.
It's hard from the root.
Really?
It's amazing!
Wow!
I think it's going to
stick to your stomach.
I know.
It's so big.
Wow!
I'll put it on you.
You have a big face.
I think it's going to stick to your eyes.
Don't you think it's a
little too much? It's true.
Don't feel it too much
that you can't drink it.
I'm already drinking it.
It's true.
Can't you drink it? It's hot.
Do you like my breast?
What are you
doing? It's not fair.
I envy you.
You are so emotional.
I feel so good.
How's it?
Are you crying?
Hey! She's crying.
What is it? She's crying.
What's it?
Could it be? Wait.
Stop!
She's shaking!
You're crying! She is crying.
She cried a lot.
She is sick.
Aww, cute! I'm scared.
I'm scared.
You are getting more and more intense.
It's good.
Ouch! Be careful.
She's nervous.
Wow.
Be careful.
Ouch!
Ouch! It's okay.
You're doing great.
Oh, my back!
Oh, my back! I feel so bad.
I love you.
I love you. I love you so much.
I love you. I love you. I love you so much.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
Too strong, too
strong Yes, she is.
It's very strong.
It's bad, it's bad.
Feel bad?
What?
Ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah I can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
Are you ok?
Oh! I feel great.
I feel great.
Oh!
What's that sound?
Wait a minute.
I'm dizzy.
Are you dizzy?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
It is a pleasure to be
able to visit here again.
I am so happy to be here.
I'm so happy!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! It's a big one.
Wow!
It's so big!
Why? Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it's great.
Oh, I don't like it.
I feel sick.
Do you feel sick?
I feel very sick.
Wow, he is cleaning.
He is kind.
You are so kind.
You have a lot on your mouth.
Wow, your mouth is full.
It feels good.
Wow, it's coming up.
Wow, it's coming up again.
Why?
Wow.
Then, next is me.
Here we go.
Wow! It's so warm.
Thank you.
I'm going to kill you! Here.
I'm going to kill you!
It's painful!
I'm going to kill you! Here.
It's painful.
Have you ever seen a dog
running around like that?
It's so slimy!
Wow, you're so strong.
Your breasts are amazing.
Ah, it feels so good.
Wow, amazing.
Please do more.
Are you going to do that?
Here?
Nice!
I'm going to do it myself.
Oh, my!
Oh, my boobs! It's heavy.
It's heavy.
You are not only looking at
me, you are also patting me.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, it's coming out!
Wow, it's coming out!
Wow, it's coming out so much!
I want to do it well.
I'm sleepy.
When did you get up?
It's my turn next.
It's not fair that you
two put your seniors first.
I didn't put mine either.
Wow!
Wow! Here it comes.
Ahh! Here it comes.
It's very good.
It's coming out!
Wow!
It's coming!
It feels good! I feel so good.
Let's go.
Look!
Wow! It's amazing.
It's so smooth.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Wow! It feels good.
It feels good.
One, two, three.
It's fun.
Look!
Wow!
It's a bear!
It's so nice!
Wow!
There are so many of them!
Wow! Wow! Good boy.
He is my only grandfather.
Good boy.
You are amazing.
He is going to go again.
Wow! It's shaking!
Wow!
Concentrate more!
It's so good!
How much is it?
It's so good! I got it.
Is it good? It's good.
Thank you.
Hi, everyone.
What's left?
The head of the family is waiting.
Can I put it in?
Are you going to
put it in? Oh, it hurts.
Man, it feels so good!
It feels so good!
Oh, that feels good!
Oh, I feel good! I'm so nervous.
I feel so good.
It's really getting in.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
It's amazing.
It's going in,
isn't it? It's going.
It's amazing.
I feel good.
Oh, my God.
I would like to be stronger.
You are already in the bath.
Yes, it's bath! It feels good.
You are bumping your head.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry You are still a baby.
You are so cute.
How old are you?
You don't have to be angry.
You love me, don't you?
How do you feel?
You are so soft.
You feel great.
You are the best.
You are so cute.
I'm scared.
I feel so good.
How do you feel? I feel so good.
It's the best!
It feels so good!
How do you feel?
You are in front of me.
You are great.
Go, go, go.
This is the first time I've ever
seen such a cute baby in my life.
I'm so happy to see
such a cute baby in my life.
We are going to make
Hayashi-no-ko, aren't we?
It's starting again.
Here we go.
Wow, it's coming out.
Wow, it's amazing.
Can you see it? I can't see it.
It's intense.
It's amazing.
You are so cute!
Go! Go!
You can do it!
You are so cute!
Wow! Your voice is echoing!
Are you OK?
Your voice is echoing all over the place.
Wow! You look so happy!
Wow!
It's gone!
It's coming out more and more.
What a life!
It's all gone,
isn't it? It's gone.
It was the best!
It was terrible!
Really?
You were so excited!
I was so excited!
Ah!
You are still standing!
Are you sad?
What's wrong?
I left the door unlocked.
As a boss, you have to take
care of your subordinates.
Didn't you like it?
What do you mean?
What do you mean? Like this.
What are you imagining?
Do you want to do it again?
I want to do it again.
I'm fine.
You were a little too excited just now.
You can do it again.
Yes.
Give me a kiss.
Kiss!
Oh, it's melting.
Oh, it's hard for everyone here.
It feels good just to kiss you.
Chikkun, do you want me to rub your back?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're moving your hips
because you're so happy.
Do you like it? I like it, too.
Do you like it, too?
It's cool, isn't it?
Oh, it's coming out.
I'm sorry.
You are so big.
You are amazing.
Do you want me to touch you?
I want you to touch me.
What do you think of me?
Just a boss?
We're a good match, aren't we?
We're the best, aren't we?
Yes.
I'm so nervous.
You told me that you like me the most.
I'd like you to be in
charge of this project.
Really?
I'll leave it to you.
I love you.
It's hot.
You like it, don't
you? It's hot.
It's delicious.
You were about to eat it.
You have to eat it.
Why do you open your mouth?
I'm a little embarrassed.
I wanted you to do this.
Eat it.
Oh, there you are.
It's OK, Hayashi-chan.
Does it feel good?
Your butthole is twitching.
Oh, great.
Oh, it feels good.
I'm sorry.
I feel sick.
You look like a pervert.
I can't do it.
It was hot, wasn't
it? Yes, it was.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
The baby is crying.
똥トリ トリトリXув ウォーカー・ひドラマ
うぅー
うぉぉ〜 ううっ
うん ん ん うーん
ぬろん
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
The baby's crying is so cute.
【The sound of a baby sleeping】
Can you lick me?
Are you sleeping?
【The sound of a baby sleeping】
Hello everyone!
This is my first time
going live on YouTube.
I'm so tired.
Wow, it's amazing.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
I want to sleep more.
I feel so good.
I don't want to wake you up.
I'm so relieved.
I'm sorry.
You're hungry, aren't
you? I'm hungry.
It feels good.
You've been scared all the
time, haven't you? Yes, I have.
Oh, dear.
Oh, no.
Don't laugh.
Shall I put it in your
mouth? It's all right.
You wanted to put it in
your mouth, didn't you?
Yes.
Oh, it's coming out.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it feels good even if I do it slowly.
Oh, my god!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Don't hurry up.
Oh, no.
Easy.
Oh, no!
I feel very uncomfortable
even though I just touched you.
I feel uncomfortable even
though I just touched you.
Oh, my god!
It feels so good.
But I'm going to leave soon.
I'm tired.
Let's get married.
I think it's a good idea.
You are too close to me.
No, you can't do that.
Oh, You must be tired, dear.
Oh, that's it, hang in there, dear.
Oh, I love it! Oh, oh, oh, oh.
I love it! Oh, nice.
え、すごい。
あ、気持ちいい。
あ、すごい。
すごい。
気持ちいい。
あ、やばい。 You are going to puke.
I'm going to puke.
Let me out of the baby's belly.
I'm so worried.
You are out of the baby's belly.
What if the baby comes to me?
What should I
do? I'll marry you.
Let's get married.
Even if I can't have a baby.
Can you do it? I can do it.
I can do it.
Please hold me.
I'm holding you.
It's open.
Please.
Is the door open?
Hayashi?
Yes.
What?
Hayashi?
What are you doing?
What's wrong? Nothing.
I was about to sleep.
Were you?
Yes.
I couldn't sleep either.
Oh, is that so? You're awake.
What?
Is it bad?
Oh, no, it's totally fine.
Oh, you're awake.
You couldn't sleep at all today.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, yes, that's true.
What did you do in the morning?
Well, I just took a walk.
Where did you go? So? Oh, no.
I just got a cold.
Oh, you got a cold.
Yeah, I thought it was a little hot.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
I see.
I was just thinking about Hayashi.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Aren't you going to do it?
What? You're strong.
What? With me.
What?
We are getting old,
aren't we? Yes, we are.
That's why it's good to do
something like this once in a while.
That's true.
Hayashi's kiss is soft.
Really?
Yes.
Your kiss is amazing.
Really?
Yes.
I'm happy.
You can feel my nipples.
Well, yes.
I see.
Yes.
Don't you think you're a bit chubby?
Oh, really?
Yes.
How is it? Do you feel your nipples?
I like to be licked.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I don't think you look like that, but
when I look at your nipples, I can tell.
Do you like to sleep?
I like that, too.
What? You like it? You're a do-it-all.
No, I'm not.
You're a do-it-all.
Oh, no.
What? You're already standing up.
Well, I'm going to stand up.
You have to sink down.
I have to sink down?
It's hard, isn't it? Well, yes.
My nipples are a little weak.
Your nipples?
You're a pervert.
Wow, it's so nice here.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's so big.
Since we're already doing this,
do you want to go out with me?
Go out with you?
Can I? Yes, you can.
Are you okay with me?
Yes.
How do you feel? I feel great.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad.
It's so big.
I don't know where to start licking.
It's so good.
Does it feel good?
It feels so good.
I can feel it.
I can feel it a lot.
That's bad.
That's bad?
It feels so good.
You look like you feel it a lot.
Yes.
I've never seen your face like that.
Touch my boobs.
Can I?
Yes.
How is it? It's good.
It's erotic.
Is it erotic?
I'm a little nervous because
it's just the two of us.
Yeah, it's kind of embarrassing.
Yeah, it's embarrassing.
Do you have something in your hand?
No, it's nothing.
Nothing? Nothing.
I just want to kiss you.
Can I touch you?
Yes.
Really?
Are you happy?
Are you happy? I love you.
You are small and cute.
You are so small.
Am I small?
What's wrong with your butt?
My butt is itchy.
You are erotic.
You are very erotic.
Do you like your
butt? Yes, I do.
Really? I love my butt.
Really?
Yes.
Can I look at your butt more?
What?
Wow, it's amazing.
This guy is really erotic.
Is he?
Yes.
Really?
Can I?
Yes.
How is it?
He's really erotic.
Is he?
Is it erotic?
Yes.
Really? That's great.
Where did you learn to lick like that?
How is it?
It feels so good.
Wow.
Your butt is so soft.
Really?
Can I touch it?
I want to put it in, but is it okay?
Because we are dating.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Oh.
No problem.
Really?
Yes.
I'm happy to hear that from Hayashi.
Well, but... Will you
ride on my back?
Yes.
Oh, great.
I'm going in.
Oh.
Oh, it feels so good!
Hey, where are you looking at?
What? Oh, I'm sorry.
You're staring at me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just look at me.
Oh, okay.
It feels good.
Does it? It feels good.
Me too.
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
I'm going to puke!
Wait, wait!
But, which one?
Will I be able to puke?
What?
Say it out loud!
Wait, wait!
What should I do?
Oh, I'm going to puke!
Puke!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm going to puke!
Oh!
Ah… Ah… Ah…
Oh my god!
You've got something white.
Ah, it comes out.
Oh, this deep?
Hey, Hayashi!
What are you doing?
I'm your friend.
Tachibana?
Hey, you said you were
going to marry me, didn't you?
Um... Hey, Hayashi,
I didn't hear that.
Um... You said it.
You said you were going
to marry me, didn't you?
What?
You made a baby, didn't you?
It might be born.
Um... I don't know what to do.
Hey, you can't do that.
You can't do that at all.
You can't do that.
You're the worst.
Let me do it.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You just licked me, didn't you?
I'm going to do it, too.
Touch me.
What? Touch me.
Which one do you like
better? I don't know.
Which one do you like better?
Which one?
Oh, it feels good.
It doesn't feel good.
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going to overwrite it.
I'm going to overwrite it because
I put it in Mizuki-san's room.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't
it? It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Say you love me the most.
Say it quickly.
I love you.
Say it.
Say you feel good.
I feel good.
You are the best.
I'm going to take off my shoes.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I felt like I had a hard time.
I've been through a lot.
It's hard.
It feels good.
I'm going to die.
You have a lot of space.
I'm tired.
My ankles are shaking.
Yes, yes.
You look so comfortable.
Stick to the bottom.
Oh, it feels good.
There, there.
Stick to the bottom.
No, no.
Stick more.
Can you show me your face?
You look so happy.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good? My baby.
..
My baby feels better, doesn't it?
Tell me I'm the best.
Tell me my baby is the best.
My baby is the best, isn't it, Hayashi?
My baby feels better, doesn't it?
My baby feels better, doesn't it, Hayashi?
My baby feels great,
doesn't it? I love my baby.
My baby is sleeping.
I love my baby.
Give me the baby.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Are you going to give birth again?
Give me the baby.
What are you doing?
You made me cry again.
I hope you can have a baby.
I want to have a baby again.
I want you to make me cry a lot.
You'll go out with me, won't
you, Hayashi? It's delicious.
It's delicious.
I have two of them.
I'm going to eat them all.
I'm going to eat two.
Are you awake,
Hayashi? Yes, I'm awake.
Did you decide which
one Mizuki and I should do?
What?
Did you decide?
No, I can't decide.
Come on, decide.
Which one was better?
Which one do you like?
Do you feel good? It's me.
It's me, isn't it? It's suspicious.
Which one do you want to eat?
Which one do you
want to eat? OK, I got it.
Mizuki-san and I will put them alternately.
Let's decide which one is better.
OK, let's do it.
You have to decide properly.
Which one is better?
It's definitely me.
Which one is better? I'm ready.
Let's decide.
Which one do you want to start with?
Hurry up and decide.
I'll start with Mizuki.
Okay, hurry up.
I'll start.
It's my turn next.
I'll look at you carefully.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Are you okay? It feels good.
What does it feel
like? It's good.
I can't touch you.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's good.
It's so hot.
Ouch!
Did you go to the
doctor? No, I didn't.
I have to do it at the office.
What?
Can I try from the back?
I can't help it.
Hurry up.
My butt.
Oh my god!
Oh my god! I can't do it.
I can't do it.
I'm going to sleep in this bag.
I'm going to sleep in your back.
Ahh, it's so good.
This is so good.
This is the best.
I'll give you a hand.
Don't forget to wash your face.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good.
Give me your face.
Give me your hand.
Oh, it's going away.
It feels good.
It feels good, doesn't
it? It feels good.
How do you feel, Tachibana?
Which one do you feel good?
Which one do you feel better?
Have you decided? Put this in.
This one? Let's compare.
Let's compare.
I feel better.
Do you feel
better? I feel better.
How is your neck? I feel better.
I'm sorry.
I feel so good.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so glad to hear it.
I feel so good.
Don't cry. I feel so good.
How do you feel, Hayashi?
Which one do you feel good?
How is it? Which one do
you like? OK, next is me.
I can't decide at all.
How do you feel?
I'm often told that I close my eyes.
I close my eyes, too.
Hurry up!
How do you feel?
Hurry up! It feels good.
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's good.
Do you like it?
Is it good?
It's good, isn't
it? It's so good.
It's so good.
feel good how do you feel?
hmm, feel good
how do you feel? well.
.
It feels so good!
Oh, no!
What?
I'm going!
You're going?
No!
Don't go!
I'm going!
No!
I'm so glad to hear that.
You're crying a lot.
I'm not ready yet.
I'm so glad to hear that.
It's a pain.
You can still do it, can't you?
You're doing great.
Let me hold you.
I'm worried.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good, doesn't it, Akari?
My baby feels good,
doesn't it? Oh, no.
Ah, I feel good, too.
Choco, let's go.
Which one do you feel better?
I want you to pet me more.
I see.
I feel good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
You're standing up well.
It's mine, isn't
it? It feels good.
It feels good for me, too.
It's so hot!
I feel sick!
I'm about to die.
I can't do this.
I'm getting more and more swollen.
I'm here!
Let me out!
Let me out from the back!
You look like you're having a hard time.
I'm so glad.
You're crying a lot.
You're crying a lot today, Hayashi.
What's wrong?
Can you still do it?
Can you?
Have you decided which one is better?
Have you?
I think they are both the best.
What is that?
You can't decide?
You can't decide? Ok, I got it.
Let's do it on a Sunday.
I'll be the guest, and you'll be the guest.
What about Sunday? Sunday.
..
Let's have Hayashi-kun decide.
I'll do it.
It's Monday, so I'll be the guest.
I'm going to do more.
Today is the first day of the school year.
So I'm going to do more.
Today is Monday.
What?
Don't take my comment.