Hi, mom.
I'm innocent.
I'm being investigated
and I'm living alone.
Mom...
Mr. Tateo Haneda?
I didn't do anything wrong.
What's going on?
Why?
You can't take such a serious action.
But...
Let's go.
I didn't do anything.
Why don't you quit smoking?
I didn't quit smoking.
Give up already.
We have proof that you are a
member of the drug organization.
I don't know anything about that.
Then, what were you doing in
such a place in the middle of the day?
No, I was just doing my job.
You were really trying to sell
drugs, weren't you? No, I wasn't.
That's enough.
Where is the place where drugs
are manufactured and traded?
What kind of secret organization
is involved? I don't know.
I didn't do it.
Do not deny it.
No, I didn't do it.
It's not good to deny it.
Spit it out.
No, I really didn't do it.
Kurata-san.
That.
Yes.
Do it quickly.
What are you saying?
Aren't you hungry?
If you want to eat, you have to confess.
No, I really didn't do it.
Stop it.
What are you doing? Admit it.
No, I don't.
Do you still want to play
Shira-Uki-Uki? No, I don't.
OK, I'll give you a lot of time.
I'll let you play all at the end.
No, I don't.
I can't believe it.
Why did this happen?
Do you have the courage
to tell the truth? But I.
..
It will be easier if you tell the truth.
Come on, stand up.
I'll help you.
I'm sorry.
Hey, how long are you
going to keep doing this?
What?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Well, I have one.
Don't you feel sorry for her?
Don't you want to admit
your sin and reset your life?
Don't you think so?
No, I didn't do it.
I see.
You don't confess no matter what happens.
Then, we have no
choice but to go out today.
What are you
doing? Go on a date.
I'm investigating.
Are you done?
You don't open your mouth,
so I'm going to ask your body.
I didn't do it.
Shut up.
I know you didn't do it.
Why?
Don't think your body is honest.
Don't move.
Be quiet.
You are listening to me.
I am listening to you.
I won't exclude you forever.
I am not doing it.
You are persistent.
Oh,
What?
What? Move your hand.
You are already standing.
I am standing.
You are standing in such a situation.
How can you stand up on your own?
You are so mean.
I didn't do anything.
You made your nipples so hard.
What are you thinking about?
I think people who don't
admit their sins are fat.
I don't care.
You don't care?
Don't you understand?
Why do you say such a thing?
I don't say such a thing.
How long are you going to
keep saying such a thing?
Are you still saying such a thing?
Oh, you are right.
In such a situation, how long are you going
to keep saying such a thing? You are right.
If you were a normal
man, you wouldn't stand up.
No, it's not like that.
You're a villain to be able
to stand in such a situation.
No, I didn't do it.
Don't deceive us.
Really.
I didn't do it.
No matter how long it
takes, I'll make you spit it out.
Did you want to spit it out?
No, I really didn't do it.
Please be quiet.
Don't you want to confess
your sin? No, I don't.
You have to admit your sin.
Otherwise, you will lose your body.
No, I don't want to lose my body.
Or do you want to be tortured forever?
No, I don't want to be tortured.
Come here.
Don't sit here.
Look at this.
It's too big.
Did you do this?
No.
Yes, yes, yes.
You skipped work and watched something
so disgusting, didn't you? No, I didn't.
Oh, I made a mistake.
You didn't skip work. You were waiting
for a deal, weren't you? No, I wasn't.
You were waiting for a deal,
but you looked so relaxed.
No, I wasn't. I was just skipping work.
You are so noisy.
Are you still not talking?
Don't you want to
cut it? No, I don't.
I'll make you want to cut it.
No, I don't.
Oh, you're really doing it.
Are you happy? No, I'm not.
Show me your happy face.
Show it to me.
I'm not angry.
You are angry.
You want me to kiss
you, don't you? No, I don't.
You don't confess your love, but
you open your mouth to kiss me.
No, I don't.
You are strange.
I'm not angry.
I'm sorry.
You can't say anything.
You can't go against me.
I'm investigating you.
Look at this.
This is my embarrassing nipple.
Pink!
Can't you change your girlfriend's nipple?
Don't you play with me?
It doesn't matter.
Poor you.
How do you feel? Do you
want to confess? No, I don't.
I don't know.
Say everything.
You look like you are in pain.
You don't need this
because it's a check-up.
Take it off.
You are wearing ugly panties.
Why are you like this? Tell me.
I don't know.
You don't know, do you?
Why are you like
this? I don't know.
Why?
You don't know?
Then I'll make you understand.
Do you want me to do it with you?
You must have won because you thought of
something unpleasant in our investigation.
No, I didn't.
You didn't?
No.
Do you want to do it together?
What's up?
What do you think?
If you don't want to be
trapped in this house,
tell me which organization you belong to.
I don't know. I can't tell you.
Well, it can't be helped.
I'll let you have fun for a while.
I don't know if it's a good idea or not
I'm sorry.
I'll keep torturing you until you give up.
No.
No matter how long I keep torturing
you, I don't know how long I can bear it.
I told you.
We've heard so many times
that villains don't do that.
I've heard it many times.
Everyone says so.
It's great.
You just pretend to hate it.
I don't know.
But you are good at acting.
No, I'm not.
I can't trust you.
What's wrong?
Your son is being made my footwear.
It's not fair.
Oh, you feel good with your legs.
You are still big. I'm embarrassed.
Do you like to be treated like this?
No, I've never been treated like this.
You are not happy, are you?
My neck feels good.
How long can you bear it?
I wonder if you can do it.
It's about time.
What's wrong?
This is your leg.
What?
Is your leg that good?
Are you going to do it? Stop it.
Why are you making such a sad face?
Did you think you could do it?
Did you have a
fever? No, I didn't.
Oh, it hurts.
Like this?
Like this? I'm sorry.
You can do it this time.
Do you want to
do it? No, I can't.
Do you want to do
it again? No, I can't.
How do you feel? No, I can't.
Oh, I see.
Did you want to
go? No, I didn't.
You couldn't go? No, I couldn't.
You're so cute.
I'll let you go if you
confess all your sins.
Really?
I didn't confess my sins.
You're so cute.
I'll let you go if you
confess all your sins.
You're breathing, aren't you?
She's just breathing, but she's trembling.
Her hands are so warm.
It's not like this yet.
The golden egg is jiggly.
She's eating a lot of noodles.
Hurry up and tell me everything.
Why don't you just give it to me here?
You're holding back, aren't you?
Don't go, just tell me.
I'm not doing it.
How about this?
You like it, don't
you? No, I don't.
Just tell me.
I'm not doing it.
Oh, you ate it all.
You are so patient.
Yes, I am.
How long will you be so patient?
I won't finish until you finish all.
At that time, Chimpanzee
may have never met.
I don't know.
Are you sure?
Are you protecting your friends?
I don't have any friends.
You have.
You don't like it,
do you? No, I don't.
Then you should tell me.
I don't know.
Tell me.
You can't tell me? I don't know.
I was just doing my job.
Your job?
You were just watching TV, weren't you?
What? Or is it your job to
make a noise? No, it's not.
There is no such a stupid job.
I used to do such a job.
Make a noise?
No.
Watch porn?
No, I was just touching.
That porn is such a camouflage.
I'm sorry. I can't forgive you anymore.
Forgive me? You can't forgive me?
Is that what everyone has been saying?
You guys say you can't forgive me.
But everyone was a criminal.
You were the first one. You are the
same, aren't you? We won't be deceived.
Come on.
You didn't come out. You poor thing.
What's wrong with you?
You've got a cramp in your leg.
Oh, it hurts.
Does it hurt?
You've been looking at this
for a while, haven't you? No, it's.
..
Look, it's a woman's body.
You've been looking at a woman's
body, so it's a man's body, isn't it?
No...
I'm telling you to look at
it, so look at it properly.
Your nipple.
Your nipple and my nipple.
You just made a good voice.
Your nipple is getting harder.
That's right.
Do you feel good? No, I don't.
Your brain will be cut off
if you hold it for too long.
I'll give you a lot of
tickling from this side.
From the left and right?
That's good, isn't it?
Can you stand it?
I haven't done it yet.
You're such a pervert.
I think you'll get a
lot of dust if I hit you.
Don't you have any other sins?
No, I didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything, did you?
I really didn't.
Really?
I wonder if you did.
You're blushing.
You're sweating.
It's embarrassing.
That's cool.
What's wrong?
Does it feel good,
Chin-chin? No, not that.
What's not good? Don't.
..
Do you want me to hit you on the neck?
Do you want me to
pinch your ear? Please.
..
What?
Are you gonna
come out? I like it.
Do you want to be a
warrior at Torihiro Festival?
No...
Tell me.
If you say, I forgive you.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Did you say, you're about to say?
Yes.
You're about to
confess? No, I didn't.
Say it.
I didn't, so I don't know.
I'll give you a pill.
You're about to say?
You're about to go?
No, I'm about to go.
Yes.
You're not about to say?
No, I don't know.
You don't know?
You're an idiot.
Come on, ring the bell.
Hurry up and do it.
Hurry up.
I got it.
I'm telling you to do it, so do it.
Do you want to be blamed for
unnecessary sins? Come here.
Don't sleep.
You look good.
You don't have the courage to say it yet.
I don't know what to say
because I haven't done it yet.
You are persistent.
Then, I'll torture you.
No, I don't want to.
You don't have to say anything.
I can't breathe.
Wait a minute.
If you don't want to do it, say it now.
Did you do it? Didn't
you do it? I don't know.
You don't know,
do you? I didn't do it.
What?
What? I can't hear what you're saying.
I can't hear you.
Pochinchi.
Binbin.
Look at you.
How was it? Was it painful?
No, it was painful.
You didn't say anything.
I thought you didn't need
such a white-faced mouth.
I think it's about time
for you to take the test.
Can I take a picture of you?
You are still a baby, aren't you?
You are still not good at
it, aren't you? I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Can you forgive me?
Why? Why?
I didn't say that.
Hey.
It's not over yet.
Until you say it.
I didn't do it.
If you don't say it quickly,
you'll really suffocate.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Huh?
I'll say it now.
I didn't do it.
I really didn't do it.
Oh, no. You are getting wet.
How do you feel?
Do you feel better? No, I don't.
Please forgive me.
Do you want to be wet?
No.
Do you want me to lick you?
Let me see your tongue.
You don't want me to lick you, do you?
I said let me see your tongue.
I'll make you wet more.
Oh, it's hot.
You're having fun, aren't you?
You haven't said it yet
because you want to continue?
It's painful, isn't it?
Because it's torture.
If you don't want to, don't say
you're the culprit of the drug deal.
No, I don't want to.
This is the last one.
I'm not doing it.
I've never done such a thing.
You have a bad sense of direction.
Do you want me to make
it easy for you to say?
Easy for me to say?
What do you want me to do?
If I do it gently like this,
you may feel a little painful.
I don't know yet.
I don't know how to do it.
You don't know?
Then I'll teach you.
Does it feel good?
You like it, don't
you? A little.
Does it feel good?
Do you want to come
here? No, you can't.
I'll give you a massage.
You love me, don't you?
I'll make you feel good.
Does it hurt? No, it doesn't.
I can't do that.
Does it hurt?
You thought you could do it, didn't you?
You don't admit it, do you?
Do you want to be treated
gently like this? No, I don't.
I didn't ask you to lick me.
What?
You're the only one who's been chasing me.
Really?
You're the only one.
It's strange.
Wait a minute.
Hurry up.
Give me a pen.
Hey.
Hurry up.
Hey!
It's been a long time.
I feel so bad.
Why did you move your
waist so much? I don't know.
Let me see your tongue.
You're moving your waist a lot.
You're scared. You're running away.
You're going to throw it away.
Did you want me to continue?
Hey, Kurata-san.
Can I control you? Please.
Are you sure?
I'll do my best.
Be prepared.
Are you sure?
I don't know how long I can say that.
Ah, ah, ahh…
Ahh…
It's okay, I'll be nice
and gentle… Oh, I can't…
You can't, really?
Do you wanna confess your love?
No, no, I've never confession my love.
Oh, so I see.
Do you want to confess
your love to Seisaku-san?
No, it's not like that.
But you know,
we can't just say, ''Oh, I
didn't do that. Thank you.
'' We're not that stupid.
Right?
Don't go on your own.
We'll do whatever we want.
Are you sure?
Do you want me to do it?
Yes.
Oh, it's so sticky.
Are you saying you haven't
done it? No, I haven't.
Why are you saying that?
You have done it! I haven't.
It's hot.
Stop it.
It's so hot.
How long are you going to sleep?
Are you not going to tell me?
Masa, I really don't know anything.
You don't know anything?
We are professionals.
We won't stop until we admit everything.
That's right.
Look.
Don't you say it yet?
Even this?
Even this? Say it.
I haven't done it yet.
Why do you say such a thing?
Can't you say even this?
Don't you have anything to do with it?
Hey!
Is this OK?
What's wrong with you? It hurts.
Does it hurt?
Is this OK?
What's wrong with you?
Don't move around.
It's moving, so the cloak
will shift, won't it? Wait, this is.
..
Ai-chan!
You want to go, don't you?
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go.
I'll go, so...
If you want to go, say everything.
Oh, it's hot.
Then, can I stay in the
hell forever? Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's hot.
He is quite patient.
Oh, it's the best.
Asumi-san.
Yes?
Let me examine you next.
Kurata-san, do you want to operate on me?
Yes.
Good.
This time, I'll operate on
you and make you spit it out.
You can't keep silent this
time, can you? I didn't do it.
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
I'm really not doing anything.
Let's continue until I tell you the truth.
That's right.
These are the days of hell.
How much harder are
you in the same situation?
Hey.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Tell me the truth.
You feel good, you look alive, and
you committed a crime, didn't you?
I sold you, didn't I?
I sold you, didn't I? Tell me.
We don't want to blame you.
We just want to help you.
I didn't do anything.
We just give you a
chance to tell the truth.
You are so kind, aren't you?
I didn't do anything.
We give you a chance to confess.
We are so kind to you.
This is the first time I've ever
seen such a large number of babies.
Wow, look at the nipples.
What's going on?
I think I'm going to wake up.
Wake up?
Are you going to wake up?
What?
Tell me everything before you wake up.
Come on.
Oh, my neck.
What's wrong with you?
You feel good when I
touch you with my feet.
How about your ears?
Here?
Do you feel good?
Don't just focus on me.
I brought a stick.
Your back is getting better.
You did it, didn't
you? No, I didn't.
What do you think?
You are such a bad liar!
You are about to show
your misdeeds, aren't you?
Do you think you can show your
misdeeds by doing bad things?
What are you doing?
I can't do it anymore.
If you can't do it, confess it.
I can't do it.
Come on.
Hey.
What?
He said he would go.
Why did you make him go?
What the hell are you doing?
Did you say it?
I said it, didn't I?
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, you are drooling.
Don't do it.
You are eating ramen without permission.
You are the worst.
This guy is so annoying.
Hey, can I continue? Please.
How selfish you are!
Who told you to serve noodles?
Sorry, I didn't know.
I told you to confess if you serve noodles.
No, I didn't.
And you let him in.
I just said it.
I'm sorry for making
you feel uncomfortable.
I don't know you just said it.
But, you are a pervert like you.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
As expected, it's a little bit of
blood, but it's a little bit of blood.
Why are you making it so hard?
I really can't do it.
I can't do it.
Hurry up and talk about everything.
It's going to be easier.
Hey!
Do you feel pain when I tighten
your neck like this? No, I don't.
No, I don't.
Say it.
You'll get drunk.
No, I don't.
You'll become self-absorbed.
I can't go any further.
Why not?
You just have to say it.
What?
What? You're not going to say it yet?
Like this? Is this how you do it?
What? Are you going to say it?
Are you going to say it?
I think I'm going to say it.
Say it before you take it off.
I can't. I can't.
Let me help you up.
Come on.
I'm up.
It's time for you to get up.
Oh my...
You're so clingy.
Here it comes.
How many noodles did you eat in the end?
I didn't eat any.
I didn't say anything to you,
but you did it on your own.
I can't sleep at all.
You did it.
It's hard.
You really didn't let me sleep with her.
She was lying.
I'm not lying.
I can't do it anymore.
That's enough.
That's all for today's interrogation.
What?
Today's interrogation?
Do you think it's over today?
Can I go home?
I'll continue until you say so.
Do you think you can go home?
I really didn't do it.
Please let me go home.
That's all for today.
If you run into me again,
Think about how to confess properly.
I really didn't do it.
It seems to be already boneless.
It's a pervert.
What? She came.
She looks kind.
You look like a good boy.
Don't you think it's bad to betray
such a good boy? I didn't do it.
What is this? Don't go.
This is.
..
Come on, stand up.
Come on, hurry up.
I'm sure it's a mistake.
Yes, I really don't know anything.
I believe you.
I'm really sorry to worry you.
Sake-kun, what do you want to eat when
you come back? I'll make anything for you.
Oh, I see. What should I make?
Oh, I guess I'll make grilled ginger.
Oh, grilled ginger.
You can make a lot of grilled ginger.
You can make something more expensive.
Well, I like grilled ginger.
You really like grilled
ginger, don't you, Take-kun?
Yes.
Well, I'll make a delicious grilled
ginger for you, so please come out soon.
No, I don't think I can come out soon.
That's right.
I really think this is a mistake.
Maybe you'll come out tomorrow.
I hope so.
I was really surprised when I got a
call from Take-kun's father and mother.
I see. I'm really sorry, Take-kun.
We were worried about you, too,
but I'll tell you what happened today.
It's all right.
Oh, really?
Don't look so anxious.
I just think I can go out soon.
But let's go somewhere far
away to play when you graduate.
Where do you want to go?
You said you wanted to
go to the museum, right?
I heard that there is a big
exhibition of dinosaurs now,
and it will be over in a
week, so let's go until then.
You don't have a cool face.
Yeah, that's right.
Hey, aren't you in
a daze? Yes, I am.
But I'm in such a state, so I'm upset.
But I'm glad to see your happy face.
I can't lock you up in a place like this.
You're right.
I'm worried about you.
I feel weak.
It's natural, isn't it?
To be suddenly arrested and imprisoned.
But if it's Take-kun, it's okay.
Because Take-kun is a sincere person.
He never makes a mistake as a person.
Take-kun is such a person.
Oh, I see.
I love your sincerity and
kindness, so I believe in you.
I'm sure I'll pick you up when you
go to work, so I'll dress up for you.
Maybe I can go to Astania,
so I'll prepare a lot for you.
Yeah, if you do that, I'll be saved.
You may not be able to
sleep at night in a place
like this, but do your
best and trust yourself.
I'm waiting for you, too.
I'm waiting for you.
It's time to finish the meeting.
I see.
I'm going to bed.
Bye-bye.
Let's go.
What a thrill.
What are you trying to do?
She is a good girl.
You didn't listen to me at all.
You don't know when I will come back.
Look at me carefully.
Now you can concentrate.
I'm concentrating.
It's hard, isn't it?
Look, I'm appealing to you.
You like it, don't you?
Stand up and look at me.
Don't move your legs.
Don't look at her. Look at her carefully.
I'll look at her.
You're pushing her boobs. Open your eyes.
You have to look at her. Look at her.
Closer.
You're so nice.
You're so mean.
Look, look, look.
This is it.
Touch it.
Do you want me to tickle you?
It makes you feel good, doesn't it?
I really didn't do it.
Hey, look at me.
You were talking to your girlfriend
until a while ago, weren't you?
You were over there, weren't you?
What are you doing now?
Look at your face.
Look at her face.
That's right.
Look at her lips.
What a nasty lips.
Look at me closer.
Closer.
I'm looking at you.
Are you sincere?
I heard you are sincere.
What's the matter?
No, you don't have to do that.
Look, look.
Wow, wow.
Look at this.
Nami is honest.
You're right.
Nami is honest to a woman's body.
She's honest to stimulation.
Hey, you did it,
didn't you? I didn't.
Look at your butt.
It's disgusting, isn't it?
I want to meet my girlfriend.
I didn't do such a thing.
You met your girlfriend.
You met your kind
girlfriend who believes in you.
Your nipples are so tight.
Yes.
Hey, aren't you stressed out by us
being bullied like this? No, I'm not.
I think it's better to
confess as soon as possible.
I haven't confessed yet.
If you hide the truth like
this, it's bad for your health.
I'm sorry. I didn't do it.
I didn't know you were so weak.
You were always so strong.
You said you believed in her so much.
What do you believe in? Your good standing?
You've been betraying me in front of me.
I was told that I was not stupid.
I was.
I'm not really a villain.
Or maybe I'm a conman.
You're actually a villain, aren't you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I see. You're fooling a cute girl like her.
I'm not fooling her.
I didn't know you could be such a bad guy.
You scared me.
You found out, didn't you?
What do you mean?
I think you didn't notice it
because I put ice cream on it.
How can I explain this?
This thickness, this
hardness, this sensitivity.
It's so good.
I was spoken by me a lot under the chair.
It's so bad.
There is no trace of honesty.
Who is being honest?
You should get rid of it soon.
Oh, you are drooling.
Oh, you are sleepy.
You are more honest than me.
You are right.
Honesty to stimulation.
You haven't done it, have you?
I wonder how long it will work.
I hope it's not through the board.
Ochinpo.
Oh, you were so worried
about her coming to the visit.
I didn't do anything.
You did.
I didn't.
If she was really important to you, you
wouldn't have gone back on your word.
You only know how to lie.
I didn't.
Didn't you tell her?
A liar is the beginning of a thief.
Did I really do that?
That's a lie, isn't
it? No, I didn't.
Really?
Did you tell the
truth? No, I didn't.
You're stubborn, aren't you?
Keep doing that.
Have a seat.
What are you doing?
You haven't done
anything, have you? Oh, no.
The tip of this chimpanzee seems to be wet.
What's this? I don't know.
It's wet.
Look, the hole is shaking.
It's embarrassing.
For example, until you confess,
you can't keep drinking.
That's hell, isn't it?
What's wrong with
you? I don't know.
He may become a fool.
He may lose his senses.
He is so full of energy.
You like boobs, don't you? You were looking
at Kurata-san's boobs a lot, weren't you?
Look at his boobs. Thank him.
Pat him.
You did it, didn't you? Say it.
What?
You don't say anything?
No.
You don't say
anything? I didn't do it.
Really? I didn't do it.
I really didn't do it.
I knew it.
Are you going to keep lying like that?
Where is the sincerity?
It's hot, isn't it?
Open your mouth.
Here you are, Gochan.
How do you feel?
I'll rub the remaining saliva on your face.
It feels good, doesn't it?
How do you feel?
Do you want to go?
If you let out your genitals,
I have to say, No, I didn't.
Hold on.
No, I didn't.
That's right.
You should be grateful.
I didn't do anything.
You're such a good boy.
If it were true, I wouldn't
take so much time for you.
Do you know how much
you are blessed? I don't know.
I'm sure you've heard that.
I didn't do anything.
I'm not doing it.
I don't understand what you are saying.
You look happy.
That's right.
Do you want me to help you?
Put strength in your muscles.
Your muscles are getting bigger.
Your buttocks are hot.
You are doing this, but
you are still not doing it.
How serious are you?
I really didn't do it.
I don't know anything.
How long are you going to keep saying that?
It's coming out little by little.
You came to admit your crime, didn't you?
Or what?
Do you want to take off
your stocking with your butt?
Come on!
Did you take it off?
Safe!
You are so fast.
※This is not a sound effect.
Did you do it? No, I didn't.
It's not over yet.
No, I didn't.
Did you make a
deal? No, I didn't.
You did, didn't
you? No, I didn't.
You're a good boy.
So, you admit it,
don't you? I'm sorry.
Take off your panties.
I'll make you feel pain again.
Show me all of your embarrassing parts.
Come on.
Support yourself.
Oh, you are Marumi Eda.
I'm embarrassed.
Really?
Do you intend not to
say anything even though
you are wearing such an
embarrassing costume?
Is this okay?
Do you want to try to spit it out?
It will be on your face.
Oh, it will be on your face.
Do you want to spit it out?
You did it, didn't
you? No, I didn't.
How do you feel?
Do you want to return it?
You didn't want to return it, did you?
What should I do?
Do you want to
return it? No, I don't.
Okay, then.
Let me know when you want to return it.
No, I don't.
Come on.
Do you want to
return it? No, I don't.
Do you want to go? No, I don't.
No, I don't.
Oh, you don't like the safe?
You were about to take it out?
I told you you can take it out now.
That's right.
Wow, wow.
You still don't want to take it out?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's tickling.
It must be painful.
If you are in pain, just let it go.
There is nothing good
if you keep the truth.
If you don't say it, I'll keep doing it.
What are you going to do?
How do you feel? Do you feel better?
I haven't done it yet.
You are so stubborn.
I got it.
I'll punish you again today.
Punish me?
Keep yourself in a state of tingling.
Can you hold it for a moment?
You are happy, aren't you?
There is nothing to be so happy about.
It hurts, doesn't it?
I didn't know you had such a big finger.
Have you ever been in
this state? No, I haven't.
No, you haven't.
I'm sure you'll be able to remember it.
It feels so good.
He looks like he's having fun.
I don't think he's just having sex.
That's why you don't say anything?
I'm going to sleep.
If you don't talk much,
you'll get in trouble.
I know that.
This is the first time
I've seen a cat like this.
He's so cute.
Oh, he's so cute.
You only say you didn't do it, don't you?
I really didn't do it.
You have no excuse
other than that, don't you?
You have an alibi,
don't you? I don't know.
You can't prove your innocence, can you?
If you say you didn't
do it, prove it yourself.
Yes, you are right.
Please convince us.
But you can't, can you?
You are doing it, aren't you?
Oh, it came off.
Because you move too much.
So?
Do you feel better?
How did it go? I don't know.
You don't know?
This is the only thing he says.
I really don't know.
Did someone tell you to do so?
No, it's not like that.
That kind of instruction?
No, it's not that kind of instruction.
Then I have an idea.
Idea?
You don't want to say it, do you?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to leave it as it is?
Are you going to leave it as
it is without doing anything?
You are hungry, aren't you?
Let us keep Chimpanzees
free as long as we
are in a tree and as
long as we are hereover.
You're free, aren't you?
I'll let you use your freedom.
You don't have any freedom.
Ouch!
Do you still want to open
the castle in this situation?
I don't want to.
Do you feel dizzy?
You are sincere, aren't you?
Tell me the truth.
I don't know.
You didn't tell me.
I didn't tell you, so I don't know.
You don't know?
Then,
I wonder if I should ask
you to move once in a while.
You're the only one who's
feeling better, aren't you?
Come on, get up.
Are you cold?
Come on, put your hands on me.
Or maybe you don't know where you are?
Have you never done anything like this?
Ah.
Move your body.
Why are you
silent? I'm doing it.
Like this, right?
Move your body.
Good.
I'm not doing it.
Ah.
Great.
I'm not doing it.
You're not doing it?
But, I see.
Your face and name are
on the list of people involved.
What do you mean?
Are you still going to investigate?
Investigate?
Don't be stupid.
That bridge is a good place for a deal.
This is your favorite place.
You don't have to be
there at such a good timing.
You are moving,
aren't you? Let's do it.
Let's do it.
Move your waist.
I'm tired.
It's OK.
I'm going to die.
I didn't ask you to stop.
Who said you could stop?
What?
Hey!
Who said you could stop?
What did you say?
I almost said it.
You almost said it?
Do everything as I say.
Come on, move!
I told you not to laugh.
Hey!
You are missing.
Down, down, down.
Go, go, go.
Let me go.
She's coming out.
She's coming out again.
It's great.
It's the best.
Look at her.
It's not over yet.
She's getting ready.
Are you ready to go to bed?
Are you ready?
I think you can do it.
It's perfect, isn't it?
Yes.
Put it in your mouth.
Don't be nervous.
Wow.
It's in your chest.
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good to be
tied up with a manko?
I want to do it over and over again.
Over and over again?
It's easy, isn't it?
If it's a confession, it's over and over
again, so does it feel good? It's painful.
Is it painful?
It's painful? Then confess it.
It's painful, isn't it? I didn't do it.
I'll tell you.
It's painful. You've been
attacked. That's why it's painful.
Move yourself.
Can you do it?
Move your waist.
Yes, yes, yes.
You can do it.
I'll hold your waist like this.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Give me a good massage.
I'm going to give you a good massage.
I'll support you.
Like this, right?
More, more, more, more, more, more, more.
It sounds good, but if you hit
your butt, you'll break your back.
Oh, it's painful.
Get out of the way.
I'm on your back.
I want to go home.
Don't stop your back.
Don't do it on your own.
Oh, you are so naughty.
Come on, rub your belly.
Good boy.
Show me your belly more.
Show me your tongue.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can see it well.
Oh, you are so naughty.
Come on, come on.
Use your waist.
What? Is she also acting cute like this?
Don't do it on your own this time.
Come on, come on, come on.
Harder.
Good sound.
I can hear a good sound here.
I'm glad you didn't go to the hospital.
It's not the end yet.
What do you mean?
Don't put it from behind your hip.
It's a scab, isn't it? Hurry up.
Put it in.
What are you waiting
for? Do it yourself.
I don't know.
Are you just doing it?
Do you always do this? You
can do it, can't you? I don't do it.
You don't do it. You don't do it.
I'm tired of hearing that line.
I don't do it. I don't do it.
Can't you hear a different line?
Can't you hear me?
I can't hear you.
Use your waist.
Come on.
More.
Good.
Shiro, Shiro, Shiro, Shiro.
Why are you taking a break?
Hey, move, move.
What are you doing? Aren't you tired?
Why are you saying
that? Come here.
Why do you think you can be forgiven?
You still have a long way to go.
Still?
Now that you've seen it,
it's your turn to move, isn't it?
Will you let it end?
Let it end?
What?
What do you want to end?
What do you want
to end? Hey, hey.
Do you want to confess
and end this interrogation?
Confess?
I want to end this interrogation.
Do you want to give up
and finish with this? It's OK.
You look like you feel good.
He is noisy, though.
It looks dangerous.
Open your eyes.
A little girl cries.
Are you done?
It's not the end.
Please forgive me.
It's painful, isn't it?
Then, don't say the same
thing as me, ok? Go on.
I…
You know, I
I … I committed a drug offence.
I committed a drug offence.
I committed it.
No, I didn't do that.
Open your mouth.
He doesn't say anything.
Amazing.
He likes to give us a hard time.
You like it, don't you?
Tell me the truth.
Not yet?
I really didn't do it.
Really?
Did you really
do it? I didn't do it.
Really? Really.
Really?
Did you do it? I did.
You can't do it anymore.
You're crazy.
It's terrible if you lie.
I'm not lying.
Say it.
Don't you do it? I do.
You do, don't you? No, I don't.
You do, don't you?
I want you to hold me tight.
I won't stop until you admit it.
I haven't done it since this morning.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you?
Are you out of your mind?
Are you kidding me?
You are good at doing whatever you want.
I thought it would last a little longer.
Wow, it's coming out a lot.
It's all muddy.
I thought it came out all yesterday.
That's true.
It's coming out so much in a day.
It's dripping a lot.
It's coming out a lot.
It's dirty.
Why don't you
take it out? It's dirty.
Isn't it your job to clean up dirty things?
Isn't it? Clean it up.
I'm going to put my blanket here.
I'm going to make it clean, too.
Lick it, lick it.
Me, too.
Siro, lick it.
It doesn't move at all.
Is it delicious? I'm so sorry.
I got dirty.
He is more stubborn than I thought.
He is a villain.
We have to be serious.
See you tomorrow.
I'll take good care of you.
Please forgive me.
Be quiet.
Other people will wake up.
You were careless.
Did you think you'd be
able to sleep at night?
You said you'd come back tomorrow.
But unfortunately, you're here.
It's not over until you tell me the truth.
It's a continuation of the investigation.
You're already reacting, aren't you?
Did you want to dream
about what you did today?
You're really making me nervous.
You're saying amazing things.
What?
You can't do that now.
You don't want to come out anymore?
Does it feel good?
You're more honest than I thought.
I know.
I'm still investigating.
We're in the middle of it, aren't we?
It's time for bed.
So what are you hiding?
Get out of my way.
You've already grown up.
Did you dream about us?
Are you happy?
You want me to pinch you, don't you?
Then, please do it like that.
I committed a crime.
So...
Pinch me.
Please do it comfortably.
Don't do that.
I'll hold you.
It feels good to be petted,
doesn't it? Wow, wow.
Do you want me to pet you?
It's hard to stay like this, isn't it?
You want to be comfortable, don't you?
You can't sleep in a
house like this, can you?
Well, I'll let you out, so be honest.
That's right.
Does it feel good?
Do you think you can
live in a house like this?
Why do you have such a bad breath?
Don't you think so?
Do you want me to do more?
Can you stand it?
It's bad that you don't talk.
You seem to be in a hurry to go home.
That's right.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Not yet?
It hurts, doesn't
it? It looks fun.
I want to do it, too.
Go ahead.
Come on.
You want to be refreshed, don't you?
You're tired, aren't you? You want
to sleep, don't you? Say it quickly.
It's so heavy.
Do you know what's left?
Do you want me to scratch it?
You don't think I'll forgive
you, do you? You did it.
Tell me the truth.
Do you want this?
Raise your hips.
Come on.
You look so good.
Do you feel good?
Do you like this?
Do you like boobs?
You're shaking your hips.
Look, it hurts.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Don't you know which one it is?
Mental illness?
Self-harm?
It doesn't matter.
But we are waiting for your confession.
Go with Seishizawa-san.
Do you want me to rub your butt?
You like butt, don't
you? Oh, it tickles.
It tickles.
Let me do it, too.
It tickles, doesn't
it? It tickles.
Oh, it tickles.
It tickles.
It's very hard.
Hey, you want to feel
good, don't you? Then, do it.
Did you do it?
Didn't you do it?
Are you going to get up again?
It can't be helped, can it?
Yattan, we have our own
ideas, don't we? Say it.
Say it.
You did it, didn't you?
Take it off while I'm being nice.
You can't sleep forever.
We can sleep all night.
Wow, your back.
I've got a lot of them.
How do you feel?
You did it, didn't you?
Hurry up and say you did it.
Do you want me to squeeze your butt more?
You're blushing.
I'm so sleepy.
Go to bed early.
You did it, didn't
you? Go to bed.
I know.
Are you not going to tell me?
How long are you going
to make me wait? You are.
Hurry up.
It's not over yet, is it?
Hurry up and tell me.
I know you did it.
I have all the evidence.
Did you commit
suicide? No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Hurry up and tell me.
No way.
What?
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Who said you could go?
I did say that, but...
It's a shame.
It's not a shame.
Shiku shiku shite.
We don't know anything about that.
Right?
If you don't admit your sins, it won't end.
That's good.
You're still going to go out, right?
There's still a lot in
there, right? Come on.
Let's go.
Are you going?
Are you going to say it?
Which one?
Which one is it?
What is this?
Oh my god!
What's going on?
You put salt on my face, didn't you?
I'll never forgive you.
What? Today? All night long.
Until you confess.
I can't let you go to sleep
until you finish eating.
Are you still
eating? I won't stop.
Tell me.
I'll do it more and more.
You want me to do it, don't you?
I'll do it, I'll do it.
I'll do it more.
I won't let you sleep tonight.
It's hard to spit it out.
That's right.
It's because we're weak.
Let's make her spit it out today.
I've been doing this for a long time.
I was put in a prison like this.
Don't you regret it yet?
No, it's not me.
It's not me? That's enough.
I know the story.
It's a factory.
How long are you going to keep doing this?
I don't want to, but please forgive me.
I'll make you confess
with candy and matcha.
I'm not doing it. I'm not angry.
Do you want me to keep
doing it until you get crazy?
You think it's not bad, don't you?
I'm not doing it.
Spread your legs.
It's warm.
You're going to collapse.
Please don't.
But it feels good, so it can't be helped.
I'm sure you're happy,
aren't you? Oh, wow, wow.
You're shaking.
Oh, wow, wow.
But you look happy.
You've been through so much.
Hey, really, why are you
standing like this today?
Is it because of the
sweets? I don't know.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Do you want to
talk? No, I don't.
Wow!
Do you want to see? Let me see.
Let me see.
Do you want to
change? No, no, no, no.
Are you alive?
Did you hurt?
You wanted to get up, didn't you?
Poor boy!
I can't help it.
You want to get petted, don't you?
I'll suck your golden
egg and swallow it all.
I'll make you crazy.
You don't admit it because you
want me to do it, do you? No, I don't.
Oh, you don't? You don't use your
delicate hands, do you? No, I don't.
Thank you, thank you.
I'm sorry.
The egg is coming up.
Did you want to go?
It's good, isn't it?
Hey, can you hold it
more? I don't know.
Put your hip down.
I'm going to put it in.
With your boobs.
Does it feel good?
Does it?
Does it feel good? Oh, I see.
You're enjoying it.
No, I'm not.
Then, let's add this to your boobs.
What?
Oh, that's not good.
That's right.
Take it out.
I can't.
Is it weird?
Don't pull my waist.
Who said you can pull my waist?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh What's going to happen?
What's going to happen?
I'm going to throw up.
Are you going to throw up?
Show me your guts.
Oh, no.
Oh, my.
You've become strange, Chin-chin.
You, what's wrong?
Ouch! It hurts!
What?
Ouch! It hurts! I can't do it.
Do you want to try again?
Shall we enjoy the nipple together?
Ouch! I can't do it.
Do you want to
stop? I can't do it.
Do you want to stop?
Do you want me to do it?
You don't want me to do it, do you?
You thought I asked
you to stop, didn't you?
You don't want me to stop?
Do you want me to tickle you on the chair?
Come on, come on, come on.
What's wrong with
you? You're fast.
Are you tired already?
Isn't it too early? I'm sorry.
Ouch!
What's wrong?
What's wrong? I can't do it.
It's coming from behind.
You don't have to say no.
We are good friends.
You have become brave.
You still want to do this
kind of thing, don't you?
Then, I will continue.
I'll give it to you.
Here you are.
Chin-chin.
Great! Great! Look at this.
I'm washing my hands from the bottom.
Look at this.
Look at the bottom.
You have been feeling good
for a long time, haven't you?
I want to eat it someday.
Then, you can take out as many as you want.
Good, good.
No, no.
It's coming a lot.
Let's lock it.
How is it?
Do you want to be patted?
You are being patted with your big boobies.
Like this?
Do you want to be
patted? Wow, wow, wow.
Come here, come here, come here.
I will give you a pressure with my boobies.
Look.
Are you okay? No, no, no.
Are you okay?
You have a lot of strength in your butt.
Hey, you like my butt, don't you?
Look, I'll be nice to you if you clap.
What? I don't know.
Don't you know? I don't know.
Hey, hey.
I can't say I don't know.
You're all red.
Hey, come here for a second.
I'm not asking you what it is.
I'm asking you what it is.
What is this?
What do you think
it is? I don't know.
Please show me your right eye.
Raise your right hand.
Raise the other hand.
You have a hard body.
You don't have to support me, do you?
How do you feel? I can't move.
Relax.
If you don't, you'll fall.
Hands up.
Pretend you're tied up.
Listen to me.
Shake, shake, shake, shake.
It's embarrassing.
What is this?
What's going on? I don't know.
You don't look like a human.
Look, look, look.
Wow, Marumi.
I can't hide it.
You can't hide it?
You can't let go of my hand.
Do you understand?
Your hands are tied there by your own will.
Yes.
You can't let go.
You can't hide it.
You're tied up.
You're a disgrace.
You're a loser.
You're just like that.
This is very easy to do.
What are you doing?
Do you want this? Do it now.
If you confess now, I'll forgive you.
I didn't do it.
By the way, who is manufacturing
and selling drugs? I don't know.
It's not me.
Then, who is selling
drugs? I don't know.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning my ears.
What are you cleaning?
I'm not cleaning my ears.
Who is it? It's not me.
It's me, isn't it? I don't know.
It's painful, isn't it?
Your dirty ass looks round.
I want to get up.
You can't get up?
Why don't you take a deep breath?
That's enough, isn't it?
I was about to die.
You were there just
now! That was close.
We bought this on the
Internet, so it's a bit weird.
That's enough.
It's boring.
Be a good boy.
Don't raise your head.
Lick him.
Like this, lick your tongue.
This side, too.
Like a tail.
Lick your tongue.
Turn around.
You have a hard tail.
It's flat.
You can bend it to the back.
Let's drink from this side.
It's amazing, isn't
it? Don't drop it.
What is it? Does it feel good?
Why are you trying to imitate me?
Do you want me to do it for you?
This one? This one?
Please raise your legs a little.
This is the pose of Shinshin, isn't it?
You are so cool!
What's wrong with you?
You want to confess, so you
want me to stop you? No, I don't.
You don't? No, I don't.
You don't, do you?
I'm going to confess again.
You're going to confess?
Yes.
You're such an ungrateful pervert.
I'm going to confess.
If you confess, I'll help you.
I'll take care of you.
Do you want to show it to me?
Show me! Show me! Show me!
Show me! Show me!
Show me! Ah! I knew it.
Is it more than before?
It's coming out a lot, isn't it?
Is there an angle that is easy to come out?
Wow!
This angle is good.
What?
What? What? What?
You're twitching.
What? What?
What? Don't move.
What?
What's going on?
He's rubbing his butt.
I know. I told you I know.
Look. Look. Look.
You're covered in blood.
You have a lot of blood on your face.
Look at me.
Can you bear with it?
Can you do it?
Can you do it? Not yet.
I'll pinch you with my butt.
Can you do it?
No matter what I do, it's always hard.
Let's do it together.
Oh, it's good.
It's good, isn't it?
This is good, isn't it?
It's hard, isn't
it? Hold me tight.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's dark, isn't it?
You are sensitive, aren't you?
What? Is it hard?
Do you want me to tell you the truth?
You said that again.
I'll do something hard for you.
Why don't you just spit it out?
I'm not going to tell you
how long it's going to take.
I told you I don't want it.
It's all in my mouth.
You don't want it? Confess it.
It's hard to stand up, isn't it?
If you don't like it, you have to stand up.
You're standing up without permission.
You're right.
Look, look, look.
This nipple is cute.
You want me to turn the wheel, don't you?
What do you want me to do?
Hurry up!
Turn the wheel!
What do you want me to do?
Wow!
Was it a mistake to make
it stronger? That's good.
It's in.
You wanted me to make
it stronger, didn't you?
Then, do you want to say it?
Hurry up and say it.
I'm not doing it.
Say it.
How long do you think
it will last? I don't know.
Oh, no.
It's fun, isn't it? Let's have more fun.
Let's do it.
Come here.
Move your body.
Stand up.
I see.
That's right.
I was surprised when I was inside.
Please move.
Of course.
Do you feel good? Please move.
What are you doing?
Do you think you are forgiven?
Please move more.
More, more!
That's right, that's right.
You've been moving a lot lately.
You're moving more than I am.
That's right, that's right.
You did it, didn't you?
You're the culprit, aren't you?
I'm not the culprit!
Hey!
I want to do it more.
Again!
Hey!
It's still moving.
No, no.
It's moving.
It's moving more and more.
It's coming out.
No.
What's going on with her?
Did she get out?
Oh my god!
Wow!
Did she get out? She ran away.
Wow! She got out!
Did she get out two times?
I don't know what to do.
Do you want to be more crazy?
I'm not ready yet.
Let me have fun.
I know.
Don't worry. You'll be fine soon.
I wonder if you like it.
It's still warm here, isn't it?
Oh, great! What's this?
Chinko, you're the
best! Hold my hand.
Yes.
I want more, more, more
This is good.
The hardness is totally different.
What's going on? It's good.
How about this?
Oh, it came off.
Oh, thank you.
It won't come off.
You can't do it anymore?
Do you want to do
it again? My sex is.
..
So, please don't do this to me.
Not yet.
Come here.
Here, put it in my pussy.
Put it in here.
What are you doing? Come here.
Fold your legs.
Give me a kiss. Hurry up.
Give me a kiss.
Why are you shaking your waist?
Why?
You're not moving at all, are you?
Don't make yourself nervous.
Come here.
Move, move, move, move.
Why don't you say anything?
Come on, be nice to me.
Let's go home.
Go to the limit.
You can do it.
It's not over yet.
How much ramen can you eat?
I can't take it off.
Don't take it off.
I'm taking it off.
Oh, no, no, no.
It feels good.
Oh, wait.
I'm gonna take it off.
Why are you so quiet?
I think you should be more quiet.
Come here.
This is it.
This is a great one.
What's going to happen?
What's going to happen if you
put it on your mouth? This is good.
What?
Your mouth looks very lonely.
What? Go to him.
He wants to lick
your eye boogers.
Go to him.
I'm going.
What?
I was going to let you lick me.
Come on, lick me.
That's right.
I haven't come out yet.
What? What's wrong?
I know you came out.
You came out.
Ah!
Haah!
You're all out!
I am!
Are you out? Are there
so many of you? A lot.
Ahh!
Ah!
There is still more.
Oh!
He's eating a lot.
It's not the end.
Did you think it was the end?
He's eating a lot.
It's painful, isn't it?
It's not fun to eat a lot.
Is that so?
He's eating a lot.
Chikubi, I'll do it for you.
This is great.
Chikubi, do you feel good?
Chinchin, you can do it.
I also shook my hips together.
We all feel good.
Are you tired?
What's wrong?
But Chinchin is moving.
No, no, no.
There are a lot of lumps.
It's true.
The viscosity is very high.
It's amazing.
I ate it.
I think you can still do it.
It's still hard.
What's wrong? I can't do it.
What's wrong?
You're noisy, Onikichi.
I told you to sit up.
I can't do it.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? I can't do it.
What's wrong? Oh, no.
What are you doing in
front of Momoko's eyes?
What's wrong?
What do you want to do?
You can still do it,
can't you? No, I can't.
I really can't.
You really can't?
Do you really think you can do it?
Hey, hey!
You can still do it,
can't you? No, I can't.
Wow, wow.
What? What?
What?
No, no, no!
This one?
Look!
No, no, no!
Hey!
Hey, wait a second!
Oh, oh, you're doing it again!
No, no, no, no!
Oh, my legs!
I'm telling you… I'm telling
you… No, I can't… I'm telling you…
No, no, no… I can't do it.
You're not crazy.
It's too late.
After all, I also thought a little.
Let's ask one more time.
You!
Don't you do it? I don't do it.
You said something.
I understand.
I believe you are invincible.
What?
I think it's only Shiro who does
this much and doesn't spit it out.
I'm sorry.
We were excited, too.
But, you know, your
father felt good, didn't he?
He made a lot of noise.
So I did something bad,
but I felt good, and I felt good,
so I have a lot of things
to apologize for next time.
Well, I did a pretty bad
thing, so if you'd like to
apologize again, I'll
take care of it at any time.
I'm going to investigate.
Well, that's what it is.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to investigate.
Well, good job.
You can go home without permission.
Well, then.
I was told that I would be
investigated at any time.