It's been a long time since we had a date.
I know.
What if my wife finds
out? No, it's okay.
My wife is in quarantine at home now.
So I came here with two people today.
I'm looking forward to it.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, the weather is good and I
want to go on a date in the city.
Have you been busy at the lounge?
I haven't been able
to shift at all recently.
I've been busy with school.
I'm going to graduate school next year.
Do you have a future?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
I haven't decided yet.
But I want to be with you.
Cool!
You don't come here,
do you? No, I don't.
I'm happy that I'm special.
I'm so excited.
Everyone is watching us.
Let's show them our love.
I'm so excited.
Because I dressed up too much.
That's right.
Everyone is watching us.
I'm so excited.
By the way,
I bought a lot of clothes for you.
Let's go to the beach!
Do you want to buy it?
Yes, I do!
Do you have it?
Do you want it?
No, I'm looking for it.
Are you looking
for it? Yes, I am.
I'm happy to walk with such a nice man.
Let's go to the beach!
Let's go!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it, too.
What should I choose?
Which one do you want to see?
I like many things.
What do you like?
I like expensive things.
It's better to be high.
It's better to look at it from a distance.
I'm getting excited.
Everyone is looking at it.
The people down there
are looking at it, too.
Look, they're looking at it.
I'm making it look good.
I'm tall, so if I do this, I
won't be in the picture at all.
It's cute.
Do you have a favorite color
of clothes you always wear?
I don't know, but white is cute, too.
White looks good on you.
Cute.
Is it famous?
It's a famous one.
It's cute.
It's an acromium.
It's a gore-tex, so
it's suitable for fishing.
It's suitable for fishing.
There are many novel items.
There are a lot of items.
If you take off the back
zipper, you can wear it like this.
There is also a plastic part on the shoes.
You can customize it.
You know a lot.
I know.
I have something.
You know a lot.
What is this place?
What is this?
This is a synthetic dynamite.
Wow, it's amazing.
It's synthetic, so you can make it bigger.
It's good.
You can make it like this.
Can I make it like
this? Yes, you can.
It's flashy.
Is it too flashy?
Is it too flashy? It's so cute.
Let's go to see the clothes.
Let's go to see the clothes..
Fukura,Fuku What?
Do you wanna buy some clothes?
Yes.
You look artistic.
You are amazing.
It's amazing.
Look.
It's nice.
It's an undercarriage.
Is it a famous one? Yes, it is.
It's about 300,000 yen.
It's 270,000 yen.
Right?
I was surprised.
But it's good.
Did you buy it? I bought it.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
It's okay.
It's cheap like this.
It's good.
It's small.
Thank you for the clothes.
I'm really happy.
We have arrived.
Leave the coffee to Yuma.
Really?
Let's eat something.
I got it.
I bought a set meal.
Thank you.
I'm going to feed you.
Are you going to
eat it? Here you are.
It's delicious.
It's hard for you.
You got on my back.
I got on your back.
Be careful.
Your hands are dirty.
Do you want me to wipe your hands?
Do you want me to wipe
your hands? Let's go.
What? What's up?
What?
Someone is watching us.
No one is here.
Don't you get excited in such a place?
I do get excited,
but... Wait a minute.
It's open.
What's up?
What are you going
to do? It's nostalgic.
I can't stand it.
Do you want to go to a
parking lot nearby? Yes, I do.
Let's go.
Thank you.
I'm going to put on a seat belt.
It was really hard, wasn't it?
It was hard, wasn't it?
Are you filming? Yes, I am.
Oh, you are filming.
Are you going to
wear it? Yes, I am.
You don't want to wear it, do you?
You are going to wear it, aren't you?
We arrived at the campsite.
I think it's safe here.
Are you sure? I'm sure.
What is it?
Do you want me to touch your knee?
You are so naughty.
You get excited when I touch
your knee, don't you? Yes, I do.
I'm not a wife, am
I? No, you're not.
You're so calm.
Oh, no.
What's wrong? I feel sick.
I want to sleep.
Do you want to sleep?
Yes.
What are you doing?
I'm going to look up what's going on.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
It feels good.
It looks like it's going
to last a long time.
It's full.
Is it full?
Yes.
OK.
Please do it properly.
Look!
Wow! Wow! I know.
You are serious.
Why?
Are you excited about this place?
What are you looking at?
Let's take it out for now.
I'm nervous.
Oh, you're ticklish.
I can hear a baby crying.
But it's a baby's voice,
so I can't tell his name.
This baby's voice is so cute.
I'm going to give him a painkiller.
I'm hungry.
I'm going crazy.
Wait a minute.
I feel so good.
I'm tired.
I'm ticklish.
I'm so tired.
What are you doing?
Did you drink a
lot? No, I didn't.
Shall we go inside?
Yes, let's go inside.
Let's go to the hotel.
It's dangerous.
Please wear your clothes properly.
I'll wear my clothes properly.
Is my clothes
okay? Yes, it's okay.
The cat took a nap on
the sofa and came to me.
You know what I do?
You know what kind of fuck it is.
Watch.
Good girl.
This is the first time
I've ever had a baby.
It's been a long time
since I've had a baby.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I can't help but laugh when
I see my daughter's face.
I'm going to sleep.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I'm sorry.
I will show my mother's reaction
when he was in the hospital.
He is a mother of three children.
She is a mother of 6 children.
She is a mother of 2 children.
She is a mother of 3 children.
I'm so sorry.
You're bleeding a lot.
Let me see your legs.
Oh, I see.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
I'm sorry, I'm going to do it again.
Wow!
Can you lie down on my lap?
There are still some parts
that are not completely healed.
I've just been here.
It's a big deal.
Oh my god.
I'm sorry.
My head hurts.
Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
I'm hungry.
Are you hungry? I'm hungry.
I just ate yakitori.
Shall we make a reservation?
Shall we?
Yes.
I made a reservation.
How is it? It's good.
The night view is beautiful, isn't it?
The night view outside the building.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
It's fashionable.
It's more fashionable inside than outside.
I think so.
I didn't know there was such a place.
It's a good place to see.
I think so, too.
I'll take a lot of pictures.
Thank you.
Pasta is here.
How is it?
Is it good? It's good.
It's good.
Let's eat.
You didn't call your wife?
She was here a while ago.
I ignored her.
Let's take a picture.
Because it's a memory.
Cheers!
Delicious!
Isn't this expensive?
What is this?
Isn't it delicious?
It's precious.
It's too precious.
It's the best, isn't it?
Are you ignoring me?
I'm ignoring you.
Look at this side only.
Yuma-chan.
I only look at Yuma-chan.
I'm happy.
Do you want me to give you a potato?
Are you OK?
How is it?
I don't have a spoon.
You don't have a spoon.
I'll take it for you.
It's too wild.
It's too wild, isn't
it? It's too wild.
Don't you need
this much? I need it.
Here you are.
Thank you.
How does it taste?
Wow, it's good!
It's good, isn't
it? Yes, it's good.
I'll give you a lot.
Oh, thank you.
You're kind.
I'm kind.
Because I like you.
I'll give you a lot.
How is it? It's good.
Is it good?
This is a meaty meat.
It's good.
It's a rice cracker pineapple.
It's a dried fruit, isn't it?
It's a rice cracker.
How is it?
It's not alcohol.
It's not a snack.
Seriously?
Maybe it's not a snack.
It's not a snack.
It's a Senbei.
It was a pineapple Senbei.
But it's good.
It's rich.
It seems like candy.
I think so.
It was like that.
It's good.
It's broken.
Oh, it was broken.
I'll give it to you.
How does it taste? It's good.
I thought it would be good, but I forgot to
eat it, so I'll give it to you next time.
It's good, isn't
it? This is good.
Thank you.
It's fun.
It's good.
Do you think you can
do a lot of things like this?
I don't think so.
I want to be with you.
I'm trying to make time, but I'm
always sorry that I feel that way.
No, it's okay. I can do a lot of
things, and it's convenient to go home.
It's easy.
I see.
I have to make more time.
I'm glad.
Are you full?
Yes.
Let's go.
Let's go back to the room.
What are you going to do?
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's go.
Was it delicious? Yes, it was.
Here, here, it's good,
isn't it? I think so.
I think it's good.
Look at this.
This is the place.
This is a photo of our second anniversary.
It's good.
It's strong.
Let's exchange.
Let's go.
Do you want to
kiss? Strong wind.
Let's climb a little more.
Let's go.
Welcome.
Please take a seat here.
Highball? Highball.
Let's have one cup of oil.
I'd like a 12-year-old Seabass, please.
Yes, sir.
Please wait a moment.
It's a drug, isn't it?
Yes.
It's a drug.
Do you drink it? Sometimes.
Excuse me.
You're fast.
Seabass is fast.
Here's your highball.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Cheers.
It's good, isn't it?
Don't you need water? I'm fine.
Really?
I don't want to get drunk.
You drink a lot.
I drink a lot.
I know.
Are you okay?
I think you drank too much.
You're drinking water.
He is drinking water.
Are you drunk? Yes, I am.
What?
You will be found out.
You do that, don't you?
I'm going to use it.
Be quiet.
Does it feel good?
You're not here,
are you? I'm fine.
You have a lot of hair.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Are you ready? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You are so cute.
You are amazing.
You are so close to me.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Why?
I want to see you.
No, I can't.
You're amazing.
Welcome to Miracle Morning!
Miracle Morning!
It's embarrassing.
You're amazing.
You're standing up so well.
You don't look tired at all.
Hey.
You did a good job.
Can I pet you?
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
I'm going to put milk in the glass.
Hey, I was waiting for you.
Hey.
You were groaning.
Were you excited? Yes, I was.
You are drooling.
You are drooling a lot.
I'm going to take a nap.
Are you sleepy?
Did you want to sleep?
Do you feel good? That's great.
It's good, isn't it?
You're eating a lot.
Do you want some
more? What? Good boy.
You are amazing.
You are beautiful.
You are so cute.
ーI'm going to sleep.
ー ーI'm tired.
ー Wow!
How do you feel? I feel good.
I feel good.
Do you feel a tightness
on your head? Yes, I do.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
It's so good.
It's a soup.
I like the sound of my dad's
voice when he's in sleep.
He's always like this when he wakes up.
He's always like this, always.
I want to be like him.
I love you.
Are you okay?
Mom, I feel so good.
You feel so good?
I feel so good.
Look, I'm massaging your back.
It's amazing.
Shin-chan, you're so cute.
You're so cute, Shin-chan.
Are you okay?
Let's make a lot of money.
Me?
Is it all right? Let me see.
Let me see.
It hurts.
Do you want it?
You got a pimple.
Look at this.
I got a lot of pimples.
A lot of pimples?
I have to buy you new clothes.
Are you tired?
I'm a little nervous.
I want you to be nervous.
Touch my belly.
Let me touch you.
You are wet.
More.
Let me touch you.
I'm a little hungry.
I want to touch you.
Let's go.
Can you do it? Yes, I can.
Come in.
He will come back.
Excuse me.
Do you want to go
home? Yes, I do.
I see.
Then, please come this way.
This way.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Were you waiting
for me? Yes, I was.
Can't you see
anything? No, I can't.
I heard someone's coming.
I can't see.
I want to see.
Can I see? No, you can't.
I can't?
This time, I'm going to show you how to
get rid of dead skin cells in cats' eyes.
I'm going to show you how to get
rid of dead skin cells in cats' eyes.
I'm so excited.
Is it good? I'm so happy.
I want you to eat it.
It's hot.
Give me your hand.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'll wipe it for you.
You have a lot of hair on your head.
Do you want more?
It's been a long time since I've
had a baby, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm going to have a baby
soon, so I'm a little nervous.
You are so cute!
What? What? I don't know.
What are you
doing? I don't know.
Where?
You are in my way.
Are you scared? No, I'm not.
Are you sure? I'm sure.
I'm going to give you a kiss.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
It's been a long time since
I've seen a cat like this.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Where is it?
I'm going to take off my panties.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
I'm not sure if it's because I've
never seen a cat like this before,
I'm not sure if it's because
I've never seen a cat like
this before, but I've never
seen a cat like this before.
What?
Do you want me to kiss you?
I don't know how to kiss you.
Do you want me to
kiss you? It feels good.
It feels good.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
I'm so sorry.
It's embarrassing.
It's so bright.
It's so good.
It feels good.
Oh, it's so itchy.
Oh, no.
It's so painful.
No, no, it's not painful.
You can't do it anymore?
I want to do it more.
Do you want to do it more?
You wanted to do it more, didn't you?
Yes, I wanted to do it more.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I've been sick of it.
You're sick? Yes, I'm sick.
Did you go to the
hospital again? Yes, I did.
hospital? Yes, I did.
Did you get a fever? Yes, I did.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I can't go to the bathroom.
I feel sick.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to give birth to a baby.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God!
She seems to have put a pyramid.
I can't breathe.
I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it
anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it
anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do
it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do it anymore, I can't do
I'm so happy that I can't
even speak properly.
I'm not used to this, so
I can't speak properly.
Mom, I want to go to the bathroom.
I want to go to the bathroom.
I won't bother you.
I just want you to be patient.