Oh, then let's sit here.
Yeah.
It's been a while since we've met like this.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, it's been a while since I saw a guy with you two.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
How's your college life going recently?
Hey, did you make a boyfriend with a circle?
No, I didn't.
Oh, I see.
I have a crush on someone.
Who?
That's a secret. What about you, Shin-chan?
I...
I wanted to end the days that I regret.
Nana-chan!
What is it?
We're childhood friends, so we might be in trouble if we suddenly say something like this, but I like Nana-chan.
Please go out with me.
Wait for me!
It's okay.
What?
The person I like is Shin-chan.
Shingen!
Shien!
I'm sorry, lyrics were a little strange.
Did I do something wrong?
No, you didn't.
Oh...
Then,
will you take me home, my boyfriend?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
Come on.
She was the first girlfriend I had.
I've been with Nana since I was in elementary school.
We went to different schools at the university.
I've been thinking about Nana all the time.
All the time.
All the time...
Nana-chan...
The day when there was no class in the morning
I looked at the SNS like this
The next day, it was the third day that I was going to tell a story about a woman.
I'm going to tell a story about a woman?
That's good.
That's good. I'm not going to tell a story about her.
It's a good memory.
This voice...
I will never forget this voice.
Hey, come here!
Stop it!
Shinji, you may be familiar with her.
But she is my girl.
I'm your girlfriend, and I'm your boyfriend.
Don't act like you don't know.
Okay.
Stop it.
You were just talking to Sen-chan.
Let's go.
Sen-chan.
I'm sorry, Sen-chan.
The
It's close.
It's good.
It's so close.
I'm going to stand up a little more.
I feel good.
Do this.
Ok
Feels good.
She is really cute.
I am eating...
Are you imitating me?
You feel good now?
Yes.
You really feel like a human being.
You're already wet, aren't you?
I'm going to take a deep breath.
Are you getting tired?
No, I'm not.
Don't say that.
Raise your hips.
Move your hands.
Your hips are running away.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
You don't have to run away.
What is that?
Don't lick it.
Why?
You haven't taken a shower yet, have you?
Oh, I see.
Do you want to take a bath?
Stop it.
Can I put it in?
Do you feel good?
I don't feel good
No
Look over there
No, no
Do you feel like giving up?
Stay here
I feel like giving up
Then let's take it as it is
Show it to me.
Show me your face.
Show me your eyes.
I'm scared.
What's the next one?
You can do it, right?
It's so cold.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
Wait
No
What?
No, no, no
Why?
I'll do it
Nana, look at me.
Show me your face.
You're so cute.
It hurts!
I feel good.
I feel good too.
You scared me.
You scared me so much.
I'll give it to you.
Go to sleep.
You're still young, aren't you?
I can't do this anymore.
Are you okay?
Stop it.
Just a little more.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What is this?
I'm sorry.
Please give me that!
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
YES!! YES! YES!
So cute.
See?
Aww!
It was IV residue.
I need to drink water...
What?
Don't drink too much.
Goodbye.
But take...
Let's go.
You want to drink too?
Why are you drinking mouthwash?
It's hot!
You should breathe less.
It's okay, I can handle it.
I'm...
How did it feel?
Huh?
Hey, Soso, show me your hand.
Hurry, hurry.
Give me a kiss.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Stop it.
Why?
Aika...
Nana.
Hey, isn't it boring to be with me?
Oh, no. No, I'm sorry.
It's our first date.
Oh, yeah.
I'm so nervous.
That video makes me lose my mind.
I see.
It's been a long time since I've seen her.
What's going on?
It's been a long time.
Huh?
There's also Mr. Motokano.
I haven't found out yet that she'd react like that.
What?
What are you talking about?
Hey, let's take him there.
Sounds good.
Let's go.
What?
Come on.
I'm sorry.
Let me go.
That was close...
You guys...
I see that you're dating
but are you dating?
Huh?
Are you serious?
That had nothing to do with it...
What?
Cut it out, and tell Shin-chan what happened!
Okay, okay.
I'm not telling you anything.
I'm gonna go work with his istiyorum.
Sorry, sorry.
What are you doing?
Be quiet.
Yuzu!
Stop it.
Shin-chan!
Be quiet.
Shin-chan, are you okay?
I can't help you.
Let me go.
I'm going home.
Wait a minute.
Don't look at me.
Look at this video.
What are you doing?
You remember, don't you?
I posted this on social media, and people liked it.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Why are you doing this to me?
What?
You're a jerk.
I see.
I heard they want to do it with you.
What?
Hey, Shinji.
Look closely.
Shin-chan.
Stop it.
Nana-chan!
Stop it!
Hey, hey, where are you going?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
No, no!
What is it?
Nana-chan!
Why?
Give me a kiss.
No! Don't touch me!
No!
What are you doing?
Shin-chan!
I don't want to do it.
Come on.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, no.
Are you crying?
I'm not.
Wait a minute.
Hey, what's wrong?
Stop it! Stop it!
What is it?
I'm a loser, so I can't see anything.
Teacher, please help me.
Did you think I could help you in that situation?
Oh, my God.
Stop it.
I'm in the way.
Okay.
I'm so scared.
Look.
You can do it like this.
No.
Can you see it clearly?
Don't look at me.
Stop it.
Really.
Hey, let me go!
Let me go!
Don't look at me!
Jin-chan!
I'm so sorry!
Stop it!
It's over!
You're so mean.
Show me more.
No, I don't want to.
Let go of my hand.
Stop it.
You're in the way.
I don't want to do it.
Don't look around.
Don't do it.
Hey, Nana.
Listen to me. Did you guys do it?
What? It has nothing to do with it!
What? What did you say?
You're as sensitive as ever.
What? You really don't want to?
No, no, no.
No?
Hey, let's do it again.
What is it?
I'm scared. Stop it.
You'll understand if you use it.
What is it?
I'll tell you.
Okay.
Stop it.
What is it?
What is this?
Help me!
You said you would understand if you don't use it.
What is this?
It makes me nervous.
Don't do that.
Wait.
I'll take it right away.
Yuzuru...
It's okay.
You're becoming more sensitive.
Don't cry.
This is amazing, isn't it?
Stop it.
Your skin is just like this.
Don't touch me.
Stop it.
Don't touch me anymore.
It feels good, isn't it?
I won't lose. Forgive me.
Here too, right?
Does it feel good?
No!
Shin-chan!
Shin-chan.
Don't do that anymore.
You can put this on.
I don't like it. Stop it.
Please be quiet.
It doesn't make any sense, does it?
Oh, I see.
Stop it, stop it.
You just said it, didn't you?
I told you, didn't I?
Ouch!
It's hot!
Are you okay?
Come on, let's go.
Stop it!
If you take the medicine, you'll lose your strength.
Hey, Shinji, it feels good to be hit by Chimpanzee's nipple.
I can't stop, I can't stop.
She is happy.
I'm sorry.
It's getting better.
This way, this way.
Hush.
Stop it.
You're so annoying.
I told you to stop it.
I can't do it anymore.
Let's do it again.
Open your mouth.
Oh, right.
When you're eating, make sure to use a rubber band.
It's easier for me.
Right.
Come on, eat.
Give it to me.
It's not heavy at all.
Do you want to use this?
Yes, let's use it.
It's heavy.
Don't do something like that to my daughter!
Hey hey hey.
What are you doing?
Get on the chair.
I can't do it anymore.
I feel so good.
Stop it.
I'll let you do it normally.
Come on, let's go.
That feels good.
You're reacting, aren't you?
Stop it.
Don't panic.
This is amazing.
It's so tight.
Is the room closed?
This guy is going.
What's wrong?
I told you, didn't I?
Shinji, I told you again!
What? What?
Kaede, come.
Thank you.
No.
Okay.
Why no one wants to debut?
Hey, wait.
Even if you do this...
Shin-chan, can you help me?
Stand up, stand up.
Shin-chan, don't sleep.
Please don't hurt me!
I'm going to get angry.
Do it.
Don't look at me.
Please don't hurt my head.
I'll show you how it's done.
It's big.
It's too big.
It's too small.
What is it?
Here you go.
Beautiful.
He doesn't move at all.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Oh, I feel it too much.
I'm so surprised.
I'm sorry.
What?
Stop it.
Are you sure you want to stop?
I'm sorry.
You look happy.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I'll get you out of here.
The thirty years have come and the
Oh...
Why are you crying?
What?
Are you crying?
Look.
It's been a while since we've seen each other.
I'm sorry.
I'm so tired.
Open your mouth.
You're about to faint, ZO-Sensei.
Seisuke...
I'm sorry, sis.
I couldn't get in touch with Nana for a while.
I got a call from her just two weeks later.
I'm sorry.
Come on in.
I'm sorry for not being able to do anything, Nana-chan.
What should I do?
I'll protect you, I'll always protect you.
Thank you.
It's been a while.
I wish everyone around me was like you.
I wish all the men were like you, Sen-chan.
I love you.
Can I take it off?
I put on my underwear and shorts.
How was that?
It was comfortable.
Really?
What are you doing?
You're good friend.
It feel good
My heart...
I'll do it for you, too.
Nez
I'm sorry. I was nervous.
Nana-chan...
It hurts, doesn't it?
Feel good.
...
He's gone.
Don't worry about it.
Shin-chan?
Just like that.
Wait, Aiku, Aiku!
What's wrong, Shin-chan?
I'm sorry, Nana-chan.
The pillow is too tight.
Neko...
I'm really sorry.
I just wanted to see it with my erotic eyes.
I really wanted to taste the excitement of that moment again.
Hey.
You're here.
Are you sure you're going to delete the video?
I want to ask you something.
What is it?
I remember.
Are you going to use that again?
Stop it! Stop it!
I'm sorry, Yuna-chan.
I'm sorry.
You're not going to leave again?
This is the 7th try, isn't it?
That's right.
I can't believe it's the 5th try.
That's too much.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure you get hit.
I'm going to hit you on the head too.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on.
I'm sorry, I can't help it.
Hello?
I did what you wanted.
Come here tonight with the money.
I'll show you the best of me.
Let's look at the
Where are you, Nana?
You're the best, Nana.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Nana,
do you have something to tell us?
How many times have you been kicked out by us?
I don't know.
Please be nice to me today.
I want you to be nice to me.
Please be nice to me.
I'll do it for you today.
Are you okay?
I will.
Open the door again.
It hasn't started yet.
You want to rest, don't you?
Come here.
No, no.
Come here, come here.
Come on, come on.
No, not that way.
I want to go home.
Are you still kissing?
Okay, I know now
How was Iroha's eating?
He always screams
Oh, you did it again.
What's wrong with you?
I'm having fun.
What are you having fun?
I can't do it.
What is it?
You're fast.
It feels so good.
Do you love me?
I love you.
I can see it clearly.
What is it?
Do you want me to kiss you?
Not yet.
You only think about your baby.
You can kiss me with your mouth.
What's going on here?
Oh, my God.
I can't help but want to see you.
I'm sorry.
It feels good.
You should feel better.
Let's get up.
Let's take a bath together.
It's the same as taking a bath together, isn't it?
It's cold.
One more here.
I'll put a handkerchief.
I'm glad you put it in.
I'll put it in.
I'm so tired.
Sit down.
Are you okay?
You're feeling good, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Don't go. It's not over yet.
This is the third one.
Can you get up, Nana?
Come here.
Stand up.
You want me to put you down, don't you?
I'll put you down.
I feel good.
Touch your waist.
Oh, my God.
That's how you get out of here.
Shhh!
Look at her legs.
I'm so tired.
Ah!
Ouch!
Come on.
Oh, it's hard.
How many times do I have to tell you this?
Wow.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Get up.
I'm sorry.
Look at the way she's turning around.
She's got blood in her eyes.
I love you, Nemo.
I can't breathe
You can see he's shaking
It hurts
Are you sure?
Will she give another one?
It's moving very fast, like crazy.
Does it feel good?
It hurts.
I can feel it.
It's okay.
I'll do another one.
It's my butt.
Thank you very much.
I can't do it anymore.
You can do it.
I can do it.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
I can't do it.
What?
Why? Do you want to die?
Let's go.
I think I can do it.
Huh?
N-N-Nana-chan...
Shin-chan...
N-Nana-chan...
Will you come with me?
Yes, I will.
I'm about to die.
Thank you.
Hey, Shinji.
If you bring money again, I'll make you feel the same way.
Come on, let's go home.
I wish all men were like you.
I'm sorry, Nana-chan.
I am the worst scumbag in the world.
Thank you for watching.