I came back to the hotel.
Thank you for waiting.
Did you wait for me?
No, I didn't.
Really? I'm glad.
I'm going to stay here tonight.
I'm looking forward to it.
You are dressed up.
Yes, I am.
You are so cute.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
Let's take a lot of pictures
on TikTok and Instagram.
OK.
I want to take a lot of pictures.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's take a picture together.
OK.
One, two, three.
Good.
One more.
What?
Nothing.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
It's OK.
Isn't it too early?
No, it's not.
Did you take a picture of me?
Yes, I did.
I have strange eyes.
Don't worry.
You look cool.
Really.
You have a nice face.
I don't.
Thank you.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
My bangs.
You look cute.
Really?
Not at all.
Do I look good?
You have a beautiful back.
Right?
Do you want to take a picture with me?
Really?
Will you take a picture of me?
Of course.
Thank you.
One more.
Good.
How is it?
Is it OK?
Good.
You are good at taking pictures.
No, I'm not.
I'm happy.
You look good in the camera.
No, I'm not.
Thank you.
Do you want to see more?
Yes.
Let's see more.
It's really sunny.
The weather has been bad recently.
So, you have a sunny belly.
I have a sunny belly.
Good.
I'm glad that I have a sunny
belly rather than a rainy day.
I'm going to have a lot of fun today.
I'm going to dress up.
You look good.
Thank you.
You look good in the picture.
You're right.
The shadow of the sun looks good.
I'll take a picture here.
I'm glad that the
temperature is comfortable.
You are too close to me.
No, I'm not.
No?
I'm embarrassed.
Don't be embarrassed.
Look.
It's the sea.
It's amazing.
Let's take a picture.
One more.
What?
No, I'm not.
I'm embarrassed.
You look good.
You look cute.
I'm embarrassed, too.
Let's take a picture together.
No, I'm not.
You look good.
I'll give you 10 seconds.
I can imitate you, right?
Yes.
Let's take a picture together.
You look cute.
I can't imitate you.
I'll take a picture of this as a souvenir.
Where should we go next?
I'm so excited.
It's dangerous.
I'm glad.
What is it?
It's going down.
Let's take a picture.
This is a video.
Look at the fountain.
It's amazing.
It's magnificent.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank you.
Which one do you like,
orange juice or ginger ale?
Which one?
I want to drink orange juice.
Then, I'll drink this one.
By the way, the manga I read
the other day was interesting.
Really?
Thank you.
I'm glad.
The manga I read the
other day was difficult.
I'm glad, too.
You're right.
There are a lot of plots in the manga.
It's strange to say that
it's a long time ago, but it's
getting more difficult than
the manga I read the other day.
You're right.
The manga I read the other day
was simple and easy to understand.
You're right.
The manga I read the other day
is a well-made example, isn't it?
You're right.
I think it's going to be interesting.
It's interesting, but I sometimes
have to look at the conjecture site.
I see.
So, I read the original
manga, look at the site,
understand it, and read
the original manga again.
I sometimes do things like
that, but I think it's really difficult.
I want to drink ginger ale, too.
I'll have a sip.
Give me more.
No, thanks.
Thank you.
This is delicious.
You're right.
Now that we're at the
sea, let's go to the sea.
Let's go.
Isn't it huge?
It's huge.
What kind of sea is this?
I don't know the name of this sea.
I don't know.
Now that we're at the sea, I
want to take a picture of TikTok.
Can you take a picture of me?
Sure.
Here we go.
I took it.
How is it?
Isn't it good?
Take a look.
It's really good.
You're really good at taking pictures.
Thank you.
It's hard to walk on the
beach, but it's a good exercise.
I've been walking a lot lately.
I've been busy studying lately, so I
haven't been able to exercise much.
When I study, I study.
When I exercise, I exercise.
I have a lot of feelings like that.
We're going to the beach.
It's perfect.
There's a circle.
That's amazing.
Let's take a look.
There used to be a lot of bead masquerade.
Do you want to try it?
I'll do it.
I'll have it as it is.
Let's move on to the last one.
I'll do my best.
Which one should I choose?
I'm so nervous.
Why are you so polite all of a sudden?
I don't know.
My hands are shaking.
Oh, my God.
I have five left.
I have one left.
You're thinking very seriously.
I want that.
This one.
You're a genius, aren't you?
I'll show you again.
It's not fake.
Really.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I was able to see your unexpected talent.
Oh, my God.
It's amazing.
It's Azitasu.
I really like Azitasu.
I want it.
It's a cat of each SNS.
Isn't this mine?
Nyakutoku.
It's raw for the time being.
It's beer.
Didn't you have anything other than beer?
It's not raw.
I don't drink it.
I want this.
You're quick to decide the size.
I want size M.
I think size M is good.
I think size L is more fluffy and cute.
That's up to you.
Personally, I like the fluffy one.
It's a little big.
It's a good size.
Let's buy it in matching colors.
Matching colors?
Let's choose the color.
I like black and white.
Black and white is good.
I think black and white
goes well with anything.
Let's go.
It's Otsuri.
You bought it.
I bought it.
I'm glad.
Do you have any other
places you want to go?
It's amazing over there.
Let's take a look.
It's rare to have a public phone.
Let's take a picture.
Did you take a picture?
I did.
I took a good picture.
Stand over there.
It's embarrassing.
Is it over?
It was really good.
Really?
Thank you.
It was really fun.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat sweet potatoes.
That's good.
What?
What's wrong?
Shadowverse.
Why are you suddenly there?
I like trading cards.
Do you want to try it?
Switch is amazing when you enter the anime.
Otaku comes out.
You went without hesitation.
My favorite came out.
It's like that.
I bought it for the first time.
Thank you.
I want to eat crepe.
Do you want to eat it?
I do.
I'll have caramel custard crepe.
Thank you.
It's big.
It's good.
Do you want to eat it?
I like it.
I'm glad.
The sunset is amazing.
It's beautiful only here.
It's really beautiful.
I'll go to the hotel.
Let's go to the hotel.
It's amazing.
The room is really big.
Isn't it?
I was surprised.
It's beautiful outside.
Really?
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
It's really beautiful.
I can see the Tokyo Tower.
It's really beautiful here.
It's really amazing.
It was scary, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't.
Really?
Thank you for today.
You're welcome.
I'm embarrassed.
There is a door over there.
Is that so?
Do you want to go there?
Yes, I'll go there.
It's amazing.
The bathroom is really big.
Oh.
It's really beautiful.
It's amazing.
It's really beautiful here.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
I'm excited.
I'll take a shower.
Wait a minute.
Don't look at me.
Okay.
What were you looking at?
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me.
Do you want to take a bath together?
Yes.
You looked at my naked body.
Show me your naked body.
What?
Don't you like it?
No, I don't like it.
Cheers.
What?
It was a prank.
I had a lot of fun today.
You're right.
Thank you.
That vending machine was the most fun.
That's right.
Let's go.
You're kind.
I'm not kind.
I'm normal.
What?
This is normal kindness.
Really?
I'm happy.
You're polite sometimes, aren't you?
That's right.
It's a habit.
I have to be polite
because I'm not good at it.
You have to close your eyes.
Take off your pants.
I'm embarrassed.
Why?
Don't be embarrassed.
Let's go in.
Do you want to go in?
What?
Do you like it?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
You're going to wash me?
I'm embarrassed.
I can't wash you.
I'm sorry.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
I feel like I'm in the toilet.
Don't mess with me.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'll wash you next.
That's right.
What?
Let's take a picture.
A picture?
I have to take a picture.
Let's take a video.
That's good.
I'll hide the important parts.
The background is very nice.
That's good.
It tickles.
Don't mess with me.
I'm standing.
Take a picture of me.
Okay.
It tickles.
Are you shaking?
I'm shaking.
Let's take a picture.
I can't take a picture.
I can't take a picture at all.
Stop it.
I can't take a picture.
I'm embarrassed.
Stop it.
I won't stop.
I can't take a picture.
I like this place.
You look good.
I'm embarrassed.
You're getting bigger.
Don't say that.
I'm embarrassed.
You're so cute.
Don't say that.
I won't.
Don't mess with me.
It feels good.
I feel good.
It tickles.
I want to stop.
I'm embarrassed.
It's hard.
It tickles.
You're mean.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I can't take a picture.
I'm embarrassed.
It tickles.
I feel good.
I like you.
I'm happy.
I've seen you many times.
I'm embarrassed.
You fell.
I fell.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good.
It tickles.
I'll give it back to you.
Does your ear feel good?
You know that.
It tickles.
You've grown up.
Don't say that.
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Do you like it?
I like it.
It feels good.
You've grown up.
Do you like it?
I don't like it.
It's delicious.
What are you going to do?
Do you want me to put it in here?
It tickles.
It feels good.
Let's continue.
Do you want to go there?
Let's go there and continue.
What?
It tickles.
I'm nervous in a place like this.
It's different from usual.
Do you want me to put it in here?
It feels good.
Look at me.
Don't do that.
You're so mischievous.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Don't do that.
It feels good.
Why do you like it?
Do you like it?
Do you want me to do more?
Do as much as you want.
You're dressed up.
I've never dressed up like this.
It feels strange.
You look excited.
I'm excited.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Look at me.
It tickles.
It feels good.
Your face is cute.
Don't do that.
Does it feel good?
It tickles.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
What?
Do you want to move again?
Yes.
I want to move.
It feels good.
I like this.
It tickles.
It feels good.
I feel good, too.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Look at me.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I can't stand it.
It tickles.
You put a lot of it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It felt good.
Do you want to go to the bathroom?
Yes.
I made you dirty again.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
I'll wipe it for you.
Thank you.
Does it tickle?
No, it's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's clean now.
We have to take a shower again.
Let's go together.
Shall we?
Let's go.
I'm happy.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep?
No, I'm not.
Look at this.
The night view is amazing.
No way.
Look.
Come here.
It's amazing.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I was surprised that
there was a lot of nature.
The buildings in the back feel like Tokyo.
It's beautiful over there, too.
You're right.
Why don't we go for a walk outside?
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Let's go for a walk outside.
I like the atmosphere of the night.
It's different from daytime.
I'm hungry.
What should we eat?
The hotel was expensive, wasn't it?
Do you want to eat something?
There's a convenience store over there.
A convenience store?
Yes, let's go to a convenience store.
I came all the way here.
You don't have to.
The hotel was expensive, wasn't it?
I'm happy to hear that.
But... You don't have to.
The convenience store
bento is delicious, so let's go.
Do you really want to go
to a convenience store?
You don't have to.
What do you want to eat?
Don't you need alcohol?
I just want to drink.
My best recommendation is grilled udon.
Grilled udon?
I don't think so.
There's grilled udon.
Really?
Isn't this it?
This is it.
I'll have grilled udon.
Will you bring it to me?
Of course.
Thank you.
I want to eat dessert.
What about alcohol?
I'll drink alcohol, too.
I'll drink less alcohol.
I'll buy two kinds of sweets.
I'd like a bag, please.
Is this okay?
Yes, it's okay.
You bought a lot.
Yes, I did.
Give me your hand.
Give me your hand?
It's the season of illumination.
That's right.
Time flies.
It's been a year.
Did you really buy this?
Yes, I did.
Why?
I wanted to eat something
delicious with you.
But it's a delicious dish.
I'm embarrassed.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm embarrassed now.
Don't make a strange face.
I'm sorry.
Make a cool face.
I'll laugh at you.
Why?
That's not true.
We took a lot of pictures.
We took a great picture.
Look at this.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
This is...
I got it.
I'll keep this a secret.
To whom?
It's my secret.
I think it's about half.
You're right.
I'll keep this a secret.
Thank you so much for today.
I want you to cheer me up.
Can I attack you a lot?
I'll take it off.
It's already this big.
You're so cute.
Do you feel good?
You're delicious.
Are you happy?
I like being patted on the head.
I'll pet you a lot.
You're so cute.
Do you feel good?
How about this?
Why are you holding back your face?
Do you want to show your face?
Do you want me to lick you?
What should I do?
Is this okay?
Do you feel good?
You can put it in your mouth.
Wow, you put a lot in your mouth.
I'm hungry, so let's go eat meat.
You put too much out.
Thank you for the meal.
Do you want a toast?
I'm not good at
drinking, so I'll put it here.
No, it's okay.
Can you open it?
I opened it.
Cheers.
It's delicious.
Thank you for the meal.
What salad are you eating?
Seaweed salad.
Seaweed is good for dieting.
I don't feel like dieting.
You don't have to do that.
Really?
Give me a bite.
I want to be healthy.
It's delicious.
You recommend it, don't you?
Do you want to eat vegetables?
Give me a carrot.
I'll give you a carrot and udon.
Carrot and udon are delicious.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
I had a lot of fun today.
I feel like I've had a lot of
dates I've never had before.
Thank you so much for today.
Are you happy to pat my head?
Yes.
I'm going to sleep a lot today.
My ears tickle.
It hurts.
I've never been touched like this.
It tickles.
Let's kiss.
I had a lot of fun today.
Thank me.
Do you feel good?
I'll lick you a lot.
I had a lot of fun today.
I want to have a lot of dates again.
It tickles.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Let me do it.
It tickles.
Can you lick me?
Do you feel good?
How do you feel?
I want you to lick me, too.
Don't spread your legs.
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
It tickles.
Don't do that.
I'll be on top of you.
I'm on top of you.
It tickles.
Do you feel good?
I like you.
It tickles.
I had a lot of fun.
I love you.
Thank you so much for today.
I was so happy.
Good night.
What did you do?
You were sleeping.
It tickles.
Were you sleeping?
It's embarrassing.
Why did you get so big in the morning?
You're amazing.
You're so energetic.
It tickles.
Is this breakfast?
I'm full.
It tickles.
I got wet.
What?
Do you like this?
I was surprised.
But I'm a little excited.
What are you going to do if you like this?
It tickles.
I've never been seen this much.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm going to get bigger.
It tickles.
No, no, no.
You look like this in the morning.
It tickles.
It's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
I didn't go to the bathroom in the morning.
This is against the rules.
It tickles.
I'm making a weird sound.
It tickles too much.
It tickles.
I'm spreading it out.
It tickles too much.
It tickles.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm scared.
It's gone.
It tickles.
We've been flirting since yesterday.
This feels good.
It tickles.
It hurts.
I've said a lot.
It feels good.
I love you.
I've said a lot.
It feels good in the morning.
I love you.
Thank you for everything since yesterday.
It was a lot of fun.
I'm glad.
Thank you so much.
Look at my cell phone.
Did you notice?
You made my face.
Can I take a picture of my cell phone?
Make a cool face.
You look great.
I'm going to choose a
good picture and take it.
Thank you for everything since yesterday.
What should I do after this?
Do you want to come to my house?
It's embarrassing.
Let's continue a lot today.