Listen carefully.
Good morning.
How long are you going to sleep?
I told you I would wake you up.
Why are you grinning?
Is it a dream?
Anyway, look at the clock.
Look at the clock.
It's crazy, isn't it?
Don't make it in time for school.
Do you want to give up?
Well, that's true.
Then you can sleep for another 30 minutes.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night.
What?
I can't sleep.
What's wrong?
Did you wake up?
What?
I'm sorry.
Because I disturbed your sleep.
What?
What do you want to do?
Okay.
But...
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'll start.
I'm not playing with you.
What?
Do you want me to lick you?
Well, then...
Do you want me to lick your face?
I'll do it in a funny way.
Thank you.
I can't do it.
I'm kidding.
Do you feel good?
I'm not laughing.
What's wrong?
Do you want me to touch you?
Can I touch you?
Then I won't touch you.
I won't touch you at all.
What's wrong?
What do you want me to do?
Do you feel good?
What?
That's not true.
I'm not playing with you.
What?
Okay.
I think you were sleeping.
You're cheating on me.
Then I'll do it next time.
Do you feel good?
I'm not playing with you.
Let's lick each other.
What?
Do you want me to put it in your mouth?
I'll put it in your mouth.
I can't do it.
Do you feel good?
It's the first time to
do it in the morning.
It's a little embarrassing.
It feels good.
It hurts.
Can I touch you?
It feels good.
Do you feel good?
I'm not playing with you.
I woke up.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to school?
Let's get ready.
I'm not playing with you.
I was teasing you a lot.
Are you brushing your teeth properly?
I'll check it.
Open your mouth.
It stinks.
I'm not playing with you.
Let's get ready and go to school.
What?
What are you doing?
I'm a little scared.
Don't do that.
It's not a bad thing.
I was surprised because it was sudden.
It's okay.
I was surprised.
How are you doing these days?
Do you have a part-time job?
Do you have a shift?
Is your shift pretty hard?
Good job.
It's true that you've been
coming home late lately.
You look busy.
Me?
I'm busy, too.
I have a lot of things to do.
Like games.
I'm sorry.
But it's important.
Games are important, too.
Since a while ago?
It's been a long time.
Did you grow up?
I think I'm growing up every day.
F cup.
I have a feeling for the F cup.
Why are you getting bigger?
Are you getting bigger?
You're touching your nipples.
I don't think it's related.
It's not related.
You've been touching
your nipples for a long time.
You're very nervous.
Do you like your nipples that much?
You don't like it?
You touched my nipples a lot.
You touched my nipples.
That's amazing.
I haven't touched you that much yet.
It's okay if you touch me.
I thought you'd understand.
What are you doing?
Do you want me to touch you?
It's okay.
You look tired.
I'll touch you.
Do you want me to touch your nipples?
It's okay.
How is it?
You're eating a lot.
You look like you want me to lick you.
It's okay.
I'll lick your nipples.
Really?
Why are you saying such a terrible thing?
I'll forgive you.
What are you doing?
What is it?
Are you licking my nipples?
Are you serious?
That's a lie.
You're kidding, aren't you?
Are you serious?
It's okay if you're serious.
I've never done that.
Are you sure?
Don't laugh even if you can't do it.
I'm serious.
I've never done that.
I love you.
Can you do that?
Are you okay?
Does it feel good?
I've never done that.
It's my first time since I was born.
I can't do that.
Does it feel good?
I feel good, too.
It's a strange feeling.
Does it feel good?
What?
I don't know if I'm doing it right.
Can you do that?
Are you serious?
What are you doing?
Did you do it?
I'm glad to hear that.
Can you do that?
I'll think about it.
I drank a lot.
Don't you drink that much?
What?
I drank a lot.
Do you like it?
I love you.
Do you like me?
I'm glad to hear that.
I drank a lot.
I love you.
I'm sweating.
I'm sweating, so I can't do that.
What?
Does it hurt?
I'm sorry.
Does it tickle?
I think I'm ticklish.
I'm sorry.
I'm ticklish.
What?
Do you want to do that?
Okay.
I want to do that.
Do you want to do that?
It's hot.
I'm sweating.
Don't do that.
I'll wipe my sweat with
the smell of my hands.
It's sticky, isn't it?
Hello.
Wow.
Hey.
Kiss me.
Kiss me more.
Wow.
Don't do that.
What are you doing?
That's not fair.
Don't do that.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'm tired.
Touch me more.
Don't open your eyes.
It's embarrassing.
Don't look at me too much.
Isn't it too much?
Do you want to look at me that much?
It's embarrassing.
It feels good.
Wow.
Don't do that.
Touch me more.
Don't look at me.
No.
Don't do that.
Don't touch my butt.
My butt.
Hey.
It tickles.
Why do you tickle me?
Why?
Kiss me.
Wow.
Hey.
I want you to kiss me.
I can't push you.
Take off your panties.
I want you to take off your panties.
Wow.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'll lick you.
Doesn't alcohol hurt?
Does it hurt?
Does it feel good?
That's how it is.
Kiss me.
Let's kiss.
Wow.
Put your hand in my mouth.
It tickles.
I'll move now.
Wow.
I want to kiss you.
It tickles.
I can't move.
Do it from behind.
Hey.
Don't tickle me.
Wow.
Let's go.
Let's go together.
Put your hand on my butt.
It's fun to drink alcohol.
Let's do it again next time.
I love you.
Kiss me.
What are you doing?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Get out.
I'm not waiting for you.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Wait a minute.
I can't.
I don't want to.
I can't get out.
Why?
Do you want to see me?
Don't you want to see me?
I don't want to see you.
You're angry.
I'm going to get out.
Get out.
Go away.
I'm really going to get out.
Wait a minute.
I'm out.
It's terrible.
I'm really going to get out.
Don't take off your clothes.
It's okay, right?
Why?
I'm going to bed.
Hey.
You don't look well.
Are you okay?
You don't sleep well?
You have to sleep well.
You can't go to school if you sleep.
Okay.
I'll make something to cheer you up.
Leave it to me.
Have you ever done this?
It's open.
If you do this, you'll wake up.
It smells good.
This is the most important thing today.
What's wrong?
One more time?
You said you were sleepy.
If you don't do this, you'll wake up.
I'm sorry.
I'll treat you to a drink.
Let's go to the convenience store.
Do you only want ice cream?
I'll have ice cream, too.
I like ice cream.
I smelled it earlier.
I want to eat ramen.
I'm hungry.
I'll buy a cup of ramen.
Unexpectedly?
Is it good?
I want to eat it.
What are you doing?
It's delicious.
You're getting better.
What did you say?
It's not a sound.
I thought it would feel good.
Do you want me to do it?
I'll think about it.
I'm going to take a break.
Okay.
How do you want me to lick you?
Like I'm in love?
What's that?
I don't know what it's like.
I don't know.
I'll lick you in various places.
I'm going to lick you.
First of all,
From the ear.
The other side.
Do you want me to be gentle?
Do you think I'm tired?
Sometimes.
Let's go.
Is it cute?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to lick you?
All right.
My feet are moving.
It was cute.
Here we go.
Is it bad?
It's like I'm in love.
Did you lick me?
Is it erotic?
What do you want me to do?
It's a little early.
Can you stand it?
It's too strong.
Really?
Is it bad?
Do you want me to get up?
I ate a lot.
My eyes are bad.
It's really bad.
I think I should sleep a little.
I'm not going to die.
Let's sleep today.
I'm going to sleep.
What?
I'm using it now.
Wait a minute.
It takes a long time to remove makeup.
I don't want to remove my makeup.
I'm going to sleep.
Do you want me to get up?
Did you get it?
I'm going to sleep.
I'm cute even if I don't have makeup on.
I'm embarrassed.
You look at me a lot.
My mouth hurts.
You're touching me too much.
I'm going to sleep.
I can't.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm going to sleep.
Did you feel dizzy?
You're right.
I'm going to sleep.
You're getting closer to me.
Am I cute?
Really?
You're lying.
I'm going to sleep.
All right.
What?
I'm going to sleep.
What are you doing?
What is this?
I'm going to sleep.
You're touching me.
It feels good.
I'm going to sleep.
You touched me again.
Are you going to sleep?
You're cute.
I'm going to sleep.
I don't want to.
Are you going to sleep?
I don't know.
I'm going to sleep.
That's not fair.
I'm not good at this.
What?
Why did you do something like me?
Are you imitating me?
I can't help it.
I was embarrassed because I was naked.
You took it off yourself.
No.
I wanted you to take it off.
What?
Wait a minute.
Did you want to do this?
I'm going to sleep.
Are you playing with me?
What?
Don't do that.
Do you want to play with me?
I want to play with you.
I'm getting sleepy.
What are you doing?
I'm going to sleep.
I forgot.
Wait a minute.
That's terrible.
I'm going to sleep.
It feels good.
That's terrible.
Are you going to sleep?
That's good.
What?
Do you want to show your face?
He showed his face.
I feel like I've seen everything.
But it's okay.
I'll only say it once, so listen.