It's the worst, really.
I was made to wear something weird.
Can you see it?
Isn't it bad?
I was told not to take it
off except for the toilet.
It hurts and hard.
I really don't like it.
But I made a promise
with the producer, the
director, and Manu,
so I'm going to keep it.
I really didn't think I'd be doing this.
I don't want this. I want to take it.
I wanted to go to the
bathroom, so I'll take it.
OK, let's go.
It's difficult, isn't it?
There is a key on the back.
Do I have to take it off
with this? It's difficult.
I did it.
You are staring at me.
I'm not staring at you.
That's right.
Of course, it's going to be ugly.
Because it's been on for a long time.
That's right.
When the camera is not running,
I'm sure you're taking a picture.
Do you think I'm taking a picture?
Really?
Do you want to see it?
You look good in it.
I told you I like it.
You've been wearing it for a while.
I've been wearing it for a long time.
I want to take it off soon.
But it looks good on you.
It's quite inconvenient.
I think so.
Did you take it off when you
went to the bathroom? I told you so.
Thank you.
I want to shoot in the best condition.
Do you want to shoot? Yes, I do.
It's enough.
It's OK now, isn't it?
Can I take it
off? It's difficult.
Please take it off.
I can't.
Can I take a picture of you?
Can I take a picture
of you? Yes, please.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I don't have to take a picture of you.
Don't do that!
I don't want to take a picture of you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It was like this.
Yes.
It was so much that it became like this.
Because I put it on for a long time.
Now, it's in a good mood.
It's in a good mood.
I'm sorry.
I can't take it because I'm in a good mood.
I love it.
What is this? Is it okay from the morning?
Really? You're good.
I heard you like it.
Let's drink it all at once.
Is that okay?
This will make it more erotic.
I'm sorry.
Everyone in front of
the camera is also cute.
I'll have it.
What is this?
I don't know what it tastes like.
It's very rich.
You don't know what it
tastes like, do you? I know.
Please drink a little more.
No, I don't know.
Isn't there something bad in it?
What? I don't know.
You just took a bite, didn't you?
Maybe it's because I brushed my teeth.
Really?
But it smells weird.
Is it rotten? Yes, it is.
I think it's rotten.
It must be something bad.
No, it's not rotten.
It's rotten.
It was very expensive.
It's terrible.
It's getting hot.
You're used to drinking expensive alcohol.
I'm not used to it.
Well, that's right.
Is it rotten?
What?
Is it rotten? No, it's not.
It's not rotten.
I put in something that
makes sex more enjoyable.
What is that?
Is it something you can
tell by the bitterness?
That's different.
The smell is different.
I enjoy the smell at first.
As expected.
I'm sorry.
You look better than before.
What?
You look better.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
Do you want to start again?
What?
Are you going to
start? Yes, I am.
This time, I'm going to start
right away without any preparation.
Are you sure? Yes, I am.
Are you going to
start? Yes, I am.
Is it hot over there? It is.
Is it humid? I saw it.
Can you show me how hot it is?
It suddenly became like a music video.
Is it a music video?
What other than a music video?
Do you want to see it?
What?
Do you want to see me there so much?
You are getting excited.
It's a big deal.
Do you understand?
Is it a big deal? It's wet.
It's terrible.
Isn't it? Yes, it is.
This is.
..
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What?
I'll be right back.
Really?
It would be a waste if you leave like this.
It's terrible if you leave like this.
No!
Why are you doing
this to me? It feels good.
I like it.
You don't look comfortable.
Because I haven't
done this for a long time.
How do you feel?
Do you feel warm?
I feel warm enough.
The inside of my body is hot.
Are you in the best condition?
Are you in a good condition?
I'm in the best condition.
Then let's get started.
Do you want to have sex?
Yes.
Let's have the best sex.
I wanted to do it from the beginning.
This is the plan for this time.
Bring me here.
I'm coming.
I'm sweating a lot.
Wow, it's getting so hard.
It's getting so hot.
It's so hot.
My body is so sticky.
It's been a while.
You want to go out, don't you?
Can I go out? It's a party.
I'm sweating a lot.
You smell.
Why do you smell? You are happy.
You are wet.
I don't like it.
Can't I kiss you?
What?
Can't I lick you or
kiss you? Yes, you can.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm going to sleep now.
You can sleep now.
I feel so good.
Give me a hug.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to go
in there? I'm going in.
From next time, I'll be a never-beat.
I'm sorry.
You have a lot of pimples.
Yes, I have a lot of pimples.
Are you happy? Yes, I am.
It feels good.
I want to do more.
It's scary.
They are playing with each other.
It's getting heavier.
You are sweating a lot.
She is calling you.
She is calling me.
Oh, you are here.
You are so active in the morning.
Because there are three of us.
It's like the last scene, isn't it?
Because it's been a long time.
I don't know if you are
full of sweat or full of spirit.
I don't know which one is better.
Which one is better?
Which one is worse?
I'm going to take a shower scene.
It's just a shower.
What's that? I know.
What?
It's suspicious here.
I haven't taken a bath yet.
Please take a bath.
Is there really
nothing? Here we go.
Why are you closing it?
Because it hurts! I knew it.
I knew it.
We have a guest.
Please use it.
No, no, we have already taken a bath.
We will help you.
Is there such a thing?
We have been waiting for you.
What is this? Is it a special time?
You will wash me.
This is the studio.
There is a service like this.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is it a service like that?
I'll make it clean.
Is it OK?
Yes.
You're making a lot of noise.
I'm just washing my hands.
Is that okay? My chest, too.
But you're standing.
What did you do? Like this.
I'll make it clean.
Thank you.
Let's wash your hair.
It's a bit erotic to wash my hair.
Are you ready?
Am I beautiful? I'm ready.
Let's wash your hair.
Thank you.
I'll wash your back hair.
It's clean here, too.
What's dirty?
I'm sensitive because
I didn't wash my hair.
It's clean.
Thank you.
Now that it's clean, let's
move on to the next stage.
What's wrong with
you? It's swollen.
This way, please.
Is it okay if it's
swollen? Yes, it's okay.
What's this?
We've been waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Please make yourself comfortable.
I'll make myself comfortable here.
Thank you.
It's warm.
Is it warm?
I was surprised.
How do you feel?
I feel very good.
I'll moisturize you.
Thank you very much.
It's too moisturized,
isn't it? This is good.
Your legs are tired,
aren't they? Yes, they are.
It's new.
I'm so happy.
Let's have a cup of tea.
I'm taking a picture of Chinchin.
Chinchin is massaging you.
Yes, he is massaging everyone's Chinchin.
He is massaging everyone's Chinchin.
Massaging.
I'm going to massage a common one.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
I'm going to give you a massage.
Are you happy? Yes, I am.
There are a lot of pimples.
I'm going to massage your pimples.
Massage my pimples?
There are a lot of pimples.
How many pimples do you have?
One, two, three, four, five.
Five pimples.
This is a massage for a small baby.
You need a good massage.
You have a lot of hands.
Saki, you can drink a lot.
You can drink more.
I feel sick.
I'm sorry.
You are a good girl.
You are not a big girl.
You can open your hips.
You have a lot on your face.
I'll massage your face.
It's warm, isn't it?
You can give me a massage.
I'll massage your mouth.
Thank you very much.
Do you feel sleepy?
I'll massage your mouth.
You have a lot on your face.
I'll touch your face.
It feels good.
I feel like my heart is melting.
Is it melting inside and outside?
Yes, it's melting inside and outside.
It feels good.
Please don't change your position.
It's about time, isn't
it? I feel so good.
I feel so good.
I want to do something.
How do you feel,
Masaru? I feel good.
I'm glad to have a baby.
I feel good.
I can move my hips.
I'll help you.
I feel good.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
My mouth is getting dry.
Your mouth is getting dry.
I'll put this here.
You're giving me a massage.
It's very slippery.
I'm going to sleep.
Please be careful.
I'll massage your back.
Thank you.
Oh, it's great.
Is it okay?
It's great, isn't it?
Oh, it feels good.
Are you feeling better?
Are you okay?
You should be more comfortable.
Can you do more? I will do more.
You are very patient.
You should be patient.
Are you okay?
You are patient, aren't you?
Ah!
I'm sorry I'm not good at explaining,
but the video I'm filming is all the same.
Oh, it hurts.
Do you feel pain now? Yes, I do.
Do you feel pain
now? Oh, it hurts.
I can't do it.
This is the last one.
Baby is crying.
We will fill this up.
We will put a lot.
Let's fill it up.
Let's put a lot.
Yes, a lot.
Look!
Wow!
You can get into your stomach.
Wow! I'm so scared.
It's so slippery.
Chinchin is fine now.
I'm so scared.
I'm sorry.
Let me hold you.
I'm so sorry.
I'll hold you.
I'm sorry.
Mmm, you are still eating.
Please go in the order.
That's amazing!
You like a fierce play, don't you?
I don't feel good in my
hands… Oh my goodness!
I'm itchy! Itchy! He's coming.
He's coming to you.
He's coming to me.
You like it.
You like it, don't
you? Yes, I do.
Yes, yes, yes.
Can you climb up?
I want to climb up.
Do you want to climb
up? Yes, I want to.
Oh, it feels good.
I was able to hold Shin-chan.
It's stable, isn't it?
It's comfortable.
I want to touch her more.
I'm sorry I didn't stop you.
What's wrong? I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I can't help it.
I'm sorry.
Look at them.
They all fell asleep.
I'm sorry.
Please come to me.
Do you want to go over
there? Yes, yes, yes.
Just like this.
Go straight up.
Yes, yes, yes.
Use your body.
Go straight up.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's fun.
It's amazing.
Yes, yes, yes.
It feels good.
I'll hold you.
It hurts.
My chest is tight.
Your chest is tight.
I like you.
Oh, it feels so good.
Good morning.
You are very energetic.
Yes, I am.
You are strong.
You can do it.
Ahhhhhhh!
Put the water in.
Oh! It feels good!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Let's do it together!
Ouch!
Ah!
It's a very cold morning.
She's now on her back.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
What?
It's so uncomfortable.
I'll help you sit on my back.
I'm scared.
【Sleeping and streaming】
I'm going to sleep now.
My leg is wet.
I want to sleep more.
I want my leg to be more wet.
I feel so comfortable.
Go, go, go!
I want you to put more.
I want more.
Really? You talk a lot.
I'm sleepy.
Is this a lotion?
Or is it a serum? It's a serum.
If I keep putting it in, I'll get a pimple.
I don't know.
It feels good.
I love it.
It's tight.
It feels good.
Give me a massage.
Do you want me to give
you a massage? Yes, please.
Give me a massage.
Yes, please.
Oh!
Oh! I can't move.
Are you OK?
Oh!
Suddenly?
It hurts when I open my eyes.
Don't use that stupid look on your face.
After all, when I eat
rice, it comes back to life.
When you eat something with a
lot of energy, you recover quickly.
I thought it was weird.
I was wondering what it was.
There were eels and tails in it.
There was something I don't usually eat.
I knew it was you.
Did you think so?
By the way, I prepared
dessert after dinner.
What?
Fresh dessert is waiting for you.
Fresh?
Yes.
I think I know what it is.
Here you are.
Wait! I just ate it.
It's waiting for you.
Dessert is important.
I hope it's really a dessert.
Here you are.
See, I knew it.
There are a lot of fresh bananas.
What are you talking about?
That's how it is.
It's a lively banana.
Can I have some?
Can I have some dessert?
Yes.
This is a ripe banana.
Does it look
delicious? Yes, it does.
You like bananas,
don't you? Yes, I do.
Please eat a lot.
May I?
Wow, it smells so good.
It smells good.
Really?
How about this one?
They all smell different.
What is it? It's thin.
It smells good.
Thank you.
Is it okay?
Can I eat this
banana? Of course.
I'm right-handed, so
I'll eat it from the right.
It looks like a banana.
I'll eat it while you drive.
Can I eat the left banana?
Are you ready?
You are a lively banana.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
I got a pimple.
I'm touching it all the time.
But it's not coming out.
I can't get it out.
It's time for me to eat, too.
I have never seen such a cute cat before.
Mom's hand is in the way.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm eating three at a time.
I'm so happy.
Come here.
You eat so well.
I'm so happy.
I can't stop smiling.
It's delicious.
It's great.
It's a luxurious dessert.
Can I focus on you one
by one? Yes, you can.
I'll taste it slowly.
I'll just eat a banana.
Can I eat this
banana? Yes, you can.
Do you like eggs?
Do you like eggs? Yes, I do.
It's good.
You're getting bigger.
Look at my neck.
It feels good.
Really?
I'm going to throw up.
Are you going to throw up?
Can I kiss you? Then? Next is.
..
Mijibata.
Yes, please.
May I?
Yes.
I'll put a stone on your back.
It's a bit raw.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry for the sound.
It's a weird feeling.
It's a weird feeling, but...
It's a strange feeling.
I'm a little excited
because I'm licking my lips.
This banana is a little bitter.
Was it bitter? It's delicious.
There is one more.
One more?
May I? This one, too.
Thank you.
It's a smooth banana.
It's delicious.
My mouth is getting hard.
You can't eat the head, either.
Wow! It's so hard.
It's so cute.
You look like you're going to puke.
Really? It's okay.
I want you to give me a hug.
I want you to put it on my face.
I'm getting ticklish.
Can I take it out? Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
You feel better, don't
you? Of course I do.
This is the end of today's party.
Isn't that too much?
Please enjoy yourself.
Wow! Please enjoy it.
I will enjoy it, too.
Wow! There are a lot of hands.
This is a touching bandage.
Your buttocks feel good, don't they?
Your buttocks are white.
You have beautiful buttocks.
I'm touching them.
I touch it when I want.
He is a cat-cat of Saga prefecture, Japan.
I'm surprised to see him so much.
He touches everyone.
His hands are full of water.
He is looking at me very much.
It hurts.
I'm crying.
I won't stop even if you cry.
I feel bad.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to
hold you? One, two.
I'm so happy.
You lick it in order.
Do you feel good?
I feel good, but...
You are drooling.
Good boy.
You are a good boy.
Now, here is your new toy.
He is a good boy.
Here is your new toy.
Now, you can play with him.
He will come in.
Oh, no!
What's wrong? My butt hurts.
My mouth hurts.
Does your mouth hurt?
Yes.
How do you want
me to lick you? Here.
Here?
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a cute baby.
I'm glad I was able to film this video.
This is the first time I've
ever seen such a cute baby.
I'm glad I was able to film this video.
You are amazing.
I can't stop crying.
I'm so happy.
Let's go to drink your favorite drink.
I'm going to take you out.
I'm going to surround you.
There are a lot of Tenko.
This is a video of my
son and my daughter
playing with my son's
favorite toy, a cat toy.
He is cute and gentle, but
he has a hard time sleeping.
Chin-chin's first time
eating Poco-chan's pizza?
Poco-chan wants to play with him.
Toto wants to play with him.
Poco-chan is a little quick
to draw attention on him.
Are you sleepy? I'm sleepy.
You're sleepy.
Does it feel good? I'm sleepy.
Is it good? I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
Haru-chan is a good boy, but
he is not good at playing with toys.
He is a little bit timid
and a little bit clumsy.
But he is a good boy.
He is a little bit timid
and a little bit clumsy.
Other than the fact that I had
a good time with my husband,
I was able to spend quality
time with my daughter.
I don't want to eat.
You don't want to eat?
I will lick you.
Will you lick me? Yes, I will.
No, no.
No? Not yet.
It's coming.
I was able to line up.
I move this, too.
This is not the way.
This is the order.
I don't want to get up.
Please try to get up.
Where? I'm behind you.
Look.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby crying like this.
I was surprised to see
a baby crying like this.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Turn this way.
Put your head on my lap.
Oh my gosh!
Wow!
It feels great!
Come on, let's go to bed.
Tama-chan, you can do it.
I'm scared.
I want a tampon, but I can't find it.
She is very popular.
I'm sorry.
Did you call me? Yes, I did.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Are you tired?
I'm so scared!
I'm scared!
Where are you going?
You can't go far if you move a lot.
I want you to do more.
I want to do more.
I'm tired.
This is a video of a baby
who was taken to the hospital.
I was so happy that I
couldn't help but cry.
A baby is crying and having a hard time.
The baby is crying and having a hard time.
Oh, it feels good.
Are you OK?
I'm very satisfied.
Are you okay?
Do you feel better?
I just woke up.
You didn't move, did you?
Please wake me up.
You must have exercised so hard.
That's right.
You slept for about 30 minutes.
30 minutes? It was amazing.
It was amazing.
It's been a while since
I've done it so hard.
I'm still a baby.
Do you still want to do it?
I can still do it.
Do you want to do it again next month?
Do you want to increase
the number of people?
OK.
How was it?
It's the best day of my life.
Makeup time?
You can put it on.
Are you sure?
I don't want to.