I was in high school, and I had nothing to
do but study, and I was alone in the class.
I used to be a quiet person.
But now, I want to change myself.
So I went to Tokyo University.
I got a girlfriend for the first time.
Unfortunately, my life
is full of ups and downs.
And this summer vacation,
I have no time to go back to my hometown.
So I decided to stay at my
parents' house for three days.
I decided to go back to my parents' house.
Ah, my parents' house is so relaxing.
I feel so good.
It's so hot.
What are you talking
about? It's so hot.
You haven't been back to
your hometown for a long time.
You must be so lazy.
You should help your mom a little.
Yes, yes.
You are so noisy.
It's been a long time since I came
back to Japan, so let me take my time.
There is nothing to do
in such a shitty country.
Besides, I'm busy
studying every day in Tokyo.
Are you really studying?
Your father is also worried about you.
Here is your favorite somen.
Eat it quickly.
Thank you.
This is what I ate for
the first meal of the week.
Please eat more slowly.
Oh, no.
Do you want me to do that?
Oh, here you are.
You have been so impatient
since a long time ago.
Is it okay?
Grandma!
I brought you a carpet board.
Yes!
Thank you for everything.
It's hot today.
You're sweating a lot.
I sweat a lot.
Did you try the corn from
our field the other day?
It was very delicious.
Next time, help me with your field.
Oh, thank you.
Can you help me with the cucumber?
I want to do it.
If you don't pick it up
quickly, it will crack.
Is that so?
Oh, I should go home.
Hey, come out here.
Yes.
Oh, it's been a while.
What?
You didn't say anything when Mio-chan came.
Well, it's been a while.
I told Mio-chan that you would come back.
You were good friends when you were little.
You played together every day.
I miss you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Of course, I am.
But I was surprised because
it's my first time to see you.
If you have a few days, let's
go to a classmate's house.
No, I don't want to.
I don't have anyone I want to meet.
You haven't changed at all.
You look the same.
You are the same.
Hey, Mio.
I got a watermelon. Do
you want to eat it? I told a lie.
Mio, whom I met after a long time,
became even cuter than before.
Mio was the Madonna of the school.
She was the manager
of the baseball club,
which everyone admired,
and she was popular.
The world where I lived was different
from the world where In-chan and I lived.
But for some reason, she was
concerned about me and took care of me.
But at that time, I
honestly felt like I wasn't
seen as a man, and
I didn't like it at all.
What?
Huh? Yeah, I'm just eating.
By the way, watermelon is the best.
It's my favorite fruit.
Fruit?
No, watermelon is a vegetable.
No, it's a fruit.
It's a vegetable.
No, it's sweet.
It's not sweet.
No, but it's sweet.
If you say it's sweet, it's sweet.
It's a fruit.
Sweet potatoes are sweet.
Sweet potatoes?
What? Watermelon? Watermelon.
Isn't it a vegetable?
What?
It's a vegetable.
It's not a fruit? Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It's hot, isn't it?
The air conditioner is broken now.
I can't say that the air conditioner
is broken in such a hot weather.
It can't be helped.
It's hard for a fisherman
to come to such a village.
Well, I can get used
to the hot weather soon.
I grew up here.
That's right.
I'm going to clean up the laundry.
Hey, I want to go to the
Tokyo Women's Festival.
I don't go there often, so I don't know.
I was looking forward to going
to the Tokyo Women's Festival.
Do you have a
girlfriend? Yes, I do.
Oh, I see.
How old are you? Where did you meet her?
I met her at the same
age at the university.
Oh, is she cute? Well, yes.
Oh, that's nice. She looks like an adult.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I haven't had a boyfriend for a long time.
What? Was Mio that popular?
Didn't she date a baseball player?
When did you talk about that?
I was surprised that Mio
didn't have a boyfriend.
I want to meet a nice person.
It's delicious.
It's really delicious.
【Birds chirping】
The next day, for some reason,
Mio came to my house to play.
I'm sure she has nothing
to do in the countryside.
I don't want to.
I'm going to the shop next door.
Can I ask you to help me?
OK. Be careful.
You, too.
Thank you.
Mio, what do you want
to eat for dinner? Sushi.
I like sushi.
That's good.
Wait a minute.
Are you going to have dinner?
I'm going to eat dinner.
Right. You're staying at my house tonight.
Didn't I tell you?
What?
I'm not staying at your house.
I'm not old enough.
You used to stay at my house a lot.
Right.
I used to, but not anymore.
It's OK.
You're like my daughter.
I'm just your friend.
I'm counting on you, Lutz.
I'm going to go.
I'm coming.
Welcome.
Stop it.
Hey, I have something to ask you.
Can I?
What is it?
Did you have a crush on her?
What? It's okay.
I'm your childhood friend.
Answer me.
Oh, well, I did.
I see.
How about compatibility? Is it OK?
What? Compatibility? I don't know.
Well, I guess it's OK.
Hmm.
What's wrong?
I have a problem.
I'm not good at flirting.
I don't know how to get along with others.
I see.
I don't think so.
So,
you are my sex partner.
What?
You mean I'm your sex partner?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
Don't make a joke.
No, no, no.
No? Please.
I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
No, no, no.
What are you doing? It's okay.
We are childhood friends.
No, we are not.
Are you serious? Yes, I am.
Can't you?
What?
Practice?
Yes.
I can't.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
What?
I have a girlfriend.
But your friend is worried about you.
Yes, but...
What?
Are your ears and nipples weak?
No, they are not.
It doesn't hurt at all.
What?
I can't do that.
But you don't resist at all.
I don't resist.
If you don't resist, it means
you like it, right? No, I'm fine.
I can't move.
You're fine, aren't
you? No, I'm not.
You're noisy.
It's weird.
What? It's weird.
It's not weird.
Say bonzai.
Bonzai.
Why?
Yes.
Bonzai.
I think it's a little disturbing.
Wait a minute.
Let me stretch a little.
No, no.
Look.
This way, like this.
Which one? This one.
Wait, Mio.
What?
I have to think like a child.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute.
This is strange.
Is it strange?
Mio, I'm not a child.
I decide if it's funny or not.
I'm sorry.
You can make a lot of noise.
Noise?
Yes.
It's embarrassing.
Isn't it a bit rude to bite your
nipple like this? It's not rude.
I'm a man.
Where is she?
She doesn't make a sound.
I've never done such a thing.
Then, I'll make you make a sound.
Make a sound? I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh! Wait a minute.
What?
I'm going to take it off.
Take it off? Here.
Can't you take it off?
No.
It's not a big deal.
I'm a little embarrassed.
What?
You've already taken it off.
It's not a big deal.
Look.
Don't do that.
If you do that, your
childhood friend will lick you.
I'm going to sleep.
You were licked by your childhood friend.
You were licked.
Don't say that. It's embarrassing.
Where do you feel good?
I'll look for it.
Here? What? Nothing.
Which one is better, you or her?
I can't compare with her.
What are you
doing? I'm practicing.
If you can't stand it, I'll do it harder.
Wait a minute.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to kiss you.
It feels good.
You shouldn't do that.
I'm so sorry.
You are so good at it.
Am I?
Are you better than my girlfriend?
No, I didn't mean that.
I was just saying how I feel.
Then,
I'll make you look embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
Yes.
Stand up.
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm not.
Can I sit down?
What?
Do you want to sit down?
I want to sit down.
Can you see me? Wait a minute.
How do you feel being licked by
your childhood friend? I was scared.
I would have licked you in many places.
What should I do? Like this.
I'm sleepy.
Wait, wait.
Don't do that.
You have a funny face.
Do you always do
like this? I don't know.
It's hot.
You shouldn't do like this.
Oh, my hand.
I've never done this before.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to slip.
I can't do it.
Look this way.
What are you doing?
What?
Hey,
Do you want to lick your
childhood friend's pussy?
Pussy?
Yes.
Really?
Come here.
Lick it.
Hey, lick me as if you were my girlfriend.
Oh, you're licking me like this.
But I'm not enough at all.
Oh..
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't stop until I go.
Ah!
Ah! It feels so good!
What are you going to do after this?
What are you going to do?
Koga-chan is not here.
Are you going to put it in as it is?
What?
Do you want to put it
in your childhood toy?
What? Wait a minute.
This is not good.
I think my dad's toy is better.
What?
Is it here?
Yes.
Oh, here it is.
Your dad is good.
My father used to hide
all these things over there.
Oh, did he? Yes, he did.
Is this OK?
Yes.
Can you put it on?
Well, I'm not sure.
Can I put it on? I did it.
You're good at it.
Why? I feel sick.
You are sick.
You look so sick.
Really?
,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,, Oh!
Oh!
We have sex at last.
Ah!
Something will pierce you.
Right?
Oh!
Oh! I want to move.
I want to move.
Oh! I'm excited.
I'm nervous.
Oh! I'm nervous.
It's hard.
It feels good.
It's too hard.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
No.
You were about to go.
Did she talk to you
about the daycare center?
What?
How was it? It was normal.
It was normal.
It's cold.
What should I do? It's cold.
We have a good chemistry, don't we?
I don't know if we have a good chemistry.
I think we have a good chemistry.
I'm sorry, but I can't help it.
That may be a good thing.
What?
Wow, I'm getting used to it.
I feel so good.
How long do I have
to do this? It's enough.
It's good, isn't
it? I feel so good.
I feel sick.
I'm sick.
Let's take a break.
A break? I'm sick, too.
I've never done this before.
Don't do it.
Don't you do it with
your girlfriend? I'm sorry.
Don't do it.
I'll let you go if you say yes.
You've been a patient type for a
long time, haven't you? Hang in there.
No, you can't.
No, you can't do that.
Put your head down.
Let me go.
Let me do it.
Oh, no.
I'm tired.
It's still my turn.
I feel better when you look at my face.
It's dangerous.
It's dangerous if you look at my face.
You look like that.
It's dangerous.
I can't do it anymore.
Hang in there.
I'm going to sleep.
Did you leave?
Did you leave? I'm sorry.
I told you no.
Why are you so fast?
Hey, Ryo!
What are you doing? My butt.
I drank the spirit of Sananajimi.
How did you drink it?
You can't drink it, can you?
It's already over.
Can you drink it again?
You are taking a video, aren't you?
You can do whatever you like.
Whatever I like?
You can do many things that
you can't do to your girlfriend.
Really?
It's amazing that you can do it right
away even though I told you to do it.
Isn't it iron? It's very hard.
You can use my pussy more.
You can do what you can't always do.
You should have told me earlier.
We are a good match,
aren't we? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let's go crazy together.
Together?
Yes.
Let's go crazy.
Pretty... It's pretty
good... Pretty good...
Ah, hot.
Take me out.
Where should I take you out?
Take me out to the bello.
No, to the bello.
Ah, hot.
Take me out.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
My neck hurts.
It's so good.
I feel so good.
Great.
It's your second time,
but you feel so good.
I'm sure you two get along well.
I like you.
What?
It seems that our body
compatibility was the best, and
that day I had sex many times
until my mother came back.
Oh, it looks delicious.
Well, let's eat it right away.
Yes, let's eat.
Let's eat!
Which one do you
want to eat? Salmon roe.
You really like salmon
roe, don't you? Yes, I love it.
Oh, there is seaweed.
It's good.
How is it? It's good.
Anago is the best, isn't it?
Anago?
Anago is the best.
By the way, can you eat anago?
Anago? I can eat it.
I'm used to eat it.
You are an adult.
Of course.
I can eat anago.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Tuna is good, too.
Tuna is the best.
You don't have to look at it.
What?
Tuna is the best?
Yes.
I'm going to talk while eating.
I'm going to eat while talking.
It was delicious.
I'm so full.
It's been a while since we had sushi.
Thank you for the tea.
It was so good.
It was, wasn't
it? Let's clean up.
What did we do during the day?
Did you go out? Well.
..
Well, but... What did we do?
We did a lot of things.
A lot of things?
A lot of things.
We talked about the old days.
We played games, too.
Yes, we did.
Games? Yes, we did.
It was nostalgic.
It was a long time ago.
Yes, it was.
You two get along well.
Shall we sit down? No, thanks.
You are our guest.
Really? Thank you.
Hayato.
I came here because I
wanted to do something erotic.
What are you talking about?
Your mother is here.
Were you excited during the day?
What do you mean?
I didn't have time, but I can't.
You can't? I can't.
It's okay.
I can't.
I'll be scolded.
I have an aunt. Let's kiss.
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
Are you okay? I'm okay.
He says he's okay.
You like this,
don't you? It's dark.
Are you sure you don't want
to be found out? Don't worry.
You like me, don't you?
I like you, but... Don't worry.
If you touch here, your
voice will come out.
Of course.
Hey, Mio.
What do you want for breakfast tomorrow?
What do you want to eat?
Breakfast?
Bread or rice? I want bread.
Bread?
Do you have any side dishes
you want to eat? I don't know.
Egg? Egg? I got it.
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
But you were a little excited,
weren't you? No, I wasn't.
I was excited, but...
You know all the weaknesses.
I don't know.
Don't make a sound.
Hey, you guys.
Yes?
Is your face all right?
My face?
Yes.
I'm not stabbed.
It's not broken.
If you need it, put it on.
OK.
The air conditioner is
broken and it's still open.
Oh, I see.
You like the left one, don't you?
Are you all right?
You have a puffy face.
Do you have a puffy
face even though I'm here?
Are you OK?
I'm going to touch you.
You don't look at me at all.
Look at me.
You look painful.
Don't do that.
Hang in there.
Hey, Rio.
What?
Did you bring the
toothbrush? I did.
Did you?
Yes.
I was going to give it to
you if you didn't have it.
Really? Thank you.
You are a good girl.
Thank you.
You did your best.
I didn't play.
You didn't.
But you did your best.
――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――――
You're making me feel sick.
I'm going to make you feel sick.
I'm going to make some noise.
Noise?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I feel light.
Oh, it's gone.
Hey, Mio.
Yes?
Aren't you thirsty?
Well, I think I'm fine now.
I see.
Let me know if you want to drink something.
Okay.
I'll make you some coffee later.
Oh, thanks.
Thank you.
It's no good.
It's close.
What are you going to do if it's found out?
Was it hard for you to be stopped
when you wanted to play Seiji?
It's a little hard.
I want to bully him a lot.
He is unconscious.
Let's go.
He is coming.
What?
It's time to take it out, isn't it?
It's a little dangerous.
What?
Dangerous?
Yes.
Do you want to
take it out? I do.
Are you okay?
You can take it off.
Oh, you're out of your mind
in front of your grandmother.
She drank it.
Hey, you guys!
What is it?
We can sleep in the same room, right?
Is it OK? Yes, it's OK.
I'll prepare a bed for you.
OK.
Are you OK?
Thank you for the meal.
And we decided to sleep in the same room.
Wake up.
It's too hot to sleep.
You're awake.
It's so hot that I can't sleep at all.
Hey, let's have sex secretly
so that my mom doesn't find out.
It's good.
Let's do it.
I'm going to be addicted to being with you.
That's right.
Because you've been the best match so far.
It's good, isn't it?
Look, you don't hate it.
Give me your tongue.
I like kissing you.
You really like ears, don't you?
I'll fill your brain with me.
Your voice came out.
You really like me, don't you?
If you make such a voice,
Grandma will find out.
I like your happy face.
I love the way you feel my nipples.
You want me to lick your
nipples quickly, don't you?
nipples like this, don't you?
This nipple is amazing.
I can't stop licking your nipples.
Look at my face carefully.
Look at me.
Look at me a lot when I talk to you.
I like to move my lips like this, too.
I'll be a little loud, so
don't make a sound.
Don't go out yet.
Because you want to have
sex with me, don't you?
So don't go out yet.
Oh, my goodness.
Well, lick my hand.
It's not good for you to come here.
Lick my hand.
How do you like my smooth hand?
Do you have a girlfriend?
What do you think?
You lick me very well.
It feels good.
I want to get along with you.
I want to sleep more.
You are so wet.
You are so sticky.
Hey, do you want to have sex?
I'll put you in my arms.
I put you in my arms.
Oh, my God.
I think I'll be fine if I just put it in.
I'm getting used to it little by little.
How do you feel?
You can't do this to
your girlfriend, can you?
I'm so happy to be able to work with you.
You want to see a movie, don't you?
I've never been this
down on my knees before.
Let me go.
Let me go from behind.
I used up all my manko.
I can't hold my voice any more.
I love this self.
I love it.
I want to look at my face properly.
I want you to taste my pussy.
You look like you can't stand it anymore.
I want you to let out a lot of your blood.
You can do it.
It's okay.
Let it out to your mouth.
Wow, it's freezing.
How many times have I done this today?
I think I can sleep well tonight.
But I might wake up again.
It's time to take a bath.
It's the best time to take a bath.
I feel so good.
I want to take a bath.
Let's take a bath.
Here we go.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's dangerous to take a bath at once.
Oh, no.
You've already taken a bath.
I took a bath by myself.
What did you buy?
Did you find it? I think so.
You found it again.
What are you doing? I found it.
I'm embarrassed.
What are you going to do?
I'm embarrassed to take a bath.
Are you?
I'm embarrassed.
I can't take a bath without permission.
Ouch!
If you find out that I'm washing
my body, you'll be in trouble.
It's OK.
Do you want me to wash your body?
Your body? Yes, your body.
It's OK.
I can wash my body by myself.
What? It's OK.
Well, I'm going to tell my mom.
What?
I'm going to tell her that we
are taking a bath together.
That's not fair.
You can't do that.
Can I wash my face?
Please wash your face.
Can I?
I did it.
I'm Toshi.
Sit here.
Here?
Yes.
You are good at saying.
I'm not good at it.
Thank you.
I'm embarrassed.
You're just laughing.
I'm embarrassed to be seen.
But I can do this.
What's this?
I want to do this every
day when I get married.
You want to be petted, don't you?
You are rubbing your boobs.
It may feel good.
What should I do? Speak up.
I can't.
What? My mom is here.
It's OK.
No, it's not.
I'll be drunk.
Really?
I feel good, too.
What?
I'll massage your butt.
My butt? Yes, your butt.
It's not sexy, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
I feel good when I do this.
You feel good?
What? Hey, touch me.
Touch you? That's right.
I always get used to being with you.
So, play with me more.
I'm so sleepy.
What did you
say? I feel so good.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm sleepy, too.
I'm sleepy.
Are you tired? No, I'm not.
Thank you.
You look so tired.
No, I'm not.
I don't know what to do.
I'll clean up here.
What? Why are you running away?
You like my Fela, don't you?
I'm not running away. I feel good.
I'm so hungry.
I'm not done yet.
You can't do that.
You're about to puke.
You're so full.
I'm about to puke.
What's that? It's hot.
You can spit it out.
Spit it out in your mouth.
Ouch!
【A】
【A】 【A】
【A】 【A】 【A】
【A】
I'll keep it a secret so
that you won't find out.
It's quite beautiful.
It's been a long time
since I saw fireworks.
It's so beautiful.
Do you want to run?
It's getting smaller.
A little more.
You're fast.
A little more?
The movement of the house is the best.
Is it? It's beautiful.
Are you going home tomorrow?
Yes.
If your girlfriend finds
out, you'll be in trouble.
I guess so.
Do you like her? I guess so.
I'm more sexy and cute.
What are you talking about?
I don't think so.
But I think we have a good compatibility.
Well, long-distance relationship
is lonely, so it's impossible.
What? Are you
serious? That's right.
I've loved you for a long time.
Well, even if I'm not there, there
are a lot of guys who like you.
That's not true. I like you.
It's easy to be with you.
That's because you haven't
seen me as a man yet.
No, that's not true. I've been
seeing you as a man for a long time.
Let's make a promise
not to forget at the end.
Let me remember everything in my body.
It may be the last time to be with me.
Thank you for being with me at the end.
You don't have to do it carefully.
Do it seriously.
I love being licked.
I love everything about you.
Lick me more.
Do you still love me?
I don't love you.
I want to lick you.
I want you to lick me.
I want you to lick me a lot.
It feels good.
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
I don't want to go.
Why?
My legs...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I want to cry.
I want to cry, too.
Oh, no.
It feels so good.
I'll hug you.
I'm sorry.
I beg you.
It's hot, isn't it?
What's wrong?
Do you like my body? I love you.
Here you are.
I'm sorry.
Go, go, go.
Ventriloquism More.
More.
I can't get it off.
Do it one more time.
It feels good, doesn't
it? I want more.
I want you to hit me more.
More.
Hit me more.
Give me a kiss.
More.
I'm going to sleep.
It's painful, isn't it?
I'm going to do what you like the most.
What I like the most?
What you like the most.
What I like the most.
Is that so? I'm scared.
You like this,
right? I feel so bad.
I'm going to cry.
This may be the last time I cry.
まけおいまけ、.
No!
Do you know how much I love you?
I don't want it to end yet.
Say, I love you.
I love you.
I will never take my life out.
Please do it forever.
I love you.
I love you so much.
※This is a sound effect.
I'm sorry.
I'm always sorry.
Is this the taste of the
last life? Oh! Come here.
Over there?
Yes.
Are you OK? I'm sorry.
I miss you.
I want to be with you. I
want to be with you forever.
I want to be with you, too.
Will you stay with
me? Yes, I will.
Really?
Yes.
You are blushing.
You are cute.
This is the best memory.
Me, too.
This is a record of a few
days when I was drunk on
sex in the countryside
with my childhood friend.