Thank you for your hard
work until the late shooting.
Thank you for your hard work.
You look a little gloomy.
Do I look gloomy?
I have only one reason.
Please introduce yourself to the camera.
Hello, everyone. I'm Ibuki Aoi.
Ibuki Aoi, how are you?
I'm fine.
How long has it been
since you made your debut?
It's been about 3 years.
How many videos have you made so far?
About 30 videos.
You're a veteran.
No, I'm not.
I'm a newbie.
Are you enjoying the shooting?
Yes, I am.
Can you tell us about today's shooting?
I'd like you to tell me about your date.
It's a 24-hour date with a man.
I'm going to have sex until the morning.
I see.
I'd like you to tell me about your date.
Can you tell us about
your first impression?
My first impression?
Well...
It was the so-called MO-kun.
He was my opponent.
I was wondering how it would be.
I think I was able to ride in a
good wave from the middle.
It was really fun.
Did you ride in a good wave?
I rode in a good wave.
I hope so.
If you have any memorable
scenes or highlights, please tell us.
Memorable scenes and highlights?
Well, it's a rare thing,
so I don't have a script.
So I think I can enjoy
watching such scenes.
I think you can enjoy
watching it today as well.
The main part of this work will start soon,
so please send a message to the viewers.
The date scene is very
fresh and I can see it,
so please don't fast forward
and watch until the end!
Please!
Ta-da!
Hello!
I'm Aoi Ibuki!
Yay!
Today,
I got this camera I heard that you can go
on a date with a guy just the two of you.
I'm nervous to go on a
date just the two of us.
I don't know what kind of person will come.
I have no idea who will come.
Who will it be?
I want someone who is easy to talk to.
Someone who is fun to be with.
Because it's a date.
So, let's go to the place where we
are going to meet up with my friends!
Let's go!
I made it to the place where we
are going to meet up with my friends.
I can't see them at all.
I feel like I'm the only one who's waiting.
It's not good to make a girl wait.
If you're a man, you should
have arrived at the place first.
Shouldn't you be waiting?
Oh, there you are!
there he is!
there he is hello.
today's date today's date.
it's been a while yeah it's
been a year how are you I'm
good how are you today's
date Aizawa I'm Aizawa-kun.
Is it okay to call you Aizawa-kun?
It's okay.
I'm Aizawa-kun.
You're so small.
You're not in the frame.
You're beautiful.
I don't like it.
I was waiting for you.
Did you wait for me?
Yes, I did.
Did you mix it well?
I think a man's clothes
should be decided first.
It's sudden, isn't it?
After this, it's half and half.
Let's take a two-shot in commemoration.
Is it okay if I take it?
Can you hold this for me?
I parked my car here Oh, you parked
your car here Yes, I parked my car here
I have a lot of things to
show you Aizawa-kun's.
I have a lot of places I want to go.
You have a lot of places you want
to go to Places you want to go to?
Yes, I have a lot of
places I want to go to.
Let's decide what to wear.
There is a big park nearby.
Did you look it up?
Yes, I did.
It's like a date.
I like this style.
This is cute.
How is it?
It's very cute.
I think it's a little cheap, but it's cute.
It's super cute.
That's the problem.
Let's go straight.
Oh, I was escorted.
Thank you.
I'll close it.
I'm going to go to a big park.
Oh, a park.
Let's go there.
Let's go.
Let's go There is
also a aquarium.
Oh, wow.
Let's go to Aizawa-kun's
date plan Oh, I see.
I'll buy some food and go on a picnic.
Sounds good.
It's like a date.
Yes, it is.
Did you think about it?
Yes, I did.
That's cute.
You thought about it.
Yes, I did.
Okay, I'm looking forward to it.
Okay.
to make me happy
I'll leave it to you.
I'll go
Please insert the card.
Wow I'm leaving Let's go.
You had a driver's license You had a
driver's license I have a driver's license.
You have a driver's license.
I don't think you have a driver's license.
I got it right away.
Right away?
When I was 18 years old.
When you were 18 years old?
Yes.
I'm going to a driving school right now.
Is that so?
I feel like I lost.
You have a driver's license.
Have you ever thought
about where you want to go?
Where do you want to go?
Are you nervous?
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
Your legs are beautiful.
What are you looking at?
Because it's a mini skirt?
I don't know.
Please concentrate
on driving I will.
But we are alone in the car.
I'm sorry Can I
take a drive date?
We are alone We are alone
It's a date for two It's a date.
I'm happy What are
you looking forward to?
Well...
What are you looking forward to?
I can't help but look forward to it.
But today is said to be a date, so
you may go on a picnic and break up.
What?
You may go on a picnic and break up.
What is it?
A date.
Oh, that kind of thing?
Yeah, that kind of thing.
I'm happy with that.
Oh, really? Then let's do that.
Let's do that.
It's a good memory.
Well, it depends on Aizawa-kun, right?
It depends on me.
I'm late, so I'm
going to... That's right.
Kusatsu Onsen is a good place.
I've never been to Kusatsu Onsen.
Oh, really?
I think so.
It's a good place to
go if you're not in a car.
Onsen has a sexy sound.
There is a place called Yubatake
which is 300m away from here.
There are so many butterflies.
What?
Do your best to speak.
You are blabbering.
When I go to the beach at night,
there are a lot of people,
and I feel like I'm in a fairy tale.
I see.
You were able to talk.
We talked a lot.
Wearing a yukata and
going on a date is the best.
With whom?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please look forward to the sequel.
It's up to you.
I don't know.
The park.
It feels good to walk in the park.
What?
Don't look at me.
Don't look at my thighs.
Your legs are longer than Aizawa-kun's.
Maybe longer than Aizawa-kun's.
How tall are you?
158 cm.
So small!
So cute!
You're 158 cm tall.
It's cute.
Mr. Aoi.
Can I call you Ibuki?
Yes, you can.
How many centimeters is it?
163 centimeters.
It's 5 centimeters.
It's like a model size.
What is it?
Can I praise you?
If you compliment me, I'm happy.
But it's true.
It's true.
I forgot to put out a wink.
Concentrate.
You're doing it in the same way.
Don't you come here often?
I don't come here often.
You don't come here often?
Sometimes I come here for cosplay events.
Oh, Big Saito?
Yes, Big Saito.
Like Comiket?
Yes.
Are you going to cosplay?
I want to.
Why?
You should.
Like a baker.
Oh, a baker.
I'm from the factory.
I'm Koushi.
Most of them are anime characters.
Please look forward and drive.
It's not shiny.
Is it fun to drive?
It's fun.
You say it's fun because I'm next to you.
That's right.
Because you're next to me.
It's fun to have a dog next to you.
That's what a popular man is.
Can I go back in time?
It's too late.
I'm driving now.
I wonder if this is okay.
I think the picnic will be canceled.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work, too.
It's too hard for me.
I can't be with you.
Mental damage?
Mental damage.
I can't be with you.
I don't know how to make you enjoy today.
I've been thinking about it.
I heard that there is also a aquarium.
Because it's close to the sea.
Do you like aquariums?
I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it either.
Which one do you like?
You just said you like it.
I just said that.
Well... The bottom...
Well... What?
The bottom part is old.
I don't know which one it is.
By the way, what's the
reason you don't like it?
The reason I don't like it
is... I'm afraid of the sea.
I'm afraid of the ocean.
I'm fine with the sea I'm looking at.
The surface of the sea.
I see.
In the sea.
In the dark water.
I don't like sharks. I'm afraid of them.
I see.
I hate sharks the most in the world.
I'm afraid of ghosts, but I
can watch scary images.
But I can't watch sharks.
Do you mean sharks?
Not only sharks.
I don't really like the view from here.
It's deep and dark.
I can't reach my feet.
I see.
I thought it was a scary place
where you can't reach your feet.
I think it's okay.
The pool is okay.
Did you make a mistake?
Are you in a hurry?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
What?
Did you make a mistake?
I want to tease you.
You made a mistake even
if you didn't say it strictly.
It's obvious.
It's obvious mistake.
How will you fix it?
I'm confused.
Confused?
Do you have a Ferris wheel?
Oh.
How is it?
Ferris wheel is good
Don't you want to ride it?
Ferris wheel is good Oh, really?
Let's ride a Ferris wheel.
Or let's go to a private room
for two Are you aiming for it?
Are you aiming for it?
Do you have any plans for a date?
I want to go on a date.
Really!?
A date you want to go on?
A date I admire?
A date you admire.
Or a date you want to go on?
A date you want to go on.
A date?
I see.
I want to go on a date.
I want to go to an amusement park.
I don't have to go out.
I can go on a date at home.
You can relax.
I can watch a movie at
home and cook together.
That's good.
I like that.
It's relaxing, isn't it?
Yes.
Is it an amusement park?
Aizawa-kun?
Well... Well...
What should I say?
Well... Well... I'd like to go to a
dream country such as Tokyo or L.A.
Dream country is definitely
something I want to visit.
And the onsen we just went to.
Onsen is definitely a good idea.
I wore a yukata at night and
walked around in a capo capo.
Capo capo?
What?
I walked around in a Zori Zori.
Zori Zori?
Capo capo?
I walked around in a capo
capo while wearing a yukata.
Kappo Kappo What is Kappo Kappo?
Walk What is Kappo Kappo?
Go to the footbath together.
Oh, that's good.
There is a footbath in September.
And at night?
Bathroom.
Bathroom at night.
Sleep in the bathroom
Sleep in the bathroom?
Sleep in the bathroom No
no no I've never heard of it.
Really?
I'm going to sleep in the bathroom.
You're so excited.
That's good.
I want to have a hot
spring date in the bathroom.
Bathroom?
I want to sleep in the bathroom at night.
I'm going to sleep in the kitchen.
You don't like it?
No, I don't.
I don't like it.
I'm going to the amusement park.
Can I ride a ride?
I love the theme park near Mt.Fuji.
It's the most famous theme park in Japan.
Do you go there often?
Have you been there recently?
Oh, you haven't been there recently.
But I need someone who can ride a scooter.
I'm looking forward to it.
I have to go there with you.
Can you ride a scooter?
I can't.
We can't get on the train, can we?
Wait a minute.
I want to get on the train.
We have arrived.
We're here.
Oh, Ferris wheel.
Today is the day to rescue the aquarium.
We couldn't go to the aquarium on the way.
Ferris wheel is working.
Yes, it's moving.
I'm here.
Please be careful not
to hit the side of the bus.
I'm here.
Thank you for driving.
You're welcome.
Thank you for telling me.
I'm here.
I'm safe.
I want to go to Shizuoka.
There is a car about 110 meters away.
110 meters away?
I wonder how many times
bigger than Aizawa-kun.
I wonder how many times bigger.
It's Aizawa-kun's bag.
It's a big Ferris wheel.
One more time.
It's a Ferris wheel pose.
It's not cool.
I don't know what to pose.
It's good.
It's great.
It's cute.
It's good.
What?
Selfie?
No.
It's unnatural.
I don't like it.
You look disgusting.
I don't like glasses.
I don't think so.
I just wear black clothes.
Why do you look at me
with such a dirty look?
I don't like it.
It's a little... It's a
little... It's like that.
It's not a bad thing to
have a hidden agenda.
But if you're forced
to do it... It's a real...
It's a serious face.
It's really depressed.
He's sleeping.
What if he tries to make
up with you by driving?
He'll get lost.
He'll be late.
What?
Why are you advertising?
what are you doing?
but at that time, we had
a lot of fun driving together
so I wanted to drive
a bit more so I made a
mistake on the way I don't
know about that though.
2 tickets, 1,600 yen.
Thank you very much.
Here you are.
It's 400 yen and a ticket for two.
Thank you very much.
Have a nice day.
This is my first date.
Are you going to drop it?
It's my first time.
It's an honor.
It means I'm stealing.
Good morning.
Please wait here.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
It's here.
Finally.
It feels faster at night.
Yeah, I think so, too.
From the outside, it
looks like it's moving.
Well, it's a secret room,
but... Wait a minute.
Thank you very much for your ride.
It's like... It's like... It's like...
It's like... It's
like... It's like...
It's like... I don't
want to go with you!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't want to!
I don't want to go with you!
Well, I mean... I mean... I
mean, it's a beautiful place.
I'm sorry.
You idiot!
I've seen that kind of thing.
You look at it and you know what it's like.
Girls are like that.
I know you're watching.
You know?
I couldn't see it.
I couldn't see the color.
It's a green.
I'm just using the scanner.
Can I go over there?
I'm sorry.
It's a green.
The sky and the forest are all lined
up, showing off everyone's heart.
Tokyo Bay's horizon line spanning
out before you, the scenery and
the blend of the sky, state and
the foliage, can warm your mind.
And this f***ing
f***ing f***ing f***ing
f***ing f***ing f**k was
erected as a landmark.
What are you doing?
No.
You're a pervert.
Why do you look that
way Isn't that tilting?
It looks a bit tilted
I'm scared It looks a bit
tilted I'm scared Tilt,
please You are tilting.
Wow.
The looks.
Pretty There is no such
thing This is beautiful
It's a big space walk,
so please enjoy it.
It's okay, I'm here.
I'm a little unreliable.
I can't relax.
Because I'm on the wrong way.
I wonder if there was a manly place.
Please enjoy the magnificent
360-degree aerial walk.
I didn't say anything to make him nervous.
He's talking a lot.
I'm fine.
I don't like it.
Look at this.
What is this?
He's trying hard.
He's trying hard to look manly.
I want to kiss you.
Why?
Why do you want to kiss me?
Anyone is fine.
Anyone is fine as long as you can kiss me.
No, no, no.
Anyone else?
I want to kiss you.
Do you choose me?
You don't choose me, do you?
You don't care who I am, do you?
No, I don't.
If you can kiss me, you
don't care who I am, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't care who you are.
She is so cute.
I'm waiting for the next train.
I want to kiss more.
It's the top of the mountain.
Isn't it too early?
I want to kiss like that.
I can't wait.
We have artificially created
fresh water ponds, I can't wait.
I can't wait.
Let's wait.
Let's wait until we get to the top.
I can't wait.
The Bird Sanctuary
is a two-story facility
where you can look out
over the bird sanctuary.
The center has videos and
panels on display for you to enjoy,
and you can also use binoculars
to observe the wild birds.
The Bird Sanctuary is
located in the south of Tokyo.
The glass dome is located in
the south of the bird sanctuary.
I'm going to kiss you.
You can't do it at all.
You have to hold it up to the top.
I'm going to kiss you.
People use the hotel
not only when visiting the
park, but also when
visiting the surrounding area.
I knew you were going to say that!
Read it!
It's pretty long.
What should I do?
Oh, you have to wait.
Oh, I see.
In the Tokyo 2020 Olympics, it will be
used as the venue for the canoe slalom.
You can see the canoe slalom.
in the Tokyo 2020 Olympics.
The course you see on the east side.
is approximately 200 meters long.
While passing through the
gate set up during the course.
It is a competition to compete for time
and technique to go down to the finish.
The course that you see on
the left is approximately 200
meters long Competitors
have to pass through the gates
while finishing with the best
time and technique I don't think so.
The Ferris wheel is now approaching
the highest point, 117 meters.
Please enjoy the
magnificent 360-degree view.
I can't believe it.
I can't stand it.
Here it comes.
I thought he would kiss me
because I couldn't hold it anymore.
I see.
Why are you laughing?
I don't like it.
I'm trying not to hit you.
You're so pumped up.
Where's Teppei?
Teppei is over there.
Don't you want to cross Teppei?
I definitely want to cross Teppei.
Teppei is over there, isn't it?
I want to cross Teppei.
Teppei is over there.
If you look from the west to the south,
you will see the Tokyo Tower, the Tokyo
Metropolitan Government Building, the
Rainbow Bridge, and the Haneda Airport.
If you look closely from the west to the
southwest, you can see the Tokyo Tower, the
Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building,
the Rainbow Bridge, and the Haneda Airport.
You can also see the Tokyo
Skytree in the north-west direction.
In addition, you can also see the
Tokyo Skytree to the north-west.
You did it well.
One more time?
Are you in a good mood?
Aren't you in a good mood
because you did it once?
I'm in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood for now.
Please look at the camera.
It's cute.
We have to start the juice.
You look so good.
I'm so shy.
But...
I want to do something.
I'm not a serious person.
I'm not good at it.
What?
My voice is coming out.
I don't feel anything.
One, two, three.
Why?
Why do I feel like this?
I don't think I've ever
touched a cat before.
No, you haven't.
It's cute.
You're doing your best.
But that's not the kind of place you're in.
I don't know.
What kind of place?
My body is moving, but
I want you to touch me.
But you said you could endure it.
I can't stand it anymore.
You can't stand it anymore?
I just touched it a little,
but it's already gone.
Isn't it fast?
Did you see the panoramic view
of the Ocean and the magnificent
scenery around the park
during the 17-minute aerial walk?
Did you see the panoramic view of
Answered by Riku ○△×△×△×●▲★
And its surrounding areas along with the
magnificent scenery off in the distance?
Answered by Riku ○△×△×△×△×●▲★
Thank you for boarding at ○△×△×△×△×●▲.
Thank you very much
for riding the giant
Ferris wheel from
Diamond Hill Flowers today.
Sounds fun!
Please sit down at the platform.
Hey, I'm standing up.
Why?
No, this is...
I'm only touching my nipples.
Why are you standing up?
I don't know.
Isn't it weird?
What do you mean you can't stand it?
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to eat something?
Yes, I do.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
In this situation,
I can't date.
I'm so upset.
I'm going to eat it before it comes out.
It's almost there.
He's hiding it.
He's so pathetic.
I don't think so.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was good.
It went by so fast.
It was like 17 or 18 minutes.
18 minutes?
It was like 5 or 6 minutes.
That's what the announcer said.
I didn't hear anything.
My consciousness...
My consciousness went to another place.
Did you hear anything?
I heard nothing.
What's wrong?
Stop it.
I want to eat fish cake.
Let's challenge.
No, no, no.
It's good.
You're a bit over the top.
I can't do it.
I'm just trying to do my best.
I know, I know, I know.
Come on.
Hey, don't poke out your nipples.
Don't poke out your nipples.
That's good, that's good.
That's why it's called Asakusa.
I can't do it.
3, 2, 1.
It's fun.
I can't do it.
It was fun.
You did your best.
I like this line-up.
You look so happy.
I like this so much.
You look like a gay.
I love this.
This is funny.
I got a good picture.
New feature, Aoharu Story.
It's outside, so it's a place in Tokyo.
I want something like this.
I want it.
It's so cute.
I'm going to use this as a thread.
Wow, it's beautiful and spacious.
It's so good.
You're good.
I don't think so.
I have a camera.
You look nervous.
I'm fine.
What are you thinking about?
It was fun.
It was sudden.
Oh well, it's Kanna.
Wait, he's wearing a
wax That's not good.
He's wearing a hat and a wax.
It's embarrassing It's cute
Do you have anything to drink?
Yeah, what do you have?
Let me see.
Water.
It's a really nice room.
Are you going to open it for me?
You're manly.
Are you showing off?
I'm not manly.
I'm going to open this.
Thank you.
You're trying to make up
for what you've been told.
I've been told that.
I made a mistake, but I also
made a mistake in putting it in.
Don't laugh.
I also made a mistake in putting it in.
What are you laughing at?
Was it fun?
It was fun.
I'm going to put a
fake lamp on Oh.
Fake lamp.
It's good.
I really like this.
I'm going to put it on
top No, I'm sorry It's
better to have two
It's better to have two.
It's more fun to have two
I'm doing my best I don't want
to wear the cap backwards.
I'm serious.
I was surprised when I was suddenly kissed.
Were you surprised?
I was surprised.
Are you satisfied?
What?
One more time?
Satisfied?
Then it's over.
What do you think?
The view is really nice.
The view?
It's nice.
It's getting hot.
What?
It's really nice.
It's not beautiful.
I'm scared.
I'm scared to stand in the back.
It's a little scary, but it's beautiful.
Look.
What is it?
It's amazing.
Why do you always take it?
You always have it, don't you?
Can you reach it?
You are great.
You are amazing.
You were great.
I'm sad.
You are sad.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Why do you feel it just by doing this?
Because it's easy to feel.
What? You haven't changed.
Why do you feel it just by doing this?
You really like it, don't you?
I'm not going to touch you.
He's so nervous.
I want you to touch me.
You want me to touch you already?
Isn't it too early?
You like to be tickled, don't you?
I like to be tickled.
I'll tickle you a lot.
I'm not going to touch you.
What?
Oh.
I don't feel anything.
You haven't touched it yet.
I think this is enough.
You can feel it without touching it.
This is a good spot.
I don't feel anything.
How do you feel when I touch here?
It feels good when I touch your nails.
Like this?
Yes.
This is good.
Yes, this is good.
It feels good when I touch here.
It's okay.
He's standing up.
What?
Oh my god.
He stands up when I touch his neck.
Let me touch your neck.
Do you want to?
Do you like the shape of your nipples?
Yes.
What?
My nipples?
Yes.
They feel good.
Really?
Yes.
They feel good?
I want you to do your best.
I'll do my best.
You like this, don't you?
I can feel it again.
Oh, you like it.
That's good.
I'll do it directly.
Directly?
Do you like it more?
Can I take this off?
No, no, no.
I can't see it, so I want to
take it off You can't take it off.
No, I don't want to.
It's painful.
Oh my god.
What's wrong?
I feel good.
I haven't touched it directly yet.
I haven't touched the area around it.
I don't think so.
Do you want me to do it around here?
No, I want you to do it directly.
Directly?
Like this?
Yes.
I don't think I can do it.
Do you like it when I scratch your nails?
Yes, I like it.
I'm trying to look at you, but I can't.
Oh no, I can't.
You're trying to look at my body.
Oh no.
Your nipples are so small.
I can't see anything.
I can't see it.
Why?
What?
I can't see it.
What can't you see?
Can I open my fingers?
No, you can't.
Do you want me to lick you?
Please lick me.
Please.
I've only licked around you.
Not around you.
Oh, it's hot.
Does it feel good?
Oh, no.
This is too much.
Too much?
I'm worried about the bottom.
Oh, no.
Show me what's going on.
Can I take this off?
Can I take the top off as well?
No, no, no.
Which one do you like better?
Which one do you like more?
Should I stop it?
No, I don't like that either.
Look at this.
Wait, wait.
Ui, take it off.
I'm sorry.
I should take this off.
You took it off.
Do you want to take it off by yourself?
Yes.
You look happy.
You look so happy.
Don't run away.
Wait a minute.
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's stained.
Uri, Uri, Uri, Uri, Uri, Uri, Uri.
I'm a little embarrassed.
This is a bit embarrassing.
You are excited.
You are naked now.
How do you feel?
Are you still standing in this situation?
You are a pervert.
Am I a pervert?
Yes.
What are you doing now?
Please do it properly.
What are you doing?
Please touch me.
Please.
Can I touch you?
You are trembling.
Oh, I see.
What?
I'm not doing anything.
You're so stubborn.
You're making that face.
Oh, no.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
I want to drink with you.
You really like me, don't you?
I'm going to put it in your mouth.
Where do you want me to put it?
It's close to your nose.
I don't need this.
I want you to eat it.
It's getting really hard.
Wow, it's so good.
I want you to lick me.
That's too fast.
You like to be teased, don't you?
But I want you to lick me.
You want me to lick you?
Ah.
Why are you frowning?
Wow.
Ah.
It's crazy.
It's too simple.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm not in a good mood.
You have a camera.
Take a picture of me.
From this side?
Yes, from this side.
I got it.
That's all I can do.
Can you take a good picture?
Can you see it?
Yes, I can.
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
It's too strong.
It's getting bigger.
It feels good.
I'm a boy.
I want to see your boobs.
My boobs?
I want to see them.
Show me.
Okay.
You've learned.
Is this okay?
I want to see you in person.
You want to see me in person?
It's special.
Thank you.
You have big boobs, so make them bigger.
Hey.
It's so big.
I took it off for you.
I want you to pinch me.
You want me to pinch you?
Yes, I want you to pinch me.
Like this.
Wow, it's amazing.
What do you mean?
You want me to pinch you, right?
I'm pinching you.
Does it feel good?
What are you enjoying?
I'll do it like this.
It's too fast.
What's that?
I'll do it like this.
Wait a minute.
Are you going to do it?
It's too fast.
Wait a minute.
What?
You're the only one who's feeling better.
What's that?
Isn't that bad?
Hey, make yourself feel better next week.
Yes, I will.
Come here.
Come on, hurry up.
What?
I'll make myself feel better.
I'm going to do it.
Can you do it?
It's so beautiful.
I'm going to do it.
Use your tongue more.
It's not good.
I can't reach it.
Concentrate on licking.
I'm going to lick this part too.
Lick that part a lot.
You're good at licking.
I can feel your pain.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I want you to lick my nipples and hug me.
You want me to do that?
You're asking too much.
You're getting carried away.
You like it, don't you?
You have to pay for it, don't you?
This one?
Yes, yes, yes.
You like this one too, don't you?
Yes.
I like it, I like it.
Do you like people in the basement too?
Yes, I like it.
It's a baby's play.
Is it a baby's play?
Yeah.
It feels good to touch it.
Yeah, it feels good.
Let's lick it.
He said, Babu.
Babu.
It's pathetic.
Yeah.
This side too.
Yes.
Oh, my goodness What?
Oh my goodness.
Do you feel good?
Wow, this part is hard Yes.
He is getting excited
Let's lick your nipples.
How much do you like your nipples?
How do you feel when you are licked?
I feel like I'm being pulled.
Oh, my God.
You're eating so much.
I'm going to drink this one.
I can't hold it in.
You can't hold it in?
I didn't put it in yet.
I want to put it in.
You're the best I'm going to sleep Did
you become a man who can't stand it?
You can stand it with
this costume I can't stand
it I can't stand it anymore
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
Oh.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it's cool
It's hot It's hot It's hot.
You look like a gentleman.
Ibuki, it feels so good.
I'm going to rub your back.
That feels good.
Does it?
I love this feeling.
I'm going to rub your back.
That's great.
You can't go yet.
I can't do it.
Sorry.
I told you not to do that.
I'm sorry.
You can't stand it, can you?
You can still do it, can't you?
I'm so happy.
Hold on.
I'll hold on.
I don't know.
Let me try again.
I haven't done it yet.
It's hot, isn't it?
Come here.
Turn around.
Turn around?
Your stomach is moving.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
You can do it.
I'm so happy!
It feels so good.
It feels good, right?
Huh?
You can do it, right?
Yes, I can.
Hurry up.
I'm going to stop.
Say something.
Yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see, I see.
Mizuko, help me.
Hurry up and move.
Don't take a break.
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to sleep again?
It's too early.
Don't go.
Hang in there.
You can do it.
You are holding it in.
Come here.
Why do you do it twice?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay Are you okay?
What?
I'm fine.
You can still do it, right?
Take a break.
I told you to take a break.
I told you to do it.
I'm sorry.
Stand up quickly.
What?
I'm sorry.
Toilet.
No.
No, don't do that.
You said you were going to do it.
I'm sorry.
I was so nervous.
I told you to be patient.
I'll be patient.
Can you be patient?
I'll be patient this time.
I can't trust you.
I can't stand it.
Can I stand it now?
I can't do this.
I can't stand it.
Can't I do this?
I can't do this.
I can't feel anything.
What?
You can't?
Then I'll stop.
No.
What?
You can't, can you?
No.
I can't.
I can't speak.
This time, I'm going to make you do it.
Really? Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Really?
I'm going to wash my body.
Are you going to wash your body?
Yes, I'm going to wash my body.
I think you can do it.
You're standing up again.
You're too energetic.
You're going to make me feel good, right?
Please be careful.
Please look at me.
It's a little dirty.
Let's wash your hair.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I'll wash your hair.
It's not enough.
I can't stand it at all.
You are getting harder and harder.
Shut up.
It's because I touch you, isn't it?
Touch me more.
It feels good.
I'm so happy I'm so
happy I'm so happy.
I have to stretch my back to reach you.
My butt too My butt too?
Do you want me to call you?
No Are you okay?
No.
I can't sleep.
You just want to touch
Aizawa-kun's butt, don't you?
That may be true.
That's absolutely true.
You're right.
I really can't sleep.
I can't sleep either.
I'm just washing it, but it's a mess.
Isn't it crazy?
It's too beautiful.
It's crazy.
Hey, I want to wash it.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it from another place.
What?
I'm just shaking it.
You have to wash it properly.
I'll wash it properly
You just want to touch it, don't you?
I'll wash it for you.
Thank you.
Why are you so excited?
Is that so?
I don't feel like it.
You don't feel like it?
You're a pervert.
Yes, I am.
I don't know.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm not sure if I'm doing it right.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can do it.
What do you think?
I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I'm telling you to go ahead.
I'll do it again.
No, no, no.
I'm too happy.
It's okay.
I'll do it again.
Let's do it again.
You're so cute.
I'm going to wash my hands.
It's been a long time since I've
had a bath, so I'm getting used to it.
What is this?
It's like a bath without a shower.
I've been to the bathroom twice.
I want to recover.
Do you still need to recover?
Yes, I need to recover.
Can you hold it in?
I'm going to take a bath now
OK Can I put this on your back?
Yes.
What?
Let me see.
Oh.
What?
Wait a second OK.
Wow What?
Why are you making such a pathetic voice?
Because...
You just made a lot of noises.
You can't help it anymore, can you?
I can't help it.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Please don't laugh at me.
I feel so bad that I can't help laughing.
What is this?
You are so strict.
What do you mean by strict?
Are you making fun of me?
You are so strict.
How is it?
Ah, it's coming.
Huh?
It's coming.
What?
Why did you say that so quickly?
Because it's too good.
Really.
It's too good I knew it
Since we're on camera,
take more More?
You can't take it off.
Stand up.
You can't take it off
in your current state.
Stand up.
You're not happy.
You're happy, aren't you?
Stand up.
Hurry up.
Can I take it off?
Yes.
Is it comfortable?
Yes, it is.
You are so cute.
Because I'm licked by my own penis?
I like your face when you're sucking it in.
You're cute.
I'm licking your face right now.
I'm not speaking well.
You don't like it?
You like the tip, don't you?
Don't eat it.
You can't eat it.
He's trying to eat the whole thing.
It's not working for him.
He's at his limit.
Can I eat it?
You can eat it?
Yes.
I thought you were going to eat it.
No, I can't.
I'm going to eat it.
I'm going.
You went again.
You just went.
Hurry up.
You're not patient at all.
Wait a minute, wait a
minute, wait a minute, wait a
minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute,
It's all over the place.
Why?
Oh, it's delicious.
Oh, my God.
I'm glad.
I'll give it to you.
You are so naughty.
You are so naughty I feel hot.
Let's continue Let's continue.
Next.
You feel better now, right?
Yes You feel better now, right?
I feel better now I feel better now I can't
trust you anymore, so I can't help it.
Look, it's very beautiful.
Yes, it's very beautiful.
What do you call that?
Like a mansion ship.
The mansion ship is beautiful.
It's good.
A simple impression.
It's very beautiful,
but... Okay.
I'm prettier, right?
Yes.
I know. Okay.
You're doing your best.
You're cute.
What?
I'm doing my best.
Really?
Yes.
You're really pretty.
Why are you appealing
with your small voice?
You're cute.
After dinner, I prepared a beer.
You are good.
Did you really prepare it?
Yes, I did.
You are good.
I made a mistake at the beginning.
I made a mistake. I'm going to be late.
Let's have a toast.
Beer is the best.
Do you drink alcohol?
Me? I get drunk easily, but
it takes a long time to drink.
I drink at night.
Can you do it?
Well...
I'll do my best.
You're so energetic.
You'd better calm down.
Cheers!
It's delicious.
Is it delicious?
What?
Is it good?
It's good.
Thank you.
It goes well with beer.
Does it?
Does beer and I go well together?
I thought I should praise you for now.
You're too sloppy.
I know.
It looks delicious. Can I eat it?
Yes, please.
I'll let you eat.
No, it's okay.
You've been waiting for
a long time, haven't you?
I've been waiting for a long time.
I was wondering if you would give it to me.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's good.
You don't eat it.
I want you to eat it.
I want you to try it.
Is it good?
It's really good.
It's good.
Can I drink beer with you?
Can I?
Can I do my best?
What are you laughing at?
It was good.
Yeah, it was good.
I'll do it for you, too.
You're spilling too much. Drink it up.
I'm not going to.
This is the most delicious
pudding I've ever had in my life.
Isn't it too bad to praise?
There's a better way to praise.
It's a penalty game.
Penalty game?
Penalty game.
This?
What do you think?
What is it?
It's cold, isn't it?
But you like nipples, so it's okay.
Wait a minute.
My nose is open.
But you like nipples, don't you?
It's embarrassing.
It's open.
Is it embarrassing?
I don't know.
I'm doing my best.
I'm so embarrassed.
Aren't you happy?
Maybe it's not a punishment.
Is it a reward?
Why do you like this?
Do you feel good?
Do you like me?
Look at this.
It's all wet.
It's embarrassing.
But you like me.
You're a pervert.
You're so cute.
I can tell you're standing up.
You stand up right away
when I touch your nipples.
What?
You can't see me?
Oh, it's painful.
Oh, it's amazing.
Oh, it's from behind.
It's not from behind.
It smells good.
It's like this.
Yes.
I just touched it from
above, but why is it like this?
Oh, great.
Your lower back is moving.
You're making a really embarrassing face.
You like this one, don't you?
I like this one.
You are moving around.
Can I pet you?
Wait a minute.
His legs are moving.
He can't move.
He is a grown-up.
You are so mischievous.
I'm so embarrassed.
You are embarrassed?
But you are excited, aren't you?
You are apologizing.
It's rare to see you in such a cool outfit.
Gin-chan, you're moving a lot.
Tanuki-chan.
You like this so much.
You're so cute.
I feel uncomfortable.
Why?
Look at me.
I'll show you this.
What?
What do you think is underneath this?
I don't know.
I don't know. I'm just having fun.
I'm shocked.
I want to see it.
You want to see it?
Please show it to me.
I want you to kiss me.
That's amazing. You can do that?
I'm going to do it.
What are you wearing?
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
Ta-da!
Wow.
Show me more reaction.
It's really good.
It's transparent.
Do you like it?
I came here for you.
For me?
Yes.
I'm so happy.
Be happy.
I'm so excited.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know if it's a good
idea to touch you directly.
I don't know if it's a good idea to
touch you from the back of your head.
I don't know if I should say that.
You are so big.
I'm sick of your belly.
I can't touch you.
I can't see you.
You are so small.
Well...
I have no idea.
Really?
Well, I am standing now.
Oh, my voice.
Yes.
How many times I've said it?
I don't know what I've said.
What?
Do you want to drink it?
Yes.
You are unusually active.
I'll make you feel better next time.
I see.
It feels good there.
Really?
Yes.
Give me that.
What?
It's embarrassing Why are
you making me embarrassed?
If you want to feel good, lick me
Come here Lie down.
Look at this.
Look at me and lick me.
Why do you look so happy?
Are you happy?
Yes, I am.
Can you drink more?
You can drink more, can't you?
Sorry, it's too sweet.
It's nice to be able to drink a lot.
I'm annoyed that you
leave me to do something.
It's annoying, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels good, but it's annoying.
I think Yare-zan is better.
It's pathetic, isn't it?
Hey, look.
It's all messed up.
It's not my fault. Did you do that?
Did you put it on?
Yes, I did.
I love this.
It's good, isn't it?
I'm embarrassed because I'm on the sofa.
Here?
Yes.
It's embarrassing.
I'm excited because it's embarrassing.
It's good that I can eat it in one day.
Uh-huh.
Ah, okay.
I don't understand.
What?
I didn't get it.
I don't understand.
No, I understood.
No, I don't think so.
I want to be four times taller than you.
Four times taller?
Yes, four times taller than you.
I can do it.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Why?
I'm 22 years old.
You look like a grown-up.
What?
He's lying down, and I'm
touching his neck from behind.
It's hard to imagine, isn't it?
It's hard, but I'm excited.
You're excited?
I'm excited.
You're cute.
What?
You are too excited.
Come here.
Put your leg up.
I'll make you more embarrassed.
Look.
No, no.
Look at this.
My hips are round.
Yeah, they are.
It's embarrassing.
This is the most embarrassing outfit.
Are you excited?
It's embarrassing.
I'm so embarrassed.
I can't see anything.
Are you excited?
You're shaking a lot.
I'm so embarrassed.
You're excited, aren't you?
You're so excited.
I'm so embarrassed.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes.
You're so pathetic.
Do you want to turn off the light?
Then you won't be embarrassed, right?
I'll turn off the light and make it darker.
You're cute.
Wait a minute.
You're not embarrassed, are you?
It's getting dark.
Sleep here.
I'll turn off the light.
Good morning.
I'm going to take a nap.
He is doing his best.
I'm embarrassed.
Are you going to take a video of me?
You are good at it.
This is the floor.
Be careful of your head.
Is it recording?
I'll give you a lot of my saliva.
What are you doing?
Does it feel good?
You are too scared.
Do you feel good?
I feel great.
Where are you licking now?
What is it?
Chinchin's...
Chinchin's collarbone.
You don't like it.
Are you embarrassed?
I like rabbit ears.
I want you to touch my nipples.
You want me to touch your nipples?
You are greedy.
Is it good?
Which do you feel
better, chin-chin or neck?
Both feel good, but chin-chin.
Chin-chin feels good.
Why is your face so swollen?
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
What do you want to do?
Do you want to put it in your mouth?
No, I don't want to.
Be patient.
You always say you'll be
patient, but you say it quickly.
Don't go before I'm satisfied.
Really?
I'll make you feel better.
Can I put this in?
Chinchin is very energetic.
I'll put it in.
Take the right place to put it in.
I feel sick.
I think I'm going to die.
I feel sick when I'm on the toilet.
I don't want you to go to the bathroom.
What's wrong?
You might be sick.
Are you sick?
I'm a little sick.
I'm going to put it on the back this time.
It's easier to see if it's in there, right?
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Come here.
I'm going to touch your neck.
Ouch!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I'm going.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no.
Did you go again?
You're so energetic.
You can still go, right?
You're energetic when I touch you.
I don't want to do it.
Whose fault do you think it is?
It hurts.
Oh, no.
I'm just a human.
Why do I have to do this?
Oh, no.
Come on, move a bit more.
I can't do it anymore.
More, more.
There's a lot more over there.
You're out of breath.
I'll move it for you.
It's really ticklish.
It feels good.
It's ticklish.
What is it?
Isn't it too early?
I just told you Please
be patient No, no.
What?
What's wrong?
It feels so good.
Kaki-chan.
What?
Again?
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
I went too far.
That was too fast.
You can't do it anymore?
You can still do it, right?
I'm fixing it.
See?
What?
Oh no.
It's okay.
Don't pretend to be impossible.
Don't move.
It's okay.
You're stammering a lot.
I told you to be patient.
You're a man, aren't you?
I'm at my limit.
You're not at your limit.
I told you it's not easy.
It's easy, isn't it?
I told you to be patient.
Did you go again?
Did you really do it?
Wow.
But you can still do it, right?
I can't do it.
You can do it.
One more time.
Come on.
You are a lively fish.
Go, go, go.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat ice cream.
It's too short.
Let's eat ice cream.
Do you usually eat ice cream?
I eat a lot.
There is an ice cream store in front of us.
It's interesting.
What should we eat?
It looks delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
How many times have you
been to a convenience store?
It's difficult, but...
Difficult?
It's difficult, but... Cute?
What's that?
What?
You're teasing me.
Difficult?
There's a lot of chopsticks in there.
The pie crust is really good.
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Right?
It's choco-choco, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
Choco-choco?
You like choco, don't you?
I like choco.
Which one do you like better, me or him?
You don't have to answer that question.
You don't answer it properly.
Mr. Ibuki.
Well done.
I'm going to buy it.
Thank you.
The night view is beautiful
at this time of the day.
Let's go to see it.
Sounds good.
Let's go to the back.
There are a lot of people.
A lot of people.
Bahe.
It's bahe, isn't it?
It's bahe.
Oh, no. I'm embarrassed.
I'm happy.
I'm happy to see you so happy.
It's like a love reality show.
I'm excited.
It's a love reality show.
This is... Don't you know this?
If you do this, it becomes a heart.
It doesn't mean a bat.
Oh, it doesn't mean a bat.
It means a heart.
I don't know what it means.
One of them is like this.
What's wrong?
Let's eat.
Itadakimasu.
It's a night view.
It's so beautiful.
Each of these lights...
Nothing.
Each of them has happiness.
I think so.
Each of us has happiness.
We have happiness.
We are happy.
Let's give it to them.
Wait.
I'll give it to you.
What?
This?
I'll give it to you.
You can eat it.
No, I'll just have a bite.
As expected.
Here you are.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's good.
I'm going to eat it.
You don't let me eat it.
Here you are.
It's spread out.
It's good.
Is it good?
How is it?
It's good.
Isn't it different from the same
chocolate vanilla ice cream?
Yes, it is.
It's good.
Both are good.
Isn't it too early to be night?
Is it cold?
No, it's not cold.
It's too early to be night.
It's early.
That means we are getting
closer and closer to the end.
It's 24 hours.
That's right.
It's too soon.
It's 24 hours.
We will meet in the morning.
But tomorrow...
We will be late.
Right?
That's right.
We took a plane, got on a car, and
went to the park with the Ferris wheel.
We took the wrong road
and went to the Ferris wheel.
I want you to forget about that.
But after that, we went to Bankai.
I wonder if I made you
go there a few times.
How many times did you go there?
How many times did I go there?
Five?
Six?
Five.
Six times.
I went there about six times.
It's crazy, isn't it?
How many times did you go there?
I went there about twice.
I think it's about 1 third of the amount.
I'm drinking 1 third of the amount.
What?
Isn't it too much?
Hey.
I can't make up for it with a kiss.
Sweet and sour.
It's good.
Let's see the other side.
It's warm.
I'll warm it up for you.
Will you warm it up for me?
Yes, I will.
I was about to fall asleep.
I'm late.
It's 4 o'clock and we
are not taking a break.
What should I do?
I can't do it anymore.
I feel like I'm going to die.
Really?
Yeah.
Let's take a break on the bed.
Okay.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
What?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Neon Key Feather.
Is this a dream?
Good morning.
What time is it now?
Is it morning already?
It's morning already.
It's almost time to say goodbye.
I don't want to say goodbye.
Oh, wow.
Oh, no.
I'm not done yet.
That's right.
I'm lonely.
Did you wake up?
What's wrong?
I don't know if it feels good or not.
My legs are shaking.
There.
Let's do it here.
The part you like the most.
Why are you standing like that?
You like to be scratched
like this, don't you?
You like it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I love it.
It's so hot in the morning.
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
You have a lot of hair on your nose.
Really?
You really like bunnies, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I love bunnies.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're very sensitive from the morning.
Because it's such a gross morning.
Oh, it's more sensitive.
This is the last time you're
going to drink gin and gin like this.
I'll drink it all at once.
Oh, it's scary.
You can't forget my fur.
You can't hold it anymore?
Are you sleepy?
It's too early.
I'll make you feel better.
Really?
I want to make you feel better.
It's hot.
Drink a lot.
It's hot, isn't it?
How do you feel?
Hey, lick me more.
Move your tongue a lot.
It's great that you feel so good.
Can I lick you?
You've grown up.
You like this, don't you?
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, that part.
How do you feel?
Did you wash your feet?
Does it feel good?
I can see you licking it.
Next, turn your head.
You know what to do, don't you?
You're all looking around.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God. You're feeling it a lot.
This is good.
Oh, no.
It's fun.
What's wrong?
It's getting worse.
No.
Hang in there.
I haven't put it in yet.
I can't help it.
I want to put it in.
Let's put it in as it is.
I wonder if it will fit.
Do your best.
I'm going to put it in.
Can you see it?
It's in there.
Wow.
Can you see it?
I can't do it.
Oh, no.
This posture is embarrassing.
I can't do it.
No?
Please stay like this.
Okay.
I want you to stay like this.
I'm so tired.
You don't want to take a break, do you?
It feels so good.
It's getting harder and harder.
You can do it.
No, you can't.
Let's go.
You can't.
I can't.
Please let me sleep.
Let me sleep.
I can't.
I'll go to the hospital.
I told you I want to sleep.
Go to sleep.
But you can do it again, can't you?
You're going too fast.
I'm going to lift you up again.
Ah...
It's just a little bit painful.
It's just a little bit painful, but
I know it's going to be better.
You can do it.
Can I?
Next, from behind.
I'll lend it to you.
It hurts a lot.
No, I don't know.
More.
I can't do it.
Wait.
I feel sick.
It's so hot.
It feels so good.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Are you all right?
It hurts.
Give me some medicine.
I have a lot of medicine.
I'll give you some.
It's hot.
It's not over yet, is it?
You're still so energetic.
You can do it, can't you?
You're a good boy.
Oh, no!
Hurry up!
It's okay.
Why are you crying?
Give me a hug.
I'm going to go.
You're going again?
I want to put it on your boobs.
I don't like it.
I don't want to.
You don't want to?
You can do it.
I don't want to.
You're almost there.
It's so hard.
You're still like this?
You're so energetic.
I'll clean you up.
It's not over yet.
Don't run away.
What?
You're going to fall.
Don't run away.
It's not over yet.
I can't do it.
You can do it.
You can do it, right?
I did my best.
Why did you do your best?
Are you done?
Did you have fun?
I had a lot of fun.
Let's go on a date again.
Yes, by all means.