It's so big.
I've never been to a hotel this big.
I'm a little nervous.
Can I take a look around?
Sure.
Let's go.
Her name is Mio.
She's a student in my class.
Half a year ago,
I was confessed to by her.
When I realized,
even though I had a wife,
I crossed the line between
a teacher and a student.
I've crossed the line with her.
I thought, no, I can't do it.
But when she looked at me,
I lost my mind.
But I can't keep this relationship forever.
I'm in my new semester.
I have to tell her today.
Sensei, thank you for
bringing me to such a nice hotel.
I was very lonely because I couldn't
meet you during the summer vacation.
I'm sorry. I thought I would be suspicious
if I met you until the summer vacation.
I know. So I was really looking
forward to seeing you today.
How long are you going to stay with me?
I'm going to stay with you forever.
Ishikawa.
Yes?
I have something important to tell you.
What is it?
Is it important?
Well...
Let's end this relationship.
What?
End? Why?
Why so suddenly?
I thought about it for a month
when I couldn't see Ishikawa.
I'm a teacher, and Ishikawa is
a student, and I have a family.
If this relationship is known to
the world, it will be a big deal.
So I think it's better to end this
relationship before it becomes a big deal.
I think it's better for us to break up.
Sensei...
I'm really sorry for being so selfish.
But this is for both of us...
What?
If you want to do that,
it's okay.
Even if we break up.
But you have a school and a wife.
It'll be bad if they find out.
But is that really okay?
I think you should
think about it a bit more.
Do you like me?
I love you.
If you still love me,
I'm sure you'll regret
it when you find out.
If you love each other,
you don't have to pretend you don't.
It's been a month since we last met.
I don't want to break up.
We're alone in such a nice hotel.
Teacher, what did you want
to do with me in the hotel?
You want to break up with me, don't you?
Teacher, you really want to
have sex with me, don't you?
If it's about you, I'll know right away.
Teacher, I want to have sex with you too.
If you have sex with
me, you don't have to
worry about school,
your wife, or anything else.
I don't care about anything else.
I was only thinking about you
during the summer vacation.
During today's training
ceremony and when I was in class,
I was always thinking
about having sex with you.
I love you.
Sensei, I love you.
Sensei, say I love you.
I love you.
Do you love me?
Sensei,
kiss me.
let's kiss.
Let's kiss.
Why don't you kiss me?
Do you still hate me?
No, I don't hate you.
Then kiss me.
It's been a month since I kissed you.
You like kissing, don't you?
Give me a kiss.
I knew you wanted to kiss me.
I'm happy.
I'll make you forget everything
about school and your wife.
Oh my god.
Do it a lot, Jin-sei.
A lot.
Can I really do it?
Yes, do it a lot.
Can I lick your hands?
Yes, lick your hands.
I wanted to see you
You wanted to see me?
I want to eat everything.
Everything.
It's very hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
How long have you been putting up with it?
I've been putting up with it for a month.
It's getting really hot.
You are getting better.
You are getting better I
did a lot Are you ready?
Yes, I want you to do it.
He is now in a deep sleep.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry.
I will do what I said.
I want to take it off now.
I don't need it anymore.
Oh, that's great.
All of it.
Do you want me to lick you more?
I want you to lick me more.
Here?
I'm going to cry.
It's okay.
Do you want me to do it this time?
I want you to do it.
A lot.
It feels good.
I drank it.
No?
You are good at it.
Oh, wow.
Does it feel good?
What's going on with your neck?
It's hard, isn't it?
It's hard.
It feels so good.
Like I did.
I'm going to give you a lot of it.
A lot?
You're getting bigger, doctor.
I want you to do more.
Really?
Yes, that's right.
Did you endure it, too?
Yes, I did.
I wanted to see you more.
Did you want to see me?
I wanted to see you, too.
It's a kiss on the buttocks.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Don't you think I'm
getting better at listening??
You are doing so well.
I watched a lot of videos and studied.
Really?
Yes.
I want you to feel much better.
Really?
I feel so good.
Ah... Ah...
Ah...
Which is better, you or me?
You're better.
Really?
I'm glad.
Yeah.
Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah... Is that so?
Is it that different?
It's so deep.
Oh, it's hard.
Wow, you're getting better.
Really?
Did you cry for me?
Yes, I did.
I watched a lot of your videos.
Really?
It feels good.
I miss you so much.
Do you miss me?
Yes, I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
Doctor, look at me.
It feels so good.
It's very tight.
Good morning!
Good morning.
I'm sleepy.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it anymore.
Do you want more?
Let me hug you.
I'm going to give you a snack.
Yeah, yeah...
It's okay, big bro!
I'll be fine I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I want you to hit me hard.
It's so hot that I can't stop it.
I can't stop it.
I'm sweating.
It's so hot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Is it hot?
Yes, it's hot.
It was a great day.
The weather is amazing.
My waist has moved a lot.
It was a very comfortable day.
Are you in a bad mood all the time?
Do you feel good all the time?
I feel good.
They seem to be getting along well.
I'm glad I can see you, but I'm
scared of what you're going through.
I'm not going to be able to see you again.
I have a lot of questions.
I thought I couldn't see you.
I'm sorry I couldn't see you.
Good boy.
Let me see your back.
I'm so sleepy.
Great.
I'm so happy.
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
Doctor, can you do that for me?
What?
The thing you did for me the other day.
I'll hold your hand.
What's wrong?
I love you, doctor.
I'm sorry.
Ahhhhhhh!!!!!
Ahhhh!!!
So scary!!!!
Noooooo!!!
I can't do anything.
Don't do it anymore.
I won't do it anymore.
You don't have to do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm going to cry.
I'll get you some water.
Thank you.
Can I have some too?
Yes.
You bought me a purse.
I was so excited.
I'll make it clean.
Clean?
It feels good.
It's getting hard.
Because you're licking it a lot.
I just took it out.
Sensei, I'm sweating a
lot, so let's go to the shower.
That's right
You're sweating a lot.
Sensei, you're getting harder
It feels good.
I'm full It's amazing.
It's amazing.
You just did it.
You're good at making a noise.
Really?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Is it okay?
It feels good.
It's hard.
Why?
It's very hard.
It feels good.
I'm sorry, I've been
whispering to you all the time.
It's been a long time
since I've been touched
by you, so I'm getting
a good feeling about it.
You're moving a lot.
I'm just touching you a little bit.
It's not a little bit.
I want to touch you more.
He was in her arms and legs
just as he was about to give birth.
It's a little scary, but
the pain is getting worse.
I think it's the same as before.
He has a lot of pus and it's hard.
I'm rubbing.
Are you rubbing?
I want to rub more.
More.
Rubbing.
I want to rub.
Here.
From this angle, he is in a good mood.
He is looking at the camera.
The camera is displayed on his finger.
I'm going to cry.
Are you ready?
I'm so sleepy.
Can I sleep?
Yes, you can.
I'm so sleepy.
What's wrong with me?
I don't know.
It's hard, right?
It's hard.
This is the hardest part.
Let's do it harder.
I'm going to try to get him to do it.
No, no, no.
You're doing it, right?
Yeah, I can't.
I can't, I can't.
OK, OK.
I'm going to put this.
I won't.
OK, I'm going to put this on.
It's not OK.
Yeah, that's right.
I love you.
Love you too.
Let's go to bed.
Bed?
But...
I'm so excited.
I know.
I'm so good at slurping noodles.
Yay!
You are so cute.
You are licking me so well.
I can't do it.
I'm going to do it here.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I am very nervous.
Are you nervous?
Look at me.
I feel good.
I feel like vomiting.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Can I go?
Can I?
Oh, my God.
Sensei, did you poop again?
Why? It felt so good.
I didn't mean to poop in the bath.
Was it no good?
No.
I want to spend more time with you.
Me too.
How long are you going to stay like this?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you?
Doctor, what's wrong with you?
Oh, it's nothing.
Are you pregnant?
What time are you coming back?
Ishikawa.
I don't want to go home.
What?
I'm sorry to say this.
But I want to be with you more.
I want to stick with you
forever until you go home.
I've been wondering
about this for a long time.
Just for now.
Can you take it off?
No, that's...
Won't you take it off?
I don't have a ring on.
You're not my wife now.
Whose is it?
Answer me.
Tell me.
It's Ishikawa's.
Sensei, you are mine now.
I'm happy.
Sensei, I want to be with you forever.
Sensei, you are mine.
I'll make you feel better.
I want you to like me more.
Oh, my God.
Where are you licking?
It's hot.
Get well soon.
Forget all the troubles.
Ah...
Your body...
is delicious.
Really?
Ah...
I'm going to lick everything.
Because you are mine.
Really?
Ah... Ah... Ah...
Ah... I'm sorry.
Hey, can I put a kiss mark here?
What? There?
Oh, that's gross.
I'm sorry.
Hey, what are you doing?
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Where are you licking?
Ah, you licked everything.
How do you feel?
It feels great.
Ah...
Ah... Ah...
Let me see how you feel.
Eh?
It feels good.
It's been good.
Yeah.
Ah.
Ah...
Be so absorbed that you
can't think of grass or school.
Are you sure?
Oh!
I'll make you forget everything.
I'll definitely give it to you.
Really?
It's intense.
The alcohol is intense.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hmm.
Do you feel good?
Stay here.
It's a cat toy.
I thought it was a cat
toy, but it's a toy for cats.
I'm so tired.
I just want to play with you.
I'm having a hard time.
It's a cat toy.
This is a toy for cats.
I want to play with you, too.
Off to sleep.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I want to play with you.
I'm gonna play with you.
I want to go to sleep.
It hurts.
Can you see it?
It was really hard.
The doctor did it for you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, wow.
Doctor, I love you.
I love you, too.
Don't say goodbye to me.
I won't.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, wow.
I'm so sorry...
Great I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it I'm sorry.
Ah.
Aha...
How does it feel?
Ah.
Yes.
Ha.
Oh.
Ah.
I'm sorry.
Good girl.
You look like you're in pain.
Really?
Oh, my God.
I want to relax.
Oh, my God. It feels so good.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good to lick it.
Wow.
Can you move?
Yes.
It's so soft.
Soft?
Wow.
That's amazing.
What's that?
Don't call me Ichikawa.
What?
Call me Mio.
Mio?
Yes, call me Mio.
Mio is amazing.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels good.
Does it feel better than your wife?
It feels good at all.
I love you.
I love you, too.
I told you to move.
I couldn't stand it.
Move more.
I want to move.
Why?
Does it hurt?
No.
Give me a kiss.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You can see it.
I can see it.
It's in here.
There are a lot in there.
Here.
It's not there.
I'm so happy.
Are you happy?
I love you.
That's great.
Do you want to do more?
I want to do more.
Let's do it again.
Can you do it?
Can you?
I'm sorry.
I don't want to.
It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
I'm sorry.
Wow... I'm sorry.
I'm so happy.
I love you so much.
Hey, doctor.
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
I don't want you to go
home to your wife today.
No?
I know I'm selfish, but I
want to be with you forever.
No?
No.
It's not a problem.
I'm happy.
I'll be with you forever.
I can't stand it yet.
Don't do it.
I'm so tired.
I want to take a nap.
Take a nap.
I'm going to die.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sensei.
I love you.
Don't go back.
I'll call you.
I don't want to.
You're my wife, aren't you?
Just think about me.