Hi, I'm Ruo.
Hi, I'm Miyo Ichikawa.
Today, I was told to come here.
Here, I can see it.
I was told to go under the Tokyo
Tower, so I came here with my luggage.
That's why I came here.
I don't have anything else.
I'm just holding the camera like this.
I'm just holding the camera.
The weather is so nice.
It's hot.
It's a little hot, so there's a
bench over there, so I'll go.
I've moved to the bench.
It's very cool in the shade here.
The temperature has changed
just by getting in the shade.
There is a pond.
It is usually too hot outside.
I thought summer is hot.
How long should I wait?
There is a cicada.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
What?
Are you Miyo Ishikawa?
What are you shooting?
I was told to meet here today.
I was handed the camera.
I'm talking alone.
It's suspicious.
What?
It's suspicious, isn't it?
What are you doing?
I was told that there
might be a cute girl here.
Yes.
It's a lie to say that.
Have you heard anything from the manager?
What? I haven't heard anything.
You've been opening your
schedule all day, haven't you?
Yes, until tomorrow morning.
Until tomorrow morning.
Have you heard anything?
Actually, it's part of the plan.
What?
I just came up with something.
So, you have a day off.
Yes.
So, what are you going to do?
Kanamiyo and AV actress are here.
So, I just came up with something.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Anyway, it's been a while since we met.
Yes, it's been a while.
How was it?
I don't think there was
anything like that recently.
I don't think so.
It looks like you brought a lot of luggage.
Yes, I thought I'd change my clothes.
I was told a lot of
things, so I brought it.
It's pretty free and unplanned.
We went to a lot of places together.
I mean, do something erotic.
Is it unplanned?
That's what I heard.
Oh, I see.
I didn't know that.
You are good at self-portrait.
Is it OK? I don't know if I look good.
Let's go.
OK.
Do you have this? Thank you.
Please park your car here.
Here?
Can't you speak
in the city? I can't.
Really?
I can't speak at all.
What do you mean?
Let's get in the car.
Let's go for a little drive.
What should we do?
I'm not hungry yet.
It's been a long time.
Really?
How many years has it been?
It's been 2 years since October.
But it's been 2 years?
1 year? 2 years?
It hasn't been 2 years yet,
but it's been 2 years
since this video came out.
How is it?
I've known you since your debut,
so I feel like I've seen you before.
You look more like an actress.
I feel like I've become like you.
Really?
But I'm often told that I don't grow up.
If I say it badly, I don't grow up.
If I say it well, I don't change.
You don't change.
No, I don't change.
I wonder if I don't have to
be dyed in a strange way.
I may not be dyed.
I feel like I'm doing it from
scratch, forgetting every time.
So, when you were told last night or the
day after tomorrow, you were like, what?
What?
What are you going to do?
I didn't know, so I watched anime.
Did you watch anime? Do
you like anime? I like anime.
Only anime? Only anime.
Why?
I'm still in bed.
You're still in bed?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Are you in love? No, I'm not.
Why?
You're not interested?
That's not what I mean.
Well, I think it's going to be hard.
It's hard.
I think it's okay now.
You have a job.
Have you ever tried something like that?
I don't think I've ever started this job.
I don't think so.
Really?
Do you want to go on a date?
No, I want to go somewhere with my friends.
With your female friends?
Yes, with my female friends.
I don't really want to go somewhere.
I don't want to go to India.
I want to go to a hot spring.
I see.
You are always relaxed, aren't you?
Don't you get angry?
I've only been angry once in my life.
That was probably the last time I was
angry when I was in elementary school.
I don't know if I'm angry or not.
Here we are.
The weather is so nice.
Where are we? Rainbow Bridge.
Oh, this is Rainbow Bridge.
You look like Miyo-chan all day.
You're already erotic.
Will it change in a day?
Don't you masturbate?
I masturbate, but it is said
that it is a man's masturbation.
I understand the feeling
of a man who wants to
masturbate because it
is good to be with me.
I don't know if you can
understand what I'm saying, but I
think it's a pain in the ass
to go through that process.
But apart from that, it's
a pain in the ass to do it.
It's a secret.
I think it's a secret, too.
Let's go to a lot of places.
Shall we go? Let's go.
Let's go.
You like sweets, don't you?
No.
I like gummies and ice cream.
I'm addicted to gummies.
It's going to be blurred.
Isn't this hard?
I like hard things.
Well, that's...
You're going to cry.
You're going to cry a lot.
It's not a natural fact
that everyone thinks.
It's an interesting project
this time, isn't it? Yeah.
So I thought it would be
more fun to shoot an AV.
What do you think, Mayu?
I didn't change for two
years, but I could change.
I want to have a sex that makes me excited.
I don't know that.
It's a worry.
It's a clothes.
I see.
Ah, Dippin Dots.
Dippin Dots? Dots.
Can't we choose the taste?
I want to eat it if I can choose.
I don't want to eat it if
there is only this flavor.
I want to eat this.
Takoyaki? Takoyaki.
Just a little.
Just a little? It's beautiful.
Eat this and then ice cream.
Eat it and then?
I don't know which one will come out.
I don't know, but all of them are cute.
Which one do you aim for?
The one with the mouth is cute.
What should I do?
There's a completely different one.
Now... I can't do it.
I can't do it.
You can't do it, can
you? I can't do it.
You don't need this, do you?
I don't need it.
You don't need this?
Trash.
What is it? Melon
soda? Melon soda.
Green.
It's good.
Zakashi is good.
I like it.
This looks like an adult's toy.
This is delicious.
Do you know? I like this.
What is it?
This is sweet and spicy curry.
I eat it with chopsticks.
If I don't eat it with chopsticks,
my hands will get dirty.
I'm dyeing my hair black.
You're done dyeing your hair black?
Yes.
When I was a kid, I
thought it was expensive.
But now that I'm an adult,
I don't know what it is.
It's expensive.
500 yen is a lot.
That's true.
It's up to 300 yen.
Right? It's cute.
It's very lively.
I really like this kind of thing.
Yes, takoyaki.
Let's eat.
This is... Oh, this is not
the one you stab a lot.
12 pieces are amazing.
Is it hot? It looks hot.
This is one bite takoyaki.
But... It's fluffy like this.
That's because I'm used to takoyaki.
Delight.
How is it?
It's hot!
You have to eat it with a puff.
Don't close your mouth
and eat it with a puff.
Isn't it good? It's good.
Doesn't it taste like dashi?
What?
You sound like a reaction comedian.
Is it good?
Is it better than you
thought? It's good.
It's small, so it's full.
It's hot.
It's been a while since I had takoyaki.
It's like the one you dip in the soup.
Akashiyaki? Oh, yeah.
It tastes like that.
The one before you dip it in the soup.
You've been doing a lot of
social media, haven't you?
I used to do it, but I don't post selfies.
I've been on Twitter all the time.
What about Instagram?
I'm on Instagram.
I'm doing TikTok and YouTube.
I've seen a little bit of YouTube.
Why?
I saw it, and it came out.
I thought, oh, you're doing it.
It's coming out.
One more.
I bought this.
Which one is the one
with the grain? This one.
I'll buy it.
You're fast.
I thought you weren't here.
What?
Okay.
What is this?
What was it?
Strawberry cheesecake.
That's a lot.
Here you go.
Thank you for the food.
Yay! It looks good.
I'm getting excited when it's ice cream.
I love ice cream.
Ice cream.
Do you eat ice cream at home?
My house is covered in ice cream.
Wow.
My freezer is full of ice cream.
What flavor is it?
The base is yogurt, right?
This is yogurt and strawberry sauce.
You put strawberry sauce on yogurt?
And this cheesecake.
Are you more excited than
when you ate takoyaki? Of course.
What?
Ice cream is my favorite food.
Ice cream?
How about this kind of project?
I'm happy to eat ice cream.
It's not a cheesecake, is it?
I don't need it.
Oh, no, it's gone.
Thank you for the meal.
Snacks, too.
Oh, snacks.
Don't forget this.
Thank you.
I got it.
I love you.
It's big.
Is it big? It's heavy.
What's in it? It's a tent.
Let's make a toast.
The weather is so nice.
Can I put it here?
Did you drink it?
My glass was like this.
Really?
I don't think so.
It's not Kirin lemon.
It's Mitsuya cider.
I like Mitsuya cider, Sprite, Kirin
lemon, Coca-Cola and Pepsi-Cola.
It's been a while since
I've seen a camera like this.
But on the contrary, it's
better not to say anything.
I'm not nervous.
I'm not going to sleep with this on.
I'm going to sleep with this on.
Can you hold this for me?
I don't think I can.
It's heavy.
It's definitely heavy.
You changed your eyes for a moment.
Do my eyes change?
Yes.
My eyes are my eyes.
Your eyes are erotic eyes.
Am I wrong? I don't know.
Is it me?
I thought you were
putting on a lot of cider.
What?
I'm about to throw up.
Let it out.
I don't know.
I'm going to put a book on it.
Oh, it's a book.
Are you interested in this book?
I'm not interested in this book.
I'm interested in this
book when I look at it.
I'm going to look at it.
You look like a person
who doesn't have a neck.
I'm going to stick out my neck.
I did it.
It's here, isn't it? Here? Here.
Because of the pants?
I can wear it like this.
When did you last do it?
When was the last time
you had sex with a woman?
When was it?
The day before yesterday.
Oh.
What was it?
It wasn't BL, was
it? No, it wasn't.
But sometimes you want to
have sex, don't you? In your mood.
Does that mean you feel dizzy?
I don't mind if I have sex with a woman.
What do you mean?
Do you feel like you want to have sex?
Do you want to have sex?
Do you go to bed
as it is? Yes, I do.
You sleep well.
I thought I had a good sleeping habit.
What are you doing?
No one is here today.
It's better than usual.
You can be bold.
You don't have to do that.
I don't know if I can do it.
Do you do like this?
Are you embarrassed
to be seen? No, I'm not.
When you are peeing.
Recently, when I'm peeing,
I rub the floor.
Do you rub your hands?
Next to my face.
Oh, you rub your hands completely.
It means rubbing.
Oh, it's like that.
It's like that.
And then it comes out.
Like rubbing, rubbing, rubbing.
Rubbing, rubbing, rubbing.
It's a cushion.
Ah.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no, no.
You're excited.
I don't want to.
It's hot, isn't
it? No, it's not.
I'm going to take off
my pants, so look at me.
For example, when you
go on a date and have sex,
which one do you prefer,
standing or standing?
I'd rather stand.
Right?
I don't want to stand outside.
It's a little dangerous to stand outside,
but don't you have such an image of Cammy?
What?
No?
It's my selfishness.
Are you ready?
Let's get started.
You are getting excited, aren't you?
Your face changes once you start.
Right?
You are amazing.
Don't get excited.
Do you want to see?
No, I don't want to.
Look at the face of the person who went.
Open your legs.
Show me your belly button.
Like this.
Come on.
Great.
You are so small.
It's small.
Is it small? It's small.
What? It's heavy.
Is it heavy or
small? It's a shield.
Really?
Do you want to see it?
It's my first time to see it.
It's my first time to see your face.
Why?
Didn't you see it in the mirror when you
were in junior high school or high school?
I think I saw it at the
end of junior high school.
Here you are.
What? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
She may be the most shy.
Touch her.
She is wet.
What?
She is a bad girl.
Wait a minute.
There is a floor over there.
Floor?
There is a floor and cushion.
No.
There is.
Just a little.
Ah.
You are so beautiful.
Which side is
better? I don't know.
Really?
Here?
Don't you like it?
No.
I'm doing my best to make him feel better.
He's so cute that I can't stop hugging him.
He's getting better and better.
He is like a commentator.
It's a hole.
It's not like that.
It's wrinkled.
Look at the other side.
I can't see it.
My favorite gummy bear.
It doesn't matter.
I can't get it.
Don't eat it.
I'll take it off.
It's too hot.
Too hot?
Is it harder? It's soft.
I'll try it.
I'm going to eat it all.
It's crumbling.
Oh!
Are you hitting me?
Yes.
You are so warm.
Look at me.
I did it.
Can I? Let's sit down.
Yes.
Let's go.
Since you are so bright,
Bright?
Isn't it erotic to have sex?
When the camera
comes like this, I look at it.
That's right.
It's a job disease.
Look.
Let's look at the navel.
Navel.
Touch my chest.
I'm going to pick it up.
You don't have to look at me.
Aren't you erotic?
Were you sleeping?
I don't like big ones.
It's deep, isn't it?
Is it deep? Yes, it's deep.
Is it deep?
Yes.
Do it more.
What? Do it more.
Look.
Is this not good?
No.
Isn't it difficult?
I'm going to give you a little more.
Today, I'm going to show
you a video of my cat,
Kikki, who's been playing
with me for a long time.
Kikki, come here.
Kikki, what are you doing?
Kikki, what are
you doing? Cushion.
Cushion?
What do you mean? Like this.
Like this.
Oh, I see.
Does it fit?
――Do you know how
to do it? ――No, I don't.
――It's my first time.
――You don't have to wear underpants.
――I should.
――It's difficult.
It's good, isn't it? Rub, rub.
Is it good?
Yes.
Do you want to try?
Can you do it with that?
Yes.
How about now?
I can't do it now.
Rub, rub.
I'm telling you that I
want to put a new one.
This is difficult.
It's difficult.
My face is getting red.
This floor is difficult.
Is it difficult? It's difficult.
I'm sorry I couldn't
get a good shot of him.
He's so wet.
You're so slippery.
Don't do that.
It's beautiful, so don't worry.
Oh, it feels good.
Let's start from here.
Put your legs together.
Are you embarrassed?
Do you want to go in?
I'm going to make a video of
the process of making a video.
Today, I'm going to show you how
to get rid of pimples on your face.
I'm sorry, baby.
I've been talking a lot.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm sorry.
When I showed them the video
of the baby, they were surprised.
I even played with her.
It's been a long time since
I've had a baby, but I'm so
happy that I can't help but
cry when I think of my baby.
I'm so happy that I can't help
but cry when I think of my baby.
She suddenly started to have sex.
Look at her.
It's out.
Is it out?
Yes.
How was it? Were you excited?
I don't know what it is, but I was excited.
I was wondering what it was.
It started with a strange feeling.
That's right.
I want to dig deeper.
From here.
Let's do it.
Can I do it more gently?
Are you excited now?
Then, be more excited.
What are you doing?
Did you want to take a bath?
Because you are sweating?
You are mischievous.
It's dangerous.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
I ate a lot, so I'm full.
Are you full?
What?
No.
I see.
I ate too much ice cream.
You stopped eating ice cream.
What?
What? Your hair.
More?
No.
I don't want to.
I don't get excited when I do
something erotic in such a place.
It's fun to look in the
mirror, isn't it? Yes, yes, yes.
You've been going up and down all the time.
What are you looking at
in the mirror? I'm laughing.
Are you laughing?
You wanted to take a shower, didn't you?
I wanted to take a shower.
Do you want to take a shower?
Are you excited? I got a pimple.
Let's stick it out to the front.
Yuriko.
Let's do it here.
Here?
You want me to do it here?
Yes.
Here? Here? Later.
Later?
Yes.
Give me your paw.
You don't like this place, do you?
Is it close?
You were a little wet,
weren't you? No, I wasn't.
You weren't? I don't know.
You don't know?
What?
Do you want to take a shower here?
Here? Yes, here.
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
I'll take a shower here.
Okay.
Put your butt here.
When you're doing it, you're looking in
the mirror and getting excited, aren't you?
What? I'm sorry.
Let's do it more.
It's really good.
Really?
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby cry like this.
It's hard.
She is holding a baby.
What did you do?
You are holding a baby.
Let's wash your face.
I'll wash my face.
Oh, my...
There is soap, isn't
there? Yes, there is.
I am a little bit nervous
because I am in my mom's home.
I am worried about my mom's health.
I am worried about the
condition of my mom's body.
I am worried about my mom's health.
She is the mother of three children, Akira.
Akira &Yui She is the mother
of three children, Chizuru & Aoki.
What are you doing?
Are you surprised?
Surprisingly, there are no ants.
There are no ants.
My body is swollen.
Your body is swollen.
My legs are swollen.
I'm sorry.
Can I do it here? Good boy.
What do you like the most?
I like this one.
You like this one.
Don't you want to go further?
I want to go further.
Do you want to go further?
You are so cool in such a great place.
Let's go to bed.
Why do you like
sleeping bag? Let's do it.
Can I sleep in a
sleeping bag? Try it.
Peace.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
I'm so happy.
I'm going to sleep here.
What? Are you going to sleep here?
Yes, I'm going to sleep here.
My son was so excited
that he couldn't get up.
He couldn't get up because he was so tired.
He was so tired that he couldn't get up.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to rub your back.
Rubbing?
You can do whatever you like.
Wow.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you a massage.
You're wet.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's ok, it's ok.
This is the first time I've had a baby, so
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
I'm going to give birth to a baby.
This cat is the oldest of
the three cats in the world.
This is her first time to have a cat bath.
She is getting more and more sensitive.
The baby is crying.
Momoko's crying.
Momoko.
You are really unlucky.
That's true.
It's true.
You're going to die.
I'm sorry.
It's so cold.
My feet are so cold.
Did you feel good?
It's a little hot, isn't
it? I'm sweating.
Do you want to go for a
walk in the night breeze?
In the night breeze?
Now?
I just said that.
Really?
I'm going to sleep.
You're going to sleep?
Let's go to sleep.
How do you feel?
It's been a while since
you've been pulled around.
Pulled around?
Maybe I've been pulled around.
But you ate a lot of ice cream, didn't you?
It was fun to eat ice cream.
I had a lot of fun today.
It's fun.
Sex, eat ice cream, sex, eat ice cream.
What's next after eating ice cream?
Sex.
Let's go.
You're completely off-mode today.
Off-mode? Not off-mode.
Well, eating ice cream.
I'm going to sleep.
If you ask your manager to open the schedule
for a day, you will sleep suspiciously.
I may be suspicious for a while.
Are you sleepy because you had sex?
I was exercising.
You can sleep now.
I think this is the best
way to wake you up.
I was surprised.
Were you surprised?
Yes.
Don't you feel sleepy?
No, I don't feel sleepy.
Are you excited?
Yes.
Do it.
Are you ready? I don't know.
Look, it's harder than before.
Let me stroke your back.
Let me know if you want to stroke my back.
Can you see it?
What? Come here.
Does it hurt?
No.
I think it's better to do this.
You've been having sex all the
time, so it's easier for you to get up.
I don't know.
Ouch!
You are shaking a lot.
Put your hand on my back and show me.
I'm going to take a bath.
What?
Do you want to take a bath?
I'm going to massage your buttocks.
You look like a rich man.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
This is the first time I've ever seen a cat
like this, and I'm very happy to see it.
I'm going to put the cat in the box.
You are so mean.
Give me more.
Harder.
That's great.
It feels good.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying.
I'm worried that she's going to be sick.
I'm worried about her.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm so happy to see a cat like this.
You don't usually
exercise, do you? No, I don't.
Oh, you fell down.
You can lie down.
Lie down?
Do whatever you like.
Whatever I like?
Whatever you like.
He woke up.
This? I knew it.
She's been living in the
car for about an hour now.
But she doesn't know that
I'm going to cut her nails.
So I decided to cut her
nails when I saw her.
Fubuki, the oldest, has a lot of hair.
He is a little bit old.
Fubuki is a young cat.
I'm sorry.
Are you OK?
Are you awake?
I'm going to sleep.
She fell asleep.
What are you doing?
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Bring the baby to me.
Do you want to lie down on the bed?
I'm going to massage your back.
Close your eyes.
I haven't gone yet.
Have you gone? I don't know.
You don't know? I don't know.
You don't know? Help me.
Wait a minute.
He looks like he is crying.
He finally woke up.
He woke up.
It's morning, so we have to go home.
We have to get ready to go home.
Are you sleepy?