This is the end of the story.
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry.
Oh, right.
I forgot to take off the gloves.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's go to the bathroom.
The bathroom is nice, isn't it?
Who's that girl?
She's my relative, Nana.
My parents went on a trip, and I'm taking care of her.
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Nana, this is Mumi.
Goro lives in the neighborhood.
Nice to meet you.
Nana is born and raised in the city.
It seems that the countryside is not as exciting as it seems.
Goro-chan, I told you not to play around.
No matter what you say, there's nothing to do these days.
All you can do is to take a bath.
I'm glad. I don't like taking a bath.
I was stabbed here earlier.
Oh, my, oh, my, it's a big deal.
Then I have to put on some medicine.
I've been working hard since I was little.
I'm a little tired.
I can't go.
It's impossible.
From here to Tokyo.
It takes a whole day by bus and train.
Why do you say that?
If you want to see me, you can come to me.
I just want to see you.
I know you met other girls.
What are you going to do?
Come on.
I'm going to leave.
Is something wrong?
You're not feeling well, are you?
No, I'm not.
You're not?
Even if you get dizzy,
you'll be fine.
Right?
Yes.
They say humans are the best.
What are you talking about?
There are good things and bad things after good things.
There are good things after bad things.
You may have a new voice when you fall in love.
If I had a boyfriend, I wouldn't be able to do what I couldn't do.
Even though I lost my grandfather, I was very lonely,
but I was supported by my neighbors,
and I could understand people's feelings better than before.
Yes, and I found a good man.
What? You have a boyfriend?
You must be bored living in the countryside.
But you can only do it here.
Maybe something good will happen.
OKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOKOK10
Hello!
What about you, Chiyoko?
I'm on a date.
A date?
I see.
It's nice to be able to fall in love no matter how old you are.
I'm jealous.
Can you lend me your hand?
You don't have a good boyfriend, do you?
I used to.
Well, I had a good boyfriend.
While I was busy, I was taken to other places.
Since then, I've been all alone.
Well, sometimes when I come to see my mother-in-law,
we talk to each other,
You know, I feel like I'm talking to you more than you are talking to me.
I'm so sleepy.
It's hot.
What is it?
What? No, no, no, no.
Nothing. Nothing.
Oh, right.
I didn't see you for a long time.
Well, I guess I'll have to go.
I'll be going.
Take care of your grandma.
Wait.
Uncle, sit here.
Okay.
Uncle, would you like to have a little chat with me?
A little chat?
Sure, but what are you going to do?
I'm so bored that I feel like I'm going to die.
Will you do anything for me?
Sure, anything is fine, but if it's something I can do for you...
Then...
Sex?
Sex? No, no, no.
Don't make fun of me.
I'm not making fun of you.
I just wanted to be with someone like you.
There are a lot of people in the industry.
Yes, there are.
A rich old man comes to me asking me if I want to be a father.
But I can't do that.
I want to have sex with someone like an old man.
What?
No?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Then it's okay?
Well, I guess so.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I have to take a bath.
What is this?
I get excited when I sweat.
You sweat like this?
No.
My sweat is the same as yours.
You don't like my sweat?
No.
I don't mind if you sweat.
But my feet are so dirty.
It's salty.
I'm going to put it on your face.
Your feet...
I can smell it.
It doesn't hurt at all.
I can't see your face properly.
What's wrong?
I'm a little embarrassed.
My feet are wet.
What's wrong?
What do you want me to do?
I've never done anything like this before.
You said you'd go out with me if you had time.
I'm going to put it on you.
Do you like nails too?
Your nails are amazing.
Amazing what?
You're good at it.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm going to take it off.
You're worried about the sweat, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
You want to take it off, don't you?
That's what you do when you're in a good mood.
Oh, I'm a little embarrassed.
Oh, I have a lot of sweat here.
Why?
It's so cold.
What's going on here?
It's a little different from usual.
What's that?
You are weird
Wait
Don't touch me
No, no, no
I wanted to have sex with you
Thank you
I haven't done it yet
Do you want to do it?
What? You don't want to do it?
No, I don't think so.
No, I don't think it's a good idea to do this.
Are you sure you don't want to do it?
Just a little bit.
You said you don't want to do it.
I think I'll stop.
Do you want to do it?
Do you want to pee?
I'm sorry.
Come here.
You don't need it, do you?
Wait a minute.
Let me touch you.
I like you a lot, don't I?
It's boring, isn't it?
You're in the way, aren't you?
Yeah.
Oh, it's gone.
Oh, it's a little out.
Cute.
I can see it.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Why?
Cute.
You're so cute.
Let me touch you.
Look at his face.
You're amazing.
It's hot.
Can I touch you?
It's okay.
It's a beautiful cup.
What kind of cup do you like?
I like this shape. This is nice.
Let me see.
Give me a hug.
You're so beautiful.
I want to see you more.
Am I beautiful?
You have a cute face.
You have a cute body.
I'm happy.
You're going to give me a lot of compliments, aren't you?
Yeah.
Oh, it's cold.
It's cold.
I don't want to run away.
I'm scared.
Hey, Uncle.
Don't be so impatient.
I'm not going to run away.
It's been a long time.
I'm bored.
That's right.
It's getting full.
It's getting like this.
How many times did you throw it away?
You are a good boy, aren't you?
Well, I haven't seen you for a long time.
It's been a long time?
Oh, look at me.
Oh, I said hello.
Take a deep breath.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Get on my side.
It's getting hot.
You can't sleep on your own.
I'll hold it in.
It's not nice to sleep together.
You're so cute.
What are you looking at?
Look at me.
I'm sorry.
I was too close.
It's okay.
Hey, wait a minute.
Don't touch me.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
Come here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You want to put it in?
But...
I can't tell you to put it in.
Why not?
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Something is coming out.
No, no, no.
It's dirty.
You're so dirty.
I'm sweating.
Are you sweating?
Can I lick it?
Oh, it's in your mouth.
Oh, your tongue.
It's all wet because of the old man.
You're lucky today.
I was lucky.
The old man came, didn't he?
I'm going on a date with my grandma.
What should I do?
I was so hungry that I couldn't eat anything.
I'm so full.
Wow, you're doing a great job.
It's very soft.
It feels so good.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's the first time I see you like this.
It's the first time I've ever seen you like this.
Is it?
It feels good, doesn't it?
It feels good.
It's coming out of my throat.
I can't stop it.
It's amazing.
It's scary.
It feels good.
Don't go.
It feels good, so hold on.
It's coming out.
No, no.
Look at that!
You're amazing, aren't you?
You're amazing.
I'm all wet.
Number one.
What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Are you still sleepy?
Are you okay?
What?
I'm fine with it.
What about you?
I'm fine with it too.
I'll do it more.
It's just a waste of time.
It's a secret from your grandmother.
What are you doing?
It's in.
Uncle,
how do you feel inside my blanket?
It feels great.
It feels great?
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm going to die.
You're so chubby.
Yes.
It's getting bigger.
It's about to tear.
It's so tight.
Does it hurt?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Yes, it feels good.
Wow, this is amazing.
It's so cool in here.
It's amazing.
Look at me.
It feels good.
No, no.
What?
You can't feel better by yourself.
It really hurts.
Feels good.
I feel good inside.
It's white.
Your waist.
Are you okay?
I feel good.
I'll do it again.
Why?
You want me to do it again?
I can't do it anymore.
It's a little intense.
It feels good.
It's so hot.
It's hot.
I'm so tired.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Oh, it's cold.
You're not moving at all, are you?
Yes, I am.
Wow.
Oh, it's cold.
More more!
This!
Oh, feels good!
Fuck it.
You can do it more.
I can see your back.
Yeah, I can see it.
I was looking somewhere.
I'm sorry.
Oh, there you are.
Did you see?
Yes, I did.
Your butt is so beautiful.
Can you see it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Really?
Yes.
Can you see me?
Yes, I can see you.
I feel so good.
I'm so tired.
Great.
Amazing.
Oh, my God.
It's so tight.
What should I do?
Wow, it feels so good.
Do you feel good?
I'll do it for you.
Really?
If you feel good, come up to me.
Okay.
You're so cute.
You want to be up there too, right?
Oh, it hurts.
It hurts.
Are you okay?
You're a pervert.
It feels good.
Feels good?
Close your eyes.
It's closed.
I'm glad you woke up.
This is amazing.
I'm so tired.
I can't sleep.
What?
I can't do it anymore.
I'm sorry.
Wake up, uncle.
Hold on, Pon-chan.
Pon-chan, hold on.
Hold on.
Thank you.
I'll go get some water.
Hold on tight.
I feel like I'm about to cry.
I'm so happy.
Ah, my legs hurt.
What happened?
What's wrong?
It hurts.
Huh?
Where is it?
Where is your favorite spot?
Right here
Okay
I don't care where it is
Ah
Huh?
I'm sorry
Ah
Oh, my God.
What should I do?
Oh, it's cold.
Let me lick you.
What is it?
You're moving too much.
I'm sorry.
You're crying too much.
Let's sit here.
Okay.
Wow.
Thank you.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
Everyone in this village is so kind.
It's a small village, so we have to support each other.
If someone's in trouble, we'll help.
That's what this village is like.
Hmm.
If there's someone in trouble, I have to help you.
Oh, that's a good idea.
I'm sorry.
What?
Nothing.
You're in trouble, aren't you?
What?
Because you were looking at me because you didn't like me.
You wanted to touch my boobs.
Don't you want to be licked like this?
Don't you think so?
I'll help you.
Let's go.
Please lie down.
Come on.
I'll help you.
I'm talking about Tsugi-san.
No?
Hey, lick it properly.
Yeah, yeah.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
Good.
How is it?
Is it good?
Yes
How is it?
I'm sorry.
I feel so bad.
Do you feel bad?
Like the people in the village?
That's right.
I'll be in trouble.
Won't you be in trouble if you do that?
I'll be in trouble if I don't do it.
You don't mind if I do it?
No, but...
Won't you wake me up?
No, I won't.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I did my best.
I'm so tired.
It's so cold.
Are you okay?
You're all sweaty.
I'm in trouble.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you in trouble?
I'm trying to help you.
Why are you running away?
Can I have a sip?
I'll always help you when you're in trouble.
What?
It's like today.
How is it?
I want you to help me.
What happened to her.
I'm sorry.
You're wearing a very embarrassing costume.
Why are you still here?
Can I talk to you?
No.
Can I make a sound?
It tickles.
You brought delicious vegetables for me, didn't you?
Yes.
Do you feel good now?
Yes, but I'm a little confused.
Look at me more.
You're not touching it yet, but it's getting harder over there.
Why is it getting harder over there?
It's because I'm holding it here.
I'm holding it here.
Can you open it for me?
Oh, like this?
There you go.
Wait a minute.
I want to go to bed.
No, but...
No?
No, you can't do that.
You're dressed like this, but you can't show it to me.
I can't show it to you.
You're weird.
You're definitely weird.
You didn't say you wanted help, did you?
I did.
I told you so.
Wait, don't do that.
Why are you hiding it?
Because...
It's not a joke.
Oh, it's warm.
No, no, no.
No?
I don't think so.
Do you want me to pet you?
No, I don't.
How do you like to be touched?
Do you like to be touched?
I'm sorry.
I want to help you.
Tell me how you feel.
Let me see your face.
You look like you've seen a doll.
Do you want to see it?
Let me show you.
Can you see it?
Yes, I can see it.
What do you think of my boobs and your boobs?
Can you see them?
Alright,
Look...
Wow...
Well, your uncle is rubbing your chin a lot.
Does it feel good?
Really?
Uncle, you're holding it in, right?
Yeah.
You're making a lot of sounds.
Wow!
Amazing!
Yes, it feels like I'm being touched by the acupuncture point, too.
This?
You like this kind of thing?
Like this?
Tell me more about what you like.
No, no. I'll do my best.
This one?
Yes.
Wow, I like this strong one.
Oh, it's a Saki-podame.
No way.
You're a pervert, too.
Oh, that's a Saki-podame.
It's getting harder and harder.
I'm gonna lick you.
No, I'm not gonna lick you.
What?
What's going on?
I told you not to lick me.
I'm so tired.
Then, I'm not gonna lick you.
No, but...
I'm so tired.
Then, I'm not gonna lick you.
No, but...
What are you going to do?
Oh, I'm counting on you.
Thank you.
No, it's here.
Wow.
You look so cool, old man.
How do you feel?
I almost fell asleep.
Wow, it's getting harder again.
Your blood pressure is getting really hard.
Yes, it feels good.
Show me how you feel.
It feels good.
Make more sounds.
Squish it.
A
May I?
Let's go.
Are you okay?
I'm glad it's not raining.
But...
No, no.
Are you going?
I'm so tired.
You can't do it anymore.
You're so fat.
I'm fine.
You can't do it anymore.
But you're coming out a lot.
I'm so tired.
Me too.
It's been a long time since I had a massage.
I'm tired again.
Did you bring it?
You're fast.
You have a grumpy face.
Can you show me more?
More, more.
It feels good.
Oh, sorry.
Ah, sorry.
You came out at once.
Did you feel good?
It's still hard.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea to have a cat that's not afraid of anything.
I'm going to take a bath.
I'm so happy.
Why are you here?
I'm here.
I'm not here tomorrow.
It's hot.
Well then, I guess I should get going.
It's fine. Take your time.
I'll be fine. I'll be fine.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
Don't be so self-righteous.
Rest until you're fully recovered.
Well then, I'll do as you say.
I'm sorry.
I drank too much.
It's okay.
Chiyo has a relative of yours and Benpin.
Are you from Tokyo?
Uncle, you smell like alcohol.
I'm sorry.
What?
You were looking at me like you didn't like me, weren't you?
No, I wasn't.
Really?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Can you hear me?
Have you ever done something like this to me?
No.
I've never done anything like that.
Huh?
It's been a long time since I've been drinking, and you've been standing up.
Don't tease me.
I'm not teasing you.
How are you?
I'm scared.
Don't make a sound.
What did you say?
What did you do?
What are you looking at?
You wanted to kiss me, right?
I'm sorry.
Well, that's...
Can I do it?
What?
Don't you want to do it?
No, I don't.
Okay, okay, okay.
Ouch!
That's...
Be clear, old man.
You're an adult, aren't you?
I want to believe.
Do you want to start from the old man?
What do you want me to do?
It's okay.
Let's start from the top.
I'm scared.
You're so cute.
Wow, you are so weak.
You were looking at me with a grumpy look.
My hands It's like this
It's hot.
Ah...
What do you want me to do?
What?
Are you okay?
What do you want to lick?
Lick me.
Where?
Here.
Here?
Ah...
If you make that sound, grandma will come.
Are you okay?
Please touch me.
What should I do?
Please.
Please touch me.
Can you do me a favor?
It hurts a lot.
You look like you're in a good mood, Mr.Sukouji.
This is in the way.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's okay, isn't it, old man?
What's wrong?
It's not good.
The old man told you to lick it, didn't he?
No, that's right, but...
Which one?
Is it no good?
Is it okay?
Which one?
You look like a pervert.
Please be quiet.
Your grandmother will hear you.
They may already hear you.
Is it good?
Does it feel good?
Oh, you feel good, don't you?
You're so cute.
You don't do it often, do you?
What are you talking about?
Are you doing it?
I'm not doing it.
Then, how about a girl's boobs?
You haven't touched it yet?
How is it?
I can't hold it.
It's so soft.
Uncle, try harder.
What are you doing?
What do you want to do?
I can't do it like this.
You are the one who needs to do it.
No, no, no.
No.
You might be watched by someone.
What should I do?
You're a pervert, aren't you, old man?
You want to do something dirty again?
I see.
You like the last one, don't you?
You can't sleep on your own.
No, I can't.
You can't sleep on your own, can you?
I can't.
He is sleeping.
Don't do that.
Let me out.
He is not feeling good yet.
What is it?
What do you want to do?
I want to feel the feeling.
What should I do?
I want to do this.
What?
You are so positive, aren't you?
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
You are always going to go.
I want to eat.
You look so sad.
Why do you look like that?
I want to go out.
No, you can't.
You'll get a fever if you stay here.
What?
It's an old man.
What are you doing?
What?
I'm closing the door.
Here?
Ah!
It's cold, isn't it?
Ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh, it's warm.
I'm coming.
It feels good.
It's warm.
It's warm and it feels good.
Don't go without permission.
Have you ever seen an old man moving?
No, I haven't.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I'm scared.
Don't do what I did.
Uncle, look at me.
Feels good.
Uncle, you look like that.
No, no, no.
Don't do that.
No.
I'm sorry.
Your face is so cute.
You're so cute.
I'm sorry.
Let's go back near your arm
Do not give up
It's okay
Disappearing
What should I do?
Ah...
It's moving a lot.
Let's go to the second floor.
From the back.
From the back?
Yes, from the back.
I like the second and third floors.
Here?
What are you doing?
Haa
I'm sleepy
I'm so cold.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, my God.
He's gone.
Masu...
Are you asleep?
I can see over there.
It's so hot.
Let's go in.
Open your mouth.
It's sweet.
I'm sorry.
Wow, amazing!
My back is moving.
I'm sorry.
It's so painful.
It hurts.
It's painful.
It's so painful.
The first time I saw her, I was shocked.
I thought she was crying.
I'm sorry.
She was so cute.
I want to see her like this.
I was surprised.
She was so cute.
I was so shocked.
It's coming.
Ouch!
It's a good smell.
It's so cool.
Oh, it hurts.
Amazing.
Have you ever done this before?
Yes, it was my first time.
First time?
Amazing.
Oh, no.
How do you feel, Mr. Kimochi?
Mr. Kimochi, Mr. Kimochi.
You're amazing.
Mr. Kimochi, touch my boobs.
My boobs?
Mr. Kimochi, Mr. Kimochi.
How are you feeling?
Well then, let's take a break.
What? Take a break?
I don't have a break.
It's been like this since morning.
Today, I'm going to do it all day long until my grandmother comes home.
All day long?
Yeah.
No?
It's getting bigger.
But...
It's impossible.
It's fun to play with you.
I'm dying because I've been playing with you for a long time.
It's a dream.
It's a feeling.
It's about time.
Don't do that.
Ouch!
It's so strange.
I'm sorry.
I've already taken care of your feelings.
The phone is ringing.
I'm tired.
Don't you want to start over?
The phone is ringing.
Well, I'll think about it when I get home.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
I might die again today.
Oh, that's boring.
I have a favor to ask you.
I think so.
You think so?
Yeah.
Nara-chan, he's a good guy, but he's a little shy and shy.
He's interested in women, but he's inexperienced.
So, Nara-chan, can you make him a man?
What are you going to do?
Well, I don't have time, so I don't mind.
You don't mind? Thank you, thank you.
Yuppe, I'm going.
Do your best.
Nara-chan, I'm counting on you.
Doutei, huh?
Doutei is so precious to an old man.
I don't think I'll see you in Tokyo.
Come here.
You're too stiff.
Are you scared?
Have you ever kissed someone?
Then what about holding hands like this?
Then what about seeing boobs?
Do you have any?
If it's a video...
A video?
Look at me.
Look at me like that.
Can I kiss you?
Huh?
Yeah.
Wow, you really are a virgin.
It's your first kiss.
I'll give you a lot.
This is...
There's a lot of hair.
How do you feel?
It's soft.
And it's warm.
It's sticky, right?
I really wanted to see you.
Then you won't forget me forever, right?
You're so cute.
Open your mouth.
Do you want more?
Wow.
It's the same as before, isn't it?
It smells like a girl.
It smells like a girl?
You're a brother, aren't you?
You don't know that it smells like a girl, do you?
But it's different from a boy.
That's right.
I was asked to make you a man.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
Can I sit down?
It's okay.
Uncle!
Pant...
Hey, old man!
No more!
You're being too harsh!
I'm sorry.
I felt bad to make a big mistake.
I behaves like this too much in Mtaanp.
That's why I...
watch too much ESP.
Am I wrong?
If you keep staring at me like that, I'll get mad at you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'll be the one to blame.
You just have to feel good today.
Yeah, I'll teach you how to do it.
Let's go to sleep.
I wonder what you like more.
Ah!
What?
I like you too.
Amazing.
Amazing. I can feel it everywhere.
You're a little sensitive, aren't you?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I'm so happy to be able to be with an old man like you.
Should I take off the bottom too?
You don't need it, do you?
Don't laugh.
Oh, no.
Is this your first time seeing this?
It's a little embarrassing.
Show me.
What?
Wait, wait.
Here.
I'll do it here.
Sorry it's too small.
You don't like the size of it?
No.
As if you can handle it?
I'm sorry, I didn't have anyone to fight with until now.
I have someone to fight with.
What about me?
If you don't move, I'll go home.
I'm sorry, I understand.
It's so big.
It's warm.
It was kind of scary.
Breeze
Tucker, you're cute!
He fell asleep.
Oh, my God.
It feels so good.
You're going to go to bed soon, aren't you?
That's not good.
Can I take it off, too?
Wait for me.
Let's have a drink.
How do you feel?
Do you want to drink with me?
Can I sleep with you?
Do you want to wake up with me?
Then, can you drink with me?
Wow!
Can I drink with you?
Did you see it for the first time?
What are you doing?
You can drink as much as you want.
I'm sorry.
No, you're about to die.
But I...
Don't do it on your own.
I'm sorry, but...
You're so sweet.
I think this is the biggest one I've seen recently.
I don't want it.
That was dangerous.
You turned really scary.
Hey, act what I do.
Don't lick my nipples.
I'm sorry.
You're so good at licking your feet, Masai-kun.
It feels so good.
You're sweating too much.
I love you too much.
What's wrong?
What are you thinking about?
Just think of something that makes you feel good.
Touch your belly.
Like this.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Look at me.
Touch me a lot.
Touch my wrist.
Gently?
Yes, gently.
Like this?
It feels good.
Touch me a lot.
I'm so tired.
Good.
Miss Shiou!
I feel so good.
I'm rubbing your butt in my belly.
Amazing.
You look like a man.
Thank you.
I haven't put it in yet.
Are you okay?
I don't want to.
I want to fall.
I want to feel good too.
Touch me a lot.
I feel so good.
You're tired, aren't you?
I'm tired.
No...
Can't you do it again?
Wow
Thank you.
Are you crying?
I just wanna talk to you.
Wow.
Ahhhh...!
No.
No, no, don't.
No, no.
You're so cute.
You're smiling like you're happy.
You're thinking about Tetsu every day, aren't you?
I'm sorry.
You're happy for the first time, aren't you?
I can't.
I can't do it.
You don't like it?
No.
I don't like it.
I'm so tired.
Let's take a deep breath.
Ah...
Do you want to sleep?
No...
Ah...
Should I put some water in?
What?
This is the first time.
You don't have to look anymore.
Amazing.
I think I can go in.
I wonder if he'll come back.
How did you get in there?
Look, he's in here.
How do you feel?
It's so hot.
It's so warm.
How do you feel?
Oh, Imao-chan.
Naga-chan, don't go too far.
I'm sorry, Imao-chan.
Naga-chan.
Ren, wait.
I can't.
More!
I fell.
More.
It feels so good.
This is...
I can't touch it.
Oh, it's so good.
It feels so good.
Let's do it one more time.
Ah!
Hmmm!
Oh!
Oh, it's cold.
It's so cold.
Oh, it's so cold.
Oh, it's cold.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
Mom.
What?
Mom's Lewis is just so cute.
What's he thinking?
What?
What are you doing?
I want to sleep more.
What are you looking at?
What is this?
You're wearing a embarrassing costume.
Have you ever dressed like this?
No.
This is the first time.
What are you going to do?
Wait a minute.
I'll put it in.
This is amazing.
You can see everything.
I've never seen anything like this in a video.
Amazing.
It's always better than being sick, right?
Where did you learn this?
Amazing.
Ai-chan, don't.
Are you going to die?
Be careful.
No.
You have to go to the hospital.
I got it.
More.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
More.
It feels so good.
Mami, show me your face!
Go!
One more time.
It's hot.
It feels good.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's the first time for me. I'm glad.
I'm happy.
It's the first time for me.
I want to be a husband.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
Let me try from the back.
From the back?
From behind...
Right here.
Let's finish.
Here.
Let's put these back in.
No.
Right, here.
Aw...
I feel so good.
Why am I so sleepy?
I'm doing a good job.
I'm tired.
Oh, no.
Mom...
I'm tired.
Mom, stay here.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm still a baby.
Don't be so mean.
I've gotten a lot better.
Thank you so much.
I'm going to go.
Are you going to go?
No.
I want you to feel better inside of me.
Let me know when you feel better.
It's okay.
How do you feel?
Minji...
I'm sorry.
I can't touch your hand.
Nana.
I'm sorry.
I want to go to the bathroom, but I can't go to the bathroom, so I'm going to go to the bathroom.
It's cold.
Where should I put it?
You can take it out.
Do you want to take it out?
No.
I want to take it out where you like.
Give me the first one.
What?
I can't do it anymore
Let's go.
I think I'm going to die.
Are you going?
No.
Please take care of him.
Be careful.
Okay.
Ooops.
That's fine.
Let's go to the cinema.
Why are you article 2?
Turkey Sorry.
Is he there?
Hello?
Sorry, can you ignore me?
I don't know whether to restart or not.
I'll tell you when I get home.
I'm busy now, so I'll call you again.
Hmm?
Well, I'm free, but...
I'm busy killing time.
I can't do this anymore, Nara-chan. Please forgive me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Thank you for watching.