This is a tour that gives a
dream to an amateur boy.
I'm so nervous.
I'm Rima Nairi. Nice to meet you.
I'm No.13. I'll do my best.
I'm Sumire Kuramoto. Nice to meet you.
I'm No.8. Bye-bye.
I'm Hana Himesaki.
I'm No.15. Nice to meet you.
I'm Nozomi Ishihara.
I'm No.1. Nice to meet you.
I'm Enna-chan, also known as Satsuki Enna.
I'm No.3.
I'm No.8.
I'm No.16.
Hi, everyone. I'm Aoi Ibuki,
a member of the ladies' team.
Let's get started.
I'm No.9.
I'm No.1, Mary.
Let's go!
No.6
Here I go!
I'm Kana Morisawa.
No.10 I'm Oka Asano.
No.5
It's my favorite number.
I'm going to go to Ico and Arisawa.
I'm Jun Seihido.
No.14
I'll do my best.
I'm Arisu Otsuwa.
No.4
I'm Mizuki Yayoi.
I'm Mizuki.
I'm No.12.
I'm Hiraku.
I'm No.9.
I'm No.5.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to win.
I'm Ichika Matsumoto.
I'm Takao Takuya.
I'm going to challenge a lot.
I'll do my best.
I'm Miyuki Kosuke.
I'm Yu.
Do you do anything special for today?
I'm drinking a lot of supplies.
I'm Okada.
Who was good? I'm Arai Ryo.
I'm Arai Ryo.
What?
You don't have it?
I don't have it.
You don't have a seat on the bus, do you?
Yes, that's all.
Thank you for watching
Moody's work from day to day.
I'm Aoi Ibuki and I'm Nozomi Ishihara.
Welcome to the legendary super super super
super super super super big, Bakobus tour!
So we have to have him today.
Yeah.
A man who knows everything about
Bakobus, KenKen, aka Shimabukuro Hiroshi.
Yay!
Good morning everyone!
Good morning!
This is Shimabukuro.
It's been 10 years since we last met.
Wow!
It's been 10 years for me, too.
It's been a long time since I had a meal.
I thought I had a stomachache.
No, you didn't.
That's it.
Thank you.
Mr. Kenkei.
I'd like to ask you for an advice.
Well, if I have to give you an advice,
Everyone, there are a
lot of fun things to do.
That's right.
Let's do our best! Let's have fun!
Wow!
Thank you!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Thank you, Mr. KenKen.
And there's one more person.
We have a special guest.
You're curious,
right? I'm Hinari.
I'm Karen Yuzuriha, and I'm in
charge of breasts and premiums.
I'll do my best to be erotic and fun.
Let's do our best.
Thank you so much!
I found it!
What is it?
It's a member of TASK.
It's me, too!
I want to write TASK, too.
She is hesitating.
Are you OK?
Let's say the title call.
Ready, set, go!
Aim!
Welcome to AVNine's
Moody's Thank You Party!
Let's start with the
self-introduction of the actresses.
It's not fun if we introduce
ourselves normally.
How about introducing
ourselves with honking?
Let me introduce myself!
Let's introduce ourselves!
Oh my god!
Let's go!
Let's start from the first team.
From us?
Yes, you can start.
Oh my god! I'm nervous.
Please introduce yourself again.
Yes.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Nozomi Ishihara.
I'm Nozomi. Nice to meet you.
How many works have you made?
Me?
I think less than 100.
Can you tell me your best work?
What? Your best work.
Eh? Ruined Orgasm.
I see.
It's on the right now.
This one.
Which part?
Which part? The highlight.
The highlight is... the
last scene with the director.
I see.
I think it's erotic when Samawari
becomes a man when he is taking a picture.
He is always saying something,
but he has become a boy.
Are you A-san? Please introduce yourself.
I'm A-san. I'm 40 years old and
I came from Fukuoka prefecture.
A-san, you have some features.
I have a wife.
A wife? A mistress?
Yes, I'm a mistress.
I'm Kenta.
Where is your
wife? She is at home.
At home?
Yes.
Don't you worry
about her? No, no.
My wife is a bit of a playboy.
I see.
She watches my works together.
She is like,
I'm not sure if I should do this or that.
I see.
She is teaching me how to act.
We are Real NTR.
She is like, I think you
need more firepower.
Yes.
I think I've managed to do something.
How many shots can you shoot this time?
It's a pleasant 15 shots,
but I'd like to shoot 10 shots.
This time, look at this, everyone.
Every time I shoot, this comes to me.
A little rock taste.
Bang, bang, burst.
Life is about shooting.
It feels like it's going to sell a little.
Think about your wife and make
her stand with a sense of guilt.
I'm going to get a divorce.
I can see you.
I'm from the top.
Can I show my
nipples? Of course.
Please show your nipples.
I can't show my nipples.
I can't.
Of course I can.
One minute left.
Hurry up.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Moody's is following the rules.
We agree to the invoice.
What do you like?
Do you like Pekoki or Ferrari?
Are you a person who likes to be licked?
I'm a person who likes to be licked.
You're lying.
Ichihara-san seems to be taking a nap.
He's taking a break.
I'm not taking a break.
He's not taking a break.
It's over.
It's a shame.
I'll do my best next time.
Hello.
I'm Aoi Ibuki, a member of Moody's.
Are you a member
of Moody's? Yes, I am.
How many do you have?
I have about 30 to 40.
You have a long way to go.
I have a long way to go.
I have a beautiful manko.
You have a beautiful manko.
You said it yourself.
I have a beautiful manko.
We will see it together later.
Yes.
We will see it together.
Taku-san, what is that?
Are you a Yari-chin?
I am a Yari-chin.
Where are you from?
Where? The back.
The back?
Then I'll lick the back a lot.
I'd like to ask you how to be popular.
How to be popular?
Yes, how to be popular.
How to be popular as a man.
Well, the ability to embrace.
The ability to embrace.
Calmness.
How dare you.
Well, by yourself.
Well.
You should take it off.
You want this, don't you? I do.
This.
I want to fill all my arms.
Did you exercise
yesterday? No, I didn't.
I thought you didn't.
How many days did you
exercise? Only one day.
The day before yesterday.
Let's work out for a week.
It's rare to have a day like this.
That's right.
What?
Ten seconds ago.
Oh, no.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Time's up!
Oh my god! Why? Nervous.
Nervous.
I'm Yuzuriha Karen, and I'm in
charge of breasts and premiums.
Look, look!
It's Piper!
She's the youngest, 21 years old!
Yes!
Plus, it's Piper!
Piper!
Nice!
It's red!
It smells red!
How old are you?
I'm 14 years old.
14 years old!
The lemon juice is amazing.
Can I lick it now?
Can I eat it? Let's eat.
Do you watch videos
often? Yes, I do.
Who do you watch?
We are quite different.
You are not different.
I watch Yuzuriha-san.
You are alone.
Who are you? I
watch Yuzuriha-san.
You buy everything, don't you?
I buy everything.
Really?
You can't buy it online.
No, I can't.
You can't, can you? No, I can't.
I was going to watch it for 300 yen.
No, you can't.
I can't.
Do you have a goal today?
How many points
will you get? I'll get 6.
That's pretty low.
I'll get 6.
6?
Yes.
What's the average number of people?
Is it okay if I get 6?
Well, maybe 15?
15? That's about 11 people.
Ah, I see.
It's not that much.
Senpai.
I don't really count.
You don't count?
You don't count one
by one? I don't know.
You are good at showing the camera.
Really?
Yes, you are good at it.
It's delicious.
It's easy to swallow
because it's a pie-pan.
It's the same pie-pan as me.
You can do it.
Close your eyes.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Time's up!
What a shame!
I'm Kana Morisawa.
You look great.
Did you take the train?
Did you bring your
bag? Yes, I did.
Who are you?
My name is Koushi.
Yes.
Let's get started.
You are Koushi,
right? Yes, I am.
Koushi.
Let's eat.
Who told you about
today? My friend.
Don't say that.
It's a secret.
Don't tell anyone.
I'm not planning a tour.
I'm just going to appear in a music video.
You can go after it's released.
Oh, after it's released.
It's delicious.
It feels good.
Can I touch your
boobs? Yes, you can.
Can I touch your boobs?
I can't stand it.
Show me.
Do you want me to put it down?
It looks so big.
I touched it.
Can you show it
to us? It's gone.
It's the same.
It's out.
It's embarrassing.
Everyone, it's your
first time to come here.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
5 seconds left.
Really?
4, 3, Oh, it's true.
It's back.
3,
2, 1 It's over.
It's a pity.
Thank you very much.
Please enjoy the rest of the show.
I really want to go.
Before the show is over.
Has it already
started? It's started.
It's a good feeling,
isn't it? It's fast.
It's fast.
They are kissing.
I'm sorry.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Ena Satsuki.
Have you already started?
I couldn't wait.
Please tell me about
your sexual orientation.
Who am I?
I'm asking you who you are.
My sexual orientation is inside the mouth.
I'm in the middle of a kiss.
So I love Pera.
I love kisses, too.
Well, well.
I don't mind if you kiss me.
Isuzu-san.
Yes.
You tried to kill yourself once.
Why again? To live.
What? To live.
I didn't know I was going to live.
You didn't know you were going to live?
Yes.
If you live, more erotic
things will happen.
That's deep.
I'm glad I'm alive.
But you're glad you're alive, right?
Yes.
Why did you stop there?
I was about to break up officially.
What?
You were about
to break up? I see.
You should have done it.
Why didn't you
do it? I was scared.
You were scared?
Yes.
Did you go to the
cliff? No, I didn't.
Where?
I thought I would go there.
Yes.
I thought I would go to Tojimbo.
But I couldn't move.
You couldn't move.
The weather has changed again.
You decided to go to Hakubasu.
Yes.
Are you looking forward to it?
Let's move forward in life.
We are important.
Look, she's taking it off.
You have to help her.
This is what leads to self-injury.
Self-injury?
Is it wrong?
Does it mean that you
are about to be injured?
I read it in a book.
It's a joint work, isn't it?
What are you going to do?
This hand!
Yes!
It's a joint work!
It's the first soil bath today!
Yes!
Please give me a seat belt.
I'm so excited that I forgot.
You have a seat belt, right?
It's long, isn't
it? Yes, it's long.
Yes, I know.
It's long.
I'm sorry.
It's a co-operation.
Sex.
You can overcome anything, right?
Yes.
In the end.
If you break it.
Please send a message to the
people who are trying to save their lives.
Keep going until something good happens.
10 seconds left.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up.
Why don't you
take it out? It's okay.
Let's go out secretly later.
You are so kind.
Thank you very much.
I'm No.11.
Are you No.
11? Can you introduce
yourself again? Of course.
Me? Yes, you.
Who are you?
You look like a man.
I'm Uta Hibino. Nice to meet you.
What is your specialty?
What do you want
people to pay attention to?
I'm good at shio-fuki and kizuo-i.
Can you do self-defense?
I can do anything.
Anything? I'm looking forward to it.
I want people to pay attention to that.
Let's get started.
Let's go.
You're Yuuki, right?
Yes.
What do you do for
a living? I'm a nurse.
Oh, you're a nurse.
Yes.
I see.
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
I've had a lot of girlfriends at work.
Have you ever had
sex? No, I haven't.
But if there's a nice girl
around, I approach her.
I want to approach.
Haven't you done it yet?
I've almost done it.
What will you do if you
get sued? I'll apologize.
I'm sorry.
You want to be an AV
actor, don't you? I do.
What kind of AV actor do you want to be?
I want to be all over the place.
They eat a lot.
Do they stand up? Yes, they do.
Please raise your hands
if you are in a hurry.
This is the first launch.
I think we can do it.
I think so, too.
Oh, no.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Raise your hands.
Did you get it?
Yes.
This is it.
Great.
It's the first launch.
It's the first launch in a week.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'll give you this.
Thank you.
It's my first time to shoot.
Put it on.
Thank you.
Life is about shooting.
It's great.
How was it?
It was so good that I couldn't hold it.
How long did you
hold it? One week.
This is the right answer.
Yes.
It was good, wasn't it?
Yes, it was great.
I was nervous all the time.
Thank you very much.
Finally, it's like AV.
It's already started.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Alice Watson.
Nice to meet you.
You are young.
Am I?
I think I'm the oldest among them.
Someone said the same thing.
Is that so? No way.
Because I'm the 11th year of Gale Key.
What?
So even if you started at 18,
you're about 29 years old, right?
No, I'm 20 years old.
I see.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Takuro.
Takuro, do you want to be an AV director?
Yes.
Do you have any plans?
I heard I've been saving up for a week.
Why?
I've been working hard.
Working hard?
Yes.
What kind of director do
you want to be? Hardware.
Hardware.
For example?
Mr.Peloto.
Oh!
Then, please enjoy the film.
I was very nervous just now.
Because I saw Uta-chan's film.
I was very nervous.
I was nervous.
He is very macho.
Look! It's coming out!
Do you want to touch it?
Touch it!
Look! It's licking you!
It's licking you!
That's right!
Say, Mama!
What?
Mama!
That's right!
Babu babu nitsuka?
This one too!
Babu!
Do you like it? It's cute.
Is it F cup?
I think it's H cup.
Excuse me, it's H cup.
Look, it's coming out.
It's amazing.
You have to say it more carefully.
I want to see it.
You want to see
it, right? Yes, I do.
I'm going to get a good one.
Do you want it? I'll get it.
Please.
Don't eat it.
I'll give it to you.
You want to see it, don't you?
Is it good?
You have to say it.
You want to see it.
I want to see it.
Show me.
This is the first time
for everyone to see it.
This is the first time for
everyone to see the mosaic.
This is a digital mosaic since 2004.
It feels good.
Maybe it's a little darker than before.
It's one minute before.
Please lick it.
Wow!
This is not a small one.
Yes, it is.
Isn't it?
But he watches my works a lot.
Does he?
Yes, so I want to do something hard.
That's good.
What do you like about him?
He has a long tongue.
What?
If you have a long tongue,
who do you like? I like blondes.
You like blondes, don't you?
It's a short hair.
10 seconds left.
I like long hair.
Put your hair down.
You should do it.
Time's up.
It's a pity.
Why didn't you do it?
I couldn't concentrate.
I couldn't do it.
I know.
Well, that's it.
I was nervous.
You were nervous.
Well, good luck.
Do you think you will win
the bronze medal this time?
Blue-winged horse.
Bronze medal.
What should I do?
Did you win the bronze medal?
Me?
Yayoi Mizuki?
Is it OK? Actually.
..
But you are not.
I will win the bronze medal with Arai Rima.
Actually, Arai Rima was good.
Do you like Arairima-chan?
Do you know that I
like her? She is here.
Wait.
You are next to Yayoi Mizuki.
Are you ready?
Are you ready? I'll kiss you.
It's your first kiss, isn't it?
It's my first kiss.
I'll steal your first kiss.
Are you ready?
Are you ready? Wait a minute.
Is it better to have different eyes?
The first kiss is...
I'll steal it.
You are happy, aren't you?
I want Mizuki-chan to do it.
I'm going to cry.
Look at me.
I'm going to get your fans' attention.
You're cute.
You look like a mussel.
Where is Kito?
Kito! I found him.
I'm nervous.
You're not cute.
Don't do that.
Your face turned red.
Are you OK?
Are you nervous? Yes, I am.
Your face is so red.
You are so cute.
I was wondering how you
would feel when I touch you.
I was imagining it.
Your dream will come true.
Yes, it will.
Let's eat.
It feels good.
You washed your hair
yesterday, didn't you? Yes, I did.
Did you wash your
hair? Yes, I did.
How did you do it?
I washed my hair carefully.
Yes, you did.
Yes, I did.
I think your hair will grow out.
Oh, no.
It's OK.
Oh, it grew out.
It's so cute.
It grew out.
It's so red.
It's so cool.
All the blood is coming to me.
Thank you so much.
It feels so good.
All of it.
You will fall down later.
It's so cool.
You will remember today when you die.
That's right.
It's so cool.
It's so cool?
You should go there.
Should I?
You don't have to
be Rimochi! Oh, no.
You want to come,
don't you? No, I don't.
I don't want to.
I'll go.
You want to go,
don't you? Oh, no.
I can't think of anything.
You can't think of Rimochi?
Really? Really.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
Is it the best?
How do you feel?
Scream!
Do you want me to shake more?
It's real!
Why couldn't I say that in my life?
One minute left!
It's a waste to take it off.
I have to take it off.
I want to take it off.
It's a waste.
You've caught a lot of AV, haven't you?
I've caught a lot.
You've bought it,
haven't you? Yes, I have.
Which one? Delivery?
Yes, it's a delivery.
It's like a delivery from a delivery man.
It's a regular delivery.
Of course.
But it's 300 yen,
isn't it? No, it's not.
It's not a campaign,
is it? No, it's not.
Thank you very much.
Please buy a new swimsuit.
Yes, I will.
I'm waiting for you.
It feels good, doesn't it?
10 seconds left.
I can't hold it.
Hurry up.
I'm in a hurry.
Oh no! They are running.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10!
Finish!
I knew it!
My erotic director is annoying, isn't he?
I told you not to be loud.
You've been annoying!
You shut up!
I did not want to tell you!
We have many chances!
Congratulations! You're a grown-up now!
You're sweating so much!
You're so cute!
It was fun!
How many times are you going to do it?
What's your plan?
I want to do it with everyone.
You bastard!
I won't forgive you!
Let's go to the next one!
I'm going to take it away!
Thank you very much!
It was fun!
No.5.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Misono Akiya. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
What is your charming point?
Charming point?
Where do you feel
confident? My boobs.
Your boobs.
What is your size?
From the bottom.
My butt is over 90cm.
I have more than 60cm.
It's not good to hit the back of your butt.
To the back of my butt.
Is it OK to hit?
No.
No? It's OK.
It's OK?
Is it a little bit smaller than the middle?
Which do you think?
Yes.
And the middle?
The middle?
Do I have to say it?
You can hide it.
How tall are you?
I'm about 60 cm.
And you?
I'm about 95 cm.
You're tall.
I'm G cup.
You're G cup.
You look like G cup.
Do you want to
see it? Yes, I do.
Please show me.
I'm G cup.
You look tall.
This is a camisole.
Camisole, isn't it?
In the past, it was called a shimizu.
Oh, great!
Don't bend it!
How is it? It's so erotic.
Isn't this light blue underwear great?
It's great, isn't it?
Do you want to see it?
Can I? No, not me.
I want to see it.
I'd like to go there.
Oh my god!
She is so erotic.
Let's go there.
Let's lick here.
Yes, here.
Let's take it off.
Who are you? Are
you Ren? Yes, I'm Ren.
Excuse me.
Someone is being bitten.
Is it a string? Yes, it is.
What do you do for a living?
I'm a concierge.
That's cool.
You're a manager of a concierge.
Yes, I am.
That's cool.
How do you feel? I feel great.
Compared to her? I feel great.
It's too much.
It's rude.
It hurts.
How do you feel? It feels good.
How do you feel? It's terrible.
I have a cramp.
You have a cramp?
Yes.
Take a deep breath.
It's getting lighter.
Isn't it better to let it out?
What should I do? Of course.
What should I do?
I want to do it.
I'll give it to you.
Really?
You want the launch
version, don't you? Yes, I do.
Really?
Do you really want it?
I really want it.
Don't sell it.
I won't.
I'll keep it.
One minute left.
The situation is not good.
I'm happy to see you, Mom.
I see.
You're in the movie, right?
Yes.
You're in the movie a lot.
I'm happy to see you.
I want you to show me your face.
Yes.
I'm happy to see you.
How do you feel?
Take a deep breath.
I'm taking a deep breath.
We don't have much time.
Isn't it better if you take a deep breath?
10 seconds left.
I'm not in a hurry.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up.
This is the 13th year
anniversary of AV-JUICY.
How do you feel?
Are you nervous?
I'm very nervous.
If you get so much attention,
you'll have plenty of chances later.
Thank you very much.
Next is No.13.
Thank you for waiting.
I'm Arai Rima.
This is the 13th year
anniversary of AV-JUICY.
Nice to meet you.
Can I ask you about your
first experience? Me? Yes, you.
Who are you asking?
You can't ask this person.
I can't help it.
You can't help it.
When I was 19 years old,
I had an affair with my
boyfriend at that time.
Did it hurt? It didn't hurt.
It felt good.
How many men do you think you are?
I really don't know.
That's cool.
Are you a takoyaki chef?
What do you do for a living?
I work as a delivery man.
What do you do? Mostly.
..
Do you say, 「Ren-san, I'm No.
2!」? No, I don't.
You don't?
I'm the receptionist.
Oh, you're the receptionist.
You're used to treating
girls, aren't you? No, not at all.
Not at all?
I'm very polite.
You're very polite.
Of course you are.
Yes.
You're quite big.
I'm not that big.
He's big.
Oh, really? It's hard.
I think it's the biggest one
among the triangles so far.
Really? I think so.
I've never seen a human's penis.
Who is it?
If you want to be an
actor, you have to look at it.
I see.
You rub it.
You rub it with a 3-Pin Ferrari.
Oh, do I rub it? Yes, you do.
It's disgusting.
I want to show it.
Today is your day
off, isn't it? Yes, it is.
Are you sure? Yes, I am.
Are you in a hurry
today? No, I'm not.
Oh, you're not.
Don't say that.
Yes.
I think you have high
expectations for the launch.
What do you think?
Well, I'm not sure.
But I'm being asked,
aren't I? Yes, you are.
I'm so sorry.
It's my job to ask.
Yes.
Let's do it.
Do you want to rub it?
Rub?
Do you want to take it off?
Do you want to take
it off? No, I don't.
Don't take it off.
No, I don't.
I'll take it off.
Take it off.
I won't hold it.
I won't.
It's OK.
I'll take it off.
I couldn't sleep because
I was looking forward to it.
You thought you were going to do it
with everyone, didn't you? That's the one.
That's the one.
This one? That's the one.
Do you understand?
That's the one.
Can you touch
the ball? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
If you can do it in 10
seconds, you'll be the MVP.
Ah, wait!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up!
What a shame!
You were a little nervous,
weren't you? Yes, I was.
Were you nervous? Yes, I was.
There are a lot of men
who don't know how to lose.
That's true.
You were surrounded by old men.
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
Next is No.6.
Let's go to No.6.
Yes.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Mary Tachibana.
Wonderful.
Your costume is wonderful.
Thank you.
Your bare face is wonderful, isn't it?
It's wonderful if I take it off.
Could you tell us about your costume?
Could you tell us about my costume?
What is your favorite size?
My favorite size is about 92cm,
about 60cm, and about 90cm.
What is your favorite skill?
My favorite skill is... I have a lot of
saliva, so I use home-made lotion.
Home-made lotion?
I'm hyperactive.
And...
I can control my blood pressure.
You can control your
blood pressure very well.
So, you're going to shoot as
you want, right? I don't know.
Right? I don't know.
Don't you want to see your boobs?
Can I?
I want to see them.
Then, ask me.
I can't ask you.
Can I see your boobs?
I can't see both.
I want to see the inside.
Please.
I'm going to break it.
How is it?
I've never seen such a soft one.
It looks soft, doesn't it?
Can I touch it? Just a little.
My hands are sweating.
I'm touching it.
How is it?
It's my first time.
Is it a match? Yes, I am.
You are not going to that
office, are you? No, I am not.
You are not going to
that office? No, I am not.
You are not going
to that office?
You are not going to
that office? No, I am not.
Oh, it's already standing.
It's a little bigger.
Yes, it is.
This is a natural lotion.
Does it feel good?
Do you like it?
It's because of you that
the world went bankrupt.
May I? Yes, please.
It's easy to shoot without a camera.
It's smooth.
My stomach is connected to the universe.
I want to do it.
Do you want to do it? Yes, I do.
I will definitely do it.
Definitely.
Can you do it?
I wonder if I can.
There is only one minute left.
I'm sorry.
Ah, but it feels good, so
it's getting red here, isn't it?
Do you want me to bite your nipple?
Yes.
Do you want me to bite it?
Can I take it off?
Please take it off.
It's coming out now.
I think this is good.
It's good, isn't it?
We only got a couple of pictures.
The director said he wanted a picture.
Concentrate.
Look. Who's talking?
Who is it? It's Mary.
It's Mary.
Mary is talking.
Look. Open your eyes.
Don't put on your glasses.
Look at me.
Those are the glasses.
Ten seconds.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three, two, one.
Let's go.
It's cool, isn't it?
It's like a baby rider.
Look at that medallion.
It's like this.
Did you feel good? No, I didn't.
I didn't feel good.
I did it.
How do you feel about
the taste of life and death?
Is it bitter? No, it's sweet.
Is it sweet? Yes, it is.
It's sweet.
I'm happy.
Great! Thank you very much.
This is the second launch.
We did it!
The shooting is going well.
I'm so excited.
Thank you very much.
Please give me a tissue.
Thank you.
It was cool.
At the countdown.
Yes, it was great.
You'll definitely see this later, right?
You'll say, I did a good
job at the countdown.
Idiot!
Thank you very much.
Let's move on.
You're number 14, right?
Yes.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Jun Tsuehiro.
Until now, you've had a lot of meat dishes,
so you look very decorative.
Can you see it? I can see it.
Is that so? I don't know.
I don't know.
What do you think?
What kind of movies do you watch?
I watch a lot of movies that get killed.
That's right.
Because you are that kind of character.
Is that so? I think so.
There are a lot
of movies like that.
Really?
Yes.
A lot of movies get killed.
A lot of movies get killed by students.
That's right.
You are still a sailor
uniform student, aren't you?
Actually, I have many wives.
Who are you?
My name is Isoyama.
Isoyama?
Yes.
What do you usually do?
I usually work as a programmer.
That's a lie, isn't it?
What? No, it's true.
No, it's true.
You're in the gay video, aren't you?
You're in it, aren't you?
You were in the Sports
Newspaper commercial, weren't you?
No, I was in the commercial.
Hey, take it off.
I want to take it off.
Take it off.
I want to blur it out.
Don't blur it out.
But it's not gay,
is it? No, it's not.
What are you going to do?
I don't know yet.
She said you are cute.
I was so excited when I saw Mary.
I think she wants to go to the other side.
I'll do my best not to lose.
Bella, please.
Look!
What's that?
Ah!
I'm putting up with it.
It's salty.
Salty.
How long did you put
up with it? Let's eat.
I did it yesterday.
It's the best.
You can touch me.
Vegetable boy.
Do you have any habits?
I like to play with fire.
And I have a big butt.
Do you have a big
butt? Vegetable boy.
I'm touching you.
You like it, don't
you? Yes, I love it.
Don't you want to see Aoyokuba?
Aoyokuba? Aoyokuba.
What?
Aoyokuba?
This one, too?
Yes, I want to see it.
You want to see this one, too?
Yes.
You are very clean today.
Yes, I am.
Look.
Do you want to touch it?
Yes.
You can touch it.
How is it? It's the best.
Can I kiss you?
Yes.
I feel so happy.
I got a tip.
It feels good.
I think I can drink it.
Do you want to
drink it? Not yet.
I want to drink it.
But we don't have time.
Then I'll drink it.
Can I eat it?
This is a serious face.
Great.
It's getting hard.
You have one minute. Concentrate.
Great. It's getting bigger.
I want to get three shots.
That's too few! Oh, wow.
Three shots are fine.
I'm getting bigger.
Go for it!
It's over!
Why didn't you
get it? I got bigger.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! I'm sorry.
You've grown up so much.
You're right.
I'm so sorry. Thank you so much.
I'll show you later.
I still have more.
Next is No.7.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Mori Hinako, who loves Emo-kun.
How many Oden did you eat?
Hundreds of Oden.
In how many
years? About 3 years.
Do you have any memorable shooting?
I love to attack.
You love to lick.
I love to lick.
I love to be licked.
Today is good, isn't it?
Can I lick a lot?
I want you to lick a lot.
I want you to teach me how to do it.
Please teach me how to do it.
I forgot how to do it.
You forgot, didn't you?
I'll look it up on the Internet.
I'll look it up on Wikipedia.
Yusuke-san, Kousuke-san.
Kousuke-san.
What do you do for a living?
I work in the construction industry.
So, you're like, Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
I do that too,
but I'm more of a manager.
Oh, that's cool.
It's good, isn't it? Yes, it is.
I see.
Then, let's start the Pilates.
Yes.
Here we go.
Mori-san, what is your specialty?
I'll show you now.
Wow!
Cool! I'll show you.
I'll show you.
Cool!
I'll show you from the top to the bottom.
Then, let's see.
Let's see.
Let's do it together.
This is the point.
The posture is different.
She walks slowly.
Look at this.
It is possible to crush a
bullet bag with this leg.
It is true that it is thin.
It is amazing.
It is really amazing.
You like it.
What? It's so hot.
I'm so excited in this situation.
What are you going to do?
What are you going
to do? It's so hot.
You have a cute face.
Your penis is purple.
It's so hot.
Is it possible to fire? Maybe.
Don't bite it.
If you bite it, the game is over.
Don't take it out.
I want to see it.
Wow, it's so red.
It's fresh.
It's fresh, isn't
it? It's fluffy.
This is a good one.
This is the first time I've seen this.
This is surprisingly good.
It's cute. It's dry.
It's been a minute.
You can do it.
Concentrate.
Close your eyes.
How is it? It feels good.
How many places have
you been in the history?
I've been in the first place.
It's a problem if
you're in the third place.
You have to be in the third place.
You're noisy.
I'm noisy, aren't I?
I'd like you to write a
comment in the corner
where you were
mixed up with the voice.
There's a tap later.
It's a corner to get a chicken tail.
30 seconds left.
You want a band, don't you?
10 seconds left.
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Time's up!
We couldn't make it.
I'm sorry.
We had limited time.
And it was noisy.
Sorry.
I know.
It was noisy.
I didn't mean it in a weird way.
This is how it is.
Thank you very much.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Hana Himesaki from I Cup.
It's been a long time.
Can you show me your chest?
My voice?
It's coming out a little.
It's okay. Just show it.
It's huge!
You can put a lot of things in here.
You can put your phone in here.
It's convenient.
It's amazing.
You can put your phone in here.
No, you can't.
I want to see it.
You can enjoy it later.
I want to see it now.
No, I can't. I'm not that kind of person.
You're strict.
What do you usually do, Kin-san?
I'm a construction worker.
So you're his subordinate?
No, it's our first meeting.
Yes, it's our first meeting.
But we might be related in the future.
So you'll be his subordinate.
Let's go.
We're almost there.
You are taking off
your clothes by yourself.
Are you ready? Let's start.
Take off your clothes quickly.
Go for it! I'm in trouble.
I'm in trouble.
Excuse me.
How many times are you
going to take off your clothes?
But I heard that Hamedori is really cool.
I want to go to Hamedori 8.
Where? 8 means 5.
I want to go to Hamedori 15.
Then, let's go to Hamedori 15.
What about Hamedori 15 and Hamedori 8?
Do you often go to Hamedori?
In private?
Yes, in private.
I heard that you are very confident.
Only Hamedori?
Yes, only Hamedori.
Maasa doesn't sell it, does she?
She doesn't sell it.
She keeps it in her personal computer.
Did you wash it
thoroughly? Yes, I did.
It's peeling off.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's cute, but it's cute.
I don't want you to think I'm
smelly, so I wash it thoroughly.
Can I kiss you? Please.
I'm going to help you, Hime-chan.
Oh, my gosh!
It's a special service.
I'm going to touch your neck.
Oh, it's getting bigger.
Wow!
It's getting stronger.
It's true.
It's hard.
It's full of meat.
Isn't it great?
You can take it out.
1 minute left.
You are fast.
I'm fast.
But it is not a wind.
Look, look, look.
It is not a wind.
It is a great pin.
It is long.
Isn't it?
It is a great pin.
It is long.
Will you be happy?
It is easy to take a picture of Hame-shiro.
It's easy to say, isn't it?
You can say, like, I'm in it.
That's the point, isn't it?
Hey, you! I love you.
Oh, my God.
You've been doing a lot of work lately.
Your nipples feel good,
don't they? I love you.
I'm leaving it to you.
I've only done two shots.
The director said he wanted
to shoot the launch scene.
Because? Yes, you.
You want to eat,
don't you? I love you.
If it's 10 seconds left, close
your eyes and concentrate!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, time's up!
Wow! It was so close!
I wish I had a little more time.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to roll it up.
I didn't roll it up at all.
Thank you so much.
We still have a lot of time.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
We've been waiting for so long.
Are you angry? I'm angry.
I've been waiting for so long.
I'm sorry.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello. I'm Sumire Kuramoto,
the best go-mon in Japan.
Nice to meet you.
I'm curious. Where is go-mon?
Go-mon is in Oman prefecture.
Is it crowded? Yes, it is.
Do you sometimes feel pain when
you insert a go-mon? Yes, I do.
I want to see it.
I don't know what to do.
It's not a joke.
I want to see it.
You want to see it, don't you?
You want to do image training, don't you?
How rough it is.
It's a lie.
It's rough.
It's true.
It's amazing.
Who are you? Hi, I'm Yu.
What do you do
usually? I'm a flutter.
Flutter?
Yes.
What's the reason for coming here today?
I'm going to launch it.
Let's launch it!
You have to launch it.
Take off your clothes.
Please take off your clothes.
It's getting hot.
You said you couldn't stand up.
What? Show me.
Show me.
Cute.
So cute!
It's a little bit hard.
Right?
Are you still nervous?
They are kissing.
They stand up right away when they kiss.
Look!
It's so big!
It's so big! I like it.
Isn't it great?
I don't like it.
Please lick it.
Please do more.
OK.
How do you feel? I feel good.
How do you feel?
Please explain in detail.
When I touch it, I feel a little tingling.
Is it warm? Yes, it is.
Is it soft?
Yes, it feels good.
It hurts.
It is good.
It has become very hard.
What kind of Ferro do you like?
Sakippo?
Ferro Ferro?
Oh, you like Ferro Ferro.
Is it spicy? It's hot.
It's good.
If you eat too much,
you'll get a stomachache.
Really?
You'll get a stomachache.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about something pleasant.
It's very hard.
It's hard, isn't it?
If I can't get it out with
this, I'll be in trouble.
Don't be scared.
10 seconds left.
8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up! I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to rush you.
I think it was too late.
I thought it was going to come out.
Because it was squeezed.
I told you not to rush.
It's noisy.
I told you 10 seconds left.
I wanted to do it a little more.
It's noisy.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Yay! Yay!
It's the last one!
I knew it!
This is the time!
Wait, don't eat
it! This is good.
It's the last one!
Then, you can lick it.
Please introduce yourself
and look at the camera.
I'm Tomirakako, and I'm in
the sixth grade of high school.
I'm so excited.
I'll put it in the video.
Thank you.
It's Icchan's.
It's a collaboration.
It's a collaboration, right?
I heard it before.
If you make a noise here,
a lot of it will come out.
It's good for the lungs.
I heard that it's easy to jump.
Then, you will jump a lot, right?
Wow, there is a lot of sugar in it.
It's amazing.
I feel like I'm on a business trip.
Yes.
Right?
I can't stop eating it.
It's like a horse sashimi.
It's a little dirty, so I'll wipe my butt.
Oh, really?
Do you have the inspection form?
What?
Do you have the inspection
form? Of course I do.
Then, please touch it.
I even showed you my buttocks.
I know you have a lot of fangs.
I'm white.
It's true.
It's noisy.
I can't do it well.
Kajitsu-san.
Do you exercise? No, I don't.
You don't, do you?
It's totally different.
It's written as Bunkeidanshi.
It was written in the answer note.
The king kaza of king
kaza does not fire at all.
Let's fire.
Let's dance.
Let's do a katsu dance.
I want to see.
I also want to see.
Let me see.
I'm going to dance, if you clap your hands.
I think you are doing small things inside.
Could you tell me what you are doing?
You are doing small things.
My body is spinning.
Your body is spinning.
You are moving with
a small body skillfully.
Don't move your body.
It's difficult, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it?
Don't take it off.
Take it off.
Let's take it off.
It's thin.
Wow!
You have only one minute left.
One minute!
If you can't make it, you
may be forced to return it.
I can do it!
You can do it!
You want to be a representative, don't you?
Let's drink it!
Right?
You are trying so hard, but you can't.
I don't know, Kin-Kin.
10 seconds left.
Decide.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up!
Argh!!
OMG!
I feel bad for the producer
who hit the countdown.
We've waited for so long.
It's just so-so.
I want to go home!
Let's change the balls now.
I can't believe it.
I'm so sad.
It's just the beginning.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
BAKOBASU BAKOBASU
BAKOBASU I can't
wait any longer.
Why don't we have sex together?
Let's start seat belt high-speed sex.
First of all, please give me a kiss.
Kiss.
This is the first time for me.
She is very active.
Are you looking
at me? Look at me.
Are you looking at me?
Are you looking at
me? Look down more.
She is happy to see me.
Look down more.
How do you feel?
Next is a man's nipples.
It's nipples.
You said it was weak, but it's nipples.
Is it weak?
Yes.
I'm looking forward to it.
I love it.
Long time no see.
Do you like Chiku-kun?
I love Chiku-kun.
Do you love her? Yes, I do.
Wow! What a nice Kana!
You are so sexy!
Are you wearing it? Yes, I am.
Be big.
Take this.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
She is already taking it.
She is holding it.
She is fast.
Good morning!
You are getting stiff.
Look at her licking.
How is your neck?
It feels so good.
Does it?
Do you want to kiss?
It's so shiny, isn't it?
Chikubi is standing up.
He is purring.
He is purring for the first time.
He has a cute voice.
Do you feel good?
Chikubi is standing up.
I'm scared.
You may lose your nipple.
You have a cute face.
Do you feel this
nipple? It's gone.
Oh, this is good.
Next, put your boobs on your face.
Boobs?
I've never seen boobs.
I'll take this off.
Boobs.
What should I do? I'll show you.
I'm so happy.
Ta-da!
Can I take it off? Sure.
You are so active.
Awesome.
I'm nervous.
It's soft.
Is it painful?
Painful?
Kuruchi? Don't fail.
I'll push you.
I'll hug you.
I can't show you my eyes.
Do you want to do
it again? Let's go.
How many seconds do I have to do it?
I don't have boobs, but
I'm going to push you.
I can push you.
What's wrong with you? You're so cute!
What?
I want to see the baby.
It feels so good.
Do you like a
big baby? I love it.
What? I love it.
I want to touch it.
I want to touch it so much.
I'm so happy.
What is this?
Are you licking my nipple?
You are so cute.
Did you lick it? Yes, I did.
Is it good?
Do you want
to try it? I'll try it.
Are you ready?
Look!
Wow!
I'm sorry for the trouble I've caused you.
Look at me.
Do you want me to kiss you?
3,2,1
It came out!
It came out! With this.
..
1,2,3 We are very sorry
for the inconvenience.
We will continue the training.
I'm going to be a right-handed person.
Can I observe you?
Can you drink it?
What?
Oh, no!
Go! Go!
It's the first step to the second step!
It's broken!
Is it beautiful?
How is it?
Beautiful?
I want to go to that side.
Can I drink it? Yes, you can.
Thank you.
This is the first time to
see a dog without a mosaic.
Donte, are you licking it?
Donte is observing the dog.
He is licking it.
This part is curly.
He is licking it with his tongue.
Is it beautiful? Yes, it is.
Be careful not to hurt your eyes.
Good boy.
I'm sorry for the delay.
Please use the ferry.
It's too early.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go again.
It's too early.
Wait.
Do you want to eat more?
Do you want to drink Nagamon juice?
Nagamon juice is full!
Nagamon juice is
full! It's delicious.
It's delicious.
Do you like it?
What are you looking
at? It feels good.
From the beginning?
It's harder than before.
It's quite hard, isn't
it? It feels good.
Is it heavy? It feels good.
It's so good.
Do you feel good?
You look like a girl
when you open your legs.
Really?
You look like an MC.
Don't make such a painful face.
Oh, no.
What?
What? Don't move.
It's a public office.
It's so tight.
It's so cute.
Don't do that.
She is No.7. She looks very comfortable.
It looks so good.
Do you want to have sex? Oh, no.
Do you want to have sex?
I'll do it for you.
I'll do it quickly.
What?
Quickly.
Do you want to do it with someone else?
Who do you want to
do it with? Mizuki-san.
Mizuki-san?
Can I play with
her? I made a wish.
Isn't it too early?
She is my fan.
That's right.
Betrayer.
You are a cheater! You are a pervert!
I want to wear a condom.
I'm going to wear a condom.
I'm going to wear it.
Let's put it in.
Wait, let's put it in quickly.
It's from the back.
It's easy to take a picture.
It's for the back, please.
I'll put it in.
It's a wonderful sight.
Please check it and see
if it fits well to the root.
Please put it in properly.
It's in!
Great!
It's a great sight.
Let's go! It's in.
Let's put it in.
Great!
It's a great sight.
It's wonderful.
How is it?
It's narrow, isn't it?
You don't have to play with it.
Not yet.
Have you graduated as a virgin?
Did you graduate from
high school? No, I didn't.
Don't worry.
Did you graduate from
high school? No, I didn't.
Great!
It's coming out!
It came out!
Look!
Oh no!
One more time!
This is no good!
It's coming out again!
It's coming out!
I can't do it anymore!
One more time, one more time.
Push.
I'm sleepy.
More please.
Oh, no.
I can't move.
This is a wonderful picture.
Now, let's have a face-to-face meeting.
We are going to start the meeting now.
I just got in.
Congratulations.
Is it warm?
Feels good?
Congratulations.
What is it?
It's a seat belt.
OK, everyone.
Let's have a face-to-face meeting.
This pervert.
Be happy.
It's dangerous.
This time, we are going to have a
face-to-face meeting, so please be kind to us.
I'm sorry.
This is a formal meeting.
Did you get it? Let me see.
It's true.
Congratulations!
Let's give her another round of applause.
It was a wonderful performance.
Congratulations!
Oh, my God!
Now, let's move on to free sex.
Please do not take off your seat belts.
Please continue this happy
moment for three minutes.
Wow! There are a lot of them!
I made a mistake.
I'll do it again.
Did you get it? Yes, I did.
Oh, I can't eat this.
We have one minute left.
One minute left.
Here we go!
Great!
Standing ovation!
Here we go!
Great!
Should I take it off?
I'm going to take it off.
Here we go!
I got it!
Thank you!
Congratulations!
I got it!
I'm going to get on the boat.
Be careful not to miss it.
Do I have to go on
the boat? Yes, you do.
You have to get on the boat.
Be careful.
I'm scared.
You have three minutes
to enjoy this happy moment.
I don't feel good.
Please lick me a lot.
Oh, you don't like it?
Please pat me a lot.
It's amazing.
10 seconds have passed.
Time's up!
Thank you very much.
How was it? I can't see it.
How was it?
Did it launch?
Look at her face!
It's so ugly!
Can you say a few words?
Ouch!
I'm so happy!
Congratulations!
Look!
Wow! So many!
I'm so happy!
Wow!
I got so many!
Is this ticklish?
Does it hurt? It's alright.
It's ticklish?
Wait! I got it off.
It doesn't hurt?
No, it's alright.
Look! Isn't this amazing?
It's too strong!
It's warm!
I wonder if it tickles.
Is it ticklish? It's ticklish.
It's a harvest.
I got the first one.
Congratulations.
Let's go.
It's dangerous.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Did you get a lot?
Yes, I got a lot.
Let me see.
Did you get it? Yes, I got it.
Let's go.
You've just put it out.
Yeah, I did.
Oh, it's leaking.
There it goes.
Wow! It's in.
Great! It's in.
Yay! Second one.
Yes, the second one.
It's in!
This is my first time to have sex!
I did it! Congratulations!
This is my first sex, congratulations!
How do you feel about your first sex?
It was totally different from what I did.
It was totally different from what you did?
Yes. It felt so good.
Oh, I think I can do it.
Help! Help!
Everyone, only one minute left.
Only one minute left.
I did it! Takago did it.
Yes! Great!
He did it in standing ovation.
Great!
The second time!
It's the second time.
It's amazing.
Did you feel good?
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
Get out of the way!
Can I do it one more
time? No, you can't.
Everyone, there is only one minute left.
Great!
It's a standing ovation.
How do you feel?
My body smells like a squid.
It smells like a squid.
It's about to start.
You can do it.
Don't stop.
10 seconds have passed.
It's still hard.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, Time's up!
Thank you very much!
Time's up!
How was it?
The time was perfect!
Wait, I can't take a picture!
Hey, what's going on?
It came out at the timing of zero!
Isn't it great?
Look, it's great!
Thank you very much!
I think everyone is getting more
and more like BAKOBASU, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
That's all for the seat
belt high-speed sex.
Thank you very much.
It's a terrible smell in the car.
BAKOBASU Hehehehe
You're hungry, aren't you?
Yes
That's what I want to say Yes
Please
Yes
Everyone
Delicious
What do you want to see?
I don't need any money Just
white rice Wow, it's delicious
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
It's already moving, the rice
What? I'm not full. I need more.
I need more.
Hey, more.
I'm full.
I need more.
It's time to eat.
It's delicious.
I'm so happy!
Look at me and eat!
Look at this!
Oh my god!
I think it's not enough.
I want all of them!
Oh my god!
Wow.
Yuujin, you are looking at me.
You look so happy.
Please eat some sweets.
It is delicious.
Thank you very much.
That's all for lunch time.
Ba
Ko
Su
Bakobasu
Now, we are going
to start the production
presentation of the revival of
BAKKON BAKKON BUS TOUR.
First of all, I would like to introduce
the actress, Ms. Fumizuki Yayoi.
On behalf of the 16 AV
actresses here, I would
like to greet you with
a round of applause.
I would like to introduce myself.
I'm a movie maker, Moody's.
I'm honored to be here.
I'm going to make a historical
work that my seniors left behind.
I'm going to make it erotic and cute.
Thank you very much.
There are a lot of congratulatory messages
from actresses who didn't appear this time.
We have received a
lot of requests, so we will
introduce only a part of
it due to time constraints.
Hello to everyone
participating in BAKOBASU.
I'm Arina Arata, and
I'm in charge of Mooding.
Congratulations to all the
amateur actors who were
selected from among the
many applicants this time.
Congratulations to all of you.
I'm so happy to have a one-night-two-days
sex with such a gorgeous AV actress.
I'm so excited when I think that
an AV actor will be born from here.
I'm looking forward to
seeing you in an AV someday.
Have fun, everyone.
I'm Rina Arata, a member of Moody's.
Congratulations on the
shooting of Bako Bus.
It's fun to travel by bus, isn't it?
I can see everyone's happy faces.
I'll do my best to be on Bako Bus someday.
I'm Mio Ishikawa, a member of Moody's.
MIOCHI!
We have received a message in the video,
so please pay attention to the monitor.
Hello to everyone who participated
in the BAKKONBASHI tour.
I'm Nana Yagi, the lead actress.
Everyone may be nervous today,
I don't have to say it, but
today, please don't hold back and
give your passionate feelings
to the actresses over there.
I also hope that one day I
can have sex with everyone.
Please enjoy it.
I would like to introduce the
actors who will appear in this movie.
Please.
This movie is called Aim for AV Actors.
The theme is to train actors.
The cast here are still beginners.
This time, congratulations on the
revival of BAKO BAKO BUS TOUR!
The most historical work of the best AV
makers in Japan, BAKO BAKO BUS TOUR,
So, I expect that AV actress
will be more sexy than usual.
Also, I heard that men
want to be like AV actresses.
So, my advice is... At first, don't think
about difficult things and enjoy sex.
Enjoy!
So, if this is released,
I will definitely buy it.
See you again!
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best and aim for
the second place in the first round.
So, before we get into the game,
Let's check the Anaru & Bokki!
Let's check it out!
No matter how embarrassing the
situation is, you don't have to give up.
Isn't that right, everyone?
That's right!
Okay, everyone on the second
floor, please take your positions.
If you want to be a model everyday,
Anal check, start!
Yes! I'm nervous.
I've never done this before.
Are you embarrassed? Yes, I am.
I'm embarrassed, but I'll do my best.
You have to get used to it.
That's right.
I'll do my best.
OK, let's start.
Pocky check!
Show me your picture.
I'm not pocky at all.
Don't do that, Kawaii-chan.
We'll write a letter for you.
Oh, no.
I have to do it!
You are getting old, Ochinpo!
Let me do it!
You are doing your best!
You can do it, Ochinpo!
Are you holding up?
This is Ochinpo, who
has the qualities of a man.
Oh, you surprised me!
Yabui-chan!
Oh, you are here again.
You are amazing!
What? It's strange.
What?
Why are you so shy?
You can't get excited, can you?
Why?
Who are you?
Yoku-san asked me.
I've got a message.
What is it?
I have 123,000 followers on SNS.
I have more than 10,000 fans.
I have 33 fans.
On my birthday, I'm going to make an AV.
I have more than 10
million followers a month.
I own several luxury cars.
I'm Kaido from Reiwa.
I'm the best disciple of director Samoari.
He is the best disciple
of Emro, the director.
He looks like a child, but he is an adult.
His name is Toy Boy Aizawa.
He is amazing.
Don't be shy.
You have to make him
stand no matter where he is.
Is he standing? No, he is not.
What are you doing?
Yes, I'm standing.
We are in the same team.
What are you doing?
What's this?
What?
You said something very arrogant.
You said you liked me.
Look at this.
I don't like it at all.
I want to see this.
What?
Where did you get that
confidence from? What? The most.
..
Wait a minute.
Don't show it to everyone.
Are you sure?
What are you doing?
Hey!
You can do whatever you want.
If the male and female
dancers see this, they will say,
「Zen, don't betray the
male and female dancers!」
「Zen, don't betray the male and
female dancers!」 Don't make me breathe.
Don't make me breathe.
What do you want me to do?
Which one is the nipple?
Nipple!
Please choose the nipple.
Should I eat the nipple?
What should I do?
I'm not used to it.
I'm scared if you don't tell me.
Did you break it? I broke it.
I want you to be kind to me.
Please tell everyone.
Please be kind to my nipples.
Do you feel good?
I'll do it for you.
I'll let you lick me.
I want to lick the commotion.
If you lick the commotion, I'll get実.
It's getting slightly bigger.
It's awesome.
If you lick Manko, it will grow bigger.
You are good at licking Manko.
If you can do it, you can
do a lot of erotic things.
Manko is licking Manko deliciously.
Is it delicious?
Come here!
Chie-pon is working out.
Chie-pon?
What?
Give it back!
I think you can become an actress.
I want to be an actress.
Hey, you.
You did your best.
But you came here, so you can't do it.
And you have been out twice.
I can't do it.
I can't do it. I became an amateur.
You can do it.
I can't do it.
It looks like it's coming out.
It's turning red.
It's coming out?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Isn't there anyone named
Waruko-sama? It's so good.
It feels good.
It's so cute!
It feels so good!
It's a butterfly!
Go! Go! Go!
You can do it! You can still do it!
It's amazing!
You can do it!
You did it!
Thank you!
Let's go!
It feels so good!
Can I really do it?
I can't do it anymore.
What? What?
Ai-chan, Ai-chan, Ai-chan.
Cute.
Are you happy? Latte is cute.
I'm scared.
What is the best thing about the meeting?
The best thing is the student council.
The best thing is the student council?
Did you kiss her a lot?
I failed the hair challenge.
I failed!
You put it on your hair!
What are you talking about?
You can do it!
Can I touch all of your hair later?
Can I?
You are so kind!
Come here!
Who do you want to play with?
Who do you like?
Who?
Can't you choose?
If you can't choose,
you can't take a picture.
Hurry up.
If you don't choose, you can't put it in.
It's Mori.
It looks big.
You have to look at Morita.
Look at her eyes.
What are you going to do with your hands?
It's a waste if you don't touch her hands.
I'm sorry.
We are going to have a concert in Tokyo.
It's a black bird.
But it's big.
Look at it. Look at it carefully.
It's so big.
Look at it. It's going in.
It's so cute.
It's going in.
You want to put it
in, don't you? Please.
What?
What are you doing?
Mori-chan!
Please do it!
Stop it!
Your waist is moving!
Don't look at the handle!
Look at my eyes!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Say it louder!
How do you feel?
How do you feel? I was scared.
I was scared.
How do you feel
now? I feel great.
Are you going to cry? Not yet.
Not yet? You are crying.
I'm worried.
How do you feel
now? I'm worried.
I'm so happy.
I have a t-shirt.
I'm free, so I'm wearing this.
Look at this.
My butt is in it.
I'm happy to wear it.
It feels good.
I like it.
This is the best.
I have a weak hip strength.
My hips are shaking.
Can I stand up?
Stand up!
Look! My hips are shaking.
This is erotic.
I can learn a lot.
There are a lot of monkeys!
Wow! This is a monkey!
This is a monkey!
It feels so good!
Which one do you want
to choose? I don't know.
Which one do you want to choose?
I can't eat it yet.
It's delicious.
I'll give it to you.
Is it really
delicious? Yes, it is.
Let's eat it.
Let me see.
Show me the truth.
I'm going to eat it.
Go ahead.
I'm going to take a bath now.
Mayuko, lie down.
Lie down close to me.
Mayuko, lick me.
I feel good.
Can you show me again?
I won't forgive you if you don't decide.
No, I won't.
Decide!
If you don't decide, I'll shoot you.
Oh, no, I'm gonna puke.
No, you can't.
I won't give it to you.
Oh, no, I'm gonna puke.
Congratulations!
It was close, wasn't it?
ばこばっす
We take off our blindfolds
and introduce ourselves.
It's a game to see if you
can guess the answer.
In this Hamehame area, if you are a
beginner, raise your hand and guess.
Please spread out to all 13 areas.
What?
Do you have enough mangos?
We heard that you don't have enough mangos.
So, we are going to support you.
We are going to help you in Hamehame area.
You came here to run,
didn't you? Yes, we did.
I see.
Well, it can't be helped.
If you say so,
Let's do our best together.
We'll do our best.
How is it?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Thank you.
Then, everyone, let's start
the Peloton Manjin Sports Day.
Ready, go!
Are you ready?
Hello, we are NiziU.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm scared.
I'm scared, too.
It's like a dental examination.
Wait a minute.
Don't laugh.
Wow, it's amazing.
Did you touch it?
This side is better.
I think it's good.
It's good.
That's why I said it's good.
This is good.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Don't take off your eye mask yet.
Let's go to bed.
Did you sleep? Yes, I did.
Are you here? Yes, I am.
Can I take this off?
Yes.
It's so bright.
Wait a minute.
Can you see me? Excuse me.
Let's check the question mark.
I already know my genius question mark.
Really?
I don't know because there is a rubber.
You don't know?
It's a password.
But what is it?
How was it?
It's hard to understand
because there is a rubber.
What number is it?
Mon-chan!
Difficult!
4!
I'm 4!
I'm 2!
Wait, I'm really 4.
Really?
Really? You're lying.
I don't know.
No.
Let's change.
Which one? Wait.
Wait a minute, this
person has a lot of voice.
Wait a minute, I remember this.
I don't know.
I think this is 2.
Too many 2s.
Oh my god! 2 and 3.
This person is 1.
This person is 1? 3? 3 and 4.
4! 4! Let's line up.
Line up.
Let's stand up.
No.1.
No.1 is here.
No.2.
No.3.
No.4.
No.5.
No.6.
It's already standing, isn't it?
It's stable, isn't it?
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
I feel like my heart is going to pop out.
Thank you very much.
Let's do our best, Kana-chan!
Sexy girls are waiting for you.
Do your best!
Are you ready?
Are you motivated?
We've arrived at the bedside!
Let's go!
I'm going to tuck you in.
I'll hold you tight.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Hang in there! Hang in there!
I'll help you a little.
Let's go!
Wow!
You got wet, didn't
you? Oh, I'm sorry.
You got wet.
Oh, wow! You're so strong!
Wow!
Are you OK? Do you want to get better?
You can do it!
You are slipping.
I'm going!
Do you want to win?
Yes!
I won! Congratulations!
I did it!
I'm so disappointed.
You have a thick arm.
Look at the third one.
It's so close!
I did it!
You did a good job.
I'm sweating a lot.
We did our best.
Look, there are four.
It's great.
I hope we can have fun.
Which one?
The biggest one.
It's cute.
It's a practice game.
Number one, Piper!
What else?
Don't concentrate on the game.
Kintama is a little stretched.
Next!
Wow!
I got it!
Next! Turn left.
Turn left.
Turn right.
Who is it? It's me.
It's amazing.
I can't hear you.
Where are you
looking at? Change.
OK.
I said something.
It's a child.
No.2 is thick.
No.1 is thin.
No.2 is so floating.
Change!
BINBI!
No.1 is...
No.2 is... Yes, yes, yes.
It's a bit thin.
No.2 is... No.2 is...
What? I don't know.
No.3 is bent.
After No.3, it's bent right and left.
No.3 and No.4 are similar.
Yes, they are.
Maybe they are.
Are they? I heard that.
No.4 is thin at the base
and has a lot of air flow.
They are quite similar.
They are very similar.
No.1 is very thin and
has a lot of air flow.
Yes, yes, yes.
OK.
No.4, please.
Have you gone to bed already?
Everyone, please take off your masks.
I don't know.
Wait, this is difficult.
I can't see the numbers.
Who is it?
I read it three times.
I don't know.
I'm going to go with this.
What did you write?
I already get it.
One, three, or three times?
Two.
What's number 2?
It's hard to read it.
It's a little difficult,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
How do you feel?
I think it's better for me
to go around and see.
It's hot.
Is it dangerous?
How do you feel?
I wonder if everyone's
stimulation is not enough.
Oh, it's good.
It's morning.
What number did you say?
No.4.
I think so.
No.3 and No.3.
I think it's No.2.
No one said No.
2, did they? No.1,
No.2, No.3, No.4.
No.1 and No.1.
I don't know.
Wait.
It's OK.
It's big.
Wait.
It's OK.
It's over.
Please leave the stage.
Don't show your back.
Everyone, please turn around.
It's slippery.
Really?
I'll give you a pie.
Give me your butt.
It's good, it's good.
OK!
It's regrettable.
Good luck!
Good luck! I'm so excited.
I'm so excited.
Let's go.
I'm going to the concert hall.
I'm flying very close.
I just got up.
You got up, didn't you?
Yes.
Let's go!
・I'm tired ・I'm tired ・Easy
・The cleaning is over there
・I'm tired ・I'm tired
Oh, my God! I'll help you.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I feel good.
8,7,6,5,4,3,2,1
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Is it over?
I'll put it in my pocket.
What?
I did it!
What's wrong?
You are exhausted.
I'm exhausted.
No, you are not.
I'm tired.
You are not exhausted.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
You can do it!
Come on!
What's going on?
I've never seen you before.
How do you feel,
Ichiban? I'm scared.
Don't do that.
What's going on? I'm sorry.
I heard that you had an interview.
Yes, I did.
These three?
You said you had nothing to do with me.
Let's switch.
It's too early.
No, it's too early.
What's going on?
It's the third stage,
so we should hurry up.
Let's change!
You're too fast! It's a mansion.
Are we already
here? Oh, we're here.
It's so fast, isn't it?
Can you see it?
The tip is smooth.
The golden ball is small.
I see.
I think so.
This is the parent-child type.
The parent-child type.
Where is the parent-child
type? Here it is.
No.2.
Wait.
Isn't No.
2 very long? Yes.
No.1, No.2, No.3 are the new face.
Who is No.
1? I don't know.
3? I don't know.
Change!
Change! Who is No.
1? I'm No.
1.
I'm No.1.
No.2 is long.
Please stand by.
I'm No.8.
What is my number?
No.4 is long and straight.
No.3 is short.
No.2 is long and straight.
No.3 is here.
No.2 and No.4 are similar,
aren't they? It's similar.
No.2 is long, and
No.4 is thin and long.
It's straight.
It's the opposite.
No.4.
It's good.
Not yet.
OK, shuffle.
Everyone, please sleep.
Not yet.
Let's take off the blindfolds.
Please take off the blindfolds.
You can take off the blindfolds.
I got it.
No way.
Did you get it? Yes, I did.
I got it.
This is No.
3.
Let's exchange No.1 and No.5.
I haven't decided yet.
What is No.
4? This is No.4.
No.4 is thin, long and straight.
I got it.
This is a new mango.
It's in!
Do you feel good?
No.1?
No.1? Oh, she's gone.
She's gone?
She's gone!
She's still so stubborn!
She's still so
stubborn! I can do it.
Why did you fail the interview?
Why? But I did it.
You couldn't do it?
This is definitely 2.
It's 2, isn't it?
It's over there.
Can I guess the
order? It's over.
Time's up!
Please line up No.1, No.2, and No.3.
Are you ready for the final answer?
Final answer!
Please look behind you.
Correct!
I got it!
What should I do?
I want to do it again.
You want to do it again, don't you?
It has a cute voice.
It's cute.
It's sleeping.
The nose is cute.
We are going to take off the
women's clothes in the service time.
Excellent chimpanzee.
Do you want to have sex?
Do you want to have sex again?
It is proud to send out like this.
I'm so proud of you.
You are going to enter the mark.
Are you ready?
Don't be swallowed.
Let's go.
I'm here.
Go, go, go.
Can you see me? Don't rush.
Take your time.
Don't rush.
Should I stand up a little?
Yes.
I can't.
Don't rush.
Can you do it?
Nice to meet you.
Oh, she flew away.
It's very good, isn't
it? Eiko, come on.
Come on.
Eiko, come on.
Come here.
Come on.
Oh, it feels good.
Are you ready? Yes, I am.
Are you a model?
Then, you go over there.
Do you want to calm
down? Calm down once.
Calm down once.
I don't want to go to a place like that.
I'll do my best.
Will you go? Yes, I will.
OK, let's go.
SEX Let's go.
Let's go.
I'll do my best.
Put the tension in.
I'll put the tension in.
Someone's tension will
be in my mango today.
I'll do my best.
Hurry up.
I'm going to help you.
You can do it.
I like Kijoi.
Go, go, go!
Go! I got a lot.
You got a lot.
Nebaspe!
Congratulations!
I have to endure with a cough.
I have to be patient,
so it may be dangerous.
I think I can do it.
Can you do it?
Go, Buki!
Great!
You are good at it!
Congratulations!
Do you want to kiss me?
I want to kiss you.
Don't drink it.
Don't let me breathe.
I want to drown.
Drink it all.
I got 2 points.
I got 1 point.
Thank you.
Let's play a game.
I'll beat you.
I got 1 point.
Hurry up.
Everyone, let's go.
It's a beautiful Chikubi.
Please wait a moment.
Please wait.
Here we are!
This is the 4th person.
Please step back.
You don't have to put
on the rubber band yet.
Please step back.
Only the 4th person seems to know.
No.2 is thin and long.
I didn't hit it.
No.4 is a big ball.
There are a lot of balls.
Wait, the ball is big.
You want to play,
don't you? I want to play.
Shuffle?
Yes, it's shuffle.
Shuffle again.
Go ahead.
Is it OK? Please wait a moment.
Let's go.
Can I take it off?
Please take it off.
OK.
Oh, it's big.
Good luck.
It feels good.
It's getting bigger.
It's not responding at all.
Let's make it bigger and play with it.
It's so warm.
There is!
Great! It's big!
It's a jackfruit today, too!
Oh, it feels good!
Great!
Oh, no! It's going to be big!
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, it's hot!
It's so cool!
Can I touch it? Yes, you can.
I'll put it in.
Do you like it?
Do you like to be
patted? Yes, I like it.
I'll pat you.
I'll put it on your face.
Does it feel good?
I want to go to the toilet.
Can you go to the toilet?
Thanks to Miria, I can go to the toilet.
You can go to the toilet.
You like Manko,
don't you? Yes, I do.
I want to go to the toilet.
Mika-san.
It's amazing.
But this is completely 2.
I need it.
I feel 2.
Here is 2 and 3.
Which one is 2 and 3? This is 2.
This is 2.
This is 2 inside.
Yes, 3.
Why do you touch
it? Don't do that.
Don't do that.
Can I take turns? Yes, I know.
Are you sure? Yes, I know.
Yes, I know.
This is 2.
Don't show your back.
Please look this way.
Please line up from 1.
Who is number 1? Number 1.
This person is No.1.
This person is No.4.
This person is No.
4? Yes.
Wait!
This person is the last one.
No, everyone knows.
Then, No.3.
Yes, No.3.
No.3 is fine.
I feel like this.
I feel like this, too.
That's Kasuke, isn't it?
Then,
Please turn around.
One, two, three.
It feels good.
It's hot.
I'll put it on you.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's good! It's good!
Let's make it a little bigger.
Have a nice trip!
The hair smells good.
One more roll.
Is it fun?
Who's your favorite member?
Is it like this?
We are going to have a photo session.
Let's go!
Have a good time!
Aiko, do you want to fall on your mom?
Hey, you don't have enough manko.
Look at the second manko.
Have a good time! Look at me.
Look at me.
Can I touch your boob?
Does it feel good? Do your best.
Are you OK?
Do you want me to put a lot of it on you?
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
It's fun, isn't it?
It feels so good!
How do you feel?
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's Harlem!
It's the best!
You're so young!
Wow!
I finally did it!
It might be thick.
It might come out.
It came out.
It came up to my eyes.
It's amazing.
It's flying.
It's not over yet.
It's amazing. The launch was amazing.
It's flying.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it one more time.
Let's do it.
I was surprised.
We don't have enough players.
Let's play a little more.
Wow!
Bakobasu!
The game is about to start.
I have an announcement to make.
Zawa Zawa Zawa Zawa
Zawa Zawa You said earlier.
Don't eat it.
Takuro-san
Takuya-san
As a result of the competition
between the director and the staff,
you three will go to the back of the box.
What?
Back of the box?
You have passed.
What?
What does that mean? Goodbye.
It's not good.
Please go to the back
of the box and rehearse.
I want you to do this.
Let's go!
Three people have decided.
I want to replenish three people.
I'd like to introduce you to the next one.
Yes, it's cool.
This is a gift from the back of the box.
Mr.Tiger and Mr.Tiger will be
replenished from the nurse's office.
We will do our best with these members.
Let's go to the game where
the new members have come.
One, two, three.
AOA Popular Series
Dice Game Yeah!
Yeah!
Now, three actors will roll
dice and go to the first square.
The name of the game
is written on the square.
So, please go to another
room and enjoy the game.
In each room, you can challenge
the popular series of the anime.
Let's enjoy and do our best
while improving your diving skills.
Of course, there are rooms that require
acting skills, so please do your best.
Please come to the first place.
Let's roll the dice.
5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13,
14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20 What is it now?
What is it now?
Let's go!
Ta-dah!
It's a go-kart!
Yeah!
Let's go to go-kart!
How do you do?
It's fast, isn't it?
It's good!
Awesome!
Wow! Hi, I'm Nari.
I'm Kotori.
I'm Nari.
We found you!
Thank you!
Thank you! This is.
..
Usami Kirei and... Amedori!
Yeah!
Time is up!
Time is up! From now on.
..
Anyway, do you want to play volleyball?
Sounds good!
Let's do it!
Let's play volleyball!
Sounds good! That's unfair.
That's Uta-chan's part.
How do you stop it?
I'll try it once.
I'll use magic.
You'll try it once?
You'll stop it once?
But it's already stopped.
Move, move, move, move.
It stopped.
This is the legend.
This is amazing.
Let's move it again.
Let's do volleyball.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
It was good, wasn't it?
Oh!
Rinko is surprised.
If you are surprised, it's a penalty game.
It's amazing.
It's like an evolved human being.
But the time has stopped.
Even if you lick your nipples, you don't
get a penalty, do you? You can do it.
What is this?
Is this a real
one? That's right.
It's Anaru Marumie.
Anaru Marumie.
It's embarrassing.
It's the same.
Oh, it's a nipple.
Oh.
Tamatama Sukko.
Oh, Tamatama Gyuute.
Oh, it's true.
Do you want to tickle your glasses?
It's a little stiff.
She is taking a nap.
She is not moving or pausing the time.
She is pausing the time.
I can't do it.
This is a great acting ability.
Amazing.
It's a little wobbly.
Is it? It's wobbly.
Isn't it wobbly? It's vertical.
It's vertical.
Can't it be
connected? It's true.
It's no good.
It's standing.
Is it out?
Out?
What's out?
If it's out, it's going to be a doggy.
Our dog is decided.
You are a dog.
You are the first dog.
Let's go next.
From today, it's a doggy.
I want to do this.
Hey, time is stopped.
Is it correct? I don't know.
I don't know if it's correct.
It's getting harder and harder.
Really?
Please touch it.
Is it a flounder?
You haven't eaten it yet, have you?
Why?
Chinguri!
Chinguri! Here we go.
Here we go.
The hole in the butt is big.
This is not good.
It's more dangerous than this.
What about the others?
This is a person who can stop time.
Time! Time!
Time!
Ready, go!
You're sweating!
You're right! I'm starting to sweat.
Isn't it too weak?
Why am I sweating when
I'm not doing anything?
Does it smell good?
I didn't do anything.
Isn't it plump?
This is the first time
I've seen such a thing.
It's stopped.
Great!
Yoisho!
Konnichiwa!
Yoisho! I see, I see.
It moved.
It's not paused.
It's not paused, is it?
It's decided!
It's decided! It's one man.
Please release it.
Can I?
I'll take it off.
Yes!
Great!
Release!
As a penalty game, you'll be our dog.
I'll take you to various places.
She is meowing.
She is a dog, isn't
she? Look at my dog.
My dog.
She is happy.
She is eating.
Great!
She wants to pee.
Thank you for the meal.
Do I look beautiful?
Yes, you do.
Thank you.
You look great.
Thank you for the meal.
This dog is the best dog.
Chinchin.
Let's go.
Here we are.
It's cute, isn't it?
I want to ride it.
Let's ride it.
It's wet here.
No, let's go this way.
I brought my dog, too.
Let's go.
We have a dog other than you.
Yes, we have.
I want a male dog.
Let's catch it until its knees break.
Where else can we catch it?
Here?
Oh, I can hear a dog barking.
What kind of pet
is it? It's a dog.
It's a stray dog.
It looks like a dog.
Look at its eyes.
Say hello to it.
Did you learn how to say hello?
Say, Wan.
Wan.
Thank you for coming.
I'm surprised.
I'm Tomomi Matsumoto.
Hello.
Lick it.
Hurry up! Excuse me.
You don't have to eat it.
Time out!
Thank you!
You're watching, aren't you?
Ready, set, go!
So cute!
I'm going to pee.
Go ahead.
Oh, there's a nice toilet here.
I'm going to pee.
I'm going to bathe your head first.
You're going to take a shower?
That's great.
I'll put it on your body.
I feel refreshed.
It would be nice if you could pick it up.
Thank you.
How is it?
Well, this is the only place where
I can have this kind of experience.
It's the best.
As you said, please stay
until someone picks you up.
Thank you for your hard work.
OK, let's go.
Boys, close your eyes and
count slowly to 100 and wait.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Good answer!
Let's go!
Hey, find it! Let's count it.
Four.
..
Five...
Six... Seven... Eight... Nine... Ten...
Eleven... Twelve... Thirteen... Fourteen...
Fifteen... Sixteen... Seventeen... Eighteen...
Nineteen... Twenty... Twenty-five...
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,18,19,20,21,22,23,24,25,26,27,28,29,30,31,32,33,34,35,36,37,38,39,40,40,41,42,43,44,45,46,47,48,49,50,50,51,52,52,53,54,55,56,57,58,59,60,61,62,63,64,65,66,67,68,69,70,71,72,73,74,75,76,77,78,79,80,81,82,83,84,85,85,86,87,89,90,91,92,23,23,24,24,25,26,27,26,27,28,29,31,24,27,28,30,31
I'm not sure where it is.
What?
I can't find it.
85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94,
95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100 Oh, it's in here.
When does it come out? Ah, 10.
Let's go.
Thank you very much.
Are you going to run? Yes, I am.
I want to go to the second floor.
Do you want to go to the second floor?
I want to find Mr.Yayoi.
Do you want to find Mr.
Yayoi? Yes, I want
to find Mr.Yayoi.
Oh, I found him.
I found him.
Can I do it?
You can do it, but are you standing up?
It's been 3 minutes.
You can take it off.
I told you to stand up.
I can't do it.
I can't get it in.
My nipples are made of chocolate.
Why?
My nipples are getting smaller.
You did a good job.
Thank you very much.
It was Himesaki Hana.
This is Rima-chan.
Can I look this
way? Yes, you can.
Oh, you surprised me.
There she is.
Hello.
I'm not ready at all.
I'm not ready either.
What should I do?
Are you kidding me?
I'll give you the order.
Hey, Zan.
I get wet easily when I see someone's pee.
Really?
Yes. So I want you to show me.
OK.
It's pee.
Isn't it squeaky?
Well, I want you to see if my pee is wet.
Let's see if I can do it.
Can you come a little
closer? Can I? Then.
..
Can I say the truth?
What is Hazure?
Hazure?
You...
can't rematch and have sex!
Why?
Don't mind! I see.
Don't mind!
I was so excited and ready to go.
But after this.
After this? After this.
Right, there's still more.
But don't you feel
sorry for her? I do.
I do feel a little.
I said, don't mind!
But I did my best for you.
Thank you.
I want to give it to you.
I'm going to eat it.
Stand up.
You were full of food.
I'll cool it down with my mouth.
This bread?
Is this okay?
Is it a miss? No, it's not.
It happens.
It seems to be over.
It's a two-shot, so it's over.
We're done.
Thank you for your hard work.
Are you using the secret weapon?
Hurry up!
Oh, no!
I can't stand up because
it's combined in 3 seconds.
You're panting a lot.
I didn't expect you to find me so soon.
Me, too.
You're so fast.
It's too early to put on condoms.
It's too early for the
duckling to stand up.
I want to put it in.
Put it in! Put it in!
I put it in because the
duckling didn't stand up.
It's supposed to be put
together in three seconds.
I'm sorry to put on condoms.
Do you like Chinchin?
I like Chinchin, too.
Look at this. This is Hicchan's dog.
There was a dog.
It's because FIX has the
word HAPPENING on it.
I'm going to go with Toko-chan.
This is great.
Can I take it off once?
Once?
No.
What's wrong? I'm so happy.
I feel so good.
Wow.
There are so many.
Is this a success?
Isn't it here?
Yeah!
I found a toilet on the second floor.
I thought it was suspicious.
Oh, I found it.
I found it.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's only three seconds.
I'm sure it's a mistake.
It's a miss.
Is it a miss? It's a miss.
How about the other
person? It's a miss.
We can't unite.
What should I do?
Sometimes it happens.
I feel sorry for her.
Take it out and shuffle it in 3 seconds.
You are so kind.
I've never heard of it.
That's all.
That's all? What a shame.
What a shame.
You are so kind.
It's a good idea, isn't it?
Are you standing up?
Oh, you're not standing up!
Why? You have to stand up
in three seconds, don't you?
You have to stand up in
three seconds, don't you?
You haven't had sex yet,
have you? No, I haven't.
No, you haven't.
You wanted to have
sex, didn't you? Yes, I did.
I wanted to do it.
I want to do it.
It's Piper.
I'm Piper, too.
It's the same.
Come here.
Let's combine.
Combine, combine.
It's scary.
It's a dark place,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
I'm excited.
Are you excited?
Yes.
It's so sexy.
Combine in 3 seconds.
Wow, it's amazing.
Can I get used to it?
How many people did you have
sex with today? About 4 people.
Which of the four of us do you want to
have the most comfortable sex? I want to.
You want to, don't you?
Can I draw it?
Which one do you like
the most? The white one.
Do you like the white one?
Yes.
Then, if I draw the white
one, it will come out right away.
If I draw the white one, it
will come out right away.
But if I draw the white
one, it will end right away.
It will end right away.
Can I go first?
Can I do it?
Oh my god!
Hey, I want to hug you.
Can I hug you? Yes, you can.
Yay!
I like hugging the most.
Let's hug! I'm so
happy! I'm so happy.
I want to grow up.
That's good.
Come here.
I'm so tired.
Hello.
Hello!
I want you to come to my house.
Please say hello.
Did you learn how to say hello?
Please say one.
One.
Go home!
Thank you for your visit.
You are wet.
You have become small.
I'm going to die.
I wanted you to take it out.
You took it out a lot.
I'm frustrated.
Empty condom.
I think it's a word that comes out.
If you can imagine it, you
should speak in your own words.
If you think you're a real
couple, you'll be able to speak.
If you start choosing, don't
think too much about the script.
Morisa-san, what's
going on? Here we go.
Ready, start!
Start!
I wanted to do it
quickly, so I followed you.
I love you so much.
Wait a minute.
Are you looking
forward to it? It's okay.
Let's go.
Ready, go.
I'm sorry.
I was found out.
Let's go.
Ready, go.
Hey, what's going on with the baby?
Are you excited?
Are you looking
forward to it? I'm sorry.
It's too late.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I think it's a movement of the heart.
I don't think Mr. Morisawa
will come in right away.
Like your husband.
Ready, go! Hurry up.
Come on, hurry up!
Hey!
Your wife's education is also
included in the assessment.
Are you okay with that?
Right?
Well, that's right.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Thank you very much.
Mr.
Tachibana, thank you for your last speech.
Let's sit down like that.
Let's get started.
Ready, go!
Yuya, what's up? Let me come closer.
It's too far.
You've decided to do it, haven't you?
Yes.
You have to enjoy it now.
Right?
Let's get started.
OK.
How long will you make me tape?
Thank you, sorry. I wanted to see you as it
is, but it's a work, so please cut it out.
It was rude, very rude in general.
Keep going, keep going.
OK, start.
I'll kiss you, Kamata.
Give me a kiss.
Hey, don't be so tough.
Hey.
Hana, Hana.
Let's start.
Let go of me.
Are you interested in the camera?
I'm not interested.
Hana, Hana.
Look at me.
Tomo, look at this.
Look at this.
What are you doing?
I think you are getting used to it.
Not yet.
Hana.
I'm touched too.
I'm sorry.
I'm touched.
I want you to feel it.
I want to be your partner.
Look at this.
Kana-san, Kana-san!
Look at this!
Kana-san!
What happened to you?
I didn't touch you.
But you're wet.
No, I'm not.
Look at this!
Wow!
Kana-san, I'm going to lick your nipples.
I'm going to lick you.
Look at me.
Stop it!
You are a good boy.
You are making your
husband to vomit so much.
Look at him. He is vomiting so much.
What's going on
with you? Let me see.
Oh, you are sleeping.
You are excited.
Your body is honest.
I'm going to make a video of my cat, Nana.
Nana is a kitten who is
very active when he's awake.
Nana is also a baby cat with a cute voice.
Nana is a kitten who is
very active when he's asleep.
Look, you're drooling.
I can't hold it anymore.
Look at this.
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going to work hard today.
There's a lot of water in here.
But you felt good, didn't you?
Let's do it again next time.
OK. Let's do it again with four people.
Let's do it like this.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Please follow her.
It was very short.
Thank you very much.
Did you go? Yes, I did.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
You did a good job.
I thought you came here as an amateur.
But, you played NTR drama.
You did your best.
Thank you very much.
I'll give you something.
I'll give you this.
Please open it.
Yes, honey.
Where are you going?
Yachi, you did your best.
Are you excited?
I'll open it for you.
I'm glad you got excited.
Thank you very much.
Hello, I'm Jun Suihiro.
Hi, I'm Jun.
From now on, we are going
to shoot a video together.
He is...
No, he is not.
He is Keen.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
How do you feel about shooting alone?
I'm very nervous.
Are you nervous?
Don't you touch your butt?
I can't stand it, so I'm touching my butt.
You're touching your butt.
You're energetic.
You've had three shots today.
I've had three shots.
But I'm still energetic.
He says he's still energetic.
Stand up and look.
You look nervous.
Because you were
shivering until a while ago.
You finally became a two-legged cat.
Did you want to be a
two-legged cat? Yes, I did.
Good boy.
You look nervous.
Oh, wow!
Your fur is messed up.
I'm glad to see you.
I want to see you more.
You are so cute.
Am I cute? Yes, you are.
Why do you get up so soon?
You are amazing.
Show me your belly.
Let me see.
Yes.
Wow.
You really put it out today.
Yes, I did.
Does it smell good?
Yes, it smells good.
Really?
You have a lot of hair.
I'm sorry. I have a lot of hair.
I like your hair.
Really? It smells good.
Really?
Wow.
It's so messy.
I'm running out of time.
Itadakimasu.
Wow!
I want to do it, too.
Why? Let's do it.
Can I touch you? It's hot.
It's OK.
It's very painful.
I see.
One more time.
Did you finish? Wait a minute.
I want to put it in.
OK?
You are standing up.
I can stand up.
No, you can't.
I can't stand up.
It's a little tight, but
it can't be helped.
I want to move.
Do you want to
move? I'm so happy.
I'll put it in.
It's thick.
Really?
It's the thickest I've put in today.
Really? I'm so happy.
I'm getting sleepy.
Wait, take your time.
Don't move yet.
It's so soft.
It's just right.
It feels so good.
Wait a minute.
It's very...
It feels good.
It's amazing.
Can I take a picture from behind?
Like this?
It's amazing that I can do such a thing.
As expected, Jun-chan is a professional.
It feels so good.
It's amazing.
It's so good.
I'm going to put my
feet firmly on the floor.
I've been doing it for a long time.
Oh, it's amazing.
Stay still.
Bibi, I like your bag.
Really?
I want you to put it in my bag.
Can I put it in your bag?
Let's put it in your bag.
Ouch! Wait, wait.
I want to pat you.
Can I go to the
bathroom? Yes, I want to.
Oh, my God.
You're really fat.
You're a really good guy.
Really?
Let's put it on when you're in a bad mood.
Let's put it on.
I'll find it.
I'll put it on.
I have a lot of bags.
You have a lot of pimples.
It feels better than the first time.
It feels so good.
It's so hard.
It's hard.
Because I'm a beauty.
It feels so good.
Oh, no.
But, you like a bag,
don't you? Yes, I do.
Can I take your bag?
Yes.
I'll take it.
Will you give it to me?
You are so kind.
Please.
We don't have time, so we have to go.
I have to go to the hospital.
I can see the hole in the buttocks.
I'm going to use this.
Help me.
Help me, Homa.
Ouch! It's out.
It's a great.
Wait, it's still thick,
so I can't take it off.
Can't you take it off?
I'll hold it, so take it off.
Well, then.
Can you take it off?
I'm afraid of this.
I'm afraid.
You are so kind.
Pass.
It's amazing.
I have to put this on.
This is the fourth one.
Thanks to you.
It's amazing.
Thank you.
It was fun and you did a good job.
Thank you for saying that.
Let's do it again later.
Promise.
If you lie, I'll beat you up.
I'm scared.
Let's kiss.
We have to go back to where we were.
I don't want to go back.
I'm lonely.
Let's do it again later.
We are SUGOTEKU BEYOND!
What are you going to do?
We are going to hold it for 10 minutes.
If we can hold it, we
are going to have sex.
If we can't hold it, we are going to stop.
We are going to stop.
If we want to have sex,
we are going to hold it.
It's simple.
But we can't move.
If we get in the way, we can't eat.
〔Riku〕 I'm going to
start from the beginning.
〔Riku〕 I don't want to do it.
〔Riku〕 Everyone, please get ready.
〔Riku〕 It may be difficult to take a video.
〔Riku〕 I can do it.
〔Riku〕 It's easy to take a video.
〔Riku〕 Let's start.
〔Riku〕 Ready.
〔Riku〕 Start.
I like it when you lick my nipples.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It's my first time.
Let me put my hand on your nipples.
It feels good visually, doesn't it?
Which do you like
better, breast or nipples?
Which one do you like?
Manko noodles or boobs noodles?
Which one do you
like? Manko noodles.
Manko noodles?
Yes.
But boobs noodles are here.
Look at this.
Let's turn it off.
Turn it off.
Oh, no.
You make it better than usual, don't you?
Yes, I make it better than usual.
That's right.
Do you want to lie down and watch?
This is good, isn't it?
I was sitting so as not to go.
Success!
This is a real success.
Here comes the lotion.
Are you going to
do it? Let's do it.
I'm trying to do it from the front.
It hurts.
I think you should sleep more.
What's wrong? My face.
What's wrong with
you? I feel sick.
10 seconds left.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Time's up!
Congratulations! I won.
Congratulations!
You were so kind to me.
You should be more kind.
You did it on purpose,
didn't you? Yes, we did.
It's just a mini-corner.
We should do it longer.
By the way, among these four
people, I'll ask you a question.
Who was the most reluctant?
One, two, three.
Can I open my eyes? I see.
I see.
I'll announce it later.
Why do you hate it so much?
The second one is Shin-Uchi.
Yuto graduated from the
same school as me a while ago.
Congratulations! I became a man.
You have only one chance.
You should have a lot of chances.
I have a lot of chances.
Show me.
Let's take it off.
It's OK to take it off
because you are handsome.
It's a handsome frame this time.
A handsome frame.
The only one.
You are so handsome.
You are the best.
I'll show you.
Is it OK to start from this position?
What are you going to do?
Doesn't it hurt here?
Isn't it hard to do?
Are you OK?
Roger is a little strong,
isn't he? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You like it, don't you?
Stop it!
I like it!
Don't look this way!
Look this way!
Look straight!
It's shaking!
It's disgusting!
It's close!
It's close! OK, let's go.
It's cute, but.
..
OK, let's go.
If you can resist it, you
can do Harlem Shake!
Ready, go!
What?
I want to kiss you.
Say, I love you, Nozomi.
Say it.
I love you, Nozomi.
What?
We are back to the beginning, aren't we?
Say something to your fans.
Yuto! Love! Love! Love!
I want you to make me bigger!
Make me bigger!
Cooperate with me!
Yuto, I'm waiting for you over there.
Who do you want
me to lick? Nozomin.
One bite for Asami-chan!
That's not fair!
You're so mean! I don't know.
Playboy?
Playboy bomb?
Who do you like the
most now? Yuzuriha-chan.
This is the first time I've ever
seen such a cute baby in my life.
Who is it now? It's a baby.
I see.
I love you.
Three minutes left.
Do you want to lick me?
Do you?
Do you want to drink it?
She became stiff after
drinking the breast milk.
Do you like breast milk?
She likes Nozomi-chan.
Do you like Nozomi-chan?
She doesn't want to go.
10 seconds left.
We have a lot of opportunities.
If you go now, you will feel good.
I love you so much.
Go now. You will feel good.
I like Nozomi the most now.
The end.
That's why you didn't want to go.
You have to have two mouths to do it.
It's difficult.
I can't do it.
Tell me your love.
We can't do it alone.
I want to have sex with you.
Say it out loud.
I want to have sex with Nozomi.
What kind of sex do you want to
have with Nozomi? Love love sex.
Do you want to have a
love-love affair? Leave it to me.
So, you want to have a
love affair with Yuzuriha.
Do you want to
help her? Yes, I do.
I'm sorry that I can't help you.
I can't help you.
Don't say that.
Who do you like the
most in this exhibition?
I'm sure it's me.
I think you have a funny face.
Look at this.
It's a lipstick.
What do you like?
It's a normal size.
Normal size.
Oh, it's in.
It's pretty deep.
Deep.
It's quite deep.
I'm going to take off my hat.
It's a lot, isn't
it? It's a lot.
I'm getting angry.
It might come out.
It's coming out.
I'm getting angry.
Oh, no. It's coming out.
Quickly, squeeze it out.
I can't.
Ah!
It's delicious!
It's like a delicious ramen.
Don't you feel
ticklish? It's okay.
Success!
Thank you!
To the camera!
Wow!
I'm starting to remember my youth.
I'm getting dizzy.
The cat who is in the
hospital has been abandoned.
The cat is in the hospital, but the vet
said that he was admitted to the hospital.
Even though the cat
was in the hospital,
the vet said that he
was in a bad condition.
The vet had to take the
cat to the vet, and the
vet said that the cat
was in a bad condition.
Yuta is kissing while opening his eyes.
You want to see various things, don't you?
Don't you want to see Omanko?
Do you want to see Omanko?
I don't want to lick Omanko.
He is a supporter.
How is Omanko?
Omanko is beautiful.
Really?
What is it? It's pink.
I'm going to lick it by myself.
Can I lick it? Yes, you can.
Please tell me how it tastes.
I'll do my best.
Oh, wow.
Taste it.
Taste it, taste it.
Slowly, slowly.
It's sticky.
Really?
Do you always do that?
How do you do that?
What do you want to do?
I want you to lick me.
Do you want me to
lick you? Look at me.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to put it in?
You want to put it in?
Do you want to
put it in? I'm sorry.
I'll put it in.
Look at me.
It's okay, it's okay.
Is this a lip? It's not a lip.
It's not shaking yet.
I'm sorry.
Yuto!
I'm a little nervous, but...
I'm sorry.
I'm a little nervous,
but... I'm a little sad.
I agree.
I'm a little emotional, too.
Well, last one.
Okay, I'll do it.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
That's all for the Sugo Tech corner.
Ma
Ko
Su
Bakobasu
Ready, set, go!
Nice chimpo voting!
We've seen the results, and now we're going
to vote to decide who's the best chimpo.
The chimpo will come
out of this hole in the wall.
Everyone, please put a sticker on the wall.
Okay, everyone, let's get started.
Oh, it's frozen.
Oh, it's hard.
Maybe.
It's shining. It's a doctor.
You can put it on when you take it out.
Have you finished putting
it on? Yes, we have.
We're going to have a meeting.
I'd like you to take out
the ones without stickers.
Please take out the ones without stickers.
How about one sticker?
I'm going to show you how
to make a chimpanzee hat.
3, 4, 2, 3.
3.
Wow.
These 3 chimpos are our Nice Chimpos.
Congratulations.
That's all.
Nice Chimpos.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
This is the first time for me to
dance at BAHO Olympics in 2012.
I started in the same way as you.
I've been dancing for 11 years.
My name is TACHI TSUYOSHI.
You still want to dance, don't you?
You want to dance, don't you?
You want to dance with
various girls, don't you?
Let's do our best!
Thank you very much.
By the way, he is from Urabako.
He is a junior high school student.
I'm from Urabako.
I don't know how to appeal.
I came here because I
didn't have a chance to do so.
How should I appeal?
This is a simple and clear answer.
I'll do my best.
Is there anything else you
want to ask? Yes, please.
I'm surrounded by four beautiful women.
This is the first experience in my life.
I can't see where I'm going.
It is said that if you
concentrate on one place, you
will be able to concentrate
on all things in the world.
It's one with the fruit,
isn't it? That's right.
Next time, I want to go to YouTube.
I want to go to YouTube.
It's written here.
I wonder if it's okay to
have a chat with the teacher.
I was very motivated.
I found out that it was easy to stand up.
Let's go!
OK!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Let's go!
Are you ready?
Can I have a kiss on the cheek?
A kiss on the cheek?
Are you ready? Please be serious.
It feels good.
There's a bigger one.
I got an ice cream.
Hello.
I'm done!
Come on!
It's only yellow and pink left!
I'm done!
Oh, no!
How did you come up with that?
How funny!
〔The first day of the
school's opening ceremony.
〕 The end!
One, two, three, Ba
Ko
Ba
SU
PAKOBASU
Everyone, we have
a special guest at the
supermarket to decorate
the end of the first day.
Who is it?
Let's see who is here.
Come on in!
What?
Why are you smiling?
I heard a moan.
The players are very excited.
You guys should not be in my way.
Let's play with the next player.
It's coming!
You wanna drink,
don't you? Yes, I do.
Let's drink.
Oh, it feels good.
Do you like cow?
I'm going to put it in a bowl.
Give me a tip.
Ouch!
I'm going to put it in a bowl.
She is a fan of you.
I'm going home.
I stood up.
I also stood up.
I was scared.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm angry.
It's hot!
It's going to be a mess.
I want to put it in.
It's going to be all over your ear.
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going to take a picture.
It's already Sunday.
You can put your butt on it.
Put your legs on it, too.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm so happy.
I can't speak a word.
It's delicious.
It's great.
I can't speak a word.
I'm a squeezing warrior.
Ouch! Almost.
Just a little bit.
Did you come
out? Ok, I love you.
Bye.
Yua, you look so good.
I love you too.
I like you.
Wait! Come here!
I'm sorry!
It's OK!
You're not good at it?
You're not good
at it? I'm sorry.
Can I touch you?
Can I touch you? I'm sorry.
Yeah!
Thank you! Thank you so much!
It's open!
Hey, put it in!
Put it in!
Don't you want to put it in?
Hurry up and put it in!
30 seconds left, everyone!
Let's go to the mountain.
I feel like I'm in the mountain.
Do you want to check it?
No.
Maybe I'm not in the mountain.
Maybe you're not in the mountain.
I feel like I'm in the mountain.
Are you sure?
I was surprised.
I'm going to do it.
You can do it, can't you?
You were doing like this.
I'll help you.
I want to wear it.
I tried so hard.
I'm so scared.
Wow, amazing.
I tried so hard.
I can't go to the front.
I can't go there.
The show has started.
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Are you OK? I feel good.
I'm going to throw up.
Wow!
Cute!
Give it to everyone!
Thank you!
Do you want it?
I'll give it to you as soon as possible.
It's the worst.
I'm not good at it.
We'll do it one last time.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Ba
Ko
Su
Bakobasu
Now, let's start the Bakobasu Festival!
I would like to start the festival.
The festival is divided into four parts.
The boys who started at once
can move on to the other stage.
The one who will liven up
the festival is DJ MIYAVI.
SS kinds turn-up last steed for
the dishem SX odds This is SixStage
If I pick up an S, If you want
to participate in the competition,
please stop at the
monument over there.
If the number of participants exceeds
the limit, something will happen.
I would like to go to the
South Pole right away.
Before that, there is
a special guest who is
not known in Japan,
Asia, Europe and the world.
Who is it?
The new leaders of AV have come
to BADOBADO FACT FESTIVAL.
Music start! Thank you.
Now, everyone, please line up.
Please give me a signal when you arrive.
Please line up.
It's still hot.
It's so hot.
What's going on? One, two.
Master, please
take care of us today.
I didn't say that.
I didn't say that alone.
It's a joint responsibility.
It's the hair of Chikubi-chan.
Does it hurt? No, it doesn't.
It doesn't hurt.
It's the hair of Kimori-chan
and Chikubi-chan.
I got my hair back.
It's strange.
Let's take off the necklace.
Let's take it off.
Oh, I see.
I want you to lick me.
I want you to take a picture of me.
I feel good.
You are cute.
You look like Kato-chan.
Oh, it's hot.
Open your mouth.
You can open your mouth, can't you?
Keep your mouth open.
If you run away, I'll take your nipples.
Here we go.
Wow!
Why are you so excited?
He's so excited.
Look!
What is this?
Wow, it's so big.
Is it good? It's hard.
Wow, it's so open.
It's open over there, too.
Oh, it's closed again.
It's not closed.
Are you watching it all the time?
What are you doing?
How are you feeling now?
I'll look after you.
Come here, come here.
Oh, you're good.
You are so cute!
Oh, my god!
You are licking my wrist.
You are so naughty!
Let me see your belly!
You are the best!
I want to see your belly.
I'm going to put it in.
It's in.
Please clean up.
Oh my god.
It feels good.
It feels good here.
Please do it properly.
Please let me in.
It's delicious.
How many people are there?
A lot of people.
Bring it to me.
It feels good.
〔The sound of a baby crying.
〕 〔The sound of a baby crying.
〕 It's still going!
That was the third shot. Thank you.
This is it.
I'm going to eat this.
Let's go.
Don't you talk?
Don't you need to pee?
Oh my god!
Do you need to pee?
I don't need to pee.
That's too bad.
Oh my god!
Oh my god! I am relieved.
Even I've become an
adult, I was able to do it.
It's hard to say.
Hey! Don't do that! It's done.
Ah, it's painful.
I'll show you.
I have to do it.
I'll make you drown.
I'll do it.
I'm worried.
You did it.
You got a white thread.
Yeah! I got it! Congratulation!
I'm glad you got it!
You did your best!
OK, let's go to the stadium.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a picture.
I told him that I came
here first because I like him.
I told him.
I'm so nervous.
Let me go.
No.
Don't go.
Let me go.
No.
She's gone.
Let's practice.
Great.
Wow, you even clean the floor.
You even clean the floor.
It's good.
No, no, no.
It feels good.
How do you feel?
Pelo Pelo?
Teacher, how do you feel
when you are being pelted?
It's a mouthful.
I'm so sleepy.
I can't open my mouth.
Look at my butt.
My nipples are swollen.
I'm going to puke.
Shake your hips.
They are in the stage.
Four people are dancing.
Let's dance in the circle.
Look all.
You did it beautifully.
I've tied it up!
This is my professionalism!
Wonderful!
Thank you!
Here we go!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Something's coming out!
Oh! Oh!
The bus ride was fun.
It was fun.
I was an amateur for the first time,
but I was able to see Uyuichi.
I felt a little embarrassed.
It was amazing that all the
boys came out unexpectedly.
That's right.
I think it's amazing to be able to reflect.
I think I can't do it because I've
squeezed out half of my energy.
It was really fun.
I had a lot of fun with everyone.
It's a bit regretful,
but I had a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Wakabosu is the best!
Six is the best.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
Next, we are going to Katsudou, Hikata.
Thank you very much.
I want to go on a rampage again.
Bakobasu is the best.
The best.
Before we go home, we
have something for you.
It's nothing special, but
I think everyone is a little
concerned about the number
of shots fired in two days.
Can I announce it?
There are two representatives.
Should I announce it from the 1st place?
Let's hear from the 2nd place.
Please come forward.
Are you ready?
In the second place, Match.
Match-san?
Match?
Yes, this person.
9 votes.
Wow! Amazing.
I'm not sure if it's amazing or not.
It's amazing.
In the second place, King Kaz.
King Kaz? Kaz-san.
King Kaz.
Wow!
King Kaz!
I want to take a Guts pose, too.
But I'm in second place.
I'm taking a Guts pose.
I'm in second place.
I'll announce the first place.
What's next?
Do you want to go to the 6th place?
I want to go to the 6th place.
Let's go.
Taku-san!
I'm in first place!
That's amazing.
It's like an invader!
Wow!
11 shots!
Here it is!
Wow!
Look at this!
Congratulations!
Ta Da Da Da Da Da Da~~
Da La La La La La La
La This golden trophy,
I will give it back in a good way.
BAKO PASS tour,
the best, the winner.
Congratulations.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Now you must be tired,
and we are going home.
Let's go.
We are leaving.
Thank you for two days.
Thank you very much.
Let's go home.
I'm tired.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yu.
It was a very fun two days.
Thank you very much.
I was able to shoot the
actress who was my dream.
It's a match.
It was fun. Thank you very much.
It was a great experience.
Thank you very much.
It was an unforgettable trip.
I'm happy.
I'll remember this and do it every day.
Thank you.
I'm Kazuma. Nice to meet you. Thank you.
I don't think I've ever had two
days of sex like this in my life.
It was fun. I had a good experience.
I'm glad I graduated from high school
and learned a lot about the taste of manko.
It was like a dream time.
Bako Bako is the best.
I'm Isayama Setsuko. I'm in Roppongi.
I learned a lot today. Thank you very much.
I'm Takkari.
I was able to run 6 laps successfully.
It was a lot of fun. Bakobasu is the best.
I'm Koshi. I ran 4 laps.
Bakobasu is the best. Moody's is the best.
It became a lifetime memory.
Thank you very much.
I ran 8 laps in 2 days.
I wanted to run 2 more laps.
I want to run again. Thank you very much.
I think it will be the past of my house.
It was the best. Thank you very much.
I'm Is. Thank you very
much. I would like to
participate in the
Katajikai work. Thank you.
I'm Toyboy Aizawa.
This time I participated as an actor.
Rather, everyone is amazing.
I thought I had to do my best.
Thank you very much.