Cheers!
It's been a while.
When was the last time
you all got together like this?
I don't remember.
Was it 3 years ago?
No way!
How's your husband?
What did you say today?
Everyone's at home.
We're going to play.
Yeah, we're going to play.
We've calmed down.
I'm glad you watched this.
It was hot.
It's Japanese style.
It's quiet.
We were supposed to meet.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, it's been a while.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
It looks hot.
Can I have a beer?
Sure, thank you.
It was late.
Hold it.
Hold it! Thank you.
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
See?
The cutest girl is next.
That's right.
Once again, congratulations on
the opening of Kinoko Dousoukai.
What's increasing?
Cheers!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Yeah, it's been a while
since we've seen each other.
By the way,
You're alone, aren't you?
Where's Takeda?
Isn't he here?
Takeda?
Takeda got married.
Oh, really?
He had a baby, so he can't come.
Really?
I didn't know Takeda was here.
Are you alone?
Hirori?
Only me?
I want to see you.
Cheers!
Where is your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
You don't have a
girlfriend now? I'm alone.
You look so pitiful.
You don't laugh.
Sorry, you look so pitiful.
I feel sorry for them.
Are you two married?
Yes.
Are you two
married? Yes, we are.
Everyone knows that.
I feel sorry for them.
Didn't you know
that? No, I didn't.
Didn't you write a
letter? No, I didn't.
You didn't write anything.
Then, let's get back on track.
Let's get back on track.
Let's eat.
Can I have a plate of chicken?
Two plates of chicken, please.
Thank you for the meal.
It's so delicious.
What are you doing? Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Please take a picture.
You drank too much.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I drank too much.
You should have drunk more.
Let's go over there.
I'm sorry.
Is it okay? It's open.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'll take a picture.
Cheese!
Yeah!
I'll take a picture.
It looks good.
Send it to me later.
You look younger today.
No, I'm not.
Are you drunk?
I'm not that drunk.
Really? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
If you're not drunk, let's drink.
I don't want to.
You're not drunk at all, Himori-kun.
Let's drink.
Cheers! Excuse me.
This one.
Drink it all at once.
I'm not good at drinking sake.
This is the real sake.
First, Uesawa.
I, Himawari, will do my best.
By the way, do you have a
boyfriend recently? Yes, I do.
So, don't you feel lonely
without him for 2 years?
Lonely? Well, it's easy.
I'm free.
You haven't had a boyfriend for
2 years, have you? No, I haven't.
Why do you know that?
What are you
doing? I'm so curious.
I'm curious about everyone's story.
We don't have a family.
You were serious,
weren't you? Yes, I was.
What are you doing?
I'm in college now.
I see.
Senpai?
That's it?
I don't think I do that much.
I think so.
How many times?
I do it once a week.
Once a week?
But I'm busy with work.
I see.
How about you, Suzaki?
I live far away from here.
I see.
So I do it once every two weeks.
Why? Is it because you don't have time?
I'm tired, so I want to go to bed early.
What is your type?
I've never heard of it.
Type? I like girls.
You are late.
I'm drunk.
I like you more than Himori.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Thank you.
How about you, Inokawa-chan?
I... I've never heard of it.
I've never heard of it.
I do it once a week, but my
husband does it so many times.
It's hard.
How many times?
About four times a night.
Oh, my God!
I don't have an image, but I do it.
I've gained some physical strength.
I want to try various things.
I haven't experienced it yet.
To be honest, I like your kiss.
How about Maeda-san?
Maeda-san? I don't know.
How bad is it? It's normal.
Normal?
Do you know normal?
I don't know normal.
Himori is a little curious.
I'm curious.
I want to be mature.
You do that, too.
I'm not interested.
That's all.
I don't know.
Let's see.
We can't see.
We don't see.
We can see what Japanese like.
That's right.
Who do you want to drink?
Who do you want to
drink? I can't choose.
I don't have enough sake.
We don't have enough sake.
Let's drink.
Drink, drink, drink.
Do you want me to drink?
I don't mean that.
I can't drink that much.
Let's drink.
Let's drink together.
Cheers!
Cheers! I can drink it.
Which one is faster?
The one who loses will show it.
Good!
Out!
Maeda, you should watch it.
Me?
The one who won.
You should watch it.
Me?
You can look back.
Let's watch it together.
No, I don't want to.
Are you serious?
Because you didn't drink it.
What?
She looks happy.
Are you serious?
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Oh, my God!
Yurika!
The string is coming out.
I can't tell the color.
I want to see the color.
Look closer.
You can see the underwear, right?
Did you take it off?
Did you miss it?
Baby?
Or is it small?
That's not the case.
Let me see.
It's okay.
Ma-chan, you missed it.
You missed it.
Wait a minute.
It's okay.
Don't do that!
I feel like a weird juice is coming out.
This is the one you
ate, so I don't like it.
I don't want to use my juice.
It's cute.
I'm sure it will come out.
What are you doing?
The result is out.
Great!
It's new, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
It's not over yet.
What are you doing? That's all.
Do you lose? I lost.
This is it!
Let's start with this one.
It's been a while.
Which one is bigger?
I think this one is bigger.
Oh my god!
You look a little happy.
You look a little happy,
don't you? I'm happy.
You look happy.
I'm happy.
I'm sorry.
But you are one of us.
Now?
What's going on?
Should I stand up?
Yes, you should.
I'll take a picture of you.
Let's take a picture together.
It's going to be a dark history.
Cheese!
One more!
Good!
Beautiful!
I sent it!
Do you want to take a thumbnail?
I want to take it off.
It's getting hot.
It's hot.
I want to take it off.
Excuse me.
It's almost done.
It's good.
It's OK.
It looks painful.
The loser of
rock-paper-scissors will do it.
It looks like a funny game.
Let's do it.
Oh!
It's open!
Rock-paper-scissors! I'm going.
Rock-paper-scissors!
Oh, really?
Please do it more carefully.
Oh, my God!
Why am I being played a
punishment game? She is excited.
It's a weird sign.
What kind of expression is that?
Does it feel good?
It's really hard.
Is it really hard?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Does it feel good?
It's the second one.
I don't want to do it either.
Seriously.
Wait, wait!
Let's play a game.
What is it?
Do you know the Survivor's game?
What's that?
There are 3 numbers, and
the one who says 31 loses.
Really? From 1 to 10.
What do we do if we lose?
What's the game?
Let's lick each other if we lose.
I'm done.
Let me go.
Really? Let me go.
It's just right.
1, 2, 3.
4, 5, 6? That's right.
I can say up to 6.
4.
Yes, I did!
Look! The second one.
Wow, there are 6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
You are so happy.
You are happy and cute.
How about the next
one? I was so happy.
Don't be so erotic.
How many? 12? 11? Here we go.
Twelve.
Fourteen.
Fifteen.
Sixteen.
Seventeen.
19 20 I'm scared.
How many?
23, 24
27, 28
From 28th...
28th...
Why are you looking at me?
Is 28th okay?
You like it, don't you? 29, 30.
Are you sure?
But everyone can
see it, right? I'll hide it.
Stand up.
This is good.
Go over there.
I can't see it.
Check it.
I want to check the
time. I can't see it.
10 seconds.
What is this?
Is it coming in? Yes, it is.
It's long.
Wait a minute.
I think it's hard
to see your hand.
Thank you.
Say like this.
Let's count.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
Why are you taking it off?
It's falling off.
It's really falling off.
I don't need it.
That's right.
2 seconds left.
That's not good.
Do it if you can.
I can't do it if I can't do it.
Then do it quickly.
One, two, three.
Nine.
Ten.
I'm going to show you how to lick it.
Everyone is licking it.
Where should I
touch? Around here.
I have ice.
You have ice.
I'm going to lick it.
My neck is cold.
Himawari, you can't do it yet.
I can't do it yet.
It's so hard.
Let's do it.
Himori, I'll teach you
how to play the piano.
You've never done it before.
It fell.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
No.
It's going to be dirty.
This is expensive.
Next.
You've been looking at it all the time.
I've been looking at it all the time.
You're going to do it.
Show me.
Don't say that!
It's a lie!
Wow, something is coming out.
This is the biggest one.
Look at the boobs.
There is no stop.
Look, there are flowers on both hands.
Let's touch here.
Let's play with it a little bit.
Oh, no. It's coming out.
It's beautiful.
Look, it's a butt.
It's a butt.
It's a butt of my beloved sister.
It's so soft.
It's a little bit erotic.
Let's change the table.
I'm scared.
I won't let you drink alcohol.
Show me your butt.
Show me.
Oh my god!
Look! She likes butt.
Look! It feels good.
She is happy.
She is cute.
Me, too.
Look! She is getting on the chair.
Hey, hey.
She likes butt.
Look!
Wow! She is happy.
I am happy.
My legs are getting bigger and bigger.
It's amazing.
I like legs, too.
You like everything.
What's so amazing? Tell me.
Your balls are swimming.
They are swimming.
We want to make you feel good.
Let me out! Let me out!
Is it possible to come out like this?
Wow!
You are so mean!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
You don't want to do it anymore?
I don't want to do it anymore!
You are so kind!
You are so kind! Thank you.
Did I make you dirty?
Asahi is full of energy.
What are you doing?
Cheers! Let's drink.
Cheers!
Are you OK?
Are you drunk? Yes, I am.
Are you crazy?
I feel like something is wrong.
No one is coming.
Let's lie down.
There is another room over there.
Let's go over there.
Are you OK?
It's better for a man to go.
Let's go together.
It's hot.
Hiyori, you go.
Be careful.
Put on your weight.
Sit here.
Me?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Look, look, look.
You are going to fall asleep.
Are you OK?
Are you going to lie down?
Yes.
Are you sleeping?
Can you see?
Well,
Kimori is getting
married, isn't she?
Yes.
I'm worried about my husband.
I'm worried about him.
Can you see it?
I touched it, but I can't
touch it a little more.
It's all right. Come here.
It's hard.
It's very hard.
I want to do it.
I can't do it.
Here.
You can sit here.
It's OK.
Everyone is here.
It feels good, doesn't it?
What is your name?
My name?
I'm going to be a weak child.
Really?
Yes.
I'm drunk.
I'm not drunk.
I was just in the mood.
It's just a little bit.
We are different.
Don't worry. It's just glue.
From here.
Can you see it?
Can I put it in?
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't worry.
I'm not good at this.
I'm a little nervous.
Oh, it's hot.
Oh, it feels good.
It's so hard.
Are you doing it? I'm doing it.
No, I was massaging.
You are too fast.
No, no, no.
You are doing it.
You should have done it properly.
What are you doing?
Show me the massage.
It's in here.
Where is the
massage? It's in here.
You are doing it.
It's in here.
It's in there.
What kind of massage?
Hey!
You are doing it, aren't you?
You are doing it,
aren't you? No, I'm not.
What are you doing?
I'm not taking a bath.
What?
She was drunk, so I tried
to give her a massage.
Massage?
I'm doing it!
Komatsu, are you okay?
Komatsu, stop, stop, stop!
What are you doing?
I'm doing it!
We're helping Masa.
Massage me properly.
But...
Don't do that to a girl.
You can move more.
Be serious.
I'm serious.
Look at this.
I want to take it off.
Let's take it off.
You don't have to do that.
You have to make her feel good.
It's a massage,
isn't it? She's drunk.
Give her a massage.
You said it yourself.
You have to move your hips more.
It looks good on you.
You look so good in it.
It's fashionable.
Let's show it to them.
What's so fashionable?
Let's do it in a different way.
Show us more.
Show me more.
Like this.
I couldn't see it well.
Oh my god!
This is a special seat.
Oh, my God!
Look at her!
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does!
Show me your boobies!
I think she's used to it.
Look! She's moving!
Wow!
Can you move like this?
You just have to train your body.
Let me see.
Your boobs are saying, help me.
I heard it.
That's good.
Let me see your butt.
Let me see.
Wait a minute.
Hello?
We are having fun!
I'm going to the concert.
Is that so?
OK.
You know? Yes, I know.
Bye.
More!
Come on!
No, no, I'm going to do it.
What?
What are you doing?
Wow!
Wow! Try licking it.
It was the best.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You look so energetic even
though you just took it out.
That's right.
You look like you can do it.
You look so energetic.
Let's do it!
I want to do it!
Which one do you like?
Which one do you
like? I can't choose.
Which one do you like?
You want to do it, don't you?
Let's do it!
I have this one, too.
What should I do?
Can't you put it in?
My panties!
Your panties are...
Hurry up!
Oh, no!
Hinata, how do you feel?
Do you feel good?
Hinata, do you feel good?
I'll give you a good one.
It's so cute.
Look.
This way.
Isn't it better to go that way?
What's going on?
What's going on? Go away.
It's good!
You can put it in your mouth.
Put it in your mouth.
It feels good!
You have a big boob!
Seriously?
Of course!
Why do you think I
called you? That's right.
I'll show you.
You can't do that.
Look.
Let's take it off.
Wow.
Are you ready? I'm waiting.
Let's do it before
everyone sees us.
Hurry up!
The order may come soon.
We are in the way.
What are you wearing?
Show me your legs.
I want to see them.
Show me.
Great!
Great?
Do you feel good?
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm my husband.
Really?
You did it!
I wanted to do it, too.
Oh, my God!
Look!
You can do it!
Give me a kiss!
Oh, my God!
Go for it! Go for it!
I have to feel good.
I'm waiting for you.
I don't want to let you go.
Next.
I'm tired.
You can still do it.
Did you feel good?
Who's next?
You don't want to do it?
You came here and
played rock-paper-scissors.
Let's change.
Next.
It's a bathing suit.
Take it off.
I'll take it off for you.
Look carefully.
Let's do it until the end.
Do it slowly.
It's not just fast.
It's not just the beginning.
I can't hold it anymore.
Wait, wait, wait!
You can still do
it? I'm so glad.
I'm so glad.
Where are you putting it?
My hair got wet.
Are you scared? I'm scared.
It's about time.
Why? I'm nervous.
Don't get too close.
You're trembling.
Who is it?
Komachi wants to do it, too.
She had a massage just now.
Do it properly.
You should take it off.
Take it off.
I'll take your clothes.
I don't need it anymore.
This way.
Hello.
I can see you.
You are amazing.
Look at your butt.
Kimori, you should drink alcohol.
I feel sick.
You don't have to do that!
Oh, my God!
Wow!
It's hot!
It's better to take a bath now.
Go ahead.
Komachi said we can take a bath.
Good for you!
Can you do it
again? No, I can't.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it.
You can't do it with two hands.
I can do it.
What's wrong? I'm hungry.
I feel good.
Kimo-Rin, please
move this side, too.
What should I do? It's not good.
It's not good, isn't
it? Come here.
Come here.
You can get tired with hot water.
Wow, you're still standing.
Look.
You're standing on this side, too.
Your balls are still tight.
Wow, you've taken it out three times.
Wow.
What are you doing?
You're playing again.
You're amazing.
You haven't taken it out yet.
Can I go in?
You haven't taken it out yet. Look.
Wow.
Wow, you've done a lot.
Why are you standing
like this? Let's see.
Look at this.
Wow.
It's cool.
It feels good.
Look at this.
Wow.
It's cute.
It feels good.
Really?
Can I hold it? Let me hold it.
Let me hold it.
What are you doing?
You just did it.
Are you still grumpy?
Look, Hikonori.
I can't do it.
You can't do it? It's painful.
Ochinchi, you are so grumpy.
I'm not grumpy.
You have double boobs.
Look at this.
Oh my gosh! It's so erotic!
Does it feel good, Himari?
Does it feel good?
Look at her boobs!
Are you still
fine? I'm still fine.
I want to pinch you!
You're good!
Let's put it in.
Put it in.
It feels so good.
It's warm.
Look, Himawari.
I can't see your picture.
It's gone.
Look, Himawari's penis is gone.
I want to see it.
It's gone.
Touch my butt.
You like my butt.
You are still playing with Chuchu.
You are not fair.
I want you to play with Chuchu.
You feel good, don't you?
You are so cute.
I want to make you feel better.
I want to drink the water.
Do you want to
drink it? I'll drink it.
Drink it.
I'll drink it.
Do you want to
drink it? I'll drink it.
I'll drink it.
Wow!
Please bear with me.
It feels good.
Are you sleepy? You're tired.
I'm glad.
I'm not sure if
I can do it well.
Here you go.
You're so kind.
Let's kiss.
What?
Wow!
Don't pinch our boobs!
What's that? I'm sorry.
I was teasing you.
Do you feel good? Yes, I do.
Let's go.
How do you feel? It's hot.
What?
I can't hear you.
I don't know what I said.
She is going.
Why are you all going there?
She is going over there.
She is not waving her hand.
It's a baby!
Do you want to lick it?
Look, I'm licking the tip of your tongue.
Are you still a baby?
Why are you still a baby?
I want to lick your tongue.
I want to drink sake.
Let's drink.
Do you want to drink?
You're standing up so much.
I want it.
It's good, isn't it? Put it in.
Put it in.
I want it.
It's a bag.
It's time to go to bed.
Hey, Himari.
Go to bed.
I feel so good.
I can't move.
It's getting hot.
I want you to lick it because it's hot.
Here you are.
Lick it.
I'll eat it.
Okay, let's go.
Don't make noise.
Don't make noise,
okay? It's gross.
Look at her.
It's gross.
It's a monster.
It's going to go in.
I'm going to cry.
Don't you want to
lose? Do your best.
You should go.
I'll go first.
Show me.
My baby is going to be born.
Who wants a baby?
Who wants a t-shirt?
Look, look!
I'm going to put it in.
I wore it once.
I was surprised.
Really?
Yes.
But you are doing well.
I want to get on the car.
It's good, isn't it? Oh, my.
I'm glad.
Can I try? Oh, my.
Oh, my.
You are so energetic.
You like boobs.
Oh, my.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You should go to bed.
Hang in there.
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, no!
Did you see that?
Are you going to show me your back?
Do you feel good?
Get comfortable.
I want to do a lot.
Mirai-chan and Yui-chan, get comfortable.
Look at this.
Where is she?
She's very excited and
is drinking hot water.
I'll pour it for you.
Wow, it's delicious!
Really?
It's delicious, isn't it?
What are you eating?
Are you still talking?
You're amazing.
I'm still talking.
You are still talking?
It's impossible.
Wait a minute.
Break time?
I'm already full.
It was delicious.
It was the best.
There are a lot of things to talk about.
That was delicious.
It was very delicious.
What's this?
Oh, I have a good one.
What's that? That is.
..
This.
What's that?
No, it's popular overseas.
It's like a supplement.
Supplement?
Isn't it popular today?
What's that? It's fun.
It's fun?
It's not dangerous at all.
It's quite popular overseas.
I want to try it.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's very delicious.
Look, Suzaki-san.
Let me see.
Look, it's staring at each other.
Do you want it?
But it's really warm.
It's warm.
You can tell the difference.
It's quick.
How is it?
It looks like it's going to blow up.
It's going to blow up.
It's so warm.
Yes, that's right.
Here you are.
I'm getting sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
I don't need it.
Here you are.
I'm sleepy.
You can do it here.
I want you to get used to it.
What do you want
me to do? Everyone.
Everyone.
She wants you to do it.
Yes.
Do it.
No.
It's so hot.
This is not good.
It's on my nipples.
It's getting hot.
Is it hot?
I can't do it anymore.
It's getting hot, isn't
it? Wait a minute.
What's wrong with you?
You are sweating a lot.
You are weak.
I'm sorry.
I feel great.
Let's open it.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
I think it's better to put it together.
Be careful.
Oh, no.
Oh, no. I can't stand it.
Open it more.
More, more.
What's wrong?
You are so cute.
You are so cute, aren't you?
You are so beautiful.
You are so cute.
Thank you for watching!