Welcome!
This is a lotion bath.
We will show you the feeling of a bath.
This is a bubble bath.
Please wash your body and body.
Then, please choose which one you like.
Please come in!
Let's do it cleanly.
Awawa! Awawa!
This is GingGing.
It's getting bigger.
Let's put it on the butt.
Oh, great! Ochi-Ochi is already big, isn't it?
Oh, my God!
Avro is the best!
Isn't it?
It's so cute.
I'm going to cut it.
It feels good.
It's so cute.
Look at this.
It's so soft.
I'm good at it.
Are you tired?
It's okay.
Oh no!
Let's go to another place.
Oh no! My neck.
Oh, no.
I can't hold it anymore.
Let's go over there.
Over there.
Can I take a bath?
Is it dangerous?
I'm so happy.
Don't touch me.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm so happy.
It's fun, isn't it?
Ah, it's so cold.
I'll wipe it for you.
Let's go outside.
It's so cold.
I'm so sorry.
More, more, more!
I want to sleep a lot!
I got a lot!
I'm so happy!
Look at this.
Let's go!
Oh, it's coming out!
Wait, wait!
No, don't, don't!
No!
I can't.
Look outside.
Really?
Should I take it out?
Let's go.
I'm scared.
It came out of the mat.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, it's coming out.
It came out.
I'm sorry.
Today is the second time.
I can't do it anymore.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Ah! Ah!
Ah, I'm sorry!
Ah, it feels so good.
Ah, it's so painful!
Ah, it's painful!
Ah, it's dangerous!
Ah!
Ah, it's amazing!
Ah, it's painful!
Ah!
Look at my eyes.
I'm scared.
Did you fall asleep?
He is licking his buttocks.
He is taking a nap.
Can I put it in?
It looks like it's going to work.
It's warm.
When did you hit me?
I'm so happy.
It came out.
I did it.
That was great.
Gin-chan is coming.
I'm so scared!
I'm so tired.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
Oh, amazing.
It's really slippery.
Amazing.
Katsuragi-kun, come here.
Oh, Katsuragi-saki!
Oh, oh, oh!
Oh, nice!
Oh, he's coming!
He's coming!
Oh, he's so cute!
Oh, oh, oh!
What's wrong with you?
I knew it was no good.
What are you doing?
I don't want to.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
I'm sorry!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Did you get it?
Are you ready?
Are you surprised?
It's hard, isn't it?
I don't know, I don't know.
Hey, Mai.
Yes?
What did you say?
I just said it.
Hey, glasses.
Glasses.
It's scary.
You're a coward.
How many are there today?
Two.
Two?
Is it not allowed?
I want to see more.
That's next to it.
Next to it?
Which one?
It's next to it.
It's hiding in the shade.
Where is it hiding?
2.5?
It's running away.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
What did you say?
I'm sorry.
You should say that it's not good.
Stop it!
It's not good.
I'm sorry.
Look at me.
Stop it!
Good boy!
Ah, it feels good.
Ah, it's dangerous.
Ah, it hurts more.
Amazing!
Oh, it came out.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
Are you okay?
It feels good.
It's scary.
Ah, I'm so scared!
I can't get up yet.
I'm sorry.
It's hard.
Move!
I'm a old man.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
Oh my God.
It's okay.
I'm fine.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
30 seconds left.
Give me your tail.
Tail.
Here, tail.
She is crying.
She is feeling good.
She is closing her eyes.
Is she closing her eyes?
She is going to close her eyes.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Go!
There's no more sheep!
I'll pet the sheep for you.
Everyone, come in here.
The end.
Come here.
If you are looking forward to it,
if you are not looking forward to it,
come here.
Come here.
I'm scared.
It's intense.
Let's go this way.
It's really scary.
Thank you.
Come here.
It's a little scary.
It's scary.
This is the place that I stand out the most.
All right.
Let the children go forward.
Everyone is looking forward to it.
Master!
Cool!
How many times did you cast this time?
I do not know.
Did you cast?
Oh!
It's amazing!
It's amazing, isn't it?
There may be one more time with this momentum.
Really?
Please look forward to it.
That's all.
It was Tomohiro Tomohiro in the bath.
Sparkle basketball.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
How many shots did you take?
One shot only.
How was it?
It was close.
Can you move away?
Excuse me.
I found a very big person.
Was there a very big person?
Yes.
Excuse me.
How many shots did you take?
It was the first time I was in the military.
The second time?
I don't know.
I went out twice today.
The second time.
The second time?
I didn't go out.
What did you go out?
The second time.
I went out twice.
Hata-no-san.
Yes.
How was it?
That one.
That's right.
It was the first time.
But the other members came in the middle of it.
Oh, right!
They thought I was busy.
That's right.
They changed my bag.
It was no good.
I'm happy.
I'll put Aichi in.
Aichi.
Really?
Aichi, you're really tight.
It's a girl!
No!
I can't stop bleeding!
It hurts!
Let me help you.
Wait!
You made me cry.
Thank you.
It's 10.40.
I am the president and Head of the House
I am the head of this shop
right
A drifter
Steering field
Hi, Lead konstruction
Is there anyone who thinks of me as a drifter?
I don't think so.
That's a good one.
What happened?
I don't know.
By the way,
what is the team like?
We are
from your team.
We are the ones
who will dominate.
Thank you.
I think you're cute.
Is there anything about me that is cute?
Yes, there is.
I'm a little happy.
Hey.
I would like to announce the results of this competition.
Anyway, both teams are very good
They can run super fast
That's really a great asset
They can perform outside of the box
so you will control they better
One more issue
I haven't seen your video yet
I don't know
I think so
How do you feel?
I don't know
You don't know?
You didn't show me your video
I don't know
It's a joke
So, I want you to practice with the feeling of launching
Let me go
Stand up
Look at your face
Say hello
Say hello?
Come here
Say hello
What is your name?
Shin
Let's change the name.
Let's do that.
It's not good.
I don't want to do it.
I understand.
Is it Oji-gi?
Yes.
Oji-gi.
Thank you.
It's strange.
You don't like it, do you?
Yes, I don't like it.
I don't like it.
Then.
It's mixed.
Go ahead, Kaz.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Wait, that was Chinko, wasn't it?
Welcome.
So, we're going to have some fun in the next scene.
Please use it more and more.
Thank you. Please look forward to it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's go home now.
Have a nice day.
Katsu-kun, you know what to do, right?
Yes.
You know what to do, right?
Do your best.
Thank you for your hard work.
You know what to do, right?
Katsu-san, go!
I don't want to drink either.
I'm not going to put it in.
I didn't put it in, so I was a little surprised.
By the way,
It's amazing.
From now on,
It's a little bit of a challenge.
Oh, line up.
I'm going to put it in.
I think it's working.
Yes, it's working.
Is it working?
Yes, it is.
Kanta & Haru-chan's
Let's do it!
What are you going to do from now on?
I'm going to do a shuffle rank.
I'm going to do it every time, but I'm going to do it again this time.
From this time on, I'm going to add one by one.
I will announce one by one.
For example, if you have a difference, you can make a difference while having sex.
What? Everyone?
Yes, everyone should cooperate.
I don't do that.
Everyone should cooperate.
Can't you make a difference?
What? Well...
Well, that's right.
Well, well, well.
Well, everyone, let's cooperate.
What we want to say is that
It's not just sex.
Everyone is encouraging and cooperating.
Let's make one art.
It's a warm welcome.
Is it okay, everyone?
Is that okay?
I'm the worst.
I don't think you know the best.
I know.
Do you understand?
You're a veteran, right?
Yes!
Now, I'll announce the winner!
Come on!
Ma!
Here you go!
Come on, come on, come on!
Are you ready?
Is it good around here?
I think it looks good.
It will start soon.
Do you like drawing?
Do you like it?
Are you ready?
Yes.
If you feel good, make more.
It's good.
You can do both.
It's like this.
Like this.
It's good.
You can't bend down here.
Up to here?
Like this.
It's good.
It's dangerous.
It's different even if you feel it.
What?
It's not the evil spirit.
It's around here.
Isn't it off?
It's off.
Isn't it off if I shoot it?
A little more.
If the remaining glue comes out, what should I do?
Then I'll put this tape and the tape on my nails.
Let's do 20 cm.
I'll do it.
Come on.
OK.
I'm nervous.
20 cm.
1 cm.
Can I get in?
Let's go inside.
Do you like it?
I like it.
It's different.
This is everyone's picture.
I have to eat it.
What is this?
Oh, but it seems to be.
It's like this.
I'm so happy to see you.
You're so cute.
Let's go.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
You'll get used to it soon enough.
Mocha? Mocha?
What's going on, Mama?
It's hot!
I'm so excited.
It feels good.
I want you to give me your tongue.
I'm scared.
It moved.
That's it.
They are terrible.
I'm scared.
It seems that there are people who say that they saw it.
Let's do it.
1,2
Ma
I will read the next letter.
You're here, you're here.
You're here, so you're wrong.
I'll put on my glasses.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
Can I lick your ears?
What is that?
Teacher?
What is this?
It's not working.
It's working.
Please continue.
I want to go home.
No, I can't.
You can do it.
I'm watching you.
Then lick the nipple.
No, no, no.
I'm watching you.
I'm going to put it in.
Can I put it in?
It's hot.
Wait, no, no, no.
There, there, there.
No, it hurts.
It hurts.
Wait, no, no, no.
No.
It's not good.
Wait.
It's okay.
Calm down.
I'm sorry.
Now, let's see the reaction.
40 people are crying.
Amazing.
3 people are crying at 10 o'clock in the front.
1, 2, 3.
I cried for 40 yen.
I cried.
The next word is...
The last word is...
I don't know where I am.
I feel like I'm going to puke.
It feels so good.
If you do it like this, it will look like this.
It's in the middle.
Look, Tamasaki-san is waiting for you.
Tamasaki-san is waiting for you.
Look, he's sitting down.
Ah, that's what you mean?
Come here.
Where are you going? Are you going to make a hole?
There's only one hole in the hole.
Is that so?
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Can I get it?
Ah! It's so nice!
Ah! Hamasaki-san, that's not it!
That's not it!
Ah!
You can do it, right?
Let's go!
One, two!
Go!
Do whatever you want!
It's so small.
Put it in your mouth.
I'll drink it all.
Really?
Is it okay to go?
It's so small.
It's so big.
How many times did you do it today?
Three times.
Three times? You did it three times?
Yes.
Then...
Wait, I can't concentrate. It feels good.
No, don't do that!
Ah!
I'm so tired.
Hey, hey, everyone, look at me.
When will you feel good when you look at me?
I can't do that.
What are you doing?
It's warm.
Pass, pass, pass, pass, pass.
Pass.
Oh, no.
Ouch!
Chinko is getting really stiff.
It's coming out.
It's coming out a lot.
The amount is getting smaller.
Will it come out?
It's coming out.
It's delicious.
Do you want to drink it?
Is it good?
Did you go?
Really?
It's dangerous.
It hurts.
Did you squeeze it?
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Wow!
I want to go to the bathroom.
What should I do?
Oh, my God.
I can't do this.
Ah!
Ah, it's so painful!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
More! More!
I'm so sorry.
Don't drink it.
It's okay, it's okay.
I will do it too.
Everyone, please stand in front of me!
Please stand in front of me.
This is the front of the female audience.
Everyone, please start.
Please start.
I will do it too.
Thank you very much for watching the first day of ORASU.
It's a long game, so I'll finish it with one shot.
Everyone, let's shake hands.
Ready!
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Good night!
Let's go.
Team Batako.
What's your team name?
Ikaregumi.
Kichigai.
Everyone is wearing different clothes.
Let's go.
Which one do you want to wear?
This one.
Let's go.
Yeah!
What is this?
This is the one.
I'm not a professional.
Everyone, let's do it.
Good, good.
This is cool.
Let's do it cool.
Cool.
This is cool.
It's over there.
Over there.
It's here.
It's a kick.
Are you okay?
Are you there?
Let's jump!
I was surprised!
Give me your tail!
Ah...
Is it okay if I put something in here?
Thank you!
Come closer!
No, no, no!
Hey!
Come closer!
Chuu!
Oh, no, no!
Hey!
Do you want to kiss?
You can lick it.
Lick it.
Is it good?
It's good, isn't it?
It's good.
Use your tongue more.
It's sweet.
Chikkun, don't hit me.
No.
Hit me.
Oh, no.
You're so erotic.
What are you doing?
Let's eat!
It's Seiza!
What are you going to do?
Here's the finished Doraemon!
Wait a minute!
It was good, wasn't it?
Seiza! Seiza!
Wait a minute.
What did you do?
It's Doraemon.
You can't do that.
Ah, yes, yes!
Bite me!
No!
Bite me.
Ah, yes!
Hey, you three.
Hey, don't start acting here!
Yes, everyone, one by one!
Yes!
Then this person is the mecha.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
You are making me dizzy.
Are you serious?
What are you doing?
Look at this.
What is this?
Look at this properly.
You shouldn't do that.
Everyone, look at this.
Hey, hey, hey.
You are making me dizzy.
This is crazy.
Don't look at it.
Look at it properly.
Wow, amazing.
If you say, don't look at it,
I'll put it in the sink.
I'm so happy.
Wait a minute.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm so happy.
Look at it.
It turned into a mess!
Oh my god!
Everyone is sleeping in the same bed today.
Congratulations!
If you're not tied up, lick it properly.
I have to do it.
Lick it.
I want to be sucked in.
You can do it.
You can't help it.
I'm so glad.
I'm so sorry.
It feels good.
Amazing.
Jin is getting stiff.
He's getting really stiff.
He's been repaid.
Please sit down.
Look at his tail.
He's getting wet.
I'll pet him.
He's getting tied up over there.
He's getting wet.
Wait a minute.
You're not even moving your body.
Let's tighten up your body.
Oh, it came off.
You can run away if you want.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's wrong?
You're being tightened up.
I'm fine if you're tightened up.
I'll help you.
I can't move my right hand.
I've been tightened up.
Here we go!
No?
It feels good when it's spilled.
OK!
Oh!
It was good!
It was the opposite, wasn't it?
Nice, Senpai!
I put out a lot.
I put out a lot today.
It's amazing.
While being double-footed.
Why did you guys become a couple?
Wow, that's great.
That's great.
I'm getting stiff.
But I'm here.
Hey, you!
Hey, you! What are you doing there?
What are you doing?
If you don't do it, you can't do it until the red card comes out, right?
Do it!
Run faster!
Otama-san, please get on.
It's a dress.
Slow down!
Oh, no!
Wait, wait, wait!
I'm going home.
Oh, no!
I'm scared!
It's hard!
Oh, no!
Let's have a good dream!
Aikaro! Aikaro!
Let's go! Let's go!
Bye bye!
What is this, Hata-chan?
Halem? The other way around, Halem?
Please enjoy with Hata-chan, everyone.
Hata-chan!
Anaru!
Bye bye!
Hey, Anaru!
I wonder if the boys are really sleeping now.
I want to go see how they are doing.
I wonder if they are sleeping.
Let's go.
Are you sleeping?
Wake up.
Can you hear anything in this room?
I don't know
I can't hear
Are you okay?
I can't see
I'm sorry
When I look this way, only my face is bright
I feel like I know who it is
What should I do?
Please tell everyone not to sleep
Please come early tomorrow
I can't sleep yet
Let's sit next to each other.
They are sleeping.
Baby is sleeping.
He is sleeping.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Why are you awake?
I'm so sorry.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
Why are you awake?
She woke me up.
If you don't go to bed early, it will be morning tomorrow.
It's not late tomorrow. It's early.
I have to go to bed early.
Can't you sleep excitedly?
Is it not enough?
I don't think so.
Then you have to check it.
I have to check it.
Look, look.
Are you still feeling better?
Show me.
Ah, you're feeling better already.
How many did you get today?
I got three.
You're still getting bigger even though you took off your pants?
Were you sleeping?
Are you having a good time?
Really?
Your cell phone is on.
You're getting bigger.
Stop it already.
Look.
You're so fat.
I'm telling you, I'm the one with the long neck.
You can't sleep at all with this.
He's saying, it's me.
It's not me, really.
What do you want to do?
What are you thinking about?
Do you want to sleep?
It's nice, isn't it?
What are you doing?
Hey, did you really sleep?
Really?
You're kidding.
Why are you so energetic?
What's wrong?
You're so energetic.
It's so cute.
What's wrong?
Are you happy?
It's coming again.
It's not happy.
It's happy.
He's saying it feels good.
I've done it twice today.
I feel like I've done it again.
I was surprised.
I was so excited.
What?
You were so excited that you stood up again?
You are such a good boy.
I was so excited.
You were excited?
You wanted to be excited?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I wonder if you'll be able to sleep right away if you feel good again.
You're so energetic.
Do you want to go home?
It's not a dream.
You woke up, didn't you?
He said he went out twice today,
so I'll let him go out more tomorrow.
I'll pet him a lot.
Is it delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
He's getting bigger.
He's energetic.
Are you happy?
Do you want to fight?
What do you want to do?
When I bite here, it becomes very sensitive.
Look!
You like it, don't you?
You like it too?
You want to be a bear?
You're cute
You're so soft
Do you want to eat it?
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry too.
Ah!
Hmm...
Ah...
Pfft...
Does it feel good?
Hmm...
I'm so sleepy.
Hmm?
Hmm...
Ah...
I'm so tired.
I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Sorry.
Don't cry.
I don't want to cry.
I've put a lot of stuff today.
Sorry.
How many times did you put it today?
I put it four times today.
Four times?
I think I can still do it.
You think you can still do it?
You can still do it!
You're so stubborn.
Take your pants off and do this.
You like him?
Oh, I was long gone.
I want to put it out tomorrow too, and I want to show it to you.
Let's sleep tonight as it is tomorrow.
Yes.
I want to show it to you too.
I'm going to sleep now.
I want to show it to you tomorrow too.
Let's sleep today.
Let's sleep.
How is it?
Why can we sleep?
Good night.
Can't sleep?
Yes.
Really?
Are you embarrassed?
But you felt good, didn't you?
Yes.
I love you.
I'm so excited.
I'll bring this to you tomorrow.
Thank you.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work.
See you later.
It's hard on your stomach.
Good night.
Bye-bye, Kotomi.
See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow!
But tomorrow's...
Tomorrow's prey is going to be two people.
See you tomorrow!
Oh, really? Then I'll stay.
Bye-bye!
Let's close the door.
Then I'll stay.
Bye-bye!
Good night!
Say bye-bye to everyone.
That's it for today. We're going to sleep too.
Good night.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! They are making me cry!
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
I have to sleep!
I'm sleepy.
Wow!
Nooo!
Everybody, cheer up!
Let's go!
OK!
OK
Let's go!
Do your best!
OK
Let's go!
Let's go for the first time.
Yes!
Good!
It's warm!
Micro, micro.
It looks heavy.
It's heavy.
Are you filming something?
Of course.
The sun is shining.
It's bright.
Great!
Bye-bye!
Okay!
Let's go!
Right arm, right arm, 3, 2, 1.
Good.
Ichi, your hips are a little too high.
Can you show us your hips while moving?
Let's go!
Let's try it.
Go ahead.
Right arm, right arm, 3, 2, 1.
OK, 1, 2, 3.
Great.
Are you ready?
OK, 1, 2, 3.
Ready?
I'm holding a swimsuit.
Are you holding a swimsuit?
It's important to feel like you're sticking out a little bit.
Thank you.
Me too.
Ready, set, go!
Noogie's Fan Festival!
Bako Bako Bus Tour 2014!
Let's go, everyone!
OK!
The first game is to find the ultimate couple.
First of all, we will choose a couple with only the correctness of each other in the Manjin feeling of Bakobasu.
Next, let's see if you can make a couple in both the inside and the outside.
Let's start with the munching feeling.
Please line up in a row.
I can see your feet.
Are you OK?
I'm tired.
Please crouch down.
Crouch down.
Are you OK?
You can move.
I'll get off the curtain at the same time as I open the door.
OK?
OK.
Open!
This is so funny!
He's laughing! He's laughing!
Everyone, please be quiet!
He's laughing!
This is so funny!
Can I touch it?
Yes, you can!
He's scared!
I think there are different shapes and different types of people you like.
I'd like you to think about that while you're at it.
Everyone, there are different types of people you like.
You don't want to do it, do you?
I don't know.
You should be energetic.
I don't know if I'm energetic or not.
That's right.
Be energetic.
You should be energetic.
If we say, be energetic, she will be energetic.
Be a honest girl.
I'm lost.
Ah!
My back is shaking.
Wow!
It's really shaking.
Rin-Pin!
Yes.
Wait!
I'm lost.
It's really strange.
Number 2.
I'm lost.
My back is shaking.
Why is it so big?
This is fun!
Wow!
It's a little wet.
Are you ready?
If you're a little worried, come over here.
We have a teacher here.
Please write down your name and number.
I think it's better to have a healthy morning, isn't it?
I wonder what it is.
It's almost time to finish.
What should I do?
I think the most useful thing in a manco is...
the most useful thing in a chinko.
I'm done.
Please give it to me.
It's difficult.
Is it that difficult?
But everyone has the same number.
It's okay.
Yes.
I see.
Is it okay?
This is a collection.
I'm a middle school student.
Okay, now we're going to change the course.
Please turn around.
Okay.
We're going to do the reverse version.
Okay, everyone, please stand by.
Chome-chome, open!
Oh!
Great!
Okay.
Okay, the camera is filming now.
I'm sure everyone is enjoying this, right?
Yeah.
It's going to take a while, isn't it?
Wow.
How is it, everyone? Take a look.
How is it?
Is it different?
It's different.
It's serious.
I'm sorry.
It's hard to see a bank that's easy to see.
It's a bit stuck.
It's stuck.
How is it?
Everyone, come closer.
Are you tired?
Can I take a look?
Not yet?
Not yet, not yet.
Oh.
Yes.
Please search for the one you like.
This is Don't Touch Me.
Is that okay?
It means you won't touch it if you break it.
Please tell me your favorite number.
I'll close up.
Number 3?
Which number do you want?
Number 3.
What? Number 3?
Number 3?
I see. Who is number 3?
Who is number 3?
I see.
I said I was happy.
Even if you say you like it, I'm sure you have a lot of feelings.
I'm a little worried about this.
Number 12.
Number 12?
I'm number 12 too.
Why?
What's the reason?
I feel like it's coming out like this.
It's coming out like this.
Is it easy to put in?
It's easy to put in.
You don't want to do half of it, do you?
There's a will to never show it.
It's coming out of the hole.
You don't want to show it, do you?
There was a lot of consciousness that it wasn't in the middle.
After that, try to get wet a little.
Are you all right?
Isn't it better not to get a cold?
Yes, please hold the staff.
What?
Isn't it a little wet in the middle?
Hey, it's fluffy.
I don't know if it's because the weather is bad.
I'm going to blow it a little.
It's fun if you blow it.
It's stupid.
Is there anything you're interested in?
You did it on number 14.
Hold on.
Even number 14 has a round butt.
You're good.
I'm not.
You're a girl.
It's time to enter.
Number 14, you've done a great job.
Which number do you want?
Say it.
Number 12.
Now, what's next?
This time, there are no stiff people.
Yes.
I see.
Like this.
Like this, like this, like this, like this.
Ah, this time it's different.
This is the same ball.
If you multiply it, it's the same.
It's the same.
No. 9 has entered.
Oh, I see.
Well then, the results will be announced later.
Goodbye. Thank you very much.
I will announce the results later.
Well then, everyone, the location has changed.
From now on, free time.
Let's start the talk time.
Start!
Please.
Don't stop.
There is no camera like this.
Thank you.
Shoshin-Gumi?
Shoshin-Gumi.
I'm sure you'll be the monster of this time.
Thank you.
I got this set.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
I'm Midori.
I saw a black one.
This is different.
I'm sorry.
And it's the opposite.
I see.
Oh, I see.
I like this feeling.
I knew it.
I want to sleep again.
You're right.
It's not clean.
I knew it.
Hi, I'm Yasuyosu, a girl.
I'm in charge of distribution.
I think it's better to do it when you're in trouble.
I often do it in the video.
Really?
I'm really surprised.
I've done it once.
This is the fifth time, so it's good.
That's right.
You've been here since you were little, haven't you?
Yeah, I've been here since I was little.
Nice to meet you.
This is for girls.
This is for boys.
It's time to confess!
It's really exciting.
Are you excited?
Yes, I'm excited.
Ladies and gentlemen, from now on,
please take the man you want to confess to on the slider and confess.
If the man is okay,
please come down the stairs together.
If you can't, please slide the slider.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Please wait a moment.
Let's go.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Where are you going?
Let's go.
Yes.
Are you serious?
Let's go.
Go for it.
Everyone is watching.
Please wait a moment.
Great.
Everyone is looking forward to it.
They think it's me.
I feel like I'm going to cry.
Don't worry.
Give it your best shot.
Do you know your name?
Say it out loud.
Can I bring her?
Of course.
Let's do it.
Do your best!
Everyone's nervous!
I don't want to slide!
I'm going to do the shooting!
I don't want to!
Raise your voice and show us your national flag!
Go!
Can you step back a little?
Yes.
Raise your voice.
Well...
This is bad!
Do your best.
Well...
I've heard a lot of things about you.
They talked about a lot of things and made me feel excited.
When we were eating, they noticed how nervous I was.
I had a great time.
If you don't mind, please come down the stairs with me.
How is it?
Please.
Yaaay!
Ok, please stand up.
No, I can't.
Yaaay!
Ok, let's go with the two of you.
Wow!
Ok.
You can call her by her name or call her by her name.
Go ahead.
Are you embarrassed?
Yes, I am.
What if she rejects you?
Yuki, please hold her hand.
Yes.
You don't have to turn around.
Go ahead.
Here?
Over there.
Thank you very much.
Please say something.
Thank you for talking to me.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
Thank you so much.
Let's sing together.
I'm so excited.
Natsume, please sing.
Really?
Do you know her name?
You can call her by her name or bring her here.
Then I'll bring her here.
Go ahead.
Who is it?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Who is it?
You two.
Please confess.
Wait a minute.
Who is it with you?
What's going to happen?
Really? I'm a little nervous.
Are you nervous?
Yes, I am.
I like your face.
Thank you.
I said I was M at first.
I'm S, so I chose it because I like people who can tease me.
Thank you very much.
I'm going. Where is the sleeper?
Let's go!
Oh no! It's cold!
I'm glad you're good at it.
You know the name and the face, right?
Yes, I do.
You can drink it or put it on your head.
I've taken care of this.
Whose turn is it?
Yes, I'll do it.
Are you ready?
Applause!
Wait a minute.
You can do it here.
Go ahead.
My back hurts.
What should I do?
Okay, please show us your reaction.
She was very kind and talkative.
I like her appearance.
I thought she would be a good match for me.
Please come down the stairs with me.
Please.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You can call me by my name.
Please.
I'll call your name.
Ichi-san, right?
Yes.
That's good.
Wait a minute.
You two, please.
I'm so happy.
Okay.
Let's start.
I'll start.
Well, I talked to him with courage, and he said yes!
Let's do it together!
Yes, please!
Thank you!
Are you ready?
Is it good?
Yeah.
Here you go.
You can drink it.
You can eat it.
Here you go.
Ryu!
Wait a minute.
Here you go.
Wow.
You can put it on.
Here you go.
Well, yesterday, Yu told me that he wanted to be developed by Sakurai-san, so I wanted to develop it.
Please give me Shiofuki and Anaru.
Please.
I did it!
Have you decided?
You can call me by my name.
I'm going.
Please.
I thought it would be nice to have a gentle face.
Let's do it together.
Please.
Thank you.
What are you going to do?
Yes.
Are you going?
Let's go.
Please.
What's wrong?
I'm going.
Are you going?
Let's go.
It's too dramatic.
Hama-san, do you want to read it?
Do you want to read it?
Please come out with the person you think you are.
Oh, it's a new pattern.
Oh, my God.
Please do it again.
Please come out with the person you think you are.
I'm sorry, I'm a husky.
Why did you come this way?
It's pretty late.
Let's do it one more time with text 3.
Okay.
Okay, for now...
For now, please go up.
Please stand up.
It was a new pattern.
Well, it's kind of a dirty pattern, isn't it?
Go up, go up.
Wait a minute, isn't there anyone who can do that?
Hey.
Okay.
I can't do it.
What do you want to say to your fans?
It's a serious story.
I've never confessed my feelings in my life.
I don't know how to confess my feelings.
I want to talk to you today and have sex with you.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Are you ready?
Is there any left?
Yes, there is.
It's perfect.
You can call her by her name.
Okay.
Here you go.
A little more.
Thank you.
Shall we start?
Well then.
Yes.
I've decided from the first impression.
Thank you.
Yes.
Please.
Do it for me.
Wow, cheating.
Yes.
I want to talk more and do more erotic things.
Let's do it.
Who's going to do it?
Yay!
Fall!
It's cold!
Get off the boat!
Let's go together.
Together?
I want to go too.
It's so cold!
It's amazing!
Here we go!
Are you ready?
Are there any left?
Of course!
Let's go!
You can pull it in or pull it out.
I can't remember the name.
I just made up my mind.
I see.
I'll show you.
Go ahead.
You did it.
It's a great choice.
Wait a minute.
Please put it on top.
It's a great choice.
I'm so nervous.
Really?
What should I do?
Let's go back to the starting line.
Yes.
Just now,
I was late.
I was saying yes, but I was late.
I was told no.
I was going back.
I thought it was cute.
Please edit it.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
I did it.
There are three people left.
There are three people left, right?
Yes.
Let's go.
I'm shaking.
You know that there is no pattern of one person, right?
I don't know.
Wait a minute, if you make a sound, which one will be dropped?
Please call your name and pull it.
Here you go!
Who do you think it is?
Oh!
Wait a minute!
It's the two of you!
You made a good voice.
It was an unexpected development.
Which one will win?
I'm getting nervous.
My heart is beating so fast.
My voice is shaking.
Well, the bus was next to me.
I was happy that you talked to me.
Well, what should I do?
Yesterday's EDGE was great.
I want to do it again.
I want to do it again!
Thank you very much.
I'm so nervous.
When I did the warm-up yesterday,
I felt really good.
I know I can't beat Hikaru-chan.
I want to have sex with Abeno again.
Please.
I was rejected for the first time in two years.
Are you going to wear this?
Yes
Thank you everyone
See you later
Bye bye
I'm scared
My nose hurts
I was hit by a car.
You are the last one.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Please.
You can call my name.
You can pull me.
Go ahead.
I want to know more about Mana.
I'm always looking at her.
I'm so excited.
I can't stand it anymore.
I want to be with her.
What do you think?
Please.
I did it!
Let's do it!
We did it!
What's going on?
I'm so happy!
Congratulations!
The two couples have succeeded in their marriage.
Thank you very much.
We will announce the final result of the final round.
The result will be announced shortly.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
So everyone, Manchin Couple's ultimate couple has been born!
This time, we're going to announce the winner!
We're going to announce it now!
Ta-da!
First, we're going to announce the boy!
Zuka.
Please come to the center.
There are some people who think it's good to see his penis.
Please take a look at it later.
You can see it later.
But...
Miss Makenara!
This is the final song!
Both of you!
Look at this face!
How is it?
I'm happy. It's the best!
It was good, wasn't it?
Thank you.
This is the best costume ever.
For the two of you, please look behind you.
We have prepared a special gold bed for you.
If you say, which one is it, and if you say, which one is it, it's because you're the ultimate couple.
Wow, that's amazing.
Then the two of you, please.
Is it unfair?
It's unfair.
Well, it can't be helped, it can't be helped.
Please go up.
Put your hands together like this.
It's a little awkward, isn't it?
That's right, that's right.
Put your hands together like this.
Okay, from the end,
shall we go to the usual Daeranko?
Let's go to the restaurant!
Hey!
I'm going to eat a spiny lobster!
This is a small restaurant!
This is our food!
Hey!
Hey, stop it!
Stop it!
What's the most difficult one?
Excuse me.
I have made the name of my wife, Hamehameha, come to life!
Thank you!
Oh my god!
It's so bad!
It's so bad.
We're done.
It's really done.
It's over.
What are we going to do?
Let's get out of here.
Shut up!
I want to say something!
Listen!
What is it?
My grandma told me that
if you put a lot of players in this deck,
you can beat the king of Hamehameha.
What is it?
Is it true?
Yes!
Good! Good!
To save the world,
let's eat a lot of food
and defeat him!
Yes!
Who is he?
Let's all do
a big round to save the world!
Let's do a big round!
Yes!
Start!
I'm tired.
I'm tired of this play.
It's very dangerous.
The baby is trying to get out of the way.
Do you feel better?
It tickles.
Oh, it hurts!
Oh, it feels good.
It hurts.
It's hot.
You're so cute.
Can you see?
How many times have I kissed you?
You can't do that.
I'm not kidding.
You don't have to do that.
You're kissing your wife.
It went in.
It feels good.
Oh, it's in.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, I'm crying.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy, too.
It's tight.
Ah!
Aw, it feels good!
Good girl, tender boy.
I'm okay.
Oh, sorry. Look at me.
Stop it.
Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Stop it.
Hey, hey.
It hurts.
It feels good.
Did you sleep?
It hurts.
It's been a while.
Stop! Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
Are you okay?
I want to go home.
What are you doing?
I want to play with you.
What do you want to do?
What's wrong?
I have to eat a little bit.
I have to eat something.
What do you want to do?
I'm going to put it in.
One, two.
I'm sorry.
Are you ready?
To defeat HameHameHadai,
I will defeat HameHameHadai.
Until the last drop.
The last one.
I slept a lot.
OK, OK!
Go! Go!
It's gone.
I got it. Please.
I got it.
I'm scared.
Oh my god!
It's stuck here.
It's too hard.
It's melted.
Is it that hard?
It's hot.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so tired.
Do you feel like taking a bath?
I'm so hot.
Yay!
I did it!
Here I go!
One, two, three!
Wow, you're pretty good!
You're right!
Don't cry.
Ouch!
No!
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
It hurts. It hurts.
Go home, go home, go home.
Wow, that's a lot.
Are you full?
I'm scared.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
I feel good.
Let's take a picture.
Do you want to eat together?
Let's eat together.
You can do it, you can do it!
It's hard to take a picture because there are so many people in front of me.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
I feel like this.
Look at me.
Haichan.
I'm sorry.
Ouch! Ouch!
It's so close!
I'm going to stop them.
It's coming out.
Let's get out of here!
I'm hungry.
I want to grow up.
I'm so hungry.
How do you feel?
I feel like I'm getting bigger.
I can't do it anymore.
I'm so scared.
I'm sorry.
Say it louder!
It's a big one.
Run away!
It's coming out.
Let's go!
Let's go inside.
Let's go together.
Bye-bye!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I want to lick the chinchu.
Ah, it feels good.
It feels good.
I want to lick the chinchu.
Oh, no.
Go, go, go, go, go.
I'm so tired.
I feel terrible...
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
You are a good boy.
Are you okay?
Don't cry.
It's okay.
Stop!
Black pergunta 1
Black pregunta 2
A good challenge
From this part
I didn't suffer
Yep
From this part
Oh, no, no, no, no!
It's a little too much.
It's too much.
What is this?
It's the other way around.
10 seconds left!
I'm scared.
This is fun.
You have ten seconds left.
I'm scared.
It's a running car.
I can't stand it.
Ah!
Thank you very much.
What happened?
It's not like that.
That's right.
You have to get closer.
Is that so?
What happened?
Thank you very much.
Please put your face together.
Mako Bus is the best!
The best!
3rd place!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Bakumatsu is the best!
Thank you for your hard work.
I wanted to do more.
It was fun.
My legs are shaking.
I almost fell asleep.
I'm sorry.
Three people.
I put it in my stomach.
How was it?
It was so much fun.
Can I put it in my stomach?
Yes, you can.
Really?
It's cold.
I'm scared!
What is this?
The rhythm is good.
It's fun.
I'm 45 years old.
It's my second time today.
I wanted to do more.
Who is it?
I touched something with my hand.
What?
It's not a bump!
It's a bump!
I'm filming.
I feel like I've done it today.
I can sleep well.
That's right.
Thank you.
Let me find it.
My back is right.
Thank you very much.
Pata-chan!
Pata-chan is here!
What?
Ega-san!
I got it!
Thank you so much!
Look, I'm happy that you got it.
One more time!
Okay, one more time!
Okay!
Look, the other side!
Let's go!
Ready, go!
Thank you so much!
Well, I did a lot of work today.
I don't know.
Why?
I don't know anything.
One, two.
Bakobasu.
BAKOBASU
Yay! Couple! Couple!
Yay!
One, two, three!
Our bodies and hearts became naked!
BAKOBASU is the best!
Thank you!
We became a happy couple!
Thank you.
Do you love me?
Yes, I do.
Thank you for the food.
How about you?
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm so happy that you're happy.
We became a good couple.
It was fun.
It was fun. Thank you.
Thank you.
We became a good couple.
Yay! Thank you so much!
Makobashi is the best!
The best!
We made a couple!
Yay!
Makobashi was so much fun!
It was the best!
Thank you!
We became a perfect couple!
Yay!
The next challenger is Arata in front of the TV!
One, two!
Makobashi is the best!
Bye-bye!
Oh my god!
It feels so good!
Bakumatsu is the best!
Yay!
It was fun! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Did you enjoy it?
It was fun!
I want to come again!
Thank you very much!
I made a plan for the first time in my life!
I got it!
One, two!
Bakumatsu is the best!
Thank you very much!
We had a great time today!
Makobasu is the best!
This is what's left.
We just became a couple.
We will be happy from now on.
Makobasu is the best!
Fusion Ha!
I love Bakobasu!
Thank you! It was fun!
Bakobasu is the best!
Bye bye!
It's so hot!
Makobashi is the worst!
It's been a very hot two days.
How was it for the two of you?
Wasn't it hard for you?
That's right.
This time, it was the front and the back.
I was nervous at the beginning, so I thought it was going to be tough.
Well, it was tough this time, but everyone had a great time this time.
It was a lot of fun.
As Hata-chan said, everyone had a good time.
I was the first one to be left to the supervisor.
I like people who get excited rather than pulling it out, so I think I was excited for these two days.
Everyone was excited, wasn't it?
If you want to go out, please go to this place.
It may not come out, but if you want to come out, please do it until here.
Then you may be able to come out.
It may be a very fun two-day trip.
So everyone, see you next time.
Good-bye.
Bye-bye.
This is Tsubomi.
This time, I had a lot of fun.
It was the first time I met a good girl, but I was happy that everyone was kind to me.
I was able to get along well with the boys and had a good time.
I want to go out again. Thank you very much.
I'm Ayu Sakurai.
The last Daeranko, the Daeranko where everyone gathers,
As expected of Aya, I was overwhelmed.
It was a very fun 2nd period.
Thank you.
I'm Kanaeruka.
This time, I was able to participate in the Bakowa Bakowa Tour for the first time.
At first, I didn't know anything.
It was really fun to actually start it.
It became a memory.
It was fun.
Thank you so much.
I'm Kanaruka.
Bye-bye.
Hi, I'm Hata-chan.
I came to Wakubasu this time.
I didn't do any spy work.
I was having fun.
I had a lot of fun.
I hope I can come to Wakubasu again next year.
At that time, thank you everyone.
Thank you very much this time.
Bye bye!
I'm Oto Hananase.
This is my first time in Bakobasu.
I was so nervous because it was my first time shooting at a parking lot.
It was a lot of fun.
Bye!
I'm Aichi Kotoe Uehara Ai.
This is my third time in Bakobasu.
Every year, the actresses are very luxurious, and they are all great actresses.
I had a great time this year, and I had a lot of fun.
I would like to appear again next year.
At that time, please apply to Bakobasu a lot.
Bye bye.
I'm Maya Kawamura.
This time, I was very nervous because it was my first time participating in Bakobasu.
I had a hard time, but it was a very good memory, and I think it was a good sense of accomplishment that I was able to do it with everyone.
Thank you very much. It was fun.
Bye-bye.
I'm Megumi Shina.
Did you watch this video from the beginning to the end without missing it?
It was amazing.
What I just thought was, how many shots did I get?
If you don't know, please count and tell me.
Please look forward to next year's MAKOBASHI.
Thank you very much.
I'm KURUBU GIMIKAN.
This is the first time I've been on MAKOBASHI.
I don't think there's anyone else who's as fun as I am.
I'm Maki Hara Mara.
I debuted with a famous girl.
I've been working with her for less than a year now.
I'm very happy.
I've had a lot of opportunities to interact with fans.
I had a lot of fun today.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
I'm Ichika Kamihata.
This is my first time to participate in Mako Bus.
It's my first time to film with so many girls.
At first, I was so nervous that my legs were shaking.
I had a lot of fun for two days.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
I'm Mao Hamasaki.
I'm Ichika-chan and this is the first time I'm taking part in this event.
I was able to experience a lot of things that I couldn't experience before.
It was a lot of fun to ride the water slide with everyone.
Please let me know what you think about it.
I'm Hikaru Kona.
This is my first time taking part in this event.
It was my first time at ZUK-SHI and I had a lot of different experiences.
It was like a girls' high school and I had a lot of fun.
I had a lot of fun talking to a lot of people.
Of course, it was a lot of fun.
If I have a chance again, I want to participate in something like this!
Yes!
Bye bye!
I'm Riku Minato.
It was my first time to take a bus.
At first, I didn't know what kind of shooting it was.
It was hard, but it was fun.
I was bitten by a bug.
When I woke up in the morning, it was like this.
Please check it out on VTR.
I think I had a lot of fun.
If you like, please try to take a bus next time.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
I'm Yuki Natsume.
I was more nervous than I imagined.
But each one of us had a lot of fun.
I had a lot of fun interacting with other people.
Thank you all for participating.
Please let me know what you think about the show.
See you later. Bye bye.
I'm Abeno Miku.
This time...
Wait, this is embarrassing.
This was my first time participating in the show.
There were some friends and some friends I met for the first time.
I had a lot of fun while watching erotic scenes of various people.
I want to do various things and have a lot of fun, and I'm looking forward to your feedback on Twitter.
So, bye-bye!
Thank you for your hard work.
I just want to improve my clothes a little more.
I always wonder if I can't do it at the same time.
I'd like you to upgrade the box a little more.
That's what I think.
That's all.
I also wanted a shell swimsuit at the end.
I'd like you to make my outfit like this.
Thank you very much.
I'm Takkun.
Today, including yesterday and today, I had five shots.
It was one of my dreams, so it was a very enjoyable memory.
Thank you very much.
It's been a while. I've been here five times since yesterday.
I think I had a really wonderful time. Thank you very much.
I'm Takapon.
I shot four shots in two days yesterday and today.
It was a two-day trip that I fell in love with Yui Hatano.
I hope I have another chance.
I'm Ichi.
I shot five shots yesterday and today.
Thank you very much to the director and staff who provided me with such a dreamy place.
I'm Kaz King. I shot 5 shots in 2 days. I want to train from tomorrow and prepare for next year's Bakobas. That's all.
Thank you very much.
I'm Shikorin. I couldn't leave a good result with 3 shots, but I was able to get along with my favorite actress.
Thank you for the good birthday present.
Goodbye.
I'm Suzukawa. I shot 4 shots yesterday.
I was chosen by Gowako Meadey-Walland, and I was chosen by the last feeling couple.
It was a journey that I was able to use all my luck. It was very fun. Thank you very much.
I'm Yu. I had a three-shot shot on the second day.
After I went, I was about to die, but I couldn't blow it, so I would like to participate in the project again and work hard to get the death blow.
Hi, I'm PUSHI. I'm here for the first time in two days.
I feel like the world has changed a lot since I came to Bako Bus.
So, Bako Bus fans, please come to Bako Bus.
I'm going to train hard so that I can come back next year.
Let's go to Bako Bus together.
Thank you.
I'm TAKETO.
I came here for the first time since yesterday and today.
It was my first time at Bako Bus.
It was a great experience. Thank you very much.
I'm Shinya. I shot 4 times in 2 days.
I saw such beautiful actresses in the video,
but when I actually saw them, they were even more beautiful.
I was able to get involved with such women.
It was a really famous time. Thank you very much.
I'm Harubo.
I was able to shoot 6 times in 2 days.
I was able to make a trip that will remain in my memory for the rest of my life.
Thank you very much.
I'm Yoppi. I was able to launch 7 shots in 2 days.
Of course, Karami, but everyone who traveled with me was a very good person, so I had a lot of fun for 2 days. Thank you very much.
I won. I launched 4 shots in 2 days.
It was the first time I was on the run, but I experienced the best run with this member. Thank you very much.
I'm Hiro. I was able to launch 3 shots in 2 days.
I was surrounded by young girls and I had a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
I was able to shoot four shots in two days.
I was able to have a very happy and fun time.
I was really happy. Thank you very much.
I was able to shoot only four shots.
I made a personal mistake and I was involved in the middle.
I was really bothered by the director and the staff.
I was able to have a great time for two days.
Thank you very much.