For the sake of this day, all the actresses who made the manko wet will gather here.
Thank you!
I'm sorry!
Who is the editor?
I'm the one who changed
So cool
Thank you very much.
I'm Ichikawa Kamihata.
I'm No.2.
Thank you very much.
This is the 7th place in Kawamura Mayan, thank you very much.
This is the 13th place in Okaeruka.
My hair is so thin that I can't pull it.
Ta-da!
Hinato Riku, 5th place.
Ta-da! Kanna Hikaru, 14th place.
Ameno Miku, 10th place.
I'm Tsurugi Mikan.
I'm No.15.
I'm Masaki Mao.
What's your number?
Number 6
Number 12
Number 16
Natsume Yuki is the 4th.
I'm Megumi Shinobu.
No.1
Here we go
No.2
No.3
No.4
No.5
No.6
Hata-chan, look at this!
Yes!
Good bye!
This...
I thought you were going to say it!
You're going to say it?
Here it is!
Hata-chan, it's your turn!
Onee-chan, you can do it!
What is it?
Oh?
Oh my god!
It's so close!
Excuse me.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning.
Who is the most beautiful?
I am.
Everyone, please take care of me.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Number 13.
Welcome to the MAKO-MAKO Festival after a year!
We're going to hold a lot of events, so be prepared!
One, two!
Congratulations!
It's done!
Hi, I'm Yui Hatano, and I'm going to be your supervisor.
And I'm Ayu Sakurai.
Nice to meet you!
Yay!
Okay, let's start with the title call.
Ready, set...
Moody's Fan Gratitude Bako Bako Bus Tour
And...
Please shout it out.
Okay.
Ready, set...
Moody's Fan Gratitude Bako Bako Bus Tour
Let's go!
Yay!
Mako Bus!
Now, please explain the rules of Mako Bus to this person.
Hello, I'm Shonokoro.
Thank you.
Now, please explain the rules.
Thank you very much.
I would like to introduce you.
This time, I would like to introduce you to Bakobako Land, which is somewhere in the southern island.
There are 16 people to be introduced, but
Injury, illness, E.T., etc.
If you do something that the actress dislikes and are watched by the staff or the director,
you will be replaced as a back-boxer.
In any case, please follow the rules and get along with each other.
This time, there is a ninja in the back of the bus, so there is a spy.
The bad guys will go on a trip to training.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Yes
Let's introduce ourselves
Yes, let's go
1, 2, 3
Self-introduction of Fela-Chu
Together
1, 2, 3
Self-introduction of Fela-Chu
Please introduce yourself to the man next to you
Ken-Ken-san, please introduce yourself.
Got it. Let's start with the first one.
Everyone, the seat belt is OK.
Let's start introducing ourselves.
Let's start with the first one.
I'm Hata-chan.
Please tell us your name.
I'm Yui Hata, who is called Hata-chan.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a girl today, so I'm the first one to be stolen today.
Thank you very much.
Hata-chan, how many people do you have in total?
Of course I have 0 people in total.
What are the three points?
The three points are beautiful skin and this high nose.
High nose?
Then from the side.
Everyone says it's straight, but it's not straight.
Really?
Look, look.
I didn't.
Then there is no difference.
Yes.
Then.
Is it okay?
It's okay.
It's pretty fast.
What are the charms of your skin, Hata-chan?
It's pretty.
What are the other things?
I have a deep skin, and I have a beautiful入.
You have a beautiful入.
Yes!
You should have seen it.
You should have searched the internet.
No, I shouldn't have.
Just search it later.
What is it?
Is it a beauty?
I don't know.
What is it?
It's a beauty.
Do you have a beauty?
Let's take a look.
How much is it?
Please tell me the number.
From the middle.
From the middle?
59 from the middle.
88 from the middle.
89 from the bottom.
What's your point?
Your beautiful skin.
Don't ask me that.
Please give it to me.
When you were a kid, you must have been happy with boys.
Do you have a point?
You were drooling, but you were Lucy.
Yes, I am Lucy.
So, what is your name?
I'm Takkun.
Takkun.
Thank you.
Is it good?
It's the 10th one.
Please eat it.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
You have 10 seconds left.
Go!
It was a good start.
Yes, it was.
But it was so close.
Yes.
Look.
What was your third point?
The down points are beautiful flowers and...
Thank you very much!
Let's move on to the second place.
Please tell us your name.
My name is Ichika Kamihata.
Call me Ichi.
It's a pretty difficult word.
Look at this.
Kamihata.
They say you can't read it.
I'll look it up later.
It's okay.
Let's go.
Please tell us your name.
My name is Takapon.
Takapon?
Thank you very much. Let's get started.
Let's start from the pedagogy course.
Please tell me the size.
The foot size is 83 from the top.
60.
84.
Long tongue.
It's really long.
What about the skin? Is it beautiful?
The skin is white.
It's white.
What's your hobby?
My hobby is cooking.
What are you good at?
I'm good at paella.
I tried it recently, but it didn't go well.
That's right.
Chocolate cake.
It's difficult.
I'm the best in Heian.
What's the average number of people?
The average number of people is...
Six people.
Six people?
There's no reason to do that.
There's a lot.
It's getting bigger.
It's good if you put it out.
Oh, it's big.
What should we do, everyone?
If you put it out now, it's a waste.
You shouldn't think about that.
I'm glad.
It's like mochi rice, isn't it?
It's very juicy.
It's very crispy.
It's 10 seconds, right?
10 seconds?
3...2...1...
It's over. What a shame.
What a shame.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
I'm embarrassed.
What is this?
Thank you very much.
That's it. Thank you very much.
Let's move on to the third question.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Oto Hananose.
Thank you very much.
I heard that you wanted to show your chest in an interview.
What should I do?
Are you confident?
No, I'm not.
Cheers!
New version.
Is this okay?
That's not it.
What is it?
You're not satisfied with this, are you?
Can I take it out?
Please.
Don't look at me.
I'm sorry.
Can you touch it?
Information.
What?
What is the size of the three?
The three sizes are
from the top,
83, 56,
83.
How do you touch it?
It's crazy.
Can you introduce yourself?
My name is Yu.
Now, please introduce yourself.
Please start.
Thank you.
You look like you just got out of the shower.
Now, please.
Okay.
You look like you just got out of the shower.
I'm not good at it.
Are you a member of the Seikantai?
Are you talking about me?
I'm a member of the Seikantai.
I'm Uchimomo.
It's a rare place, isn't it?
Isn't that the best place?
The best place is Kuri.
Of course, I'm a big fan of you.
Do you like to be licked?
I like to be licked.
I see.
Do you have any experience?
Experience?
Yes.
About three people.
I don't want to be licked.
Do you have any experience?
Most of the time.
Thank you very much.
How about you, Asafela?
Asafela, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Don't look at me.
Number 4, please.
I'm Yuki Natsume.
Thank you very much.
What's your charm point?
Charm point?
I'm a great hitter.
It's not like that.
When I sleep, I usually show my front teeth.
Isn't your butt a charm point?
What?
Your butt.
My butt? My butt is a charm point.
Like your gums?
My gums are a charm point.
Then show me.
Now?
Can I do it now?
You can do it now.
It's getting harder and harder.
It's not like that.
I can't see it well.
I can't see it.
Which one is it?
See?
Wait a minute.
I can brag about this.
It's a good way to wear it.
I'm a heart-shaped manga.
That's right.
It's a good way to subscribe to the world.
Let's start the self-introduction of the main character.
Yes, please.
That's why I kicked Rui.
Who are you?
I'm Hiro.
Hiro-san.
Nice to meet you.
Please start.
Neck, back, chest, and...
I like mangos the most.
What's your hobby?
My hobby is to go for a walk with my lover.
What kind of dog do you have?
I have Pomeranian.
Do you like Pomeranian?
I want to eat too!
Did you force yourself to eat?
I'm a boy after all.
It's better to have a golden egg.
I see.
You can do it if you're lucky.
That's right.
You won't stop, right?
It's hot.
10 seconds left.
2, 1.
Too bad.
It's a pity.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Riku Minato.
Nice to meet you.
Can I tell you the size of the foot?
The foot size is
from the top
Is it 105?
Is it okay?
It's okay.
Listen to me.
Is it okay?
It's okay, but it's small.
I want to lick it later.
How is it?
It's pretty.
Wow.
How is it?
105 cm.
105 cm, how is it?
It's heavy, isn't it?
It's heavy.
Please don't pull 105 cm.
Who are you?
I'm Yoshi.
Yes.
Let's wrap it up.
Please introduce yourself.
It's like a pervert.
It's a pervert.
I'm sorry.
It's okay to write like this.
Please take it out.
It's a pervert.
I'm laughing.
Please take it out.
It's soundproofing.
It's dangerous.
Amazing.
Where is the seikan-tai?
Me?
The seikan-tai is a wakimara.
Wakimara?
Try to answer.
I can't answer.
How?
Kindly.
What do you think about Pisa?
Pisa is...
I like to be gently touched.
I see.
Do you have any experience?
To be honest.
About...
How much is your part-time job?
It's about two digits.
So it's about 95 people.
If it's just a transit, it's one digit.
One digit?
Yes.
You took it the other way around.
The other way around?
You didn't take it too far.
I thought it was that.
You thought it was that.
What do you mean by that?
Now, don't stop.
In the direction of the launch.
It's okay.
Look up.
Look at yourself.
20 seconds before.
Thank you very much.
It's cold, isn't it?
Hello, I'm Hamasaki Mao.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hamasaki Mao.
What are the three points?
What?
Three?
I only thought about one.
Where is the first one?
I want to see the Nyu-Rin.
Nyu-Rin? I want to see it.
Nyu-Rin.
It's Nyu-Rin, not Chikumi.
Please show us Nyu-Rin as Chikumi.
Nyu-Rin! Nyu-Rin! Nyu-Rin! Nyu-Rin! Nyu-Rin! Nyu-Rin!
Great!
Please go back to the circle.
3cm!
Hurry up!
This time, it's neck and ear.
Thank you very much.
Let's go again!
Please!
You don't have much experience, do you?
No.
I remember it from the 3rd episode.
The 3rd episode?
565 people?
Why are you crying?
I don't remember Shimabukuro-san,
but once I was teased by Shimabukuro-san,
and now I'm scared.
What is your favorite movie?
If you do that, you will cry.
When Mr. Chimabukuro gets angry.
What is your favorite food?
Japanese food? Italian food? Chinese food?
My favorite food is...
It's a banana.
It's cute, isn't it?
It's a little banana.
Don't you get angry today?
I don't get angry.
Do you have a favorite TV program?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
It was a pity.
Thank you very much.
Who was it?
It was SHINYA.
Thank you very much.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Maya.
You have 3 points.
3 points?
Please smile.
I understand.
Start.
I'll show you.
Everyone wants to see Kamuro-san's boobs.
Please look at it.
If you can see it, give her a round of applause.
Look at the gold and look at it from the side.
It's very beautiful.
Please introduce yourself.
My name is Tanaka.
Can I touch you?
Yes, please.
Strong or weak?
Strong.
This is good.
I don't need an explanation.
Let's get started.
Please introduce yourself.
Please start.
I will eat.
Can I ask you a question?
My name is Chikubi.
What's next?
Hmm...
And...
The neckline...
The neckline is quite different, isn't it?
I can't stop it!
Let's check the image.
What's your favorite attitude?
Hmm...
I like the back.
The back, huh?
Yes.
I think you did it in a strange place today.
The emergency staircase of a crowded building.
It's a crime.
Is that so?
Is it a crime?
It's a crime officially.
Is that so?
Yes.
But you were seen by someone, right?
It's a crime.
It's official.
You like Doki Doki, don't you?
Yeah.
What's your favorite masterpiece?
Hmm?
My favorite masterpiece?
Please look at this.
Well...
All of them are good, but...
Especially?
Especially...
Well...
Youth School Memories.
I'm a high school girl, Mono. Nice to meet you.
I'll try to look at it with DMM.
Please.
Just look at it.
It's already 10 seconds before that.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
What is it?
It's a school memory of the players.
I will definitely see it.
Thank you very much.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Maki Hara Mada.
Please tell me about three points.
Three? I could only think of one.
Tell me one.
I have two big front teeth like a rat.
Two big front teeth?
Two big front teeth.
Aren't you running away a little?
I'm having fun.
It's true that you have big front teeth.
I'll give you three sizes.
Three sizes.
My free size is 83.
My waist size is 58.
I don't have a lot of hips, but...
It's hard to take off your clothes again today, isn't it?
If you don't touch it, you have to touch it.
Who is it?
It's Shin-san.
Touch it.
You auditioned, didn't you?
Yes.
I'm the same age as you.
How old are you now?
I'm 27 years old.
Why are you still 27 years old?
I didn't have a circle.
Maybe you don't have a circle this time.
No, no, no, this time I have a circle.
Let's start.
You are a virgin, aren't you?
Yes.
Amazing?
I can see my buttocks.
Amazing. Please come out.
What did you say?
Do your best!
Everyone is watching.
What is your life style?
My life style is...
Clitoris.
Clitoris?
You have more, right?
Where?
Back.
You have it, don't you?
My toes.
What's the hole?
I'm so sensitive.
The hole.
What's the hole, Takki?
This much.
I wonder if it will be Makihara-san.
I think I will never forget about Makihara-san.
Makihara-san.
I will never forget about her.
She is a liar.
I will remember her a lot.
I will remember her for 20 years.
How do you feel?
I'm so happy.
I will never forget this moment.
I can't think of any other time.
I'm sorry I was noisy.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
I'll take a photo of you later.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Ayu Sakurai.
I'm Chippai.
What is Chippai?
It's the sound of a cup.
It's possible to show it.
It's possible now.
Please say it's possible.
What should I do if I get caught?
What are you talking about?
Fail.
Look at it properly.
Look at it.
It's small.
We're the small ones.
What should we do?
You can't do it, right?
You want to do it, right?
I want to do it.
I'm going to do it.
You can't do it, right?
You can do it, you can do it.
You can do it.
You're used to it?
No.
Is it better?
I can hold the red one.
I'm shy.
Let's do it.
Please introduce yourself.
Nice to meet you.
Who are you?
I'm Ichi.
Ichi?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who? Ayu?
Yes.
Ayu Ayu.
The third one.
The third one?
Yes.
The back of my legs.
The back of your legs.
Yes.
Oh.
You don't usually do Ayu Ayu, do you?
It feels good when you lick it.
It's not a massage.
Yes.
It feels good when you lick it.
This is the second one.
Hmm...
The one with the feet?
The one with the feet!
Is this called the one with the feet?
Yes, it is.
The one with the feet?
Yes.
You can lick it or touch it.
That's not it.
The first one!
Clitoris.
Yay!
Clitoris is delicious, isn't it?
I love clitoris.
I see.
How many did you get?
How many videos do you have?
I have about 200 videos.
Wow, you have 200 videos?
You are saving money with DMM, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Can I see it?
Yes, you can.
DMM is very cheap.
Moody's is also in the EMM group.
It went in, didn't it?
Is it going to come out?
If it comes out, raise your hand a little.
If it comes out, you can feel it.
I'll wait.
Oh, good.
It's difficult.
I don't like it.
The picture has power.
I can't do it.
As expected of the expert.
I don't know.
I can do it somehow.
More.
First try.
Can you do this?
She became strong.
But when Ayo changed her movement,
when she became a little stiffer,
I thought it was impossible for her to do her best.
That's why I wanted to do my best.
Thank you very much.
No.10, please introduce yourself.
No.10, Abe no Miku. I made a mistake in kanji.
The staff made a mistake, didn't they?
Yes, and I made a mistake, too.
That's no good.
The result is no good.
Is this Abe no Miku?
Yes, it's Abe no Miku.
It's written with Abe no Miku, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
It's written with that.
It's easy to remember.
You're familiar with cell phones, aren't you?
Cell phones and tablets.
I don't know much about tablets.
I don't know anything.
Kawase Soba
You know it
Here it is
You are a genius
Where is the charm point?
The charm point is
Long eyelashes and
Buttocks
It looks like
From the buttocks
I want to see
Please
Here?
I don't know if I should say it or not
What should I change?
What should I do next?
I think you'll understand if you watch the news in the morning
You're so random
Everyone is watching the news
I'm watching
I only watched it once in the last 3 weeks
Okay, okay, butt
Okay, everyone, let's do it
My butt
Your first butt
I'm at the limit of my seat belt
Please do it before
Before?
Please help me, it's not the time to say thank you.
You did something like thank you.
Camera-san, do your best.
Do my best?
Please open your legs a little.
It's embarrassing to be seen from the front.
Everyone is watching.
Let me move your hand.
It's hard.
Can you see it?
It's a good mosaic.
It's a digital mosaic.
How is Japan going to be?
From now on, let's do our best.
Let's do it!
Start!
It didn't work.
It can't be helped.
Wait a minute.
I'll lick it.
I'm holding back a lot.
What's your name?
It's Saki.
Saki?
I saw a girl just now.
What do you like about the police?
Whose?
Abe's?
Yes, Abe's Mix.
I'm a big fan of Abe's.
Recently, Chikubi is coming.
Chikubi is coming?
Yes.
On the contrary, it's a big one with a large down width.
I don't think so.
Down width?
I think it's easier to say.
Ear?
The ear is a little...
Is that so?
Ah! Ah! Ah!
What are you doing?
That face!
The neck is twisted.
Ah! No! No!
Oh no! Oh no!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
It's a pity that I stuck a little
It's a pity
It was very comfortable
Do you want to take a look?
What?
I think it's easy to show
Please
From the bottom?
Why is it almost like that?
Say something
No comment
I can't see
That's good
Thank you very much
I can't do it anymore
Are you number 11?
Yes, I'm number 11.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Megumi Ishino.
You're so cute.
Can you tell us your charm points?
Charm points...
If you can, tell us about 20.
That's a lot.
Well...
Lately, I've been told that I have a nosebleed.
I see.
Not from the beginning.
It's been said a lot lately.
Show me.
It's beautiful.
Also,
it's been said a lot lately.
It's been said a lot lately.
It's broken.
It's a little broken.
Show me.
It's like this.
Wait a minute.
I'm wearing stockings today, so it's easy.
I don't know.
What's that?
Can I touch it?
It's hard.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
I can see it.
What is that?
Is it a breast?
Let's start from there.
Let's go to the new rim.
I'm looking at it.
I'm embarrassed.
This is a picture.
What is the three size?
The three size is 80 from the top.
What is that? 80?
Please be honest.
I'm 28 years old.
I'm 85 years old.
I'm next to you.
You don't have to be so big.
Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
Let's go.
Please introduce yourself.
Please start.
Thank you.
I like this.
This is a kendo and anta.
This is anta.
Can you tell me about your body?
Body?
Yes.
I like the bones of my hips.
Bones of your hips?
Yes.
Bones of your hips.
I like being licked.
I like strange things.
How old are you?
I'm 11 years old.
Let's take a picture together.
How old are you?
I'll calculate it here.
Please do it.
How many pictures do you have?
I have about 200 to 300 pictures.
That's a lot.
This is a good corner, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
I hope it will come out somehow.
Hey, it's a little...
This is a candidate, isn't it?
It's a candidate.
It smells like that.
Do you understand me?
I understand.
30 seconds left.
I think you can do it.
I might fail.
What do you usually do?
I usually go to the office.
Today is the second day.
It's been 10 seconds.
10 seconds left.
You just put your hand in.
I thought you didn't.
I'm watching you.
I'm sorry I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Let's say goodbye by showing your teeth.
Thank you very much.
Please introduce yourself.
Yes, I'm Tsugumi. Nice to meet you.
You don't have a beard, do you?
I don't have a beard.
Right?
You have a lot of hair on your head, don't you?
That's right.
Yes.
You have six hair on your head?
Yes, I have six hair on my head.
That's amazing.
I have about the second hair on my head.
Yes, that's good.
What's your favorite part of your hair?
My favorite part is black hair.
Black hair?
Yes.
It's a little black.
Black hair?
Yes.
You're a professional, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
You don't have dark hair, do you?
No, I don't.
You have blonde hair, don't you?
No, I've never dyed my hair.
If you quit this job, maybe you want to have blonde hair.
Blonde hair?
Yes.
I'll make you look bad.
Bad?
I'll make you look like a mohawk.
Mohawk?
Yes.
I don't have any plans.
No, you don't.
You'll be surprised if you make a mistake.
Now, let's go inside!
Oh, something is coming out.
Oh, something is coming out?
Something is coming out.
How many balls are there?
I think there are about 800 balls.
I think there are about 1,000 balls.
How many did you get?
I got about 1000.
Wow!
When you go to DMF and search for Tsubomi, you'll see a lot of them.
What should we look at among them?
Who should we look at?
Please look at Bakugasu.
You've gotten better.
I couldn't say that at all four years ago.
It's getting dark.
It's dark as if I'm in a tunnel.
Oh, this is a little...
It's a little hot mode.
It's getting bigger.
It's not like this veteran is showing it to the camera.
I was doing it.
Hot mode.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Isn't it going to come out?
Can you show it to the camera?
It's a human, isn't it?
Wow, it's delicious.
You can eat it there.
Like an ox.
Show it to the camera.
Wow, it's delicious.
Do it again. Show it to the camera.
It's delicious.
Look at this.
It's like a rice ball.
It's delicious.
Can I see it?
It's a lot.
Great.
It's amazing.
That's 1000.
Drink it again.
Are you going to show it again?
Amazing!
What?
You got 5 points!
Thank you very much.
It was great.
Now it's number 13.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Ruka Kanae.
Nice to meet you.
It's a difficult word.
Do you read it as Kanae?
It's not a good idea.
Please tell me more.
I'm Kanaeruka.
Please tell me the good points.
The good points are...
a big cat,
a big eye,
and a big waist.
It's a big waist.
Don't do that.
I don't want to.
I have to show this to the camera.
You said it's a big waist.
I don't know.
I didn't know.
You don't wear it.
I don't wear it.
But I wear it.
It's like a bra.
I want to get that bra.
I don't wear it.
Do you wear it under your eyes?
It's thick under my eyes.
You wear it well.
I'll introduce myself.
Please.
I'm nervous.
I'm already nervous.
Let's go!
Let's start the cut!
Start?
Let's start the cut.
Something is coming out.
Can you tell me how you feel?
So, the chest and the other side?
The other side?
Yes.
That's all you can do?
What's your waist size?
I'm 184 cm, 59 cm, and 85 cm.
You did something strange there.
What do you mean by that?
Was it a bath?
What?
You have it, don't you?
Are you shooting?
I'm shooting.
Did you take a picture?
No, I didn't.
I was shooting.
What?
It's like a beach hut.
Yeah, it's more like a trial and error kind of thing, isn't it?
I see.
Do you go outside when you go out?
Yes, I do.
Do you go to school?
No.
Private school?
No, I don't go to school.
I don't go to school.
I can't go to school anymore.
Once a year?
Once a year.
I go to school with 50 people.
That's more, right?
Yes.
That's a little different, isn't it?
500 people?
That's a lot.
5,000 people?
Is it different?
But they're all the same person.
You can't control that.
What kind of sex do you like?
I like lovey-dovey kind of sex.
What do you think?
You're kidding me?
10 seconds left.
5 seconds left.
That was close.
I'm glad you did your best.
There are still many more, so please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Number 14.
Are you nervous?
I want to go home.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Hikaru Kanna.
Yes, I am.
Can you sum up your self-experience in 30 seconds?
No, I don't have anything to say.
Please go ahead.
Well...
My three sizes are...
...82, 58, 86, and...
...my favorite type is...
...back.
Why?
I like it.
This time too.
I want to be asked from behind.
I said it was difficult.
I want to get some experience.
Experience?
Including the scene.
Including the scene? You're not lying.
Right?
100...
100 points.
About 130.
It's about 30.
It's real, isn't it?
Yes.
What are the three points?
The three points are...
a smile.
You ran away.
I didn't run away.
Then smile, please.
I'll take about three minutes.
Do you need three minutes of a smile?
I need it.
You don't need it.
You're going to cut it at all, aren't you?
Okay, let's go with that.
He says he wants to put it out.
He's full of motivation.
Is that so?
I'll do my best.
Start!
Thank you for waiting.
What would you like to be if you were to be born?
Salmon.
Salmon?
Yes.
Salmon.
Salmon?
Yes.
Why?
I want to climb it.
You want to climb it?
Yes.
You're going to break it.
You can survive there, right?
Yes.
I can survive.
You're going to die before that.
Yes.
It's broken in the tournament.
How was it?
I want to write it down.
Did you write it down?
10 seconds ago.
No.
Thank you very much.
Number 15 has powered up.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Mirai Mikami.
Nice to meet you.
Please tell us your charm points.
I want everyone to see this.
My charm points are
mouth and tongue.
Mouth and tongue?
Please tell us your high-speed tongue.
What's this?
A
Ijiri Okada
More more more
More
Too fast
It's not
It's not fast
It's long
Sorry
I'll show you the long one
Here we go
It's long
It's a long name
What's your favorite food?
My favorite food is a fried shrimp
Not a mandarin
This is the first time I've ever seen this kind of thing in real life.
It's amazing.
It looks good.
It feels good.
It looks really good.
It's entwined.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Yoppi.
You're Yoppi, right?
Yes, I am.
What about the second one?
Which one?
Hmm?
The second one?
Yes, the second one.
I'm going to put it on my wrist and wrist.
It's good, isn't it?
It looks good.
It's a long way down, isn't it?
If there is a place where I can't go, I will be disappointed.
It's a good taste, isn't it?
Yes.
It's a good taste.
10 pieces.
This is the end of the race.
I failed.
Why did you fail?
I'm sorry.
Please do your best.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
It's number 16.
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Uehara Ai.
Uehara-san, have you been on the internet before?
This is my third time.
Thank you very much.
When I search on the internet,
Uehara has quite a reputation.
Really?
As far as I can see.
I'm happy. Thank you very much.
Please do your best.
What is the jump point?
The jump point is the pink collar.
Pink? Did you just say pink?
It's always pink.
It's not mixed at all.
It's not mixed with brown.
It's not mixed.
There is no doubt.
It's definitely pink.
Probably.
Let's see it.
Will you see it?
What do you think?
It's not a shocking pink color, is it?
No, it's not.
I'm surprised.
It's my first time.
Can I touch it?
I think it's good.
Please let me touch it.
It's pink.
It's really pink.
That's right.
Is it always pink?
It's always pink.
I'm sure it'll turn black 3 times.
No, it won't.
It'll turn black 50 times or 60 times.
I don't like that.
That's great.
Maybe one side is black.
Please look at it.
It's the same.
That's right.
How is it?
There is such a pink.
I'm glad.
Let me touch it.
What kind of touch should I do?
I like the way you touch it.
I like that kind of feeling.
It's coming out.
It's very hard.
I'm getting stiff.
What do you touch?
Carbohydrate.
It doesn't matter.
Let's start.
Let's introduce ourselves.
Please start.
I'm sorry.
Let's start again.
You've seen a lot of things.
Yes.
Is it a big one?
It's a big one.
Yes.
But I've seen a lot of things.
That's right.
Where should I look at?
I wonder if there is a place to look at.
What kind of place do you want me to look at?
I want you to look at a place where you are enjoying yourself.
I want you to look at a place where everyone is enjoying themselves.
Then, I will follow this camera only to Uehara.
Is that okay?
I'm so happy.
What's the most simple thing you can do?
The most simple thing is ears and...
I'm going to do a live.
Please do it.
What kind of support do you like?
I like that.
What kind of support?
Something like...
Sweet words?
Sweet words.
It's a sweet taste.
It's delicious.
It's not good for me.
I'm happy.
It's very hard.
Is it the sound of a keyboard?
It's hard to see on the screen.
I want you to participate more and more.
Yes, I want you to participate more and more.
I went too far.
Did it come out?
I think so.
Do you want me to wait?
This is the first time I've ever had this kind of food in my life.
Do you have any goals or ambitions?
I'll do my best to keep going.
There's a car behind you.
I want to be the best in the world.
In this industry?
Yes.
In the United States?
I think Moodys is the best.
Yes.
Right?
You and Aima.
Yes.
Together.
Wow!
It's so long!
It's amazing!
Amazing!
It's so long!
Please hold it up high.
Hold it up high.
Pull it down like you're drinking wine.
Then, turn it around.
Even if you bring it to your throat once, it's delicious.
Oh, I drank it! Great!
It was delicious.
It was like drinking wine from an old age.
It was a wonderful drink.
It was amazing.
How many days did you drink it?
Thank you very much.
I will come to the inn soon.
So everyone, since it's a box bus, don't you want to put it in the bus?
Yeah!
Let's put it in!
So let's put it in the bus as much as we can!
One, two!
Seat belt! High-speed sex!
Yes!
According to the instructions given by the person in the next seat and Mr. Ken Ken,
It is a sex where everyone plays the same.
However, men should never take off their seat belts.
Let's split it in time, so let's do it together.
Let's get started.
The two of you, please take a seat.
Yes.
Itch-ka.
What?
Yes.
Itch-ka.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Let's start from the French kiss to the deep kiss.
It's French.
It's soft.
Because it's French.
Really?
It's deep.
Can I kiss you?
It's okay.
Do you want me to take a picture of you?
How is it?
Both of you are very sensitive.
Do you want to lick it?
You haven't licked it yet.
Not yet?
You are the only one who can do this.
I'm sorry.
I'm so tired.
Sit down.
It feels so good.
Ta-da!
Look, it's a tea bag.
Oh, you're right.
How is it?
It's super erotic.
Can I take a picture of you?
Here you go.
How is it?
Everyone, how is the blanket?
I can't see anything yet.
I can't see anything.
I'm scared.
Is it beautiful?
Wait a minute.
What?
Is it okay?
Thank you.
You don't like it?
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it feels good.
The curve is complete.
...
Please turn to the left and turn to the right.
I can't believe it.
Wait, wait, wait!
No, no, no!
I can't do it!
Where? Here?
No, no, no!
Really?
Here?
Yes.
No, no, no!
I'm sorry.
I want to go to the toilet.
I want to put it in my mouth.
I want to eat!
Say it!
Let's stop eating.
Let's go!
Let me in!
Everyone, let's go to the warehouse!
I'll put condoms on!
I'm so sorry.
I can't stand it anymore.
Oh, my God.
Aika, number 8.
What's going on?
I don't know what you think, but I'll try it later.
Can I put it in now?
What are you going to do?
I want to do it.
If you think about it, it's not a bus.
It's okay, so let me put it in quickly.
Everyone, please enter the room.
Everyone, please wear a mask.
Can I stay at home?
I'm going to fall asleep.
It's okay.
It's gone.
No, don't go yet.
Oh my god!
Oh, it's painful.
It's so cute!
It's so heart-pounding.
Let's go!
Look!
They are very excited.
There are a lot of them!
Let's go!
Please hold it.
Ta-da!
There are so many.
Do you want to drink?
Please drink.
I'm so happy.
I ate it.
Let's go.
Give me your hand.
Give me.
I'm sweating.
Do you want to see?
I'm saying, I'm sweating.
I'm sweating.
There are so many people.
Can you take off your gloves and show them?
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
There are so many people.
I'm sweating a lot.
It's not over yet.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
It's okay.
I want to go home.
Thank you.
One more minute.
It's gone.
Amazing.
Show me.
Show it to the camera.
How did you feel?
I felt good.
What happened to your back?
Oh, my God!
I feel like I'm going to wipe my back.
Hold on! Hold on!
30 seconds left.
Please hurry up!
Hurry up!
10 seconds left!
I don't think so.
How is it?
It's finished.
Everyone, it's finished.
Let's take a look at the front of the bus.
It was a little hot, but how is it?
It feels good to be close to each other when it's hot.
It feels good to be close to each other when we're sweating.
There is a person who seems to die, but is it okay?
Are you okay?
It's okay.
It was good, wasn't it?
Yes.
What happened to Dote-kun?
What happened?
Did you do it or not?
I did it.
Which one?
It's not good.
It was a little hot, wasn't it?
My memories are like this.
I'm sure there's something like that.
Everyone, thank you for your hard work.
That's all.
It was a high-speed set of seat belts.
Yeah!
Thank you.
Let's do it again.
Cute.
Aloha.
Everyone is different.
Everyone is different?
Oh, I have to take a picture.
Cute.
I feel like I'm a professional.
I want to be a boxer.
Look, look.
There might be someone else.
No way.
I made a mistake.
I don't like cute girls.
What do you mean?
It's so cute.
It's Chaya.
It's huge.
It's so cute.
What is it?
So cute!
I want to see it.
It's so different.
It's cute.
I want to see it.
Look at this.
It's cute.
I was surprised.
I was embarrassed.
I can't open it.
I wonder if this is the same as the one on my lips.
I don't know.
It's cute.
It's an adornment, isn't it?
You can't change your swimsuit, Ayu.
She's laughing.
What are you laughing at?
But it's sexy.
I'm not a mother.
I'm a loli.
I'm a lexie.
I'm a chida.
I'm a tatsui.
It's a juggler.
Wait! If there's a hole, it'll be like this.
Everyone, please follow me!
Yay!
Wow!
It's amazing!
It's like a fairy tale.
What is it?
I see something!
Oh, there's something!
There's something!
Everyone, the one in your right hand is...
...Lucky Life!
So cute!
What's that?
Take a picture of Gomi-san.
She's wearing a nurse's costume.
Oh, no!
So cute!
She's so cute!
What's wrong?
I'm getting dizzy!
I can't stop!
This is the charm of Bako Bako Land!
Did you see it?
I saw it!
I want Chikkun!
Oh no!
The dino!
The dino is here!
Give me the dino!
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry.
That's it!
5th place!
Go!
1st and 2nd place!
There are men too!
Let's start with the girls.
The girls will sit side by side.
11th and 12th place!
I'm hungry!
I wanted to go when I felt like it.
One more curry, please.
Rice!
Please give me a small amount.
What do you want to drink?
Orange?
Orange juice?
I can't drink it.
Everyone, itadakimasu!
Itadakimasu!
Is it good?
I did it!
It's good!
Let's try the potatoes!
Is it good?
It's good!
I did it!
Let's go!
Ta-da!
It's a sudden interview with Otoha Narase's lunch!
Yay!
So now, I'm going to go see how everyone is getting along with each other.
Let's go!
Oh, it's already started.
It's moving.
Please.
Wait.
I'll try it.
Here we go.
It's good.
Is it?
It's good!
I finished half a piece.
Do you drink water?
Not yet.
You don't?
No, I don't.
Then, your throat is dry.
It's a little dry.
It's a little dry?
Yes.
Then, I'll put some water on your dry throat.
Is it okay if I do it?
Yes.
You can spit it out.
Is it okay if I do it?
From me?
Yes.
You can do it from this side.
I want to do it from this side.
I did it.
It's delicious.
Delicious!
Thank you very much.
I'm so proud of you.
Delicious!
Who wants to drink orange juice?
Yes!
Please, please, please.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Who wants to drink beer?
Me.
Then please drink this orange juice together.
Yes!
It's delicious.
What should I do?
Drink.
But it's embarrassing.
It's about to come back.
Oh, three are facing each other.
Don't let go of it.
You can't eat it all at once.
You can drink all of it.
I don't know.
We ate it all.
So cute.
That's it for today's interview!
See you later!
Thank you for your hard work.
I would like you to experience the Bako Bako Land attraction.
I would like to choose the person who will explain it with a lottery.
Please choose the person who will explain it with a lottery.
The person with the lottery is the person who will explain it with a lottery.
You haven't seen it yet, have you?
No, I haven't seen it yet.
It's behind you.
Go ahead.
There's something on it.
You'll know if you hit it.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I don't understand.
Go ahead.
Here we go.
I wonder who it is.
Go ahead.
It's random.
It's stable.
Are you sure you're not going to be the host?
You're not here!
That's all.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You're the best host in Japan.
Please give me the script.
I'll give you the explanation.
What are you doing now?
Who is the host?
I'm the host, Ichika Tomihata.
I'm Ichi-deo.
I will explain the first attraction.
The name of the attraction is Bako Bako Ero Jungle.
I will explain.
The two of you will be a pair and explore the jungle in the pool.
This jungle is an erotic jungle, so you can experience various erotic things just by walking.
Please stand by.
Yes!
Let's start the Bako Bako Edo Jungle!
This is the Disney attraction!
Thank you.
Please
Thank you very much.
This is Chikubiname attraction.
I made a mistake.
Thank you
Thank you very much.
Welcome! This is the Tekki area.
May I?
Excuse me.
It's been a long time.
Wow!
Can I put it down?
Why is it so heavy?
Excuse me.
Wow, it's hard!
Wow!
It's flexible.
My head is full.
Does it feel good?
Wow!
The water is coming out from the first step.
There's a lot coming out!
It's so slippery!
I'm so happy.
She's so energetic.
See you later!
Have fun!
Welcome! This is Ashikoki Zone!
Welcome! This is Ashikoki Area!
Excuse me.
It feels good.
You're so cute.
I'm going to make your feet feel good.
I'm going to warm you up.
Excuse me.
You're so cute.
Do you like it here?
Yes, I do.
Then, I'll give you a lot.
Thank you.
It feels good.
Which one do you like more?
Well...
I like the one in the front.
The one in the front?
Yes.
Oh, it looks good.
Something is coming out.
What is this?
Look, it's very slippery.
Take it out like this.
It's a naughty kitten.
Thank you.
I was scared.
It's okay.
It's a waste.
Amazing.
It feels good.
It was amazing!
It was nice!
Was it nice?
See you later!
It's going to rain soon, isn't it?
Ready, set, go!
Welcome! This is Paisley!
Please come in!
Let's enjoy the rain!
How is it?
Is it good?
What do you like?
Fluffy?
Which one do you like?
Left or right?
Asakipo and Nemo are tall.
They are tall.
They are really tall.
Are they tall?
What kind of things do you like?
Well, like this.
Like this.
Yakuwari-san.
Both hands.
Both hands?
I wonder if it's okay to touch them.
Kindly?
Kindly.
Like this.
Do you like it?
Which do you like better?
I like it.
Do you want it?
Which do you like more?
I like the shell.
The shell is good.
Hello.
Have fun next time.
See you.
Welcome.
Welcome. This is Terra's attraction.
Excuse me.
I'm going to stop.
Which part do you like?
I like the crab part.
Do you want to drink it?
Does it feel good?
You're looking at the baby, aren't you?
You look so happy.
Are you happy?
Please go back to sleep.
I'm going to make it smooth.
I'm getting energetic.
It's hot.
I'm rubbing against a heavy girl.
Do you understand?
She's rubbing it with a treat.
It's so bright red.
You like being rubbed, don't you?
I feel like I'm going to die.
It feels good.
It's so warm.
It's melting.
It's melting and going to disappear.
Oh, it feels good.
How do you feel?
I'll see you later.
You're glowing.
Do you like this cup?
I like it.
It's small.
It is a cup.
It's a cup.
It's so soft.
I can understand the tingling.
It's getting hot, isn't it?
It's so hot.
What's wrong?
Are you hot?
I'm sweating.
Me too.
Thank you very much.
Take care.
One, two.
Welcome.
This is the request area.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to do Terachio.
Terachio?
Terachio, please.
Okay, thank you.
I'm going to try it.
Is it good?
I like it.
I really like it.
Do you feel good?
I haven't done anything yet.
It's very soft.
It's ticklish.
Don't touch it.
Sorry, Mingo.
It's ticklish.
My whole body is ticklish.
It's very ticklish.
Oh, it's so good.
She's rubbing it so much.
Don't touch it. It's a desert area.
Thank you for your hard work.
Your body looks surprised.
Did you feel good?
Thank you very much.
This is the ice hockey zone.
That was so lame.
I knew it.
Your feet are so cool.
Really?
Thank you.
I'll just do it in front of you.
Squishy, squishy, squishy.
Do you have any special experiences?
I love this.
Do you want to try it yourself?
No, no.
This is good.
I don't want to do it.
You don't want to do it?
Please do it.
Is it comfortable?
Yes, it is.
I wonder if you can do it.
Amazing.
This is the attraction of Kura.
Excuse me.
It was already out.
I didn't wear it.
Excuse me.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
It's amazing.
It's sparkling.
It's cold.
It's getting harder.
It's so cold.
It's cold.
Everyone is watching.
It's the last one.
No!
Don't go.
Thank you for your hard work!
Please look forward to it!
Welcome!
This is Ashikoki Zone!
Take out one of these!
Are you standing up?
I'm standing up.
You're good.
Really?
Your legs are good.
Look, there are girls around us.
It's the first time.
It's amazing.
It feels good.
Can you go up a little?
Are you okay?
It's so hot.
It's hard, isn't it?
Because it feels good.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
I'm going to do it again.
Oh, it's over.
It's dangerous.
Thank you. See you.
Bye-bye.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
One, two, three, four.
This is...
Oh, sorry.
One more time.
One, two, three, four.
This is Tera's attraction.
Nice to meet you.
Yay.
Stand up.
Can I sit down?
You can stand up.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Can I take a picture with you?
Yes, please.
Wow!
Wow! It seems to melt.
It feels good.
It's so nice.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Wow.
They are watching us.
Thank you.
Wow.
This is great.
If you think your ankle is bad, it's even worse.
It's worse than your ankle.
How do you feel?
My ankle is terrible.
Your ankle is terrible, too.
It's getting bigger.
It's even worse.
Is there something in your ankle?
It's terrible.
I moved a lot.
It's very slippery.
It's amazing.
It looks like it's going in.
It feels good.
It's erotic.
It looks like it's going in.
It's going in?
It's going in.
Let's do it one more time.
Amazing.
Her expression is a bit...
The
It came out!
Nuru Nuru Sumata is the best!
Thank you very much!
I can't stand it!
I want Sumata too!
Excuse me, can I have Sumata too?
Please lie down!
Please!
I'm going to do it.
I'm scared.
Can I do it?
Excuse me.
I'm Riku Minato.
It's my first time.
Excuse me.
I'm a beginner.
Please put this on your head.
Thank you.
I'm a beginner.
I'm looking forward to it.
What should I do?
Apply it on your face.
Make it smooth.
It's pretty cold.
Apply it.
Wow.
It's a little small.
It's okay.
It's just a little bit.
Here we go.
Wow.
Do you use this?
This is the first time I've ever felt this.
This is amazing!
Can I try?
She's being carried away.
Amazing.
She's standing.
Does it feel good?
I feel like I'm going to die.
Not yet.
What are you doing?
This is the area of request.
What do you want me to do?
Kiss.
Please.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's delicious.
It feels good.
Everyone is hungry.
Everyone is here for the last time.
Can I hug you?
What about you, Chin-chin?
Chin-chin, don't go!
Chin-chin is...
I'm sorry.
If that's the case, I'll drink Abeno mink and have a match with Renze.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I should have done it with Renze.
That's all for Bakobasso Ero Jungle!
Next, I would like to ask you to explain the next attraction.
Is this a bridge?
You look like you don't have confidence in yourself.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
I think it's good to decide randomly.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
Please raise your voice.
It's decided.
What's your name?
My name is Fururugi Mikan.
What kind of fruit do you like?
I like oranges.
I'll give you a hint of the most famous company in Japan.
Please explain it to me.
The script is in the middle.
I will explain the second attraction.
Next, Bakobako Merry-Go-Land!
First, a woman will sit on the M-shape with a rotor.
Then, a man will draw a lottery and decide the order.
One person will draw one rotor.
The person who draws the lottery can taste the Bako Bako Merry-Go-Land.
Everyone.
Everyone, please open the middle.
Please open it.
What is that?
I didn't notice it at all.
What is it?
Please open it!
I've never seen it. What is it?
What does it mean?
The two men will sit down and do something erotic from everyone.
Let's start the stand-by!
I'm the only one who can do it.
Then, the first person, please come on.
You can choose the color you like.
What does it mean?
You can choose the color until the end.
If this is the last one, I'll be sad.
No, I'm sad.
You can choose the color you like.
The face is a little serious, isn't it?
I don't know if it's on the surface.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What is the point of smiling when you look at this?
It feels good.
What are you looking at?
What color?
What color is it?
It's cool.
Is it okay to do it like this?
Yes.
Please take off your clothes.
In the end, it doesn't move.
Please be kind to me.
Oh, it came out.
Oh, that's too bad.
Come on!
Who is the winner?
You don't choose by your preference, do you?
That's right.
Please draw.
Oh, it's a pity.
Come on!
It's over.
Let's go.
Oh, too bad.
Too bad.
No.4, please.
Are you crying?
Please take your time.
Oh, I'm going to be born.
Too bad.
Please choose one of the five.
The fifth is Cherry Boy.
He is still Cherry Boy.
Please choose one of the five.
What's wrong? It's embarrassing.
Look closely.
Look at his face.
I want a manko.
How is it?
Is there something in it?
No.
Too bad.
Thank you.
Here you are.
Please record it.
No one is looking at it.
This.
This one.
Wait.
It's coming out.
Okay, go straight.
Slowly.
You can't send it.
Why?
Just the rotor isn't enough.
That's too bad.
Go back there.
Number 3, number 7, and number 6.
I can't put anything in.
Look carefully.
I put it in.
Excuse me.
I think it's going in.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Too bad.
It's terrible.
Look carefully.
Look at Manco's face.
I'm going in.
It's a funny game, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes.
How is it?
Good?
I don't know.
Slowly.
How is it?
It's a pity.
Here is your souvenir.
Here you are.
Oh, there's more.
Wow, look at that.
You're so good at this.
Amazing, right?
Oh, you came this way?
Okay, sleep well.
Sleep well.
How is it?
You got it!
You got 5 points!
Thank you!
I think you guys can do it because of the mat.
Can you?
Thank you!
Congratulations!
After this, it's reward time!
So everyone, Bako Bako Merry-Go-Land
Let's start the song!
Let's start!
Are you ready?
Let's do it one more time.
Ready, go!
It's coming out!
It's coming out.
It's amazing.
I'm sorry.
Now I'm going to eat the anus.
It's fast.
Riku, put it in.
Can I?
But I have lotion.
It's okay.
I'll do it with my fangs.
Wow.
It's crunchy.
I want to see it.
Do you want to see the butt?
Ready, set, go!
Wow!
I'm so excited.
I want to do it.
Have you developed your butt?
No, I haven't.
Do you want to do it?
Yes, I want to do it.
Are you going to do it?
Yes, I'm going to do it.
You are good.
Please be kind to her.
She is a girl.
That's right.
First of all, I'm going to take it off.
Wow!
It became a hole.
It fell down.
Wow! It fell down!
Do you want me to stab it?
Do you want me to stab your nose?
It's cute.
It's amazing.
It's cute, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Oh, it's going!
It's going!
It's going in!
Relax.
Take a deep breath.
How do you feel?
I like the way it comes out.
It's so cute!
Wow! It's J.K.Members!
Amazing!
I want to make a hole in it.
The whole thing is in it.
It's in it.
There's a finger in it!
Wow!
Can I draw a flower for you?
That's right.
Let me draw it.
Amazing!
There's a lot in it.
I'm so embarrassed.
So cute.
She's going in.
Her nose is coming out of her butt.
It's a flower!
Wow!
So cute!
The flower bloomed!
How do you feel about the flower?
It's a weird feeling.
It's a nice butt hole.
It's cute!
Change!
Change! Change! Change! Change! Change!
Wait, my nose is stuck!
Let's make it cuter.
It feels good.
It's cuter.
It's so cute.
It's so sticky.
It's very sticky.
It's full.
It's all over the place.
It's disgusting.
Is it good?
It looks delicious.
I feel sorry for you.
It's so hard.
It's hard, Binbin.
Yuka, do you feel good?
Yes.
It tastes like Dosukebe.
Really?
What do you want me to do?
I want you to push harder.
You want me to push harder?
Where?
Where is the yodo?
Yodo, yodo.
Yodo.
The second one!
It fits perfectly!
The third one!
Your boyfriend is beautiful.
It fits perfectly!
Isn't it too big?
I got a half of it!
Wow!
Let's put it down.
It's heavy.
Isn't this a butterfly?
No, it's not.
Wow!
Doesn't it hurt?
Does it hurt a little?
I'll give you a good one.
I have to give you a good one.
Is it okay now?
She is being attacked.
But I think I can do it.
Let's attack the chinko.
Chinko.
You're like a geisha.
Let's attack.
I can't do this.
Chinko Bibi-chan.
I did it.
Who is going to shoot?
Who's going to take a picture of this?
What is this guy?
It's fashionable.
What is this?
It's so modern.
Do you want to take a picture?
Yes.
I got a kiss.
A kiss.
A kiss from Ayu-chan.
This is good.
This feels good.
Ayu-chan, Ayu-chan's kiss.
I'm going to use my nose to attack Chikubi.
This is amazing.
I got a kiss.
Ayu-chan's Chikubi.
How do you feel?
It's been a long time since I've been here.
Wow!
How do you feel, Seiko?
I feel good.
How do you feel?
Nice to meet you.
Wow!
Wow, baby!
Wow, wow!
Wow!
You look happy.
Wow, how do you feel?
I feel good.
It's so cute.
Let's take a look over here.
Let's take a look over here too.
Everyone, please look at different places.
Let's take a picture.
Let's go.
How is it?
Chiko, you can take a picture.
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You are being petted in various places.
I want to pet it.
You are amazing.
I can't pet it.
I want to pet it.
It's amazing.
This?
He wants you to pet him.
He's so naughty.
He's so cute.
Which part do you like?
Various parts.
Teacher, you're doing great.
Wow, it's so clear!
Is it about to come out?
It's so clear!
You can put it out one more time!
Put it out a lot!
Everyone is watching.
I'm so hungry.
I wonder if they're really hungry.
Which one do you like? The strong one?
I like it.
Oh my!
Let me out!
Let's go!
One, two, one, two, one, two!
One, two, one, two!
Oh my, there are so many of them!
I saw it.
Look at it.
How did it fly?
Wow!
Look at it!
It's amazing.
Look at it.
I want to eat it too!
Michi drank it!
Come on!
I want to eat it too!
Thank you very much!
Congratulations!
That was MakoBus and MakoBus!
The correct answer is 95% of the answers, so it's embarrassing if you get it wrong.
I'll explain it to you.
You have to listen to the notice.
You won't say it again.
The rule is to guess the order of the girls who are blindfolded and the boys who are shuffled without the blindfold.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The team with the highest number of correct answers will receive an expensive present!
Thank you!
Everyone, please close your eyes!
What is this game?
I can't see you.
If you can see me, I'll punish you.
Really?
I won't do it.
If you can see me, I won't punish you.
I won't punish you.
How many do you have?
Help! Help!
Ah, the button came out!
What's going on?
How many people are here?
Let's start the live!
I got it!
Wow! I can feel it!
Ichiban!
Ichiban's man is here.
It's just me, right?
Don't touch it!
It's red.
When will it come?
Is it coming?
No, it hasn't come yet.
Okay.
It's cold.
The boys will be exposed if they make a sound.
Like U, A, or Z.
I want number 1.
Here we go! Change!
I remember.
It's the first one.
I think this is the second one.
Where?
I think number 2.
Wait, my hair is really messy.
I see.
This is number 1.
This is number 2.
Yes.
Number 2.
Let's take it out.
It's so fast!
You're only talking about the first one.
What about the second one?
The second one is...
I think it's warm.
Warm?
It's warm.
I remember.
It's big.
I can't get in.
Does it feel good?
Can you eat it?
I don't know if it's dry or not.
I think I know what it is.
I know.
Change!
This is the fourth one.
Do you understand?
You finally understood.
I don't know.
There are 10 members.
Men and women.
Change.
I don't know.
Is this shuffle change?
The second time.
Don't touch it.
You will understand.
Are you nervous?
It's dangerous.
Please wait for a moment.
I'm the only one.
Everyone is doing it.
Why do you make it?
Change.
Oh, it's hot.
It's so big.
Change!
Uwaaah!
Oh!
It's going to be forgotten.
It's so big.
Uwaaah!
It's really big.
Change!
It's a little more.
It's the last one.
If you shake it,
You can hit it with the window.
You can hit it if you don't have it.
I think I can understand.
The fourth one is a little longer.
My hands are sticky.
Do you understand?
The second one is the smallest.
The third one is probably the second one.
It's probably the second one.
And the first one is...
But if you forget the rest...
It's the sixth one.
The sixth one is the third one.
The seventh one.
The second one is...
I wrote the second one.
What is it?
The first step is to make a circle.
Is there any difference?
OK, cut!
Don't take a picture of your eyebrows yet!
This is the end, but you still have to take a picture of your eyebrows.
You can't take a picture of your eyebrows.
Please circle the male and put it in front of the female.
Yes, yes.
Please wear a scarf.
I don't know.
What should I do?
I think so.
What?
Hey.
If you do this,
What are you going to do next?
I'm going to trade.
What?
I don't know if I'm going to trade.
Please take a picture.
Yes.
I'm going to take a picture.
Please take a picture.
Yes.
It's bright.
It's fun!
Please get used to it.
I don't know.
A man is already playing shuffle.
Let's start.
Fela-chin time start!
Thank you very much.
Everyone, please pay.
Please pay in the direction of delivery.
Then, please go in that direction.
I got it.
You don't listen to the instructions.
Let's clean up.
Let's vote.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Here you are.
Is it like this?
But I can see it.
It's like this.
No.1
No.1?
I see
No way
No.1 photo
No.3 photo
What?
Really?
No.1 photo
No way
Really?
No.4 photo
Mine is No.2 photo
Can I put it in?
I think it's definitely number 4.
I got it.
Can I put it in?
I'll put it in.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
My legs are sore.
Let's go inside.
Look at the entrance.
It's open.
Let's go, Shin-chan.
It's so big!
Wow, it's huge!
I can't do it anymore.
It's so big.
I don't think I can do it alone.
Which one is the best?
Everyone said number 4.
Definitely number 4.
I think the difference between number 1 and number 2 is that number 2 is a little thicker.
Huh? You didn't notice?
I couldn't reach the bottom.
Number 2.
So I think number 2 is...
Do you want to exchange?
I do.
That's suspicious.
Number 2.
This is number 1?
I think it's probably number 1, but I don't know if it's number 2.
But the amount of hair is number 1.
I don't know.
You got it, didn't you?
How many do you want?
It came out.
What should I do?
What number is it?
It was number 4.
Number 4.
Number 1.
Number 1?
4, 2, 1
4, 2, 3
3?
I'm sure it's number 4
Do you like Chikume too?
Number 3?
Are you sleeping?
I'm not sleeping
It's out
OK, OK
I'm not sleeping
Are you OK?
Yeah
You look like you're going to fall
I feel good.
What?
Wait.
That's...
That's right.
What?
I got the same score as you.
Please continue.
This face.
I thought it was okay because you looked like you were in pain.
It was my first time, so I felt really good.
How was it?
Do you feel good?
Keep going.
You'll probably never forget it.
Wow!
You'll remember this face.
Right?
You'll remember it.
How was it?
Are you feeling good?
It was amazing.
It was a good memory, wasn't it?
It was captured on VTR.
Look, it's in there.
Can't I show my face?
You don't have to see it.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
I feel good too.
No, is this a game I'm playing?
It's okay.
Is it okay?
3 minutes left.
You can write it in 3 minutes.
You can't write it like that.
I don't know.
I think it's number 2.
What?
This is number 1.
Wait a minute.
It feels good.
I'm so tired.
Wait a minute, I'm already sweating.
Isn't it number 1?
Isn't it?
I think it's number 1.
Number 4.
Number 4, number 4.
What is it?
A foot?
Is it a foot?
I see
He's going to poop
You're going to poop?
Yes, he's going to poop
I can't
She said it.
It's hidden.
Everyone said it.
She said this.
Please don't say that.
She said it.
Say it.
Please don't say that.
It's Yura!
It came out!
Amazing!
This is your first time, isn't it?
I won't say it.
Everyone, 30 seconds left!
30 seconds left!
It came out!
Are you okay?
It was comfortable.
Don't make fun of me.
1st place, right?
10 seconds left.
1st place.
2nd place?
Really?
It's amazing.
Look at this.
I'm going.
Everyone is going.
Everyone is going here?
Mr.Dote graduated.
It's a graduation.
But it's a little half, isn't it?
It's about Dote now.
Next.
OK, everyone, let's do a thinking time.
OK.
Ishikawa, a man shouldn't get up yet.
You can see it.
OK, let's do it.
Thinking time.
Think about it.
Which one?
Shall we say it together?
Ready, set, go!
No worries!
Can we get the number plate?
Then, number 3!
What?
Can we get the number plate?
The number plate?
Yeah
Let's write it down
I wonder if it's number 3.
That's correct.
This person is number 1.
You got it right.
If you get it right next time, you're correct.
This person is number 3.
Congratulations.
Correct.
Team Tarutsu is correct.
Let's go to the dog team.
Dote-kun is No. 4, right?
Yes, come on.
This boy is also No. 3, right?
Yes, correct.
If this person is No.2, it is correct.
Team U-san, please go ahead.
Congratulations!
Next is the Neko-san team.
Who is Neko-san?
Neko-san team is also here.
There is no meaning.
This Tadaka-kun is 1!
Yay!
He's right, he's right!
This Bōhatsu-Yarōu is also 4!
Yay!
This Bōhatsu-Ossan is also 2!
Correct!
Yay!
Now, the last one!
Chameleon team!
Chameleon?
Is it called Chameleon team?
Now, I just got it.
I'm the first one, aren't I?
Correct!
I'm the second one, aren't I?
Go ahead!
I'm the fourth one, aren't I?
That's correct!
You say it yourself!
Congratulations!
Yay!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
That's correct!
Everyone, please come out one by one for each team.
I'll give you a big round of applause.
You understand, right?
As much as possible, I think Fukuyaka will be better.
Now, everyone.
Let's have a toast.
Fukuyaka is better.
What is it?
Let's have a toast and play rock-paper-scissors.
I didn't hear you.
What? What?
What are you going to do?
What?
We're going to play rock-paper-scissors.
No way.
Rock-paper-scissors.
It's hard to see.
Why are you laughing?
Let's eat.
Everyone.
Let's do it!
Oppari janken!
First, Pai!
Janken Pai!
Oh, no!
This is Pa, right?
This is Gu, right?
This is Aiko, right?
Aiko and Pai!
This is Choki, right?
This is Gu, right?
Gu and Choki
I made a mistake
Let's go to the final round.
Let's go!
This is embarrassing!
Be serious!
Rock, paper, scissors!
This is embarrassing!
Please stand in front of the camera.
The luxury goods are coming.
Please wait a moment.
I heard it's a luxury product.
What is it?
It may be a present.
Can I have it?
The Moody's.
The world's Moody's.
I'm so happy.
What is it?
Congratulations!
Thank you so much!
There are about 50 million people watching this video.
Please look at the camera.
I'm so happy.
I use it every day at home.
It's the fifth machine.
This is the fourth machine.
I'm the first machine.
Thank you very much.
It was a matching game.
Let's do it again next time.
Thank you very much.
Let's look at the boxed room.
You were young at that time.
Start!
What is that?
Let's start!
Oh!
Wow! It's beautiful!
Wow!
It looks like a pear tree.
It's interesting.
It looks like a banana tree.
Xuanyi
I can't drink it.
But you can drink it.
Drink it.
What is this?
It's coming out, it's coming out
It's funny
It's been black for a long time
It's like a movie.
It's good.
It's true.
It's good and fun.
This is so much fun.
This is because it's that season.
It's cold now.
Let's get on the bus!
Takobasu!
I'm going to the bathroom.
Did you turn on the camera?
I did.
Let's go!
Mama!
Mama looks so fun!
Neko-kun you're so cute!
Mama looks so cute!
Oh my god!
You're a baby!
I was born!
Mama is so cute!
Look, it's breast milk.
Mom!
The breast milk is coming out!
It's coming out, it's coming out.
The breast milk is coming out from the mouth.
Oh, no.
I'll hold it for you, Ai-chan.
I've finished brushing my teeth.
Look.
Let's see how it goes.
Go ahead.
Fail.
The biggest fail in this room.
What are you going to do?
Say it's a failure.
I'm going to make an oppa.
Try sticking it on.
Stick it on.
It's cold!
Shoes, please!
It's so cold!
Do we go outside?
It's cold!
Can you close the curtain?
Are you sure?
Yes!
I'm sorry. It's night.
Let's open it when we can see the sea.
No.
I can see the sea from here.
It's open.
Let's open it.
It's true. The next door is also open.
One, two, three.
There is something.
Is it a ghost?
Who is it?
What were you doing?
I was trying to kiss you, but what are you doing?
I was petting the window.
The window?
You were petting the window?
It's a new window.
It's all wet.
It's all wet here.
Look, this is just the right height for you, Ruu-chan.
Are you all wearing your underwear?
Huh?
Huh? No one's wearing their underwear?
I'm not wearing my underwear.
You're lying.
I'm not wearing my underwear either.
Why am I the only one wearing my underwear?
No pants?
No pants.
No one's wearing anything on the top.
The camera went off.
No pants, no pants.
Yay!
I'm not wearing anything.
You're right.
Why are you wearing panties?
Why?
You can't.
If you're an AV actress,
you have to wear no pants and no bra.
You can't.
It's natural, right?
It's always like that.
I wear room wear and pajamas at home.
It's NO PAN NO BRA, right?
No, it's not!
What?
Aimee soy sauce is NO PAN NO BRA.
There was such a record?
That's right.
I didn't know.
You didn't know?
That's right.
If you break it, it's a fine.
I'll do it today.
What are you doing today?
No, no, no.
It's a little...
It's gone.
So, this is the secret.
There's no one to tell the secret.
You have to take it off.
Why?
You have to take it off quickly.
You have to take it off here.
I'm so excited!
So cute!
You're so cute!
Let's go outside!
Let's run outside!
Let's run from the hallway.
Let's release all the sounds.
Full speed.
Full power.
Let's go.
We're going to film.
It was too much.
What are you wearing?
It looks fun.
I want to do it too.
I'm scared.
It smells good.
Try it.
It's 1500 yen for DMV.
I want to try it too.
It's hard.
It's premium.
How much is it?
It's so cute.
Is it an auction?
It's 3500 yen.
It's cheap.
This one is 5000 yen.
It's in.
Let's run.
Let's go.
Ready, go!
Cute!
It just became a show-off.
Poor you.
Look, the AV actress is Nobun Nobun.
Nobun Nobun.
Nobun.
I'm waiting.
I can't hear Nobun.
Nobun Nobun.
It's a basic.
It's basic.
Chira!
Everyone!
It's wonderful!
What are you doing?
Let's run together.
What the hell are we doing?
Let's stand in a line.
My butt hurts.
One, two, three, four.
Ta-da!
I'm so tired.
What's going on here?
You're so small.
There's a stranger.
I'm scared.
What's happening?
It's coming off.
I like you guys.
They're perverts.
It's the same with the flag.
It's coming off.
Yui Hadake!
What are you doing?
What is this?
Yui Hadake!
Bye-bye!
I'm going to take a picture of Kamihata Ichika and the girl's room from now on.
What are you doing?
It's so funny.
I'm so embarrassed.
Don't be embarrassed.
I can see your boobs.
I wonder if someone will come out.
I can see the boobs!
I wonder if someone is watching us.
The boobs!
I can see the boobs.
I can't see anyone, so I'm so embarrassed.
This is bad!
Let's go to the bathroom.
We have to go to the bathroom.
Wait, wait!
Wait!
Why is Ichika-chan wearing something?
What is it?
What is it? It's weird.
We have to go to the bathroom.
Let's do it together!
This is fun!
This feels good!
Where?
Over there.
Is everyone here?
I don't think so.
I haven't seen them yet.
Let's take a look.
What is Shizuka doing?
Oh, right.
I wonder what everyone is doing.
What?
They're not here.
Where are you guys?
Where are you?
I can hear you.
Oh, really?
What? What? What?
Isn't anyone here?
What are you doing?
You can't see clearly here.
Don't look at me.
What are you doing?
It's a mess.
Show me.
What are you doing?
Are you feeling good?
Are you getting wet?
Nishikawa-chan, take a picture of that.
What's going on there?
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
What's going on?
I'm getting wet.
Are you getting wet?
One, two, three, go!
Wait, what are you doing hiding under the bed?
What about Ayu-chan?
I don't know.
Where did Ayu-chan go?
Isn't she in her room?
Why is she under the desk?
Because she's excited.
Are you excited?
Ayu-chan, are you happy?
Ayu-chan is not here.
Ayu?
Ayu-san!
Where are you?
I'm in the way.
Ayu, where are you?
I'm here.
You weren't in the room?
I didn't see you.
The balcony is open.
It's cold.
Ayu-san, where are you?
Why?
Wait, wait, wait.
No way.
What's going on?
What is it?
I don't know what it is.
I'm sorry.
Haruka, you're so cute!
What are you doing?
You're the best!
What is it?
It feels good!
Amazing!
What is it?
Ichi too!
It feels good!
Ichi?
Really?
It's amazing!
Look at her butt!
It's sticking out!
It feels so good!
I love it!
That was so good!
That was a kiss!
Isn't that so good?
I want to do it with you too
I haven't done it yet
Me neither
That feels so good
It feels so good.
I want to go home.
You don't want to go home?
Good evening. I'd like to introduce our room.
Please follow me.
I'm Minato Riku.
Let me introduce our room.
Let's go.
Ta-da!
They are sleeping now
One of them is sitting
The room looks like this
I can hear their voices
Let's leave them alone
This one is...
Let's go to the bathroom.
What are you doing?
I was in the bathroom.
You were in the bathroom?
I was trying to do it.
Don't worry about me.
But it's a little embarrassing.
It's okay. If you want, you can take it off.
Then I can still see it.
It's okay.
I can't stand it.
Hurry up.
Oh no.
I think I'm being watched.
I'm nervous.
I can't stand it.
I'm peeing.
Let's take a look at the camera.
You have a good tongue.
Did you decide that?
I've been holding it in.
Please stay there.
Don't leave me.
Come over here.
I was suddenly surprised in the bathroom.
Next, let's take a look at the room.
I just saw it.
This back view is probably...
Ah, she's using it.
What are you doing there using the rotor?
Who are you?
I'm KONNO HIKARU.
KONNO HIKARU, what are you doing?
Please continue.
Here is ABENOMIKU.
It's open.
And...
It's a little open.
Suspicious.
Is it okay to open it?
Here we go.
One, two, three!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Tsubomi-san who is doing onani in the back.
I like darkness.
Do you get excited when it's dark?
Then I'll keep my hands closed.
Can you show me?
You don't have to worry about the camera.
Can I?
Yes, please.
Are you putting your finger in now?
I can hear the sound.
How do you feel about being a girl in the dark?
Do you feel good?
I feel good.
You are cute.
This is Ms. Tsubumi who is a girl.
I was surprised that she was a girl when she opened her buttocks.
What are you doing?
I'm going to the bathroom.
I'm back from the bathroom.
What are you doing?
I see something over there.
What?
Is that a magazine cover?
A magazine cover.
You're laughing.
You're acting suspiciously.
What are you filming?
I'm filming an AV right now.
Miku-chan, do you like girls?
I like girls.
Really? I really like girls.
What?
Let's kiss.
Someone take a picture of me.
I was acting like I was in a good mood.
Wait wait wait wait wait
What are you doing?
She's coming to see
Wait
So cute
What is this?
Look look look
Look at her butt
Tsugumi-san is looking at it
It's a magazine
Amazing
Are you going to do it?
You don't like it?
What did I say?
I don't like it.
You were alone in a dark place.
You were very sexy.
I was looking at the mirror.
Were you looking at yourself?
I found a sexy girl.
Who are you?
I'm Shinobegami.
You found me.
You're so cute.
What are you going to do?
Look at me.
You're so cute.
Let's leave Tsubomi-san and the other two sleeping together.
I wonder if it's still like this.
It's still outside.
Isn't one person not enough?
One person is not enough.
Are you hiding your hair?
No, I'm hiding my hair.
It's not on the air conditioner.
Wait a minute.
Look, it's Abeno.
Good morning, Abeno-san.
Good morning, Natsume.
Wait, wait, wait.
Natsume is here too.
Natsume Yuki is here too.
Did you film all of us?
I filmed Natsume sleeping.
Really?
I filmed all of you.
Don't say scary things.
I thought I dropped something.
You're kidding, right?
Because...
That's where you put the futon.
Wait, it's dark!
Scary, scary, scary!
What?
Wait, wait, wait.
There's nothing.
It's dark, it's dark. Wait a minute.
What is it?
Be careful.
Hey, the camera is too dark to be seen.
Something is falling.
Scary, scary, scary.
Can I get a pillow?
A blanket.
What are you doing?
Mikan?
I was really surprised.
What's wrong?
KURURUGIMIKAN-SAN is in the middle of the bed.
What are you doing?
Well...
What is it?
What are you doing?
I'm writing down the heart-throbbing and the heart-throbbing of Kimo-dameshi.
Oh, I see.
I can't understand you.
I see.
Everyone's here.
Abe-no-san, what are you doing with your phone?
Abe-no-san, what are you doing?
Abe-no-san?
What are you doing?
Abe-no-san, what are you doing?
I'm just waking up.
Abe-no-san!
Oh no!
This is Yuki Natsume, who is watching the girls in Abeno-san's village.
Minato is a good role, so it's okay.
Really, how many times did you get hit in the head today?
No, not here.
I can not go. I can not go.
Because.
Really.
The role to put in the pattern.
Someone put it in a little bit, just now.
Really?
My whole body is in trouble.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
Pervert.
It doesn't matter.
Everyone is a pervert.
Who is the person who was a woman while turning on the rotor?
Oh, I see.
Well, then, we'll continue tonight.
Thank you very much. See you later.
This is for you.
Did you get it?
I got it.
Wait, wait!
Thank you.
I'm Tsubomi.
I'll start eating.
Thank you.
Thank you!
Can I eat Shabu-Shabu?
This is shabu-shabu.
Shabu-shabu.
I can't open it.
Add vegetables.
Is this the one with cabbage?
Yes.
It looks delicious with vegetables.
Add vegetables.
Add meat.
Yes.
Cheers.
It's good!
Thank you for the meal!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Let's eat!
I can't drink it, so I asked Natsume to drink it for me.
Yay!
It looks good.
It's good.
The way you put it in is very good.
It's hard.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
How is the egg?
It's delicious.
Cheers.
Why did you say that?
Ready, set, go!
Let's go!
Everyone!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Now, let's go to the bathroom.
Please follow me.
Please go inside.
Please.
Thank you.
Everyone, please stand here.
Everyone, please come in.
Are you ready?
Hurry up! Hurry up!