I'm home.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
Did anything interesting
happen at work today?
Did you have any strange
customers? As usual.
Electricity, shoes,
Electricity, shoes, laundry.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
I've heard that before.
I want to talk about
something fun when I'm eating.
Don't you want to go on a
trip next month? I'm sorry.
I don't feel like that even
if you say it suddenly.
I see. I'm sorry.
You know,
I don't want to say this because
I don't want to get into a fight,
but you have to keep your promise.
When you come home, you leave
the lights on everywhere in the house.
You don't have your shoes on.
You leave the laundry out.
The electric bill is not free.
I'm sorry.
You don't keep your promise no
matter how many times I tell you.
But you don't have to be so angry.
I'm telling you to keep your promise.
If you don't keep your
promise, you'll be worried
that you'll be cheated
again. Don't you know that?
I know, but I swore to Yamato that I
wouldn't cheat. I'm keeping my promise.
When did you talk about it?
It was three years ago.
It's been three years,
so it doesn't matter.
I've kept my promise not to cheat on you.
If you insist, I can't see what's inside.
I don't want to see it.
I'm going to bed.
Wash it and throw it away.
Are you awake?
I'm sorry about today.
I'll be careful from tomorrow.
I'm sorry I said too much.
Do you want to go on a trip next month?
Yes.
Please look up some candidates.
Okay.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Yes.
Thank you for choosing a
convenience store today.
I know.
Thank you.
I made up with you.
It's not a kiss.
I think I feel like that today.
I think so, too.
It's been a long time.
Yeah.
Don't you want to take
a shower? No, I'm fine.
It felt good, but I need to
get in the mood a little more.
I'll go take a shower.
Good night.
You heard everything
today, didn't you? Yes, I did.
Let's eat.
Hey, don't flush the water.
Don't let it out.
Can you be a little more gentle?
Not gentle, but careful.
I don't know if it breaks suddenly.
It's white. You can tell by the smell.
I don't know.
Even if I know, I don't
know if I shouldn't let it out.
I don't know.
Don't you understand if I
don't tell you everything?
I'd like to, but...
I'll tell you next time.
But you'll make the same mistake again.
I've told you so many times
about the weather and the laundry.
I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
Do you think I haven't kept
my promise not to cheat on you?
I've been telling you that I haven't.
I don't have any proof.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you here to fight at home?
No, I just want to have fun with you.
But you're always the one
who says something like a fight.
Then please be careful not to do that.
I'll be careful from tomorrow.
You always try to end
the conversation like that.
You don't protect me.
I want to forgive you
for cheating on me, but
I'm worried if you don't
keep your promise.
It's hard for me to be
suspected every time I don't do it.
It's hard for me too.
I don't want to do it! Fine.
You can cheat on me again.
I did it, too.
What are you talking about?
I didn't say that.
You don't understand me at all.
I'm telling you that you
can do the same thing.
I don't want to cheat on you.
I don't think so.
When I cheated on you,
we talked a lot, didn't we?
Yes.
I thought I'd get a divorce
when I knew I'd cheated on you.
But you tried so hard to forgive
me, so I decided not to get a divorce.
I don't know why I decided to do it.
You're right.
What if I cheat on you?
I won't get mad at you.
But I might get a divorce.
I'm not hungry anymore.
I'm going to take a shower.
In the middle of the night.
Are you Ms.
Akarin? Yes, I am.
Kanayan? Yes, I am.
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
You are very beautiful.
Not at all.
I have made a reservation at the
restaurant you were talking about.
Shall we go? Yes, please.
It's about five minutes from here.
It's close.
Gratin is famous here.
I want to try it.
It's this way, so let's go.
Did you like Japanese
food better? I like both.
I ate a lot, so I'm hungry.
Me too. It was delicious.
I'm glad you liked it.
There was a lot of seafood in it.
It was delicious.
Thank you very much.
Have you ever been to a
hotel with this kind of app?
No, you said it was your
first time to use an app.
Yes, I wanted to try it.
You must be curious.
Yes, I am.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby crying.
The baby is crying.
Thank you very much.
Ms. Akarin, you were amazing.
I'm glad.
Did you feel good?
Yes.
Was there anything wrong?
Did something happen between you two?
No, it's not like that.
The reason why we met like this today...
My husband cheated on me before.
I forgave him.
When we had a fight the
other day, I said to him,
「I cheated on you, so you
should cheat on me, too.
」 Yes.
That's why I'm here today.
That's why I came here.
I came here because I wanted to know
how my husband felt when he threw up.
I felt like I was disconnected.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
If you want to see me
again, please contact me.
Thank you.
Yes.
夜中、。 I'm home.
I'm home.
It's rare to see you here.
Hey, can I talk to you
after I change my clothes?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I cheated on you.
What?
I said I could cheat on you, so I did.
How far did you cheat
on me? Until the end.
Do you have any questions?
Is there anything you want to know?
What kind of person was she?
Do you want to know?
Aren't you jealous?
Of what you've done for me.
Of this feeling.
You know...
Shall we... Get a divorce?
What?
I thought about it when you cheated on me.
I thought about it when you
told me I could cheat on you.
I thought about it when you cheated on me.
I don't like it.
I'm stubborn.
I see.
We cheated on each other.
I won't be lenient with you.
I don't care. I've changed.
I don't want to get a divorce.
But I have the right to
say that I cheated on you.
I don't want to change Akari's mind.
I don't have the right to say that.
I'm going to write it
because it's important, but
instead of writing it,
can I say one condition?
What is it?
Don't have sex at the end.
Why?
If I write this and submit
it, I'll be a stranger, right?
I like Akari, and I can't get
along with others so quickly.
I feel like I'll be cut off
if I have sex at the end.
I thought you'd say something else.
You don't have to write to me.
Really?
But you know what?
If you're going to do it, let's
have a sex that feels good.
And?
I want you to make me regret.
I can't have sex with such a good woman.
I understand.
I'll make you regret.
I'll do it for you.
OK.
If you take a shower, you'll catch a cold.
What?
Even if you sleep every
day, you smell so smooth.
It's good.
What's that? Are you cheating on me?
No, it's a spare.
Give me a kiss.
You are very wet.
I'm going to work out.
I'm tired.
It's longer than usual, isn't it?
What did you think of that man?
Why do you want to know?
If you do that, I'll ask you, too.
You're full of lies.
Get out of my way.
It feels so good.
Hey, relax.
Can't you do it?
You want to regret
it, don't you? I'm sorry.
If you were a good boy,
we could have sex forever.
Right?
※This is the sound of a baby crying.
I'm going to make a mood.
It's the last one.
I'm determined to win.
I was so close to win.
I was so nervous.
I felt so good.
Can you go home?
I'll do it tomorrow.
I have to work until
night, so I'll do it today.
Today?
I'll go if you change,
but let's go together.
OK.
OK, let's change.
It's hot.
It's humid.
I remember walking like
this when we were dating.
What? A memory talk?
It's a good time.
It's been a long time since I laughed.
When we first dated,
Akari was so drunk that it was
dangerous to walk on the street at night.
Do you remember?
I think I was excited.
Why?
I have to take off my ring.
Oh, I see.
It's strange, isn't it?
If I wear a ring.
I think so.
What do you do with this ring?
Do you want to sell it?
No, I don't want to.
It looks like it has electricity in it.
By the way, did you bring the
divorce certificate? Yes, I did.
What?
I told you to put it at the end.
Why is it like this?
Is it okay?
No, it's impossible.
The letters are torn here.
I don't think they'll take it.
It's impossible.
Let's rewrite it.
There's a new one, but
it's too far to go home.
What should I do?
Isn't there a cafe around here?
I don't want to go to a cafe.
It's embarrassing to be seen
writing something like this.
Then there's a good place.
Let's write there.
Really? Yeah.
Oh, I thought I put it in properly.
Be firm.
Until the end.
It's true.
Please check the delivery of divorce.
Isn't it too dirty?
I thought this is the only
place that can't be seen.
Well, let's go.
Do you want something
to drink? No, I'm fine.
I don't want my hair to get dirty.
Are you sure? Yes, I'm fine.
It's been a while since
we've been to a small hotel.
The last time we went to a
small hotel was 5 or 6 years ago.
We went to see the sea in Fukui.
It was so delicious that I
could see the sea of the sea.
Yes, it was.
The crab was delicious.
It was so delicious.
It was in the middle of winter,
but the heater didn't work at all.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
It was on all the time.
Yes, it was.
Even today, there was only a breeze.
It was so cold that we
were hugging each other.
Are you going to buy a dojo
and not let me get a divorce?
I'm not going to do that.
I'm going to get a divorce.
OK, go home.
OK.
I have a condition.
What?
I'm still alive, so I'm going to
have sex with you at the end.
Are you going to do
it again? That's right.
I'm going to do it again.
Otherwise, I won't write it.
You just want to have sex.
It doesn't matter if I want to have sex.
I've always wanted to break up.
But I've been fighting all
the time since I got home.
Well, it's bad because I'm here.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
earlier, but I still wanted to do it.
You should have told me earlier.
This is the last time.
Do you want to do it here?
Let's go to bed.
Akari.
Yes?
It's the last night, so
let's have the best sex.
What's that line?
You're the worst.
Do you want to see it soon?
Yes.
Okay.
You don't know how to
take off your clothes, do you?
Do you know? Do your best.
I'll do it for you.
You are so kind today.
You are so kind.
Sometimes it hurts a little.
Does it feel good here?
Yes.
Really?
Who invented it?
It's you, isn't
it? No, it's not.
It wasn't like that.
It's the last one, so I'll do it for you.
It's stained.
I hate selfishness.
I really hate it.
Hey.
Remember Lady First.
Okay?
Hey.
If you don't remember that, you'll make her
sad forever. Do you understand? I understand.
You don't understand.
How do you feel?
Are you comfortable?
Yes, I'm comfortable.
I like being licked by Akari the most.
That's why I'm late.
Oh, it's hot.
What?
I don't have a rubber band.
Do you? Yes, I do.
Why do you always have it?
I just happen to have it.
You must be lying. You're keeping it.
Akari always tells me to put it on.
Of course she tells you to put it on.
Unlike you, she does it properly.
Hey, did you put a rubber
band around your armpit?
What?
What? Of course not.
You're lying.
You're lying, aren't you?
This is the last one.
Of course.
Oh, it's good.
It feels good.
I can't do it.
I want to do it more.
It feels good.
Give me a kiss.
Feels good.
What? Feels good.
Give me a kiss.
Make it stronger.
Do it like a wind.
It feels good.
It's funny.
I'm having sex, but I can't get a divorce.
I'll never do it again.
Isn't it too funny?
I don't want to have sex with you.
What are you talking about?
You're the worst.
What's that? It's not bad.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Please do not re-upload without permission.
Don't you want to go to bed?
You want to go to bed, don't you?
Are you going to sleep with this?
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Oh, it feels so good.
This is the last one. Thank you.
Hey, do you want to do this?
I wanted to do this.
Don't do it like an experiment.
It's the last one, so please forgive me.
Then, I'll give you a lot.
You're always like this.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God?
But, you know, I was sick the other day.
But, you know, my head feels good.
I'll never say it again.
Why are you laughing?
Well, you know.
..
You know, I've been working
with a guy for a long time.
Suddenly, he came into my life.
I don't know.
It's strange, isn't it?
What's with that face?
You look like you just got off
work, but there's still some left.
What? Over there.
What?
Marriage certificate.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
Ah! No, no, no.
Here.
Yes.
Please keep your promise.
There's something to do
before you go to the shower.
Don't mess it up again.
It's okay.
How do you feel about the last sex?
It was the best.
What's that?
It was the most comfortable I've ever had.
Really? You know, men.
..
...feel sorry for you at
times like this, don't they?
Well, I'm going to take a shower.
You were able to get out safely.
Yes, I was.
Now that I'm out, I feel much better.
I was surprised.
Let's go there and talk.
We used to go to the park at night.
Yes, we did.
Even though we had nothing.
We didn't have money.
You're right.
It was fun.
It was raining a lot.
Sometimes it seems to get entangled.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It was very early for us to run away.
Is it okay today?
It was raining yesterday.
Yes, it is.
It's a strange weather today.
It's sunny and rainy.
Yes, yes, yes. It's been a lot lately.
Do you want to sit down a little?
Yes.
Unexpectedly, it was refreshing.
Yeah.
You know,
the man at the reception at night,
he was like,
yes, yes,
and it was over in a second.
At the reception,
he was bright and smiling.
Yeah.
That's why it was
good, like this.
Maybe.
What are you going to do now?
I haven't decided yet.
I'll think about it when I wake up.
I have to find a house.
Let's talk about that later.
I'm going to clean up the house.
You can leave the electricity
and air conditioner on.
I don't want to.
I've been raising public funds lately.
Thank you for your hard work.
What are you going
to do? This? Yeah.
Throw it?
Yeah, that's good.
Let's do that.
Wait a minute.
Let's go with one, two.
Let's go together.
OK, I'll definitely make you fly far away.
OK, let's go.
OK.
One, two.
It's the last joint work.
It went well.
Right?
Thank you for everything.
Thank you, too.
Be happy.
Akari Mama.
Bye-bye.