FUJISAKI YUKARI in the middle of the night
Hello!
It's hot, isn't it? It's so hot.
Yes, it was hot.
Really? Yes, it was.
It's hot, isn't it?
That's why I brought a special watermelon.
It was a little heavy, though.
This is a mini-watermelon.
It's a little hot,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
Let's cool it down and eat it.
Yes.
It's good, isn't
it? No, it's not.
Is that so? Yes, it is.
You guys seem to get along well.
Not at all, not at all.
Really?
Yes.
But you two are close, aren't you?
We don't have any special relationship.
Really?
What about you, Akemi?
I don't want you to say it, but my
husband has been cheating on me lately.
Really?
I didn't mean to look at it, but I was on my phone
on the table, and it wasn't locked, so I didn't
mean to look at it, but when I looked at LINE, I
was having a fun conversation with a young woman.
Oh my god, I can't believe it.
I've never seen him saying,
I'll be there,
even though he sent me a
message that he'll be there.
Oh my god,
I can't believe it.
I'm not going to say anything,
but he's going to make money
for me, right?
But divorce is
Yeah, it's a pain in the ass.
If I go there, as long as Marudake
doesn't tell me, I don't want to do it.
Oh, yeah.
Do you want to take a doctor
and go on a trip with everyone?
That's a good idea.
But I don't care about that.
It doesn't matter to me.
But, you know, in LINE,
you don't have to send a
message that you are sexless.
You don't have to do that.
Don't you think so?
I can't believe it.
That's true.
But,
if you have been together for a long
time, couples are like that, aren't they?
We haven't been together for years.
I don't think so.
Sexist is normal.
Is that so?
How about you,
Yukari? Well, I'm.
..
Well, I'm... I'm fine.
Well... I've been less often.
But, I do it a little.
That's great.
Well... I don't know.
Actually, I'm a little more like a work.
Actually, I'm a little more like a priest.
I wanted to do something like this.
That's a luxury.
I want you to do it.
Like this?
I want to do this.
You are so cute.
You look like you are
eating fruit with your husband.
I am worried about what will happen.
I think we will wait for a while.
I think so, too.
It would be better if you ate it.
What's going on?
Are you wearing a heart when you transform?
Of course I am!
That's great!
I want my husband to wear it too!
You're not wearing
it? No, I'm not.
It's like a circle.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
Are you hungry?
Yes.
Is it curry today?
I haven't eaten curry for a long time.
Do you want to drink
with me? Sounds good.
Let's go out.
OK.
I'll change my clothes.
I can't afford this.
Look at this!
Oh! Wait a minute for a moment!
Oh! Wait!
It's filled with so much bubbles.
Amazing!
Wow!
It looks delicious.
Thank you.
It's a special way to open.
Yes, I found it.
I opened it randomly.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
I have more than you.
Really?
You have more than I.
I see.
I'll give you this one.
No, it's OK.
I'm OK with this much.
Really?
Next time, I'll drink a different one.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's delicious.
It was hot today, too.
Are you okay? It was hot, wasn't it?
I'm going to make curry.
But it's okay.
Let's eat.
I'll eat, too.
It's delicious.
I think we should open a shop.
A shop?
Can I do it alone? Yes, you can.
I'm going to be a waiter.
Really?
Who are you going to be?
I'm going to be a cook and
you're going to be a waiter?
Yes.
I'm going to be a waitress.
Waitress?
Don't waitresses usually cook?
Yes.
I see.
You should wear maid clothes.
Me?
I'm going to be a cook.
I see.
We live in a time like that.
I'm sure it suits you.
What did you use as a
secret ingredient? Apple? I see.
This is a secret.
If you say so.
That's why it's so sour.
It's a good drink.
My throat is dry.
What's wrong?
I took a picture of the
trip I went to the other day.
Oh, I see.
Did you edit it? I edited it.
I didn't know.
It's a little blurry,
so I'll make it clearer.
That's great. It's like a poster.
I was praised.
Let's go again.
To the southern island.
There is also a hot spring.
Where? Hot spring.
Oh, I like it, too.
We've been there quite a few times.
There are a lot of Hakone
because it's a suburb.
Yeah, how many times have we been there?
We've been there quite a few times.
I feel like I've said it all.
Like Izu.
Yeah.
It's a little far.
It's even further.
Oh, even further?
We've been to Nishi-Izu.
Oh, Nishi-Izu.
It's good, isn't it?
Did we go to Nishizu by train?
It's quite tough.
It ends at Shimoda, so we
have to go this way, don't we?
I think we have to go by rental car.
It was very delicious.
Thank you.
Do you want to drink a little more?
I'll have a little more.
What should we do next?
How about a light one?
How about a fruity one?
Sounds good!
I'll take this one.
Really? Here you are.
Thank you.
How much? This much.
Are you OK? You eat fast.
I found something.
Thank you.
I always watch you.
By the way, I'm sweating a lot.
Don't you sweat?
Well, it was hot today.
Do you want me to take a shower?
Sorry, I haven't taken a bath yet.
It's hot, so I'll just take a shower.
Oh, I see.
Can I have some sake? Oh, sure.
Thank you for the meal.
It's hot.
I did my best.
What did I do wrong?
I should have thought a little more.
I wonder if it would have been
better if I hadn't been there.
Let's go in together.
You're sleepy, aren't you?
I'm not sleepy today.
It's hot, but I've been walking a lot.
It's cold.
Turn it off.
What?
It's still hot, isn't
it? No, it's cold.
Really? Yes, I'm happy.
How was today's meal?
It was delicious.
It's always delicious.
Yes.
Let me know if you feel sick.
Do you want to sleep?
Do you want to
take it off? It's cold.
I'll take it off.
I woke up a little.
Can't you sleep?
No.
But I'm sleepy, so can I go to bed first?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
Yukari Fujisaki I see.
Oh, you can buy it at Rakuten.
You can buy it at Rakuten.
I see.
It's hot every day.
Oh, I see.
White!
White! I'm not sure.
It looks good.
It's not that bad.
I'm eating it.
You're eating it.
But it's white.
I see.
I think I'm the fattest.
You're fat and short.
Stop it!
Are you laughing?
No, I'm not laughing.
You're laughing a lot.
No, I'm not.
I'd like to ask you about your husband.
How is he doing?
He's in the middle of swimming.
I'll have sashimi for dinner.
What's that?
Sashimi? Why?
You're letting him swim, aren't you?
Then, fish and sashimi.
Wow, that's great!
You're so bold.
I'm surprised.
What's that?
Hey, hey, hey, listen.
It's been a while since I had
dinner with my husband last night.
Really?
You heard it, didn't you?
What's wrong with you?
Did you have a good time?
Do you know Kogi? I don't know.
Kogi? Dog? No, it's not.
Is it katakana? No, it's kanji.
It's written as Yuukinuki on the back.
You know Zengi,
right? Yes, I know.
Yes, that kind of story.
Zen practice is done
before marriage, isn't it?
It's like the end version of that.
Oh, so you do something like Zen practice
again after marriage? Yes, yes, yes.
I looked it up on the
Internet, and it said,
deepening the love of
the couple, so I tried it.
Then, I heard that my
husband was fine, too.
So, I kissed him today.
It's great, isn't
it? It's great.
Hey, what kind of things do you do?
What I saw was,
like good manners,
hugging, skinship,
those are also included in the lecture.
You know, in sex,
when a man is satisfied, it's over.
But women are not satisfied at all.
So, in the lecture,
it's important to be with a
woman until she is satisfied.
That's right.
I'm not satisfied at all.
Yukari-san, your voice is too loud.
I don't like it.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
I don't know who is listening to you.
So, you should look it up.
What? Look it up.
I got it.
Thank you.
I'm leaving.
See you.
It's so hot.
What was it?
A lecture?
The snow in the back.
What?
【Q】What is the most common
form of sexual harassment?
1.Sexual harassment that is done in
a manner that is forced upon a woman.
2.Sexual harassment that is done in
a manner that is forced upon a man.
3.Sexual harassment that is done in
a manner that is forced upon a woman.
In the lecture, it is said
to put a kiss on the cheek.
What if I add it to my eyelids?
If you sleep, your partner will
be satisfied and go to bed early.
Oh, this kind of thing. I know.
skinship
light kiss
skinship of sexual intercourse other
than sexual intercourse touch on hair
touch on face
After a short break, such
as lying on each other's
arms and lying on each
other's shoulders and sleeping,
enjoy meals together,
take a bath together, talk
while lying down, and
extend your daily life.
Today's lecture.
Wow.
Oh, I see.
Well.
Hug the first line of the page carefully.
Hug, French kiss, soft touch.
Measure the skin-ship
and enter the second line.
If you can't see the recovery of the side that was
satisfied first, the side that is not satisfied can
be a little patient and exchange opinions on both
sides, make improvements, and move on to the next time.
If you have plenty of time, you
can take a long break at the entrance
or at the table, and then you can
be satisfied enough by doing it twice.
I have a weak point.
Hmm.
I see.
I don't even give a lecture at Bonobo.
Hmm.
Oh, that Bonobo.
It is a human privilege to give a lecture.
It's a bit strange.
I'll talk to him during dinner.
Good sound.
Good.
Lemon sour.
Good sound.
Thank you.
I put a lot of vegetables
because they were cheap.
I put a lot of vegetables in it.
It's good.
Is it good?
When I eat heavy food, my chest hurts.
Your chest hurts?
Yes.
Oh, I see.
That's right.
Let's eat.
It's a little expensive today.
It's a little colorful,
isn't it? It's delicious.
It's the best.
Oh, look.
This time, I'm going to
the museum I always go to.
The museum?
Yes, the museum.
I'm going to have a special
exhibition of my favorite fish.
Is that so?
Yes.
Since when?
It's been about a week since I tasted it.
A week ago?
No, a week later.
A week later?
Is that so? That's soon.
What about the ticket?
What about you?
I thought I'd take a ticket
if I could go with you.
Really? Thank you.
Can you go with me?
Yes.
Vegetables are fat.
I feel guilty.
What are you going to do if
you lose weight more than that?
Am I thin? That's all.
Is that so?
Do you think so? Yes, I do.
But I wanted more meat around here.
Around here?
Yes.
I have a big butt.
So I wanted more breasts.
Other men would see it.
Other men? Yes, other men.
I wonder if they would see it.
I always wear fluffy clothes.
I don't know.
But I don't meet men at all.
Really?
I go out in the daytime.
It doesn't matter if it's daytime.
Yeah.
It's not necessarily that there are no men.
Because I go around the
house and the supermarket.
Is it good? Yeah.
You're happy, aren't you?
It's great that the rice is delicious.
Oh, it's very soft.
Do you know Kogi?
Kogi?
It's a kind of dog,
isn't it? No, it's not.
Kogi.
Kogi?
What's that?
What is Kogi?
Kogi is a character.
Character?
How do you write it?
In Kanji, you write 後の遊戯 and then Kogi.
Oh.
Yeah.
後の遊戯.
Don't you understand?
What?
So, you know, you do that.
That? That.
What? After that.
After that.
What? What? That.
At night.
Something like that?
Yes.
Well.
At night.
After that.
You mean the one you do in the morning
and the one you do in the afternoon?
Yes, the one I do in the morning
and the one I do in the afternoon.
Zen-gi is the one you
do in the morning, right?
And the one I do in the
afternoon is called Kogi.
I see.
I can understand it somehow.
You have your own words.
Yes, I do.
This afternoon, I met my friend,
Kinjo, and she told me a lot of things.
We did a lot of research.
Is that what you were talking about?
Yes.
I see.
I like that kind of conversation.
While you were working hard, I was talking
about craftsmanship, and I looked it up.
Did you look it up?
Yes.
Well, I looked up a lot of things today.
What's that? You wrote a lot of characters.
Look.
Is craftsmanship that difficult?
What is Kougi?
To put it simply,
it is a mandatory act that
makes you tired of sleepiness.
By doing Kougi,
it affects your daily life,
and causes sleepiness.
Isn't it a very important
thing? Yes, it is.
And,
This is a place where you can touch the skin
of your genitals, touch your hair, touch
your face, touch your arm pillows, lie
down, rest a little and then eat together,
take baths, talk while lying
down, and extend your daily life.
This extension is also a kougi.
It's quite wide.
Yes, it is.
I think everyone does it.
Don't they? Well, yes.
They take a shower together.
We haven't taken a shower yet.
They eat together and have fun.
For example, this is a kougi.
This is a kougi.
But we haven't done it yet.
I see.
You're sharp.
No, I'm not. This is Zenki.
Oh, I see.
Yes, this is Zenki.
I see.
Yes.
You're smart.
I don't know, but I think so.
I see.
Yes.
So, shall we do it
today? What? Kogi.
Kogi?
Yes, shall we do Kogi today?
Today?
Yes.
It's a good chance.
I see.
Wait a minute. Let's take a bath together.
Do you want to take a
bath together? Today.
..
But...
It's a little embarrassing.
Hey, listen.
Do you know Bonobo?
Bonobo? Yes, Bonobo.
A car?
No.
Isn't that Bonobo?
What's that?
Bonobo is like a monkey.
It's like a chimpanzee.
Do you know?
I don't know much about it.
What is it? Bonobo.
Look up Bonobo.
Bonobo.
Here.
Anyway, Bonobo has a lot of sex.
What?
What do you think?
He has a lot of sex.
Yes. Isn't it amazing?
He can't differentiate
between male and female.
What?
He has a lot of sex?
It's amazing, isn't it?
I used to do it on TV before.
I'm doing a lot of sex.
Are you pregnant? No, I'm not.
Genetics is strong.
There is only a strong one.
In other words, there is only a life
and death that wins in competition.
It's amazing.
I knew it.
It was compared on TV.
It was compared to the movement
of the life and death of a human male.
What does it mean?
Does it mean that humans are weak?
It means that humans
are getting weaker because
they are made up of
one part and one part.
So, one part and one part are not good?
It means that weakness is being copied.
It's like a group of people
who are about to have sex.
It's like a plurality.
It's like a group of people
who are about to have sex.
Is that so?
Like a family?
No, that's not what I'm talking about.
I heard that even a
monk doesn't do a ritual.
You don't do a
ritual? That's right.
I heard that only
humans do a ritual.
This is amazing.
I don't think there's
anything you don't do.
Think about it.
Okay, I'll be honest with you.
I had a little problem recently.
What?
Your sex was very plain.
Plain? Plain.
It was plain, wasn't
it? Yes, it was.
It was like an
extension of work.
It ended quickly.
I took a shower quickly.
I turned my back and went to bed quickly.
I was worried about that.
I see.
Yes.
I didn't notice.
That's why I did my best today.
I'm sorry.
I made you worried.
Have you finished eating?
Yes.
Well,
I'm going to take a shower.
Together?
What is it?
Well,
you know,
you have to turn around
to write a poem, right?
Yes.
So,
I want you to look forward to the next one.
The next one? Yes, yes, yes.
So, I'll go first.
Huh?
The next one? I'll be back.
Are you looking forward to it?
Well,
yes.
Bye.
Later.
OK.
You know,
I can't help but be conscious of you.
I know.
What are you doing?
Why are you laughing?
Do you want to do it?
Yes.
It's hard to do.
Well, if you don't mind, you
can do it when you feel like it.
I'm going to sleep.
Hey, you can go to sleep now.
Do you want to take it off?
Yes.
Your face.
What? Is it weird?
Lend it to me.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Please be aware that this is a
derivative work of the Touhou Project.
It might be dangerous.
Let's do it.
Oh, it came out a lot.
I have a handkerchief, too.
Thank you.
What?
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Thank you.
Is it cold?
No, but it's not that bad.
Hey.
Yes?
Let's have a coffee.
Yes.
Coffee?
What are you going to do today?
Is this a lecture? Yes, it is.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to have a
skin-shaping session after this.
Skin-shaping?
That's a big budget.
It says I have to stroke your hair.
There is also a route written on it.
What's wrong? Is it stuck?
Is this okay?
It's got hair on it.
Give me a second.
No, you can't smell it.
Why?
Are you sweating?
You're sweating.
Stop it.
It was hot during the
day, so you're sweating.
Why?
Why are you sniffing
too much? I'm sweating.
Oh, is that so?
How was it? It felt good.
I've never touched your
hands like this before.
Maybe it was a little rough
because I was doing housework.
Thank you for everything.
I really like you.
Really?
But...
Just a little more...
It felt good, but just a
little more... A little more?
I want to make other people feel good, too.
What do you mean?
I want to make you feel better.
I want you to lick me.
Lick you?
What is it?
What do you want
me to eat? Your face.
Your tongue.
My tongue?
It's hot!
Really? Is it that
hot? Around there.
I want you to eat it.
Your breath is warm.
Your nose is breathing.
Your breath is hot.
It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it? It's okay.
It's the wind.
It feels good.
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Is it like this?
Yes, it feels good.
Which part of the body did you feel good?
It's been a long time, so forget it.
It's like a fish.
My stomach feels good, too.
It feels so good.
It's hot, isn't it?
Oh, it feels good...
Yeah, that's right.
I'm sleepy...
Thank you for your hard work.
It's so hot.
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
Doesn't it hurt? No, it doesn't.
It felt so good.
Let's start from the side.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not that hot.
Is it hot?
It's hot, isn't it?
It's painful, isn't it?
It smells again.
Are you okay?
Is it that bad? I don't know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're sweating a lot today.
Really?
I think you should let it out a little.
I know.
It's difficult.
Do you want to take a shower?
Do you want to take a shower together?
Yes.
I'm going to take a shower.
Take a shower?
Yes.
Okay.
I got it.
It's hot.
No, it's not.
Is it hot? Yes, it's hot.
Really? It's hot.
Let's take a shower and do something.
This is my room.
Yes, it is.
Did you make it? Yes, I did.
Thank you.
FUJISAKI YUKARI
What are you
doing? Oh, it's windy.
I found it.
You found it.
What's wrong?
It's getting thinner.
I can see the white part clearly.
No, it's not.
You should change the parting line.
If you make it the same,
the white part will spread out.
Should I make it like 7-3?
I think it's better to divide it like that.
No, you can't make a lot of divisions.
Oh, you don't make divisions?
There are a lot of women.
It's thin.
There's a clinic like that.
Oh, there is.
You don't have to massage.
Oh, is it okay to
massage? Massage.
I'll do it.
Will it work soon?
No, it won't work soon.
I don't know if it's because
I have the life of a monk.
I don't know what to do with three people.
It's hot.
What's up?
I'm thinking of getting a divorce.
What's wrong?
I think I should get a
divorce and get a doctor.
I thought I could make time for myself.
Oh, I see.
I'm looking for a good lawyer.
Let me know if you find one.
But it's only once in a lifetime.
I think it's good.
I envy you.
I want to get a divorce, too.
I wish I had some evidence of divorce.
Don't you have one as a husband?
Well, it's a long story, isn't it?
It's been a while, but we
don't get together that often.
I see.
Well, I feel like we're back to normal.
You said you wanted
to get a divorce, but
we've been together
for the rest of our lives.
I see. You two get along well, don't you?
Hey, hey, hey, Ms. Yukari.
Did you look into the lecture?
I did, and I practiced.
I did it!
How was it?
In conclusion, it was really good.
I was able to do it for the
first time in a long time.
What is that?
I don't understand at all.
Great!
It was good that you taught me.
But I'm glad you didn't.
Thank you so much.
I'm a little jealous.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's going to be a lot of
trouble for the lawyer.
I know.
I hope we can talk about it.
Like a mud horse marriage.
Mud horse?
We're not in that kind of relationship.
It's not like that, really.
Well, it's refreshing.
But I still want to take a picture.
Did you have anything
interesting today? Well, yes.
Today,
I talked with my neighbors.
What did you talk about?
Did you talk about it?
Yes.
I cut my hair again.
Do you still talk about it?
Yes.
You like to talk about it, don't you?
So,
what did you talk
about? It's a secret.
It's a secret?
But you are talking about it, aren't you?
I'm sure you'll remember.
I haven't talked that much.
Just a little.
I see.
But if it's that face,
I'm sure it's a good story.
I'm blushing.
This is the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had
a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time
I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the
first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed, and it's the first time I've ever had a nosebleed
There may be a lot of places
where you haven't kissed yet.
It's a bit perverted.
Then I'll kiss you until
my whole body is numb.
Really?
I'll kiss you in the fall, too.
Fall? I'm sweating.
It smells so good.
Really?
Did you smell something?
I wonder what it is.
Is it shampoo? It's amazing.
Thank you.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I'm curious
about how it feels to touch it.
What?
What is it? Wait a minute.
Did I do something
wrong? No, not at all.
Is this a
strawberry? Yes, it is.
Only this part is a strawberry.
Only this part is 3D.
It's 3D.
I thought you would be happy.
I was surprised. It's vivid.
Show me the back.
How is the back?
The back is normal.
You're right.
You look happy.
I just wanted to play with you.
You're cuter than usual.
That's right.
Let me see.
It's the same,
isn't it? It's hot.
I hear my baby is crying crying.
It's a little tight.
My baby is getting around my husband's arm.
I can't believe I'm just
looking at my baby.
I had no idea that the baby was so dirty.
I'm going to sleep.
Really?
Yes.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
I want you to relax a little.
I want you to feel it.
Did it hurt?
I want you to feel it slowly.
Is it in a good
place? It feels good.
Does it feel good,
Kyary? Yes, it does.
I'm going to take a shower.
It feels good.
Can I take a bath?
This is amazing.
I'm going to take a bath.
My friend seems to be in a bad mood, but
I can't help it because it's a good day.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Are you
okay? I'm okay.
It feels good.
Wait a minute.
I'll take it off.
Can you do it?
Gently, gently, gently.
Are you okay?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat play with a ball.
I'm not sure if it's a good
idea to play with a ball.
Huh?
Are you going to pull again?
Yes.
Wow!
It's going to be on the back of my head.
Really?
That's very embarrassing.
It's done.
Huh?
My husband is a little
surprised when I touch his neck.
He's never touched my neck.
But he seems to be interested in my neck.
He plays with my neck,
then he tries to touch it.
Haha.
You are ticklish.
You are sensitive now.
Are you blowing?
You are in the back.
Girls come out from the back, don't they?
Now...
You can do it.
Hey, where are you touching?
Where are you touching?
What are you doing?
I'll touch you, too.
I think you should sweat a little.
You'll be a little calmer.
I'm going to take a bath.
Thank you.
It's amazing.
What?
It looks like it's done.
Really?
Yes.
It's done.
Really?
Yes.
It's blue.
What?
I bought a new hair dryer.
It's been a while since I wore a
dryer, but I'm glad I got a new one.
How far have you come since then?
I'm a little hungry because
I'm working from now on.
It's been a long time
since I've had a bath, so
I'm a little tired, but I'm
going to take a break.
I'm going to take a break,
but I'm going to take a break,
so I'm going to take a break,
so I'm going to take a break.
It's true.
It's amazing. I can do it again.
You can put it in here.
What?
Here?
Yes.
Then, I'll take it off.
No, I don't want to do it here.
It's a pain in the ass.
I want you to do it in the bath.
What?
I want you to do it here.
But I don't want the baby to come out.
Then let's think about it at that time.
You did a good
job, didn't you? I see.
Oh, it's okay.
I'm going to put a
bandage on your arm.
I'm going to put a bandage on your arm.
It's been a long time since
I've done this kind of exercise.
This time I was able to do it.
This is the first time
I've had a baby, so I'm a
little nervous, but I'm
sure it's going to be okay.
I'm sure it's going to be okay.
It's OK, isn't it?
Is that so? Oh, I'm tired.
It's ticklish.
Oh, I'm tired.
Hello.
My name is Michiko
and I'm 12 years old.
I'm a junior in high school and
I'm currently in my final year.
Me too.
5th month 7th month
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to close the door.
What are you going to do?
Really? I'm fine.
This is the first time I've
had a baby, so I'm a little
worried, but I'm doing my
best to take care of my baby.
I was surprised when I opened the door.
I have a lot of things.
Tama Zoo, Chimpanzee
It's hot, isn't it?
Do you want me to
hold it for you? It's hot.
Oh, are you OK? It's hot.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it? I'm sorry.
Oh, is it hot? It's hot.
This is a video of the process
of making a leather belt.
I will explain how to make a leather belt.
Do you have any bubbles left?
Is it OK? OK, that's all.
Thank you.
This is a video of my son and my
daughter playing in the living room.
My son and my daughter
are playing in the living room.
It's dry.
Do you want to drink
something? Yes, I do.
What do you want to drink?
What? I don't know.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's great.
It reminds me of the old days.
The old days?
When we first met.
When I entered the university.
At first.
I see.
I thought you were a kind senior.
Since that time.
We were in the same circle.
You taught me a lot of things.
I thought you were
different from other girls.
Really?
I was surprised.
What?
You were the first one to
invite me on a date, right?
Me?
Yes.
At first, we went to a good
Italian restaurant near our school.
We went there to have a meal together.
Yes, that's right.
We met on the way home.
That restaurant is quite famous.
I was very excited.
I was surprised when I heard the
news that you were going to be a couple.
I wonder if they saw it.
I don't know.
It's a rumor that you're
going to be a couple soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think everyone knew it right away.
I feel like it's been a long
time since we started dating.
I miss that time.
We used to do it a lot.
We were young.
I didn't know that.
At that time, you weren't
aware of Kougi, were you?
I didn't know at all.
I felt like I was taking a
shower when it was over.
I talked to him a little.
I was conscious of it when I
was told again by the name of the
lecture, but I was conscious of it
more than I was conscious of it.
I thought that I shouldn't do it as it is.
Thank you.
I didn't think you would do it properly.
Like in the old days?
It's a little different from the old days.
Is my hand long?
What about me?
Oh, it's bright.
Oh, you're right.
It's that time already?
Yes.
Do you mean you had a lecture last night?
Do you mean that?
It's a new record.
You're right.
Yes.
I haven't been to a
nightclub in a long time.
It's a new record.
Shall we go to the room?
Yes.
What time is it? I don't know.
What time is it? It's so bright.
It's so bright.
Do you want to do it one more time?
I'm going to try it.
Is it my fault?
I have to go to the bathroom.
What are you doing?
I'm taking a bath.
It's getting cold.
It's delicious.
You seem to be ready.
Do you want to go home like this?
Yes.
Take your time.
Ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh,
ahh, I'm so comfortable.
Ah,
oh,
ah,
Ah, it feels good.
Ah.
Ah, here.
It's easier to take it from this side.
Ah.
Really?
Look at my feet.
Ah.
Ah~~~~~~~~~
Ah~~~~~~~~~ I feel good.
Ah~~~~~~
Ah~~
But I don't like the other side.
What?
I want to do something else.
What? Try to guess.
Ah~~~~~~ I'm tired.
It feels good.
It's very tight.
Does it feel good? Don't move.
I've been trying to make a video
of myself, but I couldn't get it.
I'm sorry.
When I first met Riki, I tried
to straighten my leg on a chair.
It's hot, isn't it? It's hot.
Is it hot?
It's hotter than before.
Yes, it is.
Already.
It's fine.
I'm going to hide my face in the mirror.
This video is a derivative work of the
Tohoku Prefecture Tourism Promotion Agency.
This is the first time
I've had a baby, so I'm
a little nervous, but
I'm sure it'll be okay.
I'm sure it's going to be okay.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Mmm... Mmm... Mmm...
It's cold, isn't it? Yes, it is.
It's cold, isn't it?
Really?
Give me your hand.
Let me help you.
It's cold.
I was surprised.
Oh, it came out.
Why did it come out?
It's a great picture.
It's going down.
I have to wash it later.
Oh, thank you.
It's a lot of rice.
Thank you.
Are you okay? Wait a minute.
I'll hold it down a little.
Are you okay?
Do you wear underwear?
No, I don't wear underwear.
Wow, it's amazing.
Tissue?
It's going to harden.
It's the same as the tissue.
How was it? Did you feel good?
Yes, I felt good.
Really?
Yes.
What?
What should I do?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
But I want to stay like this for a while.
Do you want to sleep together?
Don't you have to take a shower?
Just a little bit.
About 5 minutes is fine.
It's before work.
I have to get ready.
I see.
Then, just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
Please make a straight face.
Are you tired?
No, I'm not tired.
Just a little.
Let's take a nap.
Oh, by the way.
It's Friday next week.
I have to finish work a little early.
Let's go out for a meal sometime.
Really?
Yes.
Of course.
Well, this way?
This way?
Well, that's right.
Next Friday.
It's a promise.
Yukari Fujisaki
Thank you for your hard work.
It must have been hard for you.
I know.
But you did your best.
I envy you.
What's up?
I got a divorce yesterday.
Congratulations.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy, too.
I can fly as a woman.
I'm glad.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you.
Hey, did you change your
make-up recently? No, I didn't.
Is there any change?
Well, I was looking at you because I
thought you had a strong skin recently.
I thought so, too.
That's right.
Do you do anything?
No, I don't do anything.
I don't know, but I think I've
been doing it quite a bit recently.
What?
I've been doing it quite a bit.
Really? No way! I see.
That's why? I think so.
I see.
So, you've been doing it.
Yes.
I see.
For me, it was like, I did it
at the beginning, and then
I went back to my usual
pace, like I didn't do anything.
It was normal, so I
think it's a good feeling.
I see.
Oh, by the way, it's rare, but that
person invited me to dinner tonight.
After work?
Is that so?
We're going to be together.
That's rare.
You always said you wanted to eat at home.
Yes, this is also thanks to Kouki.
Thank you so much.
It's good to have Kouka.
I'm a little jealous.
No, I'll give it to you.
Thank you so much.
From now on, if you're alone, you
can have a meal with three people.
That's great.
That's right.
It's a girl's cafe.
It's fun.
You two are cute.
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
I couldn't get out of the car.
I see.
What do you
want to eat? Italian.
Italian? Sounds good.
It's like our first date.
What did you eat that day?
I think I ate aglio e olio.
That's fashionable.
Isn't it? Today.
..
What do you want
to eat? Pasta and.
..
pizza? That's right.
It's okay to eat garlic.
It's okay to eat what's in the bag.
Oh, really?
If you're going to eat it,
it's okay if you two eat it.
I'll kiss you a lot.
Yeah, sure.
It was delicious.
Yeah, it was good.
I'm full.
Really.
Yeah.
It's been a while since I had fun.
I'm sorry. I don't usually do this to you.
It's okay. I'm busy.
Invite me again when you have time.
Thank you.
The first shop we went
to was very delicious.
That's right.
Is that shop still there?
Which one was better?
I wonder if there is still.
I wonder if it's still there.
It's been more than 20 years.
It's a miracle if it's still there.
But the chef may have changed.
I wonder if the taste will change.
I miss it.
Because I couldn't go at that time.
That's right.
But now that I think about
it, I wonder if it was like this.
I think so.
When I was a student, I
thought it was very delicious.
I made money and
became a member of society.
I ate it with everyone and
said, It was delicious here.
Did everyone agree with you?
Yes.
That's right.
Did I eat too much delicious food?
I wonder if it's gone.
But you know, you can update it again.
Yeah.
So let's look for a lot of good
restaurants together again.
Yeah, that's right.
Today,
After this,
I'll ask you to go out
with me a little more.
Kouki, Yeah.
Yes.
Was it the right answer?
The right answer?
Was there anything you were glad about?
Well, until the morning,
I talked about memories all night.
You talked about
memories? All night long.
In the living room.
I was wondering if that would happen, too.
I see.
I don't know the correct
answer, but it was fun.
I see.
It's a two-way race.
It's fun to find it.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's a little hard to go out
every day until the morning.
It's a little hard.
But sometimes we have a day off.
Sometimes we have a day off.
What do you do when you
don't wear clothes all day?
What do you do on days
when you can't sleep?
What do you do when you can't stop?
I don't stop until morning.
That's amazing.
I don't wear clothes.
I don't wear clothes all day.
You're always flirting.
I wash my face,
I eat on the bed,
I do laundry on the way,
I do cleaning on the way,
I do cleaning on the
way, What are you doing?
It's so beautiful.
Ta-da! I did my best.
Wow!
Did you hear that?
Yes.
It's amazing.
It's like... Isn't it that?
Isn't it the newlywed travel
to Hawaii? That may be so.
What is this?
I think this is also a free plan.
Is that so? Wow! It's cute.
You can drink whatever
you want in the refrigerator.
Really?
Yes.
It usually costs a lot
of money, doesn't it?
Yes.
Refrigerator... Here? Oh, I see.
There are a lot of things in it.
Yes.
Oh, great.
Oh, that object.
Great.
Yes.
I've never stayed in a place like this.
I've never seen it.
No, I haven't.
Was it expensive?
Well, let's not talk about that.
Let's leave it.
Hey, it's trash day tomorrow.
I can't carry the cardboard.
Can you do something
difficult for me? Let's see.
But,
It's already 10 o'clock.
Oh, I see.
It's already been collected.
Yes, it is.
I think it will be
collected until next week.
Yes, it was a bad timing.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Oh, did I turn off the gas generator?
Did I turn it off? I don't know.
I'm fine.
I see. I'm worried about you.
But you're always fine.
Yes, you're right.
Are you nervous? No, I'm not.
Really?
I'm not used to this kind of place.
So I'm a little nervous.
I see.
Yes.
Do you want to take a
shower? It's a hassle.
What?
It's a hassle?
Yes.
You're a grown-up now.
Because you're old.
Oh, really?
I'll be cute if I become like that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
I was just trying to relax.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Then say you're cute.
You are cute.
Thank you.
You are the cutest in the world.
In the world? Thank you.
Did I hurt you?
What?
What's wrong with
you? No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
I'm really nervous in a place like this.
But it's wonderful.
I'm very happy.
Thank you.
Thank you for being with me.
That's right.
It's been 20 years.
20 years is early.
I see.
How often did you
come with me? 20 years.
I didn't imagine that.
What?
I didn't imagine that I
would be with you for so long.
Did you think we would break up
at an earlier stage? No, not at all.
I couldn't imagine
it for 20 years.
I didn't know if I was alive or not.
But we were together.
Yes.
What?
Where do you want to go
when you are 30 years old?
Abroad?
Do you want to go?
Yes.
How about 40 years?
40 years? Do you want to go to space?
Do you want to go?
I think I can go there.
I think so, too.
Then, let's stay together forever.
What's going on
over there? Bedroom.
Let's go to bed.
Let's go.
It's so beautiful.
Let's take a look.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
When I look at the night
view, I can't help but cry.
Tears?
I think I'm getting older.
What?
When I see something beautiful like this.
I'm impressed.
Yes.
I see.
But I wonder if I can look at it forever.
I feel like I'm in a place
I've been to before.
I feel like I'm in a video.
Video?
Yes.
Thank you.
You look great today.
Yes.
Did you buy something
for today? Yes, I did.
For you.
You look so cute.
Thank you.
I love pink tie.
What should I do with this?
Do something?
Yes.
I'm kidding.
Really?
I don't hate it.
Really? Just a little.
Just a little.
I just played with it.
Well, next time.
Yes, next time.
Let's try it.
This clothes is very erotic.
What?
Yes.
I was wondering.
Have you ever seen this underwear?
Yes.
It's a new underwear.
I see.
Can I wear it today?
Yes.
Are you happy? Of course I am.
You look great.
Thank you.
Do you need this?
Yes.
It fits the image of Yukari.
Thank you.
But this... What?
What?
Isn't this too tight?
It's too aggressive, isn't it?
Too aggressive?
Is it?
Hmm...
Wow...
The shop staff told me that
this is a fighting underwear.
Really?
Yes.
Awesome.
Awesome?
Yes.
Awesome.
I bought it because you said
you wanted to play a game.
I didn't know you asked me.
So, today is the day to play a game.
I'm normal. Are you okay?
What about my
game pants? It's okay.
I like this.
Really?
Yes.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Yes, I'm okay.
Oh, yes.
This is the first time I've ever
seen such a large bed in my life.
It's a big bed, isn't it?
Where is it?
The pillow is big,
isn't it? My butt is big.
Thank you.
You said your butt is big.
What?
I love you.
It's a pillow fight.
If I throw a pillow, you'll get angry.
That's right. You'll get angry.
Let's go.
Wow, it's so soft.
Yes, it is.
It's so soft.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
I hit something.
「」「せっかくの新しいヤツに裏切られちゃった。」
「うるさくて」 It's hard.
What? It's very hard.
Is it hard?
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's so cute.
I'm glad I was able to film this video.
Today is the day when I will start eating.
I'm not good at eating
out, but I try to take it.
I always think that eating and
sleeping are two different things.
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
Oh, wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I felt so good just now.
Really? Yeah.
The pillow is too low.
Yeah.
I think it's better to
put it on the pillow.
OK.
Where? Here.
How do you feel? I feel good.
You feel too good.
Should I stop?
I feel too good.
What should I do?
Should I be a little
gentle? That's right.
ああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああ
It's a very loud sound.
I feel it more than usual.
Really?
I'm glad if you enjoy this video.
Oh my god.
Can I lick you?
Are you okay?
What should I do?
This way? It's fluffy.
It's really fluffy.
It's hot, isn't it? Yes, it is.
This is a video of me and
my husband playing with a cat.
I'm not used to this kind of
video, so I'm a little nervous.
Hey.
It's not your business.
It's not your business?
Don't get dirty.
It feels really good.
I'm sorry I'm not good at speaking English.
I'm having a hard time with my teeth.
It's so bad today.
It's so bad that it's full.
There's a lot in my mouth.
Don't you have teeth?
Don't you feel any pain?
I don't feel any pain at all.
Is your jaw tired?
Yes, just a little.
Because it's big.
Oh, my God.
It feels good.
Oh, no.
Oh, no?
It's coming out.
It's coming out? No.
No?
No.
Not this way.
But it feels so good.
Oh, no.
Well, then.
I'm sorry.
Ah.
It's hot.
It's okay.
What about the ball?
Ah.
It's in my bag.
I don't like it.
If it's stuck here, I
don't want to take it off.
Then, put it in this bag.
Do you want me to put it in?
Yes.
Wow.
Isn't it melting? It's melting.
If it melts, it will disappear.
Wow.
It's melting.
Is it melting?
It's easy to put it in.
Can I put it in?
Ah...
Ah... Ah...
You have gone very far.
I feel good.
Ah...
Ah... Ah... Ah...
Oh, it's very red.
Can I put it this deep?
It's rubbing a lot.
It feels good.
Do you like this? I love it.
It's amazing.
That's it.
This?
This? That's it.
That's amazing.
Here?
Ah!
How do you feel,
Ikari? I feel good.
I feel like I'm in my stomach.
In my stomach.
Ah, I see.
I can't say anything.
Oh, that's right.
You have the deepest one now.
I knew it.
Today, I'm going to show
you a video of my cat,
Sukude, who was caught
by the owner of the cat tower.
The owner of the cat tower, Sukude,
was caught by the owner of the cat tower.
Oh, dear.
Oh, it's too wet.
You touched my belly.
Please be gentle, my dear.
Not yet.
Do you feel tired, staying
on bed all the time? A little bit.
Well, I'm going to lie down.
Good night.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's been
a long time since I've seen a
cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm not sure if it's because
it's been a long time since
I've seen a cat like this,
but I'm a little nervous.
I'm sorry.
Put your legs straight.
It feels good.
Today, I'm going to show you
how to get rid of bad breath.
I'm going to show you
It's like a vacuum cleaner.
It's amazing.
Here, do you
see this? This is it.
What is that?
What is that? I don't know.
It's a good place.
It's amazing.
It's terrible.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat like this.
It's been a long time since
I've seen a cat like this.
Are you okay? I can't sleep.
You can't sleep? I can't sleep.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it feels good.
It feels good there.
Oh, my God.
Oh, but it feels good to
rub the tip of my nose.
Oh, my God.
Oh, it hurts.
I'm going to sleep.
Where are you going to sleep tonight?
What should I do?
A different place than usual.
A different place than usual?
Yes.
What?
A place I've never been.
Your face...
But your make-up is going to be messed up.
I don't care.
I'm going to wash my face and go to bed.
I don't care. I'm going to wash my face.
I've never done it before.
Let's do it.
It's not good if you put it in your mouth.
I'm closing my mouth.
I'm going to rub your neck a lot.
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to have a hard time.
Oh, my God! I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Oh, my God.
You have a mosquito bite.
Do I have a mosquito
bite? I can't see.
I can't see.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay? I'm sorry.
Wait, what's going on?
Is it serious?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Can't you see?
Hold it for a moment.
This video includes paid advertisement.
If you want to watch this video,
please refer to the description column.
Please enjoy the video.
Please subscribe to my channel.
This is a video of a child who
had a lot of food on the floor.
A child who has a lot of food on her mouth.
Oh, it didn't go into my mouth.
It was dripping here.
Did you know it was dripping?
It was dripping. My stomach was throbbing.
A shooting star was flowing.
I don't know.
I forgot to say shooting star or wish.
But it seems to be okay.
Are you okay?
What did you want
to ask me? Well.
..
Can we be together until 50 years later?
Can we be together
until 50 years later? Well.
..
It's said that life is 90 years.
90 years is not 100 years.
Do you want to live with me until
you are 100 years old? Yes, I do.
I wonder if I can live with you.
Then let's live together for 60 years.
Let's live together for 60 years.
If you die before me,
it's definitely no good.
That's right.
I made a lot of promises.
Did you make a lot of promises?
I feel like I've been
doing a lot of things lately.
My body is so hot.
It's okay.
I don't have to put on a blanket.
Then I'll just put on my waist.
I'll get a cold.
Girls shouldn't get a cold.
You can't let go of your hand.
Do you want to try to be a
child again? I don't know.
Are you okay now?
I think I'm okay.
I didn't expect you to
be so excited at this age.
I didn't think it would be so much fun.
That's right.
After all, it's thanks to the lecture.
It's amazing.
The lecture is amazing.
I think there are still many more lectures.
Let's develop more.
That's right.
It's fun.