Minami Riona in the middle of the night.
Minami-san, is it okay if we put
the cups together? Yes, it's okay.
It's for one person.
Yes, it's for one person.
Welcome.
Then, this is for you.
Thank you.
That's all for today.
Thank you very much.
It's rare.
It's a weekday.
I think it's going to run out.
Is it?
It's still fine.
I'll check it.
Please.
Minami-san.
Yes?
Did you drink the
new coffee? Yes, I did.
It smells so good.
Right?
I think I'm going to fall
in love with the coffee.
I think I'm going to fall in
love with the scent of the tree.
Didn't you say that when
you were a freshman?
Did I? Yes, you did.
It's been about a year since I came here.
Yes, it's been almost a year.
Time flies.
How long have you been here?
I've been working here
for about five years.
Five years? That's right.
I see.
It's easy to work here.
It's dark here.
I like this kind of atmosphere.
You're right.
By the way, what did you
say before? No, not really.
I just went out for a meal.
I'm not good at snoring.
Minami, do you get along
with your boyfriend? Me? Well.
..
I guess so.
What do you mean?
Did something happen?
What would you like
to drink? Excuse me.
Yes?
I'd like to order watermelon.
Do you have any recommendation?
Recommendation?
How would you like to drink?
I'm a little tired, so I'd like to
drink something refreshing.
I'd like to drink herbal tea.
What kind of herbal tea do you have?
What do you want to drink?
I want to drink chamomile,
jasmine, and hibiscus.
Do you want to drink rooibos tea?
Yes, I want to drink rooibos tea.
It was a good night.
Did you sleep well? Yes, I did.
By the way, the resort
was closed, wasn't it?
Yes.
If you get tired, you
should go to bed early.
It's hard to go back to the temple early.
I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
It's a little dark. I'll turn on the light.
I'm sleepy.
I'll turn off the light and go to bed.
Are you going to sleep?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little dizzy.
Do you want some
salt? No, thank you.
I like bright places.
I see.
But last time, I heard what you
said and turned off the light for you.
I know.
But you said you were sleepy.
Okay, I got it.
Like this? More.
More?
Like this?
Is it too dark?
A little?
How about this?
Do you want to fix it?
Are you okay?
You have a stiff neck.
Don't say that.
How long are you going to be shy?
Can I lick you? It tickles.
You are very cute.
You have a nice tongue.
Your head is wet.
I can't see anything.
Can I take off your blanket?
I want to see you more.
I don't want to see you.
You don't want to see me?
No.
I feel good.
I feel so good.
I'm going to cry.
Can I take a shower with you?
Yes.
It felt good.
Thank you.
Do you want to take a
shower with me? No, I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I'm going to take a shower.
Yes.
Good night.
Good morning.
You're early.
Yes, I am.
It's going to rain today.
Really?
I didn't bring an umbrella.
I'm home.
I'm sure you'll be home soon.
I'm going to use the bathroom.
What's wrong?
You don't look well.
Really?
I'm not good at it.
What's wrong?
Can you say it?
I can say it, but...
I recently broke up with my boyfriend.
Really?
Are you sure?
Have you heard the reason?
Personality is important.
I see.
Well, I'm sure.
Then, let's have a drink today.
Yes, please.
How can I help you?
I'd like to pay by smart phone.
Then, please pay by this card.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Do you need a
receipt? No, thank you.
Thank you.
I had a hard time today.
Me, too.
Shall I clean up? Yes, please.
Yes, please.
Good morning.
Did you order the new
tea from Kyoto? Yes, I did.
But maybe I should wait a little longer.
Maybe it's not enough.
That's not good.
I'll ask tomorrow.
Please.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at my friend's
touring week next week.
Do you have a driver's license?
Yes.
I didn't know that.
Didn't I tell you? I don't know.
I have it.
That's great.
When can you get
it? On my day off.
That's great.
Do you have a driver's license?
I only have a car license.
Are you going to drive?
I'm going to drive.
It's been a long time since I last drove.
I want to go swimming.
Are you interested?
Yes.
I want to ride a car behind you.
No problem.
Really?
Are you worried about my driving?
I'm a little scared.
What's going on? I don't know.
Should I go to the breaker?
Yes, you should.
I'll go to the breaker.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm fine.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you.
How was it?
I called the management company,
but it seems that all
the buildings are closed.
It seems that it will take
some time to reopen.
I'm glad it's still open.
I think it's good to be
open during business hours.
Isn't it a little too dark?
Oh, is this okay?
I found it in the storeroom
when I saw the breaker.
Yes, it's very helpful. Thank you.
Can you go? Yes, I can.
I didn't know such a thing existed.
It's my first time, too.
Do you want me to turn off
your smartphone? No, it's okay.
When it's dark, you can
see the other person's face.
I don't think I need to see your face.
It's embarrassing, so please don't.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize like that.
I'm not serious.
Really?
I don't feel anything at all.
I see.
Do you want to talk about something?
Talk?
Yes.
Do you want to talk about something?
Me?
Let's start with the theme of love.
Love?
Yes.
What do you think, Minami?
I...
How about this?
What do you mean?
I don't hate it at all, but I also
like this kind of atmosphere.
I see.
Do you like to do it in the dark?
What do you mean? Matching.
Matching?
I don't hate it.
I don't mean that.
I like the dark side.
Is that so?
I told you that I broke
up with my boyfriend.
I mean, my ex-boyfriend.
The reason why we broke
up was that my ex-boyfriend
liked to turn on the light
and do it in a bright place.
Then we gradually broke up
because we didn't get along.
I broke up with my boyfriend.
Is that so?
Yes.
I asked him why he wanted
to do it in such a bright place.
I see.
Then,
he said,
all AVs are shot in bright places.
I don't know why.
He said,
all AVs are shot in bright places.
I see.
I prefer dark places.
I like dark places.
Me, too.
I sometimes watch porn.
I wonder if it's not embarrassing
to do it in a bright place.
I think so, too.
I think it's better to be dark.
I'm sorry. I look like a fool.
No, not at all.
Here...
What do you mean?
Like this? It's so weird.
Sorry.
Please don't apologize.
I'm sorry, too.
I didn't expect you to come here.
I know.
Well, let's get ready to go home.
Yes.
Well,
I know I'm late today, but...
It's okay.
Please.
I'll give it back to you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay.
What do you want to eat?
How about meat?
How about steak? I'll treat you.
No, thanks.
How about hamburger?
Sounds good.
I'd like to have a drink, too.
A drink? I know a good
place that serves good Jibiru.
Really? Let's go there.
Yes, let's.
Is it close? Yes, it is.
Let's go.
This way?
Jibiru? That's nice.
How was Jibiru?
I might have drunk too much.
Are you all right?
I think I'm a little sick.
There's a park. Do you want to sit down?
Yeah, I want to take a break.
Do you want to come
closer? Let's do that.
I drank too much.
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
Yes, I feel better after a little rest.
That's good.
By the way, you drink a lot, don't you?
I used to be a bartender before this job.
Is that so?
You should have told me that earlier.
I'm sorry. I didn't ask you.
The moon is beautiful,
isn't it? Yes, it is.
Hey, do you want to kiss me?
Are you still drunk? A little.
You're living on your own, aren't you?
Well, a little bit.
That's enough.
It's bright here.
I think it's darker.
Let's go to a darker place.
Where? I don't know.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Are you okay? Can
you walk? I can walk.
I'm a little dizzy, though.
Shall we take a
nap? No, I'm fine.
I can walk.
But I might still be a little dizzy.
I don't know if I can do it.
I don't think it's a hot spot.
Please support me.
The shower was narrow,
but it was beautiful.
Yes, it was.
I finally cooled down.
Yes, you did.
I want to drink sake.
You should have bought it on the way.
But I'm fine.
I'm nervous.
Do you want to take a shower?
Then, you go first.
Isn't it too dark?
It was a little bright.
I think this is better.
Do you want to make it a little darker?
I want to make it darker.
It's dark.
Let's get started.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm glad you feel something.
This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
I can't see you.
You smell good.
I'm sorry.
I'm embarrassed to say this.
Mom, who's been living with me for
ten years, has already passed away.
I'm going to take a break
from childbirth because I'm sick.
Are you okay? It's a mess.
She is a mother of three.
Her name is Kako.
She is a mother of two.
Her name is Furuko.
This is the first time I've had a baby, so
I'm a little nervous, but I'll do my best.
I'm going to start with a massage.
I'm sorry.
Oh my god!
How do you feel?
Oh, it feels so good.
Good girl.
Here we go.
I'm a little shy, but I'm still using it.
Thank you.
I hope you get along
with each other better.
It's good to use the voice.
I'm still a little shy.
I'm shy.
Why don't we take a bath together?
I don't mind if it's dark.
Let's do that.
It's cute.
Are you all right? Be careful.
I'm scared.
Midnight.
Riona Minami
It was a little darker, wasn't it?
I was in a bad mood at that time.
Why?
I thought I was doing something I
shouldn't do because it was a shop.
I'm going to put a towel under the bed.
It's OK.
This is a video of a baby who was
born in a cage and tried to escape.
This video is a video of
the birth of a new baby.
I am a mother of three.
I am a mother of five.
I'm full.
By the way,
next Wednesday is off, isn't it?
I'm off tomorrow morning.
I'll be there in the evening.
Let's have dinner together again.
OK.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
It's not like I invited you.
It's fun.
Yes, it's fun for me, too.
It feels good, doesn't it?
The wind outside.
It's beautiful.
I'm glad you like it.
You like it, don't you?
Yes.
You're biting too much.
I want to drink more.
Which one is the
best? I want this.
Oh, good.
Do you want this?
Can I have it?
My body is a little hot.
I drank a lot.
Thank you.
Isn't it good? It's good.
It has a strong lemon flavor.
Today's pizza was really good.
It was good, wasn't it?
There were so many kinds.
I want to try this one.
It was quite big and I was surprised.
I was surprised, but I could eat it.
There is a pizza with cheese.
It looks like quattro con macchi.
I want to try that.
Let's go there next time.
There were a lot of pasta, too.
If there are so many
kinds of pasta, I will laugh.
By the way, I heard that
you have a room for a party.
Don't you have a
job? I have a room.
Really?
Yes.
I'm glad to hear that.
You must be busy.
I have a day off tomorrow.
Good night.
Do I have to do a lot
of things for you? Soon.
Do you want to take a shower?
I don't have to take a shower today.
Really?
You are sweating a lot.
Then, I'll take a shower.
I'm going to take a bath.
You don't have to take a bath.
Really?
I see.
It's getting dark.
With this? I'm nervous.
Ah, my body.
I told you that I did my
hair, but I'm quite drunk.
Oh, really? I'm drunk.
、。。 、。。
、。。
You have a cute voice.
Thank you.
I'm happy.
This is the first time I've had a
baby, and it's been a while since
I've had a baby, so I'm a little
nervous, but I'm sure I'll be fine.
I'm sure I'll be fine.
I'm so sorry.
Really? I can't do it.
Are you OK?
Are you okay? I'm okay.
I'll do it slowly.
I can't do it.
I'm sorry, sorry, sorry,
sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
How about this? No, but.
..
I can do it.
Just wear it as it is.
As it is.
I'm sweating.
It's hot.
No, it's not.
I feel sick.
It's hot.
※I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
Oh my god!
I love you! I feel sick.
It's hitting my stomach.
Me, too.
It's totally different.
This might be bad.
I'm sorry.
What should I do?
I can't help but cry.
It hurts, it hurts,
it hurts!! It's gone.
It's gone.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a baby cry.
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
It's embarrassing.
It's different from when I was born.
It's different.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'm going to sleep.
You're going to fall asleep.
It looks like you're going to fall asleep.
I'm going to fall asleep.
Where?
You don't have to do anything.
Oh, it's hot.
Give it to me.
It's wet.
I feel so good.
Me, too.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm going to take a shower.
I'm going to take a shower and go home.
But it's bright.
It's bright, but it's so dark that I
think it's okay not to turn on the light.
Really?
It's not a bad idea.
It's so beautiful.
Don't say that.
It's so good.
It's hard.
Let me see your face.
It's very hard.
It's too hard.
Don't read it.
I have a weak heart.
I don't want to read it.
I want you to know that.
My son is having a hard time.
I'm worried about him.
I'm so happy to see you, dad.
How do you feel? I feel so good.
Oh, my gosh.
I have never seen such a cute child before.
In your mouth.
Are you okay? You look fine.
What? Why are you crying? Cute.
Cute.
Please take your time.
I'm going to take a shower first.
If you feel like it, please come with me.
It's okay if it's dark.
I don't mind.
Can you close the curtains?
Can you do that again? Sure.
What? Good job.
You were busy today
as well, weren't you?
Oh, did you drink the new black
tea that came out the other day?
It was really good.
It was really fun.
Hey,
you know,
we played in a bright place the other day.
It felt really good,
but I thought it would be
better to do it in a dark place.
You know,
when it's dark,
you can feel that part a lot.
I'm a shy person, so I think it's
better to have sex in a dark place.
I'm going to have sex here again.
I'm going to do a lot of exciting things.
Come here.