Did you get used to
work? No, not at all.
Suzuki-san just got mad at me.
Really?
Isn't she scary?
Well, a little bit.
But you and her are like colleagues.
Yes, we are.
She's one year older than me.
I see.
She's really scary.
I can't get used to her.
I know.
I've been told a lot.
I think it's normal.
I was the same when I quit my job.
Good morning.
You're early.
I came a little early.
Are you here alone?
No, I'm with Hiroko.
You drank a lot yesterday, didn't you?
Did I? Yes, you did.
Did you see it? Yes, I did.
Did you drink with
a man? No, I didn't.
No, I didn't.
Did you drink with a man
in the company? No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
I didn't.
No, I didn't.
Really? I don't drink.
But you drink quite a lot.
I don't drink.
If you drink alcohol, you drink
a lot, don't you? I don't know.
You drink a lot, don't
you? I drink a lot.
You have a strong image.
I drink a lot.
You were drunk yesterday.
I'm not drunk at all.
Really?
I'm not energetic at all.
I'm so energetic that I
can drink from now on.
Isn't it dangerous to come to the office
in the middle of the day? Yes, it is.
That's right.
Last time, I was drunk
and I was about to be late.
That's true.
I was scolded a lot.
I was scared.
If it's the next time, I'll be late.
It's dangerous.
I was so scared that I couldn't get out.
I felt so quiet.
What? You were not quiet at all.
I was so nervous that I
couldn't answer the phone.
I see.
I was so nervous that I
couldn't answer the phone.
I know.
I was nervous when I had my first year.
Well, I guess the first year is like zero.
Yeah, we don't want to be on TV.
You know about the
crane last time, don't you?
What? Yes, I know.
I saw a crane and made a lot of tea.
What? That's amazing.
I drank a lot.
That's amazing.
I was so tired that day.
That's right.
That's why you drank again.
I said I couldn't do it.
That's amazing.
Don't you get drunk?
I get drunk sometimes, but
I don't get drunk on Fridays.
I see.
I don't get drunk on the next day's work.
I don't get drunk.
Maybe.
Is that so?
It's early in the morning.
Yes.
I drank too much and gained weight.
Really?
Isn't it bad? I don't know.
Don't worry.
I'm a little worried.
Really?
You wear a uniform every day, so you
know how much you've gained, don't you?
That's the scariest thing.
I don't know what this means.
The cameraman makes choices
because you are very sensitive.
What a good boy!
But I had never imagined such a situation.
You are smart.
You may have a sit here.
It tickles me when you lean on my belly.
Do you sleep now? Wait a minute.
I don't think so.
Are you OK?
I'm going to be scolded
if I don't do it properly.
Are you OK?
Are you OK? But, you know.
..
But, you know... What?
You two are different.
What?
Are you OK?
Are you OK? Thank you.
But, you know.
..
But, you know... Are you OK?
Are you OK?
〔Laughing〕
〔Speaking Japanese〕
Everyone, that's all for today.
Thanks to everyone's
hard work, our club achieved
the first place in sales
in the previous season.
Today, as a celebration of the win, we
will have a meeting in the break room.
I'll do it, so please move from people
who have a good work atmosphere.
Yes, yes.
Let me finish my work early.
Please say that in advance.
I'm counting on you.
It's a surprise.
Thank you.
I bought a lot of things.
I bought a lot.
It looks so heavy.
I recommend this.
It's the best.
Can I drink this? I'm sorry.
We have beer, too.
What would you like to drink?
What should I do?
We have beer, too.
Thank you.
Please drink as much as you can.
Don't drink too much.
No, no, no.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'll take it off.
Shimizu, too.
Please tie it up.
I'm sorry.
I don't need it.
I'd like a beer.
I'll have a beer.
Everyone, please take a seat.
Thank you.
I'll have a beer with my senior.
What?
That's too much.
One, two, three.
Thank you very much.
I'm hungry.
Do it yourself.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Cheers!
Please prepare more snacks.
I bought a lot.
Cheese!
Thank you for the meal.
Is it leaking? It's important.
Who bought this?
It smells so good.
It's me.
Then, it's your turn.
This is the first time I've ever
seen such a large amount of cheese.
It's a lot of cheese, isn't it?
I want to eat cheese.
How did you buy it?
I bought it in a pack.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
It's the first time I've ever seen
such a large amount of cheese.
I can't drink at all.
This is a gift for you.
Oh, really? Thank you.
Thank you.
Is this all for
me? No, it's not.
Don't eat too much.
It's noisy.
I'm sorry.
Is that so?
Can I have this?
What? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It is the first time for us
to have a meeting like this.
We are so happy to be here.
I'm sorry. It's not going to leak.
It may not leak.
Please hold it.
It's not going to leak.
It was on the camera, wasn't it?
It was on the camera.
Your face is too red.
It's not good.
Oh, it's true.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? You look bad.
You look bad.
I hit my forehead.
You hit your forehead.
It's hard to say that a girl is bad
at boys, isn't it? You're so cute.
You're so cute.
I'm getting sleepy.
Oh, my God!
It's like a labyrinth.
I know.
Hello, Shizuka.
Hi.
Are you drunk? A little.
Then, please drink.
You're getting red.
I'm getting red, too.
No, you're not.
You're drunk, aren't
you? No, I'm not.
I don't know if I'm drunk.
We're drinking together.
Cheers!
We were the ones who took off the clothes.
They are the ones who are wearing it.
What's wrong? I'm sorry.
We'll do our best.
I'm fine.
Is it leaking?
Don't worry about it.
You're so cute.
It's noisy.
If you take it from the top, it will leak.
I was taught how to do it.
It's so cute.
It's heavy.
It's like a boy's belly button.
My face is so heavy.
What are you talking
about? It's so heavy.
You've been taking
care of your beauty lately.
Really?
Do you have a
boyfriend? No, I don't.
What?
You don't have a
boyfriend? I don't.
You told me something today, didn't you?
What? I don't know.
Mion-chan told me something.
Did she? Tell me.
I'll tell you.
It's a secret.
Don't say that.
We are a team.
We are friends.
It's a secret.
Senpai is more.
..
than I thought.
Really?
Don't make fun of me!
I'm going to put it in my mouth.
Are you going to put it in
your mouth? Yes, please.
It's spinning, isn't it?
It's spinning,
isn't it? I'm scared.
Why?
Isn't it too early?
I don't know.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not good at it.
Senpai, are you drinking?
I'm drinking a lot.
Really?
I gave you three bottles.
Really? I'm losing.
Don't say such a lonely thing.
I'm lonely.
Are you drinking?
Yes, I'm drinking.
You don't drink, do you?
I like to put cream on when I drink.
What is it?
I don't want to do it.
Take a cute picture of him.
I'm going to bed.
Thank you for your hard work.
Your face is red, so be careful.
Are you okay?
Are you okay? I'm sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Tsuki?
What's wrong? Your eyes.
Your eyes are scary.
What's wrong? Oh, no.
I have a psychopathic eye.
Help me.
Psychopathic eye.
It's not a big deal.
Oh, no.
What should I do with this guy?
Don't flirt with him.
What?
You have a bad memory.
It's normal, isn't
it? It's normal.
It's not normal.
You have a bad memory.
You have a bad heart.
No, I don't.
I don't touch my seniors.
You have a kind heart.
You were doing like this.
You were fighting back and forth.
Who do you like the
most? Ayase-chan.
Oh! Wait a minute.
Don't go there.
I thought so.
What's wrong? Cute.
You guys are not good.
Everyone is cute.
Three cute girls of the same age.
No.1, No.2, No.3.
It's not in order.
It's the second year.
It's a mistake.
Shun, are you
sleeping? No, I'm not.
Wake up.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm OK.
Your wife will be angry.
I'm alive.
Shun, you can go home soon.
You must be tired.
Please take a rest at home.
Thank you for the food.
Are you going home?
Really?
You're going home?
She's so eager to eat.
Thank you for the food.
Sorry, guys.
Nice to see you.
You're still drinking, aren't you?
He's not drinking at all.
He's drinking a lot.
You're not good at it, are you?
I don't know how to do it.
It's totally different.
What are you doing?
There are girls, too.
Everyone likes my T-shirt.
No, no, no.
Don't get close to the table.
Don't do that.
Oh my god.
I'm doing it.
That's not good.
Look at your body.
Don't trick me.
What do you think of this body?
What do you
think of it? It's cute.
It's cute.
Senpai, please touch it.
You can touch it.
It's amazing.
Senpai, what do you think of it?
Well, it's not bad.
But it's not crooked, so it's okay.
If you put it in a normal
way, it's about this.
Stand up. Stand up.
Take it off. Take it off.
Hey, ladies.
Are you okay? I'm fine.
Can I look down?
I can't see anything.
It was bigger than I thought.
Did we get along well?
Did we get along
well? Sometimes.
Sometimes.
Is it a little
hot? No, it's not.
It's a chair.
A chair.
It looks comfortable to sit on.
You're going to sit on it.
How do you feel? I'm sweating.
That's because you're working.
It's hot.
I can see a triangle.
A triangle?
What is it? I can see it.
I'm a pervert.
I'm also a pervert.
How long are you going to be a pervert?
You really like it, don't you?
But your eyes were fixed all the time.
Do you like that
kind of thing? I hate it.
I hate it.
You hate it, don't
you? I hate it.
I hate it.
This is the first time in a
year that I drink a lot of alcohol.
You drink a lot of high-calorie
alcohol, don't you? Yes, I do.
Drink more.
It's good.
You became a woman again.
Ayase, you can't drink alcohol.
Is it good?
Do you drink beer? No, I can't.
Don't you drink highball?
I don't drink at all.
I don't drink.
There is.
I think the first place this time is because
of the hard work of the young people.
Thank you very much.
I'm really happy.
I see.
This kind of success
experience is very important.
I think I got the first place.
I want you to do your best from now on.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll buy it.
Thank you very much.
Then I have to go home soon.
I can't do it
I should have been the one to get it.
Oh, you're right.
I can't buy it anymore.
I've been listening to what
you've been talking about.
Koba has been holding your hand.
I can't say I'm going to buy it.
You're too much.
By the way, Hoshinaga-san.
What is it? Show me.
What's wrong? I'm scared.
What's going on?
Don't say that to Senpai.
I'll show you my boobs.
Show me.
I have proof.
Will you show me if I take off my pants?
I'll take off my pants.
Seriously, stop it.
Seriously, your
life is... Stop it.
It's dangerous.
It's Sekuhara's turn.
Go, go, go!
Stop it! Shinokawa-san.
I saw it.
Shinokawa-san, show me your boobs.
I told you I was the scariest.
I told you I don't need it.
That's right.
You're cheating.
Show it to her.
Can I?
I don't need it.
Do you want to see it up close?
No, I don't want to.
I'm so surprised.
Show me your boobs.
To be honest,
not only Kobayashi-kun,
It's not just me.
What are you talking about?
My boobs are not equal.
They are.
They are not equal.
What's that face?
What's that face? It's Tsume.
Kobayashi-kun, Tsume.
Is it that one?
Isn't it?
It's this one, right? No, no.
If other men also take off their
masks, I think I can show it to them.
I don't want to be a mouth yet.
She is excited.
I don't want to be a rabbit.
Is it my fault?
Hoshigaka-senpai said so.
Oh, he took it off.
Kobayashi-san, please give me some money.
Are you sure?
Can you pay for it, Hoshirama-san?
If it's my senior, I don't mind.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, really?
He said he would show it to me if he could.
Oh, no.
Here it is.
Wow! It's big.
It's not big.
It's normal.
It doesn't stand up.
Look at this.
Wow!
Is this OK? Wow! Two more.
Two more? Two more.
I'm taking a video with great effort.
Oh, no.
It looks fun.
How do you feel?
What do you think? I don't know.
Don't show it to the camera.
Can I close it now?
You look like a senpai.
Why can't you see it?
It's fine even if you cover your eyes.
Why do you take it off?
3 vs 1
Take it off! Take it off!
What? Really?
Are you going to take it off?
Shall I start?
Let's do it properly.
Huh?
Please take it off quickly.
Is it big? The smallest.
..
Hurry up!
No, I can't see!
You took it off at once.
It's rare.
There is nothing scary in the world.
There is nothing.
Do you want to be a chinchin model?
Do you want to stand up?
Aya-san will follow me.
I can't stand up.
Let's take a walk.
Oh!
This is a video of Seiko.
Yes, it is.
It's so funny.
Look at this.
This picture is absolutely funny.
What?
Look at this picture. Isn't
it funny? It's too funny.
What are you
hiding? It's so funny.
You are too proud.
How do you feel?
I didn't take off my clothes.
Do you want to show your boobs?
How do you feel?
It's a close-up camera.
The person on the far right is hiding it.
Please don't hide it.
Please roll up your sleeves.
Please take off your clothes,
so that we can see you.
Can you see me?
You are standing a little bit, Senpai.
Can I take off my top?
What?
It's embarrassing.
You said you would show your
boobs if you show your boobs.
You are stupid.
Show me your boobs.
I can't help it.
Are you serious, Senpai?
Well, if you take it off
for four people like this...
Are you serious? Here you are.
Why are you going to the middle?
Are you serious?
It's amazing that you're
sleeping in such a cold.
It's so tight.
Are you serious?
What should I do?
Really?
Wait, wait, wait.
It's so funny.
I'm taking a video.
But you're watching us, aren't you?
You're curious about Aya-san, aren't you?
I'm curious, aren't I?
But it's a locker
room, isn't it? I see.
It's quite big.
It's not big.
So, the result is... Let's see.
Hey, what do you think?
What do you think?
She's asking for your name.
Well, she's got some bra.
Oh, really? Of course.
Tell me where you're
going to buy it next time.
I'm going to take it off.
No way.
I'm going to give it to Chaki.
Wait.
I didn't think you'd really take it off.
Really?
If everyone takes it off, it's a mistake.
I'm going to show you.
I told you, so I can't help it.
You are cool.
I showed it to my juniors.
The bra is cute.
Cute.
I'll take a picture.
How is it?
Is this a breast?
Is this a bra?
This is a breast.
These are boobs.
What do you mean, Kobayashi?
I mean I don't have boobs.
I see.
You have a lot of boobs.
Really?
I think they are big.
I'm glad.
Let's compare which one is bigger.
Hey, stop it.
I don't like it.
You are so gross, Kobayashi.
You have a size B,
don't you? Yes, I do.
You have a size B, don't you?
What are you talking
about? Oh, she's gone.
I won't take it off.
You're in a bad position now.
Everyone is taking it off.
Why don't you take it off by yourself?
You can't help it because
you're sleeping alone.
It's not good to try to run away in
front of the camera when you're awake.
I'm a cameraman.
Come here.
I don't know.
I don't know what's going to happen.
Why? Why? Do your best.
Me too?
I want to see Ayase-san.
Tsukki and Sajima are involved.
I'm involved, too.
Everyone is involved.
It's been a while since the
two of you touched each other.
I think it's better to take it off.
It's because everyone took it off.
Please take it off.
Are you sure? I can't say it.
Really?
I can't say it, senpai.
Then, I'll do it.
Isn't this picture bad?
Is it bad?
The picture is bad.
The picture is bad, but... What
are you doing surrounded by a bed?
Yume-chan is sleeping all the time.
Yume-chan is cheating.
Can you show me something sexy?
What is that?
What's that?
I don't know what to do.
What do you mean? I don't know.
It's difficult.
I don't know what to do.
Senpai, did you say
something? Oh, no.
Oh, no? Oh, no.
I didn't know.
What? Senpai.
..
What? What?
What? I heard rumors.
What?
Did you hear rumors?
I heard rumors.
What?
What? What? What? What?
What? Senpai is erotic.
Senpai is erotic?
What's that simple question?
I said it earlier.
Senpai is erotic?
What's that?
I said it earlier.
It's cute.
Tsukimura is behind you.
I'm shy, Senpai.
By the way, I'm shooting like this now.
It's so cute.
It's so big.
Do I take it off?
I don't know how to take off my braids.
How should I take it off?
Like this?
I don't know how to do it.
Hey, it's not like that.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so nervous?
Because everyone took off their braids.
So, are you going to go
home after sharing your secret?
Are you satisfied,
Kobayashi-kun? Not yet.
Not yet?
What do you want to do?
What's wrong with you, Kobayashi?
You're crazy, Kobayashi.
You're crazy.
You're more crazy than before.
Really?
What? You're crazy.
You're doing it.
You can't just sleep, can you?
I have to wake her up.
What?
It's like a prank.
A prank?
What kind of prank?
It's going to be like I'm the suspect.
What?
I'm the suspect.
What are you going to do? Well.
..
There are men around me.
Surround me.
Surround you?
What do you mean? I'll hold you.
What's going on?
When I woke up, I was surprised that
there were so many people around me.
Wow, you look like you're
going to have a trauma.
It's a prank.
Two, three, four? Four.
You're thinking about something crazy.
Because I took it off.
Show me again.
Can you see it? It's cute.
Where are you going?
It's not a make-up.
I see.
What should I do?
This is amazing.
Chikorin.
How should I wake
her up? Wake her up.
Wake up.
She is standing.
She is so excited.
I'm going home.
I saw her.
What's up?
Is there someone in there?
That's what happened.
What's up, Yume-chan?
Wait a minute, Kobayashi.
Don't rub your head.
Everyone is taking off their clothes.
What?
Are you happy,
Yume-chan? I'm happy.
Are you happy?
Why? Why are you taking it off?
It's blubbering.
Oh, no.
It's embarrassing.
You're happy, aren't you?
Do you want to take it off, too?
Which one looks the best?
I'd like to hear that.
What do you think?
The one you like.
Let's line up.
What's that?
Are you OK?
Please come here.
You can put it on your left and right.
What do you mean?
You can choose your favorite person.
Why did you go to that side?
It's easy to see.
Senpai, you are the most
popular one, aren't you? Yes, I am.
Oh my god!
What?
It's really chaos.
What are you doing in the company?
What should I do?
Do you choose Senpai? Yes, I do.
What? Yes, I do.
It's so long.
What should I do?
Please choose one.
Please study one by one.
I'm doing close-up camera.
Thank you.
If you don't leave it in the document,
everyone's health... I'll delete it.
No, no, no.
Progress report?
Progress report.
It's important.
What should I do with this?
Should I stand up? Yeah, stand up.
Then I'll stand in front.
Do you know the
distance? I know.
What should I do?
By the way, why are you like
this all the time? Oh, my God.
What should I do?
Today's lucky item is this!
What's the reason?
The reason is the perfect length.
Is length important?
The perfect thickness and length.
Do you like the length?
What is it?
It looks good, doesn't it?
And this golden egg is small and cute.
What are you talking about?
It's cute, isn't it?
What's wrong?
Senpai, what?
Can I touch it? Touch it.
No.
Why?
You've been talking about a lot of guys.
That's right.
There were a lot of guys.
Originally.
It's original.
What? Why? Senpai, please.
What's wrong?
Is it bad? I can't do it.
Someone, please touch it.
No, no, no.
Please touch it.
Senpai, Senpai, Senpai.
I'm going to be the one
who makes you have sex.
What?
Wait, Kobayashi-kun,
what's that hand? I hate it.
Let me change my clothes.
I'm doing it over there.
I was nervous.
Do you want me to lick you?
What's wrong? Please lick me.
I'm watching you.
What?
Why?
She is licking your hand.
She is licking my hand.
She is taking a photo.
How do I look?
You look comfortable.
I feel good.
Do you feel good? Really? Wait.
Don't take a photo.
Don't take it off.
It's hot.
It's cute.
What are you doing, Senpai?
Which Senpai? Pera.
Hoshinaka Senpai.
Pera.
I saw it.
It's dangerous.
Pera.
Shimo-san, do Pera.
Can I?
It's so beautiful.
I can't see it.
Wow! It's beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Senpai, it's so beautiful.
It's soft.
It's beautiful. It's cute.
What is it?
Both of you have boobies.
It's showing.
Yume-chan, why don't you take it off?
Why don't you take
it off? Take it off.
Take it off?
Senpai, you keep touching it.
What? Wait a minute.
There are two.
I took it off.
What?
Shizuya is rubbing it.
Rubbing? That's bad.
Wait a minute.
It's been 5 minutes.
5 minutes? Look at me.
I'm embarrassed.
It's fast.
I took it off.
You have beautiful legs.
He said I have beautiful legs.
You are standing on tiptoe.
I'm so jealous!
I'm more jealous than
when I got my boobs out.
Do you have a favorite among
the cute and beautiful ones?
What?
I like them the most.
I see.
I can't say it.
I can't get close to you.
You are so cute.
Show me your butt.
You have a nice butt.
Can I touch your butt?
Let me touch you.
Let's do it together.
Together?
Emi-chan, you are pulling out a lot.
I pulled out a lot.
Emi-chan is pulling out a lot.
I'll pull it out.
It's difficult for men
to take it off like this.
Can I take it off for you?
Take it off for me.
Wait.
It's difficult.
Is it difficult?
I'm going to take it off for you.
It's really good.
Please take it off for me.
I'm going to take off my skirt.
One, two, three.
It's hot.
What are you talking about?
Your skin is so white.
Yui's skin is white, too.
No, I'm not.
I'm white.
I'm sorry.
You're too drunk.
I'm not drunk.
You look pale.
I'm not. I'm not.
I want to touch you.
I want to touch you, too.
Can I touch you? You're so soft.
Am I? You're so soft.
What? You're running.
You're sweating a lot.
I'm sweating a lot.
Because of the alcohol.
I feel something.
What?
How do you feel?
I don't want to touch you.
I'm waiting for you, Hoshinoko-san.
I'm waiting for you.
Our company is like this.
It's dangerous.
Is it soft? Wait a minute.
One person.
I think I can be a cameraman.
Why?
Are you waiting for me?
What are you going to do?
Will you bite me?
Will you use me?
You chose Saji-kun,
didn't you? I chose him.
Are you going to take off
your clothes? Hey, hey, hey.
Senpai's chinpo is lonely.
Are you lonely,
Senpai? Yes, I am.
I'm so lonely.
Let's lick together.
Let's lick together?
Yes, let's lick together.
Then, let's lick this side.
Is it possible to lick
together? No problem.
I'll open the door.
Will you lick me if I
fall down? No problem.
No problem?
Really? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Is it OK?
Oh my god!
It's so nice!
Isn't it too big?
Isn't it a pottery?
Oh my god!
Please take a good picture.
I'm embarrassed.
Can we take a picture with three people?
Yume, come here.
Please touch this.
Thank you.
It's hard to see.
You are so worried.
I didn't know it was so big.
It's so big.
If you knew it, you would be surprised.
It's amazing.
It's like heaven.
Hey, do something!
I feel like I'm being touched all the time.
I just turned around.
Hey, touch me properly.
Senior?
Aise has a weak breasts.
I don't think so.
She looks erotic when I rub her breasts.
Yume looks more erotic than Aise.
She looks more erotic than Aise.
Aise is so cute.
I hope you don't mind.
No, I don't.
Then, I'll have this one next.
It feels good.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
That's good.
Which one do you like better,
Hoshinaka-senpai or me?
What?
I like both of you.
I smell something.
Oh, no.
My stomach is in trouble.
Why don't you lick Tsukki?
What?
Do you want me to lick Tsukki?
Yes.
What?
OK.
How about this?
What?
It's hard to do both.
Yes, it is.
Are you not used
to it? No, I'm not.
Both of them are big, so it's difficult.
Difficult.
I can't stand it.
It's big, isn't
it? It's amazing.
It's true.
It's a real baby.
It looks like a golden egg.
What is it? It's amazing.
Senpai, you're doing great.
It's very delicious.
It's been a while, isn't it?
Can I lick you?
No, I don't want to.
Can I borrow your camera?
It's been a while, isn't it?
Wait, you are taking it off by yourself.
It's embarrassing.
Are you serious?
It's embarrassing, so don't get so close.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a baby sitting
on a baby's lap, and
I'm very happy to see it.
I'm glad I was able to see it.
I can't do it.
You are out of breath.
I'm really good at this.
What's that compliment?
It's embarrassing.
What's that?
What's that? It's so erotic.
It's embarrassing.
What's that? It's terrible.
I'm happy to be with you.
I feel good.
Everyone is having fun.
Which one do you
like? It feels good.
I should take a picture of you.
He is touching you.
He thinks it's good.
The baby is going to be born.
The baby is not yet born.
The baby is in the cradle.
What are you talking
about? Wait a minute.
Is it a song? Yes, it is.
Hime-chan, you are awesome.
You are awesome, too.
No, I'm not.
Are you sure? Yes, I am.
OK.
How do you feel? I feel so good.
I'm getting a little jealous.
Is that so?
Oh, wait a minute.
Can I take this? I'm so nervous.
Oh, my God.
Are you nervous? Yes, I am.
I feel so good.
You can do it.
You can't do it.
What? From behind.
From behind?
Yes.
Oh, no.
It's dangerous from behind.
It feels good from behind.
Can you take it
off? It feels good.
I'm going to put it in.
I'm going to put it in, too.
Are you all right?
Look, there's a lot in here.
You put a lot in there.
Coco, let's go.
No, no, no, no.
It's hot.
You're losing weight.
I can't do it.
Do you want to do
it again? I can't do it.
What do you mean? I can't do it.
Do you want to do
it again? I'm sorry.
Thank you.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a baby who has a lot of boobs.
The baby has a lot of boobs.
This is the first in a long time that I
have seen Taniguchi's childHodoo's body.
It is a very rare form of labor.
The only other child in Taniguchi's
family was Que, his father.
She is the only one of the Que's family
that the Taniguchi family has raised.
Since she has been
raised by her mom,
Taniguchi has been able
to make great progress.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Are you all
right? It's all right.
What's wrong with you?
I can't stand it.
Look at this.
Isn't it terrible?
I can't stand it.
You are a bad boy.
I'm sorry.
I can't stand it.
I'm sorry. I'll do my best at work.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
What's wrong with
you? Oh, my God.
You are so cute, aren't you?
What's wrong with you?
You are so excited.
You are so cute.
I can go deep into the mountain.
Oh, it tickles.
Let's go.
I'm going to be bullied by you guys.
I'm not bullying you.
I'm not good at it.
I'm nervous.
I'm getting a lot of it.
Did you get it?
Really?
I'm not good at it.
I'm getting a lot of it.
She is eating a little.
It's hot.
She doesn't like it.
I'm scared.
It's hot.
It's dangerous.
Everyone does it, isn't it great?
I said I don't want to see your boobs.
I said I want to see my boobs.
Oh, from here?
I want to see it.
It's disgusting.
Wait a minute, Yome-chan.
It's scary.
I'm scared.
I want to get up.
Do you like to get up?
I like to get up.
You look like a toy in an amusement park.
That's true.
Wait a minute. I think I can do it.
Really?
Yes.
Isn't it too early? I can do it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it.
I can do it.
I forgot how to do it.
That's not good.
I'm sorry.
You have a delicate face.
I have to record it.
Are you satisfied? Yes, we are.
Stand up.
Let's clean up.
Oh, no.
We have to wear uniforms tomorrow.
What about the day after tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow...
It's good, isn't it? It's good.
Well, it is good.
Then, it's good.
I don't know if the first-year
students have spare time.
No, they don't.
Oh, no.
Are you all right?
Let's clean up.
You look sleepy.
I'm sleepy.
You can sleep. I'll clean up.
Really? Yes, you can.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
All right.
Trash.
Clean up the table.
If you bring a tissue, I
want you to feed them.
Tissue?
There was a tissue.
Is there a tissue? Here it is.
Thank you.
I don't have a towel.
Hot!
Is the shower room closed
at this time? I think so.
I think so.
No, the bedding is here.
Oh, it's much cleaner.
Is this garbage?
Yes, this is garbage.
Kanna, Ime-chan brought it for you.
Oh, yes, I washed it in the bathroom.
Certainly.
Where is the trash?
I'll flush the trash.
There is a trash can over there.
Kobayashi.
I'll flush the trash.
Thank you.
Can I open it? Let's open it.
Please.
It's heavy.
Shall we put the rest in the warehouse?
Yes, let's do that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
Shall we put this in the warehouse?
Don't forget your employee card.
Thank you for your hard work.
What should I do? Should I wait?
Don't you want to see
something you don't usually see?
I'm trying to eat now.
I haven't done it yet.
I'm not in the middle of it.
I'm a little drunk.
What do you want to do?
I want to go to the president's office.
Do you want to step
on the president's sofa?
I want to do that.
That's great.
Let's go.
Let's clean up this mess.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
Should I wear it?
No, you don't have to.
You can put it on your desk.
OK.
We're almost done.
I'm ready.
The festival was amazing.
It was amazing.
The party was full of people.
Everyone had a drink.
Did I prepare too much alcohol?
Maybe we bought too much.
There were some left.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's been a while,
hasn't it? Yes, it has.
The manager
said, let's buy a lot.
We don't have much.
Yes, yes.
We bought too much.
What?
Did you bring the
camera? Yes, I did.
Why? Don't you
need it? Just in case.
Did you throw it away properly?
You said you drank a lot.
Yes, I did.
What's that?
I thought I'd keep a record.
I don't need a record.
You drank a lot, but were you okay?
Yes, I was fine.
What?
I thought I'd stab you in the back.
Were you okay? I was fine.
Aren't you weak?
I might be a little weak.
Really?
You were pretty drunk.
Yes.
What? Nothing.
Let's go.
I'm still fine.
What do you
mean? I'm still fine.
I know, but I'm still fine.
What are you talking
about? Let's go home.
What?
You have a big chest.
What are you talking about?
I thought it was amazing
when I saw it earlier.
No, it's not like that.
Is that so?
I think it's normal.
Really?
What?
I thought it was really cute.
You don't usually say that.
Because I can't say that at work.
That's true.
Isn't it such a character?
It's not like that,
is it? Yes, it is.
What?
No?
What are you
filming? It's funny.
Just in case.
It's so funny.
What?
You like chocolate pie, don't you?
I was watching it.
You were?
It's still not enough.
What's that? You were so sexy just now.
Yes, I was.
I was so sexy.
No, you weren't.
Yes, I was.
I'll give you a beer.
Really? Sorry.
No problem.
Thank you.
I'm so nervous.
What are you doing?
No, I'm not doing anything.
You're taking a picture
of a high school girl.
Do you usually take pictures like that?
No, it's not like that.
Do you have a camera on your butt?
Yes, it's very beautiful.
There's a man in a suit.
What are you talking about?
I'm out of breath.
It's ticklish.
It's not hot.
This is a video that I
took when I was in the
hospital for the first
time in a long time.
Oh!
I want you to touch me.
What?
You want me to touch you?
I want you to touch me.
I did it.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Someone is coming.
Are you OK?
I don't think so.
You are sick.
I don't think it's a good idea.
What if someone
else comes? Oh, I see.
Let's go in there.
Let's go in there and continue.
Okay.
Isn't it dangerous?
Is it dangerous?
It's dangerous, isn't it?
You're taking a lot of pictures.
Because you're so cute.
I'm a little embarrassed.
When you look at me like this.
You're right.
I don't talk to you while I'm working.
You don't talk to me at all.
What?
I talked to you a lot a while ago.
No, because the content of
the work is a little different.
Do you feel good? I feel good.
It's hard here.
It feels good.
I was surprised because you
were out of breath suddenly.
I couldn't stand it.
I want you to look at me.
What?
I want to be licked.
I can't help it.
It feels great.
I'm going to show you a cute
video of a cat playing with a ball.
My husband and I bought a new cat
tower for the first time in a long time,
and we are very happy to have a cat
tower for the first time in a long time.
I took it out a while ago.
What's that?
What should I do? Sit down.
Is it like this?
Yes, that's right.
Oh my god!
Like this?
Yes.
Is this right?
How do you know my voice?
I watch your videos.
Oh, do you watch my videos?
Yes.
You are so cute.
You said something.
Yes.
You are so soft.
Am I soft?
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
I've never seen a cat like this before,
and I've never seen a cat like this before.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's been
a long time since I've seen a
cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous.
Mom, I want to see if
you are in a good mood.
Mom, are you going to go out again?
You can't go out in a place like this.
This is a video of the
process of making a
massage chair for
the first time in my life.
This is a video of the
process of making a
massage chair for
the first time in my life.
Tickle
Do you want me to remove
the acupuncture point?
Yes.
Wow, it's amazing.
Wow, it's amazing, isn't it?
Yes.
What?
I want to make you feel good.
Really? It's difficult.
It's amazing.
Don't open your eyes.
I was worried about you.
Really?
I have a cat that I love so much that I
have never thought of taking a video of him.
It's been a while since
I have seen such a cat.
I'm going to take the
video of you holding the cat.
Because this is the first time for
me to hold the cat, I'm a little nervous.
Are you ready?
Do I have to do it automatically?
Yes, do it automatically.
It's embarrassing.
What's that?
I can't hold it in.
Can I put it in? Yes, you can.
I'll put it in here.
Can you put it in like this?
Yes, I want to put it in like this.
It feels good.
She has been in hot water for a while.
This time, bring her some water.
She has been in hot water
for three days, but she is okay.
She was only a little bit hot.
It's narrow and difficult, isn't it?
Do you want me to ride on you?
Is it OK?
You're not used to it, are you?
I can't help it, so I'll ride on you.
I'm still recording.
Yes, you are.
Oh, it feels so good.
There's a lot in there.
It feels so good.
Oh, it feels so good.
This is a video of my son and my
daughter playing in the living room.
My son is playing with my daughter.
This is the first time I've ever seen a
cat like this, and I've never seen a cat
like this before, so I'm looking forward
to seeing what kind of cat it will be.
I'm going to take a
look at the cat's reaction.
The cat's reaction is very good.
Hi,laria.
It's finally time to see the outlook.
I'm so excited to see the result.
I'm so excited.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Aoyama-san was treated so well that it
was a big problem when he had surgery.
A mother fox who is not
good at letting go of her baby.
The mother fox who has
already given up on her baby,
My husband and I bought a new cat
tower for the first time in a long time.
The cat tower has been
in use for a long time.
I'm going to put a towel on your head.
It's dangerous if I don't
put a towel on your head.
That's right.
Wait a minute.
There's a lot on the toilet.
Oh, my God.
I'm afraid I'll get caught.
It's okay if I put a towel on your head.
Is it okay if I put a towel on your head?
Put a towel on my head.
Yes.
Are you satisfied?
But I want to do it again.
After this, I will come to your house.
I want to go.
OK.
Let's go home.
Let's go home together.
OK.
Do you have clothes?
Clothes?
Yes.
Are you OK? I'm OK.
Good morning.
Let's go home together.
You've never been in here, have you?
I've never been in here, either.
Why?
Haven't you been called?
You've been called here, haven't you?
If you say, I'm sorry,
you'll get a slap on the butt.
No, I haven't.
That's terrible.
Oh, you are here.
Yes, I am the president.
You don't have time for
shooting, do you? No, I don't.
By the way, it's open.
Yes, it is.
Really?
The security is tight.
Yes, it is.
May I come in? Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Great.
Is it like this? Great.
What is this?
This is a living room.
It's very nice.
Great.
Can I come in?
I just came here.
Are you OK?
Yes.
You know, when you go back to the office...
How do you like it? It's great.
It's great?
I'm looking at my secretary's butt.
What?
I'm not touching it now.
You're not touching
it now? No, I'm not.
I'm looking at it.
You're pretending to
work, aren't you? It's great.
It's great, isn't it?
It's a very good chair, isn't it?
Do you want to sit on it?
I want to sit on it.
Excuse me.
How do you like it? It's great.
How do you feel now? It's great.
Please sit on it.
What?
Can I sit on it? Thank you.
How is it? It's small.
But I think the height
of the desk is just right.
You look like a very small president.
And you look like
you're having a hard time.
What? Me?
Yes.
Touch the person next to you with a stick.
Touch.
Kasia, Totoki.
Makizuni.
That's good. Is that all you can do?
What?
More?
I think Uchinoichi-sensei is in trouble.
I just felt that
Uchinoichi-sensei is in trouble.
Give it to me!
What did you do?
I'm trying to put my butt on it.
It's not good, is it?
I'll try to sit on it.
Are you sure?
Please sit on it.
Really? I'm holding it.
What's wrong?
How do I look?
You look like a female president.
But you're going to sleep there
anyway, right? It's a reward.
It's like a lap
pillow, isn't it?
It's like a lap pillow, isn't it?
Can I put it on? It's cute.
It's cute.
It's like a lap pillow,
isn't it? It's cute.
don't you have anything more to say?
More?
What the president doesn't like.
It's like Sekuhara.
It's crazy.
I consulted with him.
What did you do?
When we were alone in the
elevator, he touched my boobs.
Have you ever been
touched? No, I haven't.
No? What?
Let's play the video again.
We're in the elevator.
If you do that, it will be like this.
That's terrible.
You have to take revenge.
Then, I will take revenge.
What?
What will you do?
I will have my tongue rubbed.
Your tongue will be rubbed?
That's terrible.
What will you do?
Will you rub it on your boss's desk?
I'm going to rub it on your back.
I'm going to rub it on your son.
Like this, right? I'm sorry.
Really? Really.
You're going to rub it on my back?
Then I'm going to get revenge.
I'm going to do it three times.
Ah!
Is she sleeping?
She's not sexy, is she?
Really? She's doing it.
I'm going to rub it on your back.
Is she doing it?
I'm going to do it.
It's so beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Let's get in.
I think there is a baby's play area.
I don't like it.
I haven't been there much.
Where? In the dressing room?
Yes.
I was here.
What? Wait a minute.
You can't make a joke,
can you? No, I can't.
I have a lot of questions.
You have a lot of questions?
Yes.
Do you have a
boyfriend? Yes, I do.
What? Wait a minute.
You haven't heard about me, have you?
I haven't heard about you.
Really?
Has it changed?
Maybe this year?
Did you change your mind?
I thought you were the president,
so I asked you a question.
What did you ask me?
Well,
Do you do such a sexy thing alone?
What did you answer?
I can't answer that.
I can't get in unless I answer honestly.
That's right.
I like fat guys.
Is it a miracle?
I like a person who can make
me laugh and deceive me like this.
I think so, too.
Because you are likely to get angry.
Me, too.
I'm likely to get angry.
Look, raise your legs.
What?
Raise your legs.
I'll get angry.
What? Look.
I can't help it.
You are so kind.
You will give me a bonus.
I will give you a bonus.
No, I won't.
I won't give you a bonus.
How much bonus do you want me to give you?
Well, the bonus is... 5 times?
5 times!
Oh my god!
I'm sure you'll get a lot of love.
I won't give you more than 5 times.
By the way, I don't have sex with you two.
What?
What did you say?
Oh, you're right.
Oh, you're right. I don't.
I want to.
What? I want to.
Do you still have a crush
on me? Of course I do.
Don't underestimate
the safety of men.
Great!
Great! I'm fine.
I'd like to see you two
playing with each other.
What?
Do you feel good with girls?
I feel good when I'm touched.
Oh!
You're so active.
You touched me a little while ago.
I did.
It felt good.
Can I see you for a moment?
I'll take a good picture of you.
I wonder if I can take a picture of it.
Do you like that kind of thing?
I buy a lot of those AVs.
No, you don't.
Really?
Of course, I do.
What should I do? Where
should I go? I'm confused.
I'm a little nervous.
Right?
I don't usually do this.
There were a lot of people
earlier, so I was in a good mood.
I don't think the president will think so.
A young woman has sex at her desk.
The president hasn't come back yet.
I don't think he'll come back today.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
He's young and fast.
Are you angry?
Are you angry, Ushi?
Oh, I can see it.
Please take a good picture of it.
Are you going to take a picture of it?
I don't remember at all what I saw earlier.
But this is cute,
isn't it? It's cute.
It's cuter to wear it, isn't it?
You look like you want to touch it.
Don't you want to touch it?
I'm not sure if I can touch it.
You can keep touching it.
I want to touch it.
I can't touch it.
I got it.
Thank you.
It's good.
I touched it.
No?
You're so aggressive.
You were aggressive towards Kobayashi-kun.
Yes, I was.
I turned on the power switch.
Really? Excuse me.
No, I'm embarrassed.
Are you sweating?
I'm embarrassed.
Your nipples are really beautiful.
How do you feel?
It feels so good.
Does it feel good?
If you attack both of
my nipples, I'll bite you.
Oh, no.
This is bad.
Isn't it bad to blame
your junior by yourself?
It's bad, isn't it?
I want you to lick me, too.
What? Don't you want to lick me?
What's that?
It's good, but it's like
being used by a good toy.
This is the first time I've
ever seen a cat using it.
Can you use it? Excuse me.
It's hot here, isn't
it? It's hot here.
If I turn on the air conditioner,
the cat will be in danger.
I see.
Great.
It's cold.
Does it feel good?
I want to touch you.
I've never seen a female
dog so close to a male dog.
I don't have one.
You don't have one, do you?
It matches with you.
What?
How about you?
This one?
I was surprised.
Rinkutaro.
Oh, my God.
You just licked it.
Oh, good.
I want to take it off.
Really?
I'm laughing so hard.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
I'm sorry to make you laugh.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
I licked your boobs.
Oh, it feels good.
It's getting really hard.
Oh, my God.
I am a little shy.
It feels good.
Senpai is good.
What? Senpai is good.
You are good.
I am excited.
It feels good.
It's smooth.
Can I serve you more?
Can you? Of course.
I'll lick you.
What?
Yes.
I want to lick you.
Excuse me.
I'm going to take off my clothes.
You should take off your clothes.
It's not good to get dirty.
You look like an old man on the way home.
You look nice.
I wanted to take off my clothes.
She is sniffing.
Are you good at sniffing?
Yes, I am good at sniffing.
Are you going for a walk?
Oh, my God!
What's going on?
Oh, my God! Wait a minute.
Isn't it bigger than the
last one? No, it's not.
It's the same size as usual.
This one, too.
Oh, no!
Hey, I'm licking you. Take it off.
I'll take it off.
Oh, no!
You're grabbing me.
You know how I feel, don't you?
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Wait a minute!
Don't do it!
Oh, my God!
You are bullying me.
I'm not bullying you.
Are you okay?
Oh, my God!
This is a difficult one.
Oh!
The seal has come out.
Do you want to know what's next?
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
It's so hot!
Do you want to
take it off? Yes, I do.
May I?
It's so hot!
Do you want to take it off that much?
It's so hot, isn't it?
Oh, no!
Shoya, you are wrong.
Oh, really?
Then, one by one, please.
One by one?
Yes, one by one, please.
One by one? Excuse me.
Wow, it's so big.
Is it big?
Do you compare it with Kobayashi-kun?
Are you comparing
with me? Yes, I am.
Oh, no!
I want Senpai to lick me soon.
She seems to enjoy licking you.
Right?
She is really big.
Really?
I think she is the biggest in the company.
It's the biggest in the world, isn't it?
Yes, it looks like the biggest.
If I put it in here, will I be happy?
If you put it in here,
you'll be happy, won't you?
You'll be happy, won't you?
Wow! Wait a minute.
I think it's better to
take off my clothes.
Yes, just like that.
The baby is full.
The baby is too energetic.
This is a video I took when I was a baby.
I'm not good at talking.
I'm getting a lot of comments
that I'm not good at eating.
I'm not good at eating well.
Can I lick here too? Yeah.
Yeah? Yeah.
Ah, this side comes.
Somehow.
This is Tengu?
Does the president always do this?
But you can do this,
right? Yes, I can.
Great.
I'm a little nervous.
Will you get angry if I shoot it suddenly?
What?
That's not good.
You look happy.
That makes me happy.
But I'll get a lot of pictures on my face.
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'm holding it in.
It feels so good.
Do you want a change
of clothes? Yes, I do.
I want it.
It's too erotic.
Why?
You're sweating a lot.
She's doing something crazy, isn't she?
She's doing something
crazy, isn't she? Wait a minute.
Stop, stop.
Go, go, go.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
I thought my nose was going to explode.
That was close.
Was it really close?
Yes, it was really close.
Let's switch.
Switch?
What should we do?
Do you want to do it
at the president's table?
Or do you want to do it
on the sofa? It's up to you.
Sofa?
Is it dangerous? I don't know.
I'm scared if I break it.
Where are you looking at?
I'm looking at the bench.
How do you want me to look at you?
I just want you to feel good.
Please hug me.
I'm going to hug you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so glad to see you.
You look so nervous.
You're going to go, Senpai?
You're going to be barefoot.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Oh, no!
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Gomen-kutsu,gomen-kutsu.
There's no proof.
Thank you for the meal.
That's dangerous.
It's so beautiful.
Do you want to do it?
No, I have to change my clothes.
Do you have to change
your clothes? It's not good.
It's not good.
It's not good? It's not good.
I just wiped it, so it's okay.
Don't you smell it?
It's not a stain.
Isn't it good? It's hot.
It's hot.
It's very hot.
It's not good.
Wait a minute.
Is it not good? It's not good.
It's not good.
This is not good.
Her technique is not good.
How did you learn it?
I think she is not good at it.
What?
Is it because of her passion for research?
I want her to feel good.
If you move the camera there,
I wonder if it will move.
I want to see your face closer.
Please wait a moment.
Is it bad?
Are you serious? Come here.
Let's get along with each other.
Do you want to get along with me?
What are you doing?
You look like a man.
Do you want to get along
with me? Wait a minute.
Don't do that.
Wait a minute.
Do you think it's better to
play with me? I don't know.
Wait a minute.
No.
It hurts.
Don't laugh.
You are laughing.
Are you laughing?
I didn't notice.
Are you OK?
Are you OK? No, I'm not.
Are you OK? Oh, no.
I'm going to be scolded.
Excuse me.
Can I go now?
What?
I think I've loosened up.
Can I go now? Yes, you have.
I've massaged you a lot.
I don't want to.
Can I go now?
I want to put Senpai's picture in it, too.
You said that, didn't you?
I said it twice.
I'm so active.
What do you want to put in it?
Can I?
Can I turn the
camera to you? Sure.
Look at it.
Do you want to lie down?
What?
Is it better to lie down?
It's better to lie down.
What? Put this in it.
Oh, coffee beans.
Coffee beans.
With a coffee bean cushion.
I'm going to take a bath.
Please.
It's big.
Is it big?
Your bath is big.
I'm back to normal.
How do you feel? I'm so nervous.
I feel great.
I feel like I'm
going to explode.
Really?
I was patient to go to the vet, so
it's not strange to go out at any time.
I feel good.
That's a honorific.
Choco-chan is already eating.
I thought it was that,
but that's a honorific.
I feel good.
Do you have anything you don't do?
How do you feel? I feel so good.
You feel good,
don't you? Yes, I do.
He is laughing at me.
It's fun to take a video like this.
It's fun.
It's your first time, isn't it?
Of course, it is.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
Please say that you usually do it.
How do you feel? It's the best.
Isn't her face
cute? It's so cute.
It's embarrassing.
Her voice is cute, too.
Hold on tight.
Her butt is cute.
Is it dangerous?
He touched my butt.
Your butt is amazing.
Your butt is twitching.
Let's go to annoy the president.
What? Wait a minute.
Oh my gosh!
This is terrible.
I can't do this.
I can't sit on the president's desk.
You'll be scolded.
I'll be scolded.
Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh, it feels so good.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm OK.
Oh, no!
Are you OK?
Yes, I feel so bad.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm OK.
Are you OK?
Oh, no!
Do you feel bad?
Oh, no! I'm scared.
It's dangerous.
It's really dangerous if you get caught.
I have to check your chest, too.
It's more dangerous.
You'll get caught if you get caught.
Take it off.
What's going on? It's difficult.
What?
You look so cool.
Am I on the screen?
Yes, you are.
Is it the same one? Yes, it is.
The white one.
The white one was in the frame.
Was it? Yes, it was.
Pass the camera to her.
What?
I don't know what to do.
Can you do it? Let's try.
OK.
Can you do it?
Can you do it? Wait a minute.
You are so sexy.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
Don't push me.
I want to go out.
Do you want to
go slowly? Slowly.
Oh, no!
You are licking my tongue.
You are cute.
Are you OK?
Do you want me to do it slowly?
Yes.
Oh, no!
Are you OK? It's big.
Is it big? It's big.
You said it in an erotic way.
It's big.
But it feels good.
I'm glad you got used to it.
Let me know when you get used to it.
I got used to it.
You got used to it.
You are fast.
Go slowly.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Senpai's face looks like a pervert.
She is a mother of three children,
and is also a mother of four children.
She is the oldest daughter,
who is the oldest in the family.
She is the oldest child, who
is the oldest in the family.
I'm scared.
Your legs.
My legs.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm in trouble.
You're in trouble.
You're not in trouble.
What? I'm not.
I'm in trouble.
Are you okay? I feel good.
I feel good.
I'm in trouble.
I can't believe it.
Oh, my God! It's so big.
Oh, my God!
Which one do you feel better?
You can do it like this,
and you can do it like this.
Oh, my God!
You can do it like this,
and you can do it like this.
Oh, my God! It's difficult.
It's difficult.
Both of them.
Both of them look uncomfortable.
Oh, no.
When he was a baby, he was very tenacious.
He was the youngest child in the world.
I'm glad he's a good boy.
He's a good boy who's a good boy.
What's this?
Oh my gosh! This is cute.
She is very picky!
What was that just now?
It was a normal kiss.
Do you want to do it?
Do you want to see it?
I want to see it, but I also want to do it.
Which one do you want to do?
I don't want to do it.
Senpai, you have a great face.
Senpai, this is a joke.
I feel sick.
It's really bad.
Do you think you can hold
the camera? Yes, I can.
I'll do my best.
What's wrong?
Do you have a sore throat?
My back?
Your back? It feels good.
Does it feel good?
Do you feel good?
Do you want to touch it?
I want to touch it.
Here?
It's easy to touch, isn't it?
It's easy to touch.
Do you want to touch it, Senpai?
I want to touch it.
Do you feel good? It's hot.
My neck is hot.
Is it hot? It's hot.
It's hot.
Is it hot?
I think it's overflowing.
What's wrong?
It's overflowing.
Oh, no!
Can you suck out the sperm?
I'm still in the urine.
Do you want me to suck it out?
Do I suck it out?
Yes.
I think I'll suck it out.
Do I suck it out?
Yes.
What?
What did you think I was doing?
How is it?
It's very delicious.
Is it? It's delicious.
Really?
Do you eat it?
What?
Do you eat it? No, I don't.
What do you want to eat?
This?
Then, I'll take it.
Let's take a commemorative photo.
I'll take a commemorative photo.
What's your favorite body part?
What? My favorite body part?
What? I like my back.
I like my back, too.
Oh, my God.
It's easy.
It's a yoyo.
What do you mean? It's a yoyo.
I have a yoyo in my house.
What? Neck.
Neck?
Yes.
Where is it?
Hey.
What?
Hey, it's dangerous.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What was that?
It's a sweet tooth.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It feels good.
She is 17 years old.
She is very erotic.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, no, I'm going to have a nosebleed.
Oh, my God!
How are you feeling?
Oh, my God! You are sweating a lot.
I'm sorry.
Your clothes are dirty.
My clothes? Your clothes.
Really? It's so dirty.
I don't think it's my fault.
It's a mess.
I'm glad.
It's really painful.
It's a mess.
It's all over the place.
How are you? I'm fine.
How about you? I'm fine, too.
That's great.
You are strong.
Look at her.
Riko, how are you?
You guys are so fast.
Senpai... Oh, no!
I'll put my hand on your shoulder.
Can you take a picture of my face?
It's pretty close.
How about this?
Are you okay? Wait a minute.
Are you scared?
You are scared,
aren't you? I'm scared.
Can I just watch you?
I want to do it.
Do you want to
do it? It's amazing.
I'm scared.
I'm getting tired.
What does Senpai look like?
Senpai is smiling.
Senpai, do you want to do it?
Do you want
to do it? I'll do it.
I'm going to do it.
Then, stick out your butt.
You can raise the camera.
I'm going to do it.
I'm sorry.
It's close.
Because it's dangerous.
What's wrong?
I stood on the desk.
Because it was dangerous.
I felt good.
I felt good, but I thought
it would be too long.
Yes, it would be too long.
When I noticed it, I stood on the desk.
You are happy.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Don't tighten yourself and go by yourself.
I'm not tightening.
Every time you hug
yourself, you say, Oh, my God.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go to the hospital.
I'm going to the hospital.
Oh, no!
Can we put our faces
side by side? Yes, we can.
Can I put it on your
face? Yes, you can.
Oh, no!
When I was in the hospital,
I was really surprised.
I had a surgery and I was
hospitalized for about a year and a half.
I was hospitalized for
about a year and a half.
Where are you going? I'm sorry.
Oh, no!
Senpai, please wipe it off.
Senpai, are you going to wipe it off?
Tissue? Isn't it
around here? Maybe.
Thank you.
It's here.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I can't wear it because
I'm being taken care of.
I'm wearing a lot.
Give me a tissue.
I mean, clothes.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
What? It's true.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
Isn't it great?
What's this?
There's a lot coming out.
The president's desk is really scary.
It's scary.
It's scary, isn't it?
Are you okay?
Can you wipe it off? Yes, I can.
It's scary.
Have you ever pressed
the 3-point button?
Have you?
What?
I think you have about 10.
I don't think so.
Yes, yes, yes.
After this, let's take a picture together.
No way!
How many times have you done it?
Isn't it amazing? No way.
If it's about two or three
times, I'll do it again.
Really?
I want to do it.
I'm not good at this.
Let's keep it a secret.
What should I do with this?
Can I wipe it with a
tissue? It's not good.
I'll dry it first.
If you turn it upside down, it's not good.
I can do it, can't I?
Wow!
How about this? I can do it.
Are you OK? Yes, I'm OK.
Awesome!