This is the first time I've ever done this, so I'm looking forward to seeing how it will turn out.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it will turn out.
...
You.
Have some coffee?
No!
I'm okay.
Yes, yes.
This weekend is weekend,
what about shifts?
hollow-out work.
This week?
See?
The new garden.
We promised to go by car.
Oh, that's right.
It was this week.
Well, I think it's okay.
Really?
It depends on the progress of the company's project.
Maybe I'll have to work overtime again.
I see.
But don't worry too much.
You've been working all the time lately.
It's because I got fired from Tokyo and got a job at the management office.
If I don't contribute to the company's business, I won't look good.
Yes, it's hard for you, isn't it?
It's okay, it's okay.
There's still room for discussion in the apartment.
I'll do my best today as well.
Huh?
Oh, it's already this time.
Then, I'll go to the office.
See you later.
Did you forget something?
Yeah, it's okay.
The next day
Hello.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Have a good night.
Hey, I'm home.
Welcome home.
This is Kanae.
Nice to meet you.
This is Iguchi-senbu.
Hello, I'm Iguchi.
This is Yamashita from Doki.
I'm Yamashita. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Senbu, your wife is really nice, isn't she?
She's got a great body.
More than that, I'm going to that club.
You're going to the hotel?
That's right.
Please come in.
This way.
Thank you.
Please come in.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry...
Here, sit down.
This is for you.
I'm sorry for the trouble, but I'm really sorry.
Hey, Yamashita, drink it.
No, it's for you.
This is for Kyoshiku.
Hey, you're my friend. Please forgive me.
No, it's not like that.
It's good. This time, I'll give it to the new head of the Amakawa branch.
It's a great mansion.
Is this the office?
Yes.
I've been working as a loaner for 35 years.
Well, I see. But it's a management job starting next year.
If I were the head of the department, I would have worked hard and returned it as soon as possible.
I'm sorry.
It's true.
No, no, no.
No, I really want to return it.
I can't believe I'm going to be a manager soon.
Thank you for waiting. Here's your snack.
Oh, thank you.
Kimu, sit down here.
Oh, okay.
Sit down, sit down.
You have to sit down here.
Oh, thank you.
Here's your snack.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm so glad to be invited by such a beautiful lady.
By the way, the vice president's group is doing something suspicious.
They are really bad guys.
Well, we have to be careful not to cause trouble.
That's right.
If we like, we'll try to make the people of the executive branch lose their jobs.
We'll start a scandal.
Well, Amakawa-kun, you're going to lose your job from next term.
We have to be careful not to cause trouble.
Yes, executive.
What do you think of Ms. Amakawa?
Well, I don't know.
She's the best in the class.
Right, Ms. Amakawa?
Thank you very much.
But Ms. Amakawa is really beautiful.
You're right, Senmu.
You're so beautiful.
You have a good style.
Did you do anything like modeling?
No, I didn't do anything like that.
By the way,
when I was a student,
I went to Miss Campus.
Yeah, I think I got second place.
Wow, that's amazing.
You got second place in Miss Can?
I wonder if that's true.
I can't believe it.
I don't remember anything about the past.
I'm so jealous of the beautiful wife of Mr. Harukawa.
You should get married too, Yamashita.
You're single, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I envy you.
I'll get married soon.
Is that so?
Yes.
Anyway, Hamakawa-kun,
With a beautiful wife and a nice apartment.
Anyway, I hope you will continue to do your best as our manager.
Yes, sir.
Well, let's toast.
Well, let's toast again.
Cheers.
Thank you for the food.
Wow, it's so nice.
It's amazing that you can make such a wonderful dish even though it's so beautiful.
I just used what I had.
You really don't have a place to go during the day, do you?
No, I don't.
As expected, you are the most successful wife of the year.
Please stop, Director.
I don't want to. It's embarrassing.
Here is your sake.
Thank you.
Your cooking is very good.
I'm glad that you like it.
It's the best.
Every time I cook such a delicious dish, the food is delicious.
I'm going to go to the bathroom for a while
Please come in.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for the sudden request.
No problem.
What kind of request do you have today?
Where are you from?
Actually, I'd like to talk to you about your husband, Mr. Amakawa.
About my husband?
As a new manager, he's still working hard at the company.
In fact, our company also has what is called a school punishment, which is like a fight for the school punishment.
The people of the opposite class are playing a lot of tricks.
So, to make Mr. Amakawa, who has just been promoted to the management office, lose his job,
I've been pointing out the drawbacks of last year's project.
If things go on like this, Master,
I don't know if I'll be able to get a promotion,
or if I'll be able to get rid of some kind of bribes.
Um, um...
Can't you do something about it?
Master...
He's busy with work every day.
He said he wanted to get a job as a manager.
He said he'll do his best because he has a lot to do at home.
Can't we do something about it, teacher?
Even the loan at home...
We can do something about it with the bonus.
We're really working hard together right now.
But...
Um...
It's like this.
Please.
Well...
We can't do anything about it, can we?
Really?
Yeah.
If I don't do the opposite, I'll be at a risk.
Well, I'm at a risk, so I can't just say it.
What should I do?
Um, Sam, this is...
Well, if you leave me to it, I'll take good care of you.
But...
There's a risk, but there's also a risk.
I trusted you as the head of the department, but I failed.
I'm sorry, but my husband will scold me.
You still have a loan, don't you?
Your husband is silent, so I don't know.
I'm sorry, but please don't do this.
I don't know if my husband can stay as the head of the department or not.
You understand, don't you?
I'm in trouble.
If you can't pay the loan, you'll be in more trouble.
That's...
Which one do you think is in trouble?
But...
You have a really good body, don't you?
Please stop. I can't see you.
Please stop, Mr. Eguchi.
I'm in trouble.
Where are you going, madam?
I'm really in trouble.
I don't want to do it. I'm going to be scolded by my boss.
If you don't pay the rent, you might have to leave this apartment.
That's...
And this and that...
I've been curious about your body for a long time.
Please stop.
If you let me touch your body, I'll wipe away the work of the other party.
It's not a bad thing, isn't it?
What if my husband finds out about this?
I don't know.
If you leave it to me, it will be over soon.
What do you think?
For me...
I'm in trouble...
As the wife of the chief...
You have to support your husband.
This is...
As expected...
Please stop.
If you leave it to me, I'll do something about my husband.
I'm sorry
It's not over yet.
Please stop.
You can't just swallow it.
It's really good, isn't it?
Are you sensitive here?
No, I'm not!
You're saying you're not, but you're reacting, aren't you?
Right?
Or...
Is there a more sensitive place?
No, please don't do that!
There is, isn't there?
There is...
Please don't do this to me.
If you leave it to me, I'll keep working at the company.
What is it?
I don't like it.
Show me your beautiful butt.
It's really covered.
Stop.
If your husband's future is promised, it's a good deal, isn't it?
Don't you think so?
My husband's future...
I didn't know that.
Don't say that.
It's getting tighter here.
I can feel it.
Is it here?
Please don't do that.
I don't want to.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
You're getting wet.
It's okay.
You'll feel better.
Stop it.
Please don't do that.
Did you say something?
It's that easy, isn't it?
No, no, no.
Please let me go.
No, no.
I'm sorry, I'm not a skipper.
That's not true!
It's okay, it doesn't hurt.
It's getting worse and worse.
Please stop it.
No, no
I'm sorry.
You're really going too far, aren't you?
No.
Right?
Just now...
Um...
My husband...
No...
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
No, no, no.
You're full of energy, aren't you?
You're not going to run away, are you?
Mr. Izuchi, Mr. Izuchi...
Oh no!
Please don't!
What?
What are you doing?
No, you can't get mad at me like this, can you?
No, I can't get mad at you like this, can you?
I'll cover it up.
Let's do something more pleasant.
Please stop.
I can't.
I can't do it.
Is it okay?
No.
No matter what happens to my husband.
Stop.
No!
Go! No!
I'm sorry
Me too.
Well then, see you later.
You don't have to do this anymore.
If you leave it to me, I'll do something about my husband.
Isn't it cheap if your husband's future is promised with this?
Don't you think so?
If you leave it to me, I will continue to work in the company from now on.
I'm sorry
I'm home!
Welcome home!
You took a bath?
Yes, I'm sweating.
I'll get you some food.
Thank you.
By the way,
about my project,
I'm having a hard time.
I'm sorry.
I had a hard time.
It was Saturday, right?
Yes.
I wanted to go to a gardening shop.
It may be a little strict.
Is that so?
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Anyway,
I'm working hard as a manager now.
For the sake of our future,
we have no choice but to do our best now.
I understand. I'll do my best, too.
What's for dinner tonight?
I don't know.
Do you have any requests?
I see.
How about hamburgers?
I'll go get them.
I'm sorry
I'm sorry.
As expected of your wife.
It's a wise decision.
I'm sorry.
I thought you would understand because you are smart.
Please keep it a secret from your husband.
Of course.
I don't know why, but I'm not sure if it's because I don't know how to do it
Please wait for me.
Of course I will.
You don't have to worry about your husband.
Your husband is working hard at the company right now, so you should do your best, too.
Hold him tight.
Oh, oh
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I'm so happy.
I'm so jealous that you have such a good style and a wife who is easy to feel.
Ah, ah, ah
Slurping
Hmm?
Stomachs areVAgGn
Ah no
onsidering
Ah, don't play with me
Wait..
Stop
Stop it
I'm sorry.
You're in love, aren't you?
Stop it, stop it.
Why are you crying?
I'm so hungry.
I can't do it anymore.
No, no
Are you okay?
I'm not done yet.
I'm almost done.
Stop it.
Forgive me.
Ah...
It's all over the place.
No, it's not.
It's...
Ah...
No...
I'm so sorry.
It's time to make you feel better.
What is it?
I'm sorry
Yes.
Do you smell good?
You've been through so much.
Please take care of me.
I wonder if the owner is really okay.
Isn't it natural?
How is the taste of Chimpanzee other than your husband?
That's right.
Please lie down.
Here we go, madam.
Ah!
As expected of your wife.
With this, you can be sure of your husband's identity.
Please, please, don't leave me.
I can't do it anymore.
No!
No, I can't.
Please wait.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't go.
You're full of wounds.
No, I can't go.
I can't do it anymore.
Please wait.
I just said it.
I'm sorry.
Mom, I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
How do you feel?
Compared to your husband
Do you feel better?
Hey, what do you think?
Be honest with me.
If you behave like that, I'll cut your hair.
See?
It's a big one.
It's my husband's.
It's dangerous.
No, no
What should I do?
I can't die.
Oh, no, no
I can't do it anymore.
No, no, no.
Go, go, go.
Please stop.
I'm going!
I'm going to cry.
I'm sorry
Are you happy?
Please leave it to me.
Before that, your wife is going to go to work.
Mom
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
I think it's time for you to go to the shop.
Please.
No, I can't go there.
I'm going.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I'm sorry!
Would you like to take a shower?
Actually I have a meeting after this.
Mr. Shinji...
It's the pleasure to meet you.
Well now...
Feel your armsScraping
Hey, Amaka-kun, your husband is working hard at the company.
Now that I'm on your side, your husband is safe in the future.
You don't have to worry about anything.
Thank you very much.
Senma, how long are you going to stay here?
It's good to have a bath in the middle of the night.
It's comfortable.
I'm not used to bathing in the middle of the night.
I don't want to.
There's nothing to do.
You're doing your best, Ran-chan.
But when I come back...
Why don't you come back?
Ran-chan, you're standing up again.
But...
I'm sorry
You can't forget the chimp from before, can you?
What's wrong? You went too far a while ago.
Are you okay now?
Stop it, please stop it.
Did you feel lucky to have a chimp from before?
I want to take a bath.
You want to take a bath, don't you?
Please don't do this to me.
It's been a long time since the last time I saw it
You're so mean!
You rubbed me like that for the first time in my life!
You just ate all the food with this chimp, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I'm sorry.
Do you do this with your husband in the bathroom?
What are you going to do if I ask you?
You're a good girl.
I've never done anything like that.
I see.
So you're not going to do this for me?
You're rude.
You can't be satisfied with just a little bit of it, can you?
Right?
I can't be satisfied with just a little bit of it, can you?
Are you satisfied with just a little bit of sex?
To be honest, I do love you.
I'm not asking if you love me or not.
I'm asking if you're satisfied with me.
It's not enough, is it?
I feel good.
I'm sorry
I'm going to take care of you for the rest of your life, so please take good care of me.
Oh, oh
Oh, it's hot.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
You're so good
Madam
Oh no, oh no
It's so hot
I don't know what to do with my body, but I feel like I'm going to die if I don't do something about my body
I'm going to eat the rest of it.
Then I'll go to the office.
Oh, you're early in the morning again today.
It's been a week, isn't it?
It's okay, it's okay.
I've been told a lot of things like my brain and my normal days.
Don't overdo it.
But recently, I'm really happy to work with you.
I wonder what happened.
Well, it's easy for me to work, so it's okay.
Well, I'm going.
Yeah.
Welcome.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm Amakawa.
I'm sorry for being so busy.
Actually,
regarding this project,
I'd like to ask you
for your opinion.
That's right.
Also,
I'd like to ask you
for your opinion
I'd like to talk to you about the negotiation with the vanguard and the subcontractor.
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry.
Oh, and about the order form.
Oh, Hamakawa-kun.
How is it?
Well, thank you in advance.
You're the boss, so you have to do your best from now on.
I'm counting on you.
From now on, the company's main members are all up to you.
Right?
I'm counting on you.
Well then,
make sure to give me the documents by next week.
Yeah.
Even if I can't win, please do your best.
Right
Yes.
Yes, yes, of course.
Rock!
Ah...
Well, I'm counting on you from now on.
Oh!
It doesn't matter.
Amakawa-kun, I'm counting on you.
I told you earlier, but the company is entrusted to you.
I'm sorry,
I'm going to make your beautiful wife sad.
I'm begging you.
Let's go.
Do your best.
It's like your husband is doing his best.
You have to do your best too.
Yamashita-kun, I'm glad you're a professional.
I'll always be with you from now on.
It's great that you're so beautiful.
I didn't think you were this good.
You look so clean.
I really like you.
Say something.
Hmm?
I love you so much.
Don't worry.
Yamashita-kun.
You're so skinny.
You're amazing.
How is it?
It's beautiful.
Do you want to know what's going on down there?
Yes, I do.
Let me help you.
This body is beautiful.
Wow, it's so beautiful.
Is it heavy?
Wow.
It's a beautiful combination.
I wonder if it's okay if I pinch it with this.
It's good.
I'm scared.
Hold her.
Widen your wings.
That's right.
You can do anything.
I love you, Chimpanzee.
I love you, too.
Don't cry.
I'm going to keep it to myself.
I told you the truth.
You won't find out.
Great.
Look at this side.
It's a body.
Touch it.
Make it feel good.
You're the best.
You can do such a cruel thing, can't you?
No, it's for my husband.
For your husband?
Are you sure?
You're probably excited to hear that.
What?
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm sleepy.
What?
You want to get wet again?
No, I don't want to.
Why?
Um.
I'm sleepy.
Hey.
What?
You're probably wet.
It hurts.
Say something.
Please.
I'm sorry.
You're happy that you got two of them.
What do you think?
Please answer.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry
No, no
You know what to do.
Hurry up.
You can go now.
Go on.
I'm sorry
Let's get out of here.
Put it in your mouth.
Oh, no.
Ah ah
Thank you so much.
Yeah, it was really good.
I'm going to give you a lot of good things from now on.
That's right.
Be sure to follow me.
Thank you very much.
Let's drink.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Please drink.
Please be with me.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that you came.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm so relieved this time.
Thanks to you, I was able to do this project.
You really did a great job, Maka.
It's true. It's a difficult case, but it's great.
Well, well, well, well, this is all thanks to all of you who supported me.
Well, well, well, you don't have to say that.
Well, I'll just have a drink.
Please drink.
Thank you.
It's really delicious.
Tonight as well.
It's true.
The taste of your wife.
No, it's not like that.
Hamakawa-kun, you should be thankful for your wife's kindness.
Yes, sir.
I'll do my best.
Let's drink.
Thank you for the food.
The sake is delicious.
It's the best.
Let's drink more.
It's because your wife supported you in the shadows.
Right, wife?
Hooray!
Swallow all of them!
The first !
The first!
Better, hey?
Don't expect much
This is a departmental question
It's all thanks to you guys
Oh, another one
The first...
The first...!
I'm sorry
I'm sorry.
The doctor will wake up.
If you do it here, your voice will come out, right?
You wanted to do something like this, right?
OK, now...
Lower, lower.
You really want it, don't you?
Everyone knows that you like it.
You're just pretending to be serious in front of your husband, aren't you?
You want to touch it, don't you?
You really want to touch it, don't you?
Huh?
The teacher is coming.
Why are you saying that?
Hey.
The royal gear is bad.
Which one do you want?
I'm sorry
Calm down.
Don't worry, I'll lend you a lot of money so you don't have to worry about me.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about me. I'll lend you a lot of money.
Don't cry.
Don't wake up like that.
I'm going to wipe your tears.
I'm sorry
No, no
Ouch, it hurts
Your beautiful wife right here is in such a bad situation.
Look at her face, she's lost a big part of her body
What happened to you?
I'm sick?
Oh, sorry.
It's okay.
You're not satisfied with your husband's chimp, are you?
Master...
You like to run, don't you?
You're talking to yourself, aren't you?
Please drink hot water.
The memory is very bad.
Who were you touching just now?
It's my...
It's my poop.
You touched it on your own.
Right?
Show it to them.
That's embarrassing.
It's dirty.
No, no.
You came here by yourself, didn't you?
Show me.
How did you do it?
What a nasty finger.
It's so dirty.
You always do it by yourself.
You can't do anything by yourself.
Show me your mouth.
Open your mouth.
You're amazing, madam.
You're so cute.
You've grown so much.
Don't say that.
That's good.
You can't do such a horrible job.
Right?
You can't make your wife happy, can you?
I can't take it anymore.
Please let me go.
Your wife didn't listen to you.
I can't take it anymore.
Please let me go.
What do you want?
What do you want to do here?
I want to be close to you.
Open your eyes.
What do you want here?
What's going on?
I can't breathe.
Be quiet.
Oh, no.
It's bigger than the master.
Oh, no. It's amazing.
Ouch.
I'm going.
Oh, oh
Oh, it hurts!
Why?
It hurts!
She's gone.
She's not here yet.
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh no, this is...
You're really going to do this, aren't you?
You look like a shrimp.
I can't do this.
Oh, oh
Move your tongue.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
It feels so good.
Does it feel so good?
You're going to get in trouble.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Oh, no
Ah, ah
You're going to wake her up.
I don't know.
What? You want me to hold you?
You're moving by yourself.
What's going on?
Can I take it out again?
I haven't taken it out yet.
What happened to your mouth?
My mouth is the best.
It's the best.
I'm sorry
Why?
No, no
Oh, oh
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Don't!
You're the best, ma'am.
Now you're free to go.
If you want to do it again, I'll let you do it.
See you later.
Take care of her.