Kanna-san Kanna-san
You are Kanna-san, right?
Yes.
Who are you?
I'm Sana-san's junior.
Today, Sana-san will...
Kanna-san will come.
So...
She said she wanted to start first.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You know...
Wait a minute.
I've heard that you have an erotic wife.
No, no, no.
I've heard that you like her.
You haven't heard
that? No, I haven't.
What?
What do you mean?
Me?
Yes.
Sada-san proposed to me.
What? I haven't heard about it.
Sada-san said she would come later.
Really?
She said she wanted me to be the first one.
That's strange.
You are beautiful.
Do you like erotic things?
Do you like it?
No, I don't like it.
I heard you are very erotic.
I didn't know that.
You started to like it at the entrance
of the hotel, didn't you? Yes, I did.
You said you were
happy at the drinking party.
I'm touching it now.
Do you like it? I don't know.
Look at me.
No.
Why not? It's a promise.
But it's okay.
No.
What should I do?
Sada-san told me to take care of you.
I have to take care of you.
No.
Did you ask me to take care of you?
Yes.
Why?
She said she wanted
to see something erotic.
Something erotic?
It seems to excite her.
It's erotic, isn't it?
I don't want to touch it.
But you don't look like
you don't like it, do you?
I don't know what to do.
Suddenly...
You have a very erotic face.
You look so happy.
Does it feel good? Yes, it does.
Wow.
You look so happy.
I'm so excited.
Do it like you did the other day.
Do it.
I showed you the video
I took the other day.
Did you see it?
What are you doing?
I was showing off.
I was showing off my happiness by drinking.
Why do you do that?
I didn't think I would
show it to this person.
I was saying that I had a sexy wife.
What are you doing?
I was showing off my happiness.
I didn't expect you to touch me like that.
How can I touch you?
I just had a nosebleed.
I didn't expect you to touch me like that.
I'm sorry.
She is purring.
She is crouching.
Wait a minute.
Can I contact you once?
Can I contact you?
What?
To whom?
Who are you going to contact?
You.
Why are you going to contact me?
Because you didn't ask me.
I didn't ask you?
You said you would be happy.
I was surprised.
I'm sorry. Can I call
you just once? Sure.
I'll call you.
Oh, excuse me. Kanna-san came to see me.
Really? That was fast.
He said he couldn't hear
me. Can I talk to him? Sure.
What's going on?
He's a really nice guy.
You should get along with him.
Really?
What do you mean?
I understand what you mean.
He's not a bad guy.
He's my junior.
I'm sorry, but I think it's
more erotic to be non-daily.
What?
Are you going to do it with such a person?
I've been thinking about it for a while
because it might be better than that.
I've been thinking about it for a while.
Is that so? Why? It's okay.
Just a little.
Will you be happy
if I do that? Yeah.
What?
Is that so?
I'm counting on you. Just a little.
If you don't mind, I'll go later.
Come on.
I'm listening.
Do you understand? I don't know.
He's been rejected a lot.
Is it my fault? I think so.
Oh, that's what it is, isn't it?
What?
Is it a lie? Well, then.
..
Lily?
Yes, there was something.
Come quickly.
See you.
Yes.
That's what it is,
isn't it? Wait a minute.
It's definitely strange.
I'm embarrassed
sure I'm embarrassed
You like it, don't you?
It's not that I like it.
You are so cute.
Why are you making that face?
I don't feel good.
You don't feel
good? I feel sick.
Sit down.
I feel sick.
Don't you feel better?
Don't you feel pain?
I don't feel pain at all.
Why don't you feel pain?
I don't feel pain.
I don't feel pain at all.
I feel pain a little bit.
I don't feel pain.
I borrowed this for a while.
This is the first time I've heard of it.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
I've heard of it.
I can't do this anymore.
I'll give you a shot.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's been
a long time since I've seen a
cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm not sure if it's because it's
been a long time since I've seen a cat
like this, but it's been a long
time since I've seen a cat like this.
You want it, don't you?
I want you to tell me that you want it.
I want you to tell me that
you want to have a puppy.
I'll call my dad.
I want to have a puppy.
You want a puppy?
Yes.
That's right.
Because I massage
your back, I feel good.
Wow, that's great.
It feels so good.
You have a nice face.
Oh, it's scary!
Oh, I feel good!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
This feels really good!
Huh?
Can I go to bed?
Yeah!
Kana-san, are you going to
move like that by yourself?
If you want to move like that,
you have to live, Kana-san.
You really like penis,
don't you? No, I don't.
You didn't like it at first, but I
think it was good for everyone.
I don't like it at all now.
You like it, don't you?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!!!
What are you doing?
You can't even see me as I go in.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!!!
Oh!!
Oh, oh!!!
Don't go backward.
Ah...
Ah, that feels good...
Yeah, stick out your butt.
Yes, yes, yes...
Sada-san said she'll look at it later, so I
have to take a lot of pictures of Ecchan's.
Is she really going to look at it?
I won't pick it up.
I'll take a video of you taking a bath.
You are amazing.
What's wrong?
Tell me what's wrong.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Do you want me to
kiss you? What? No.
I'm sorry.
Hey, don't do that.
I told you.
Put your legs up.
I can't do that.
It hurts.
Oh, no.
It feels terrible.
Look at me.
Wow, wow, wow. It's very tight.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm in trouble, too.
If you keep doing this, I'll be in trouble.
Can I take it out?
No.
What?
Do you want to
take it out? Yes, I do.
Can I take it out?
Yes.
Look forward.
You can do like this.
I can do whatever I want.
You can do whatever you want.
I'm so excited to see your face.
Have you ever seen your erotic face?
You have a very erotic face.
Kana-san is crying.
I feel so bad.
Kana-san, I'm so sorry.
Are you all right?
Can I cry?
Can I cry for you?
Are you okay?
Hurry up! Oh, no.
I screamed so much.
Please try to do it.
It's so ticklish.
I'm tired.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I saw your message on LINE.
I'm in a hurry.
Are you coming?
Yes, about 5 minutes ago.
I heard you were drinking tea.
No, I'm not.
I sent you a message
saying it was the best.
What?
I sent you a message
saying it was the best.
No, I didn't.
I'm going to send this to
Sada-san, so I'll spread it out a little.
If Sada-san comes, will you stop it again?
No, I don't know.
I have to get in the way a little,
so I'll take a shower and go out.
Then let's do everything.
What are you doing?
I'm in such a state.
I'm in such a mess.
I'm in a big trouble.
You're too excited.
I don't want to.
I was changing.
What? I was changing.
Were you all right?
I wasn't all right.
Why?
What are you doing?
What did you do?
Why are you asking me such a question?
I don't want you to ask me such a question.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Did you take a
video? Yes, I did.
I'll watch it later.
Don't look at me. I'm angry.
Was he mean?
I don't know if he was mean.
Did you feel good?
Which one? It wasn't bad.
What? I'm jealous.
I want to be jealous.
Did you feel good? Yes, I did.
Did you feel good?
I'm going to show you something erotic.
Oh, my God.
So, what's in the box?
I don't think it's all out.
There was a little bit.
What? Because.
..
What?
I didn't have time to clean it up.
Really? That's right.
You didn't like this?
No.
Were you a little
surprised? I was nervous.
Because I didn't know.
It's not bad, is it?
Your face and so on.
My face?
I was a good person.
Right?
Yes.
But, suddenly...
Next time, let's do something different.
Something different?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
No problem.
You're blushing.
I'm going to show you how to get rid
of the hair on the back of a cat's head.
I'm scared.
Which one do you like?
This one?
Yes.
Do you like this one?
No.
What?
I like this one.
It's coming out a little.
I don't think so.
It's dry.
It's a mess.
Yes.
It's no good. Wait a minute.
It came out.
Really? Tissue.
It's true.
Look at it.
Hey.
Tissue came out.
It's true.
I didn't have time to bathe you.
I want to take a bath there.
Do you want to take a
bath now? No, I don't.
What did he do? It's normal.
What do you mean by normal?
I touched him a little
and put him in the bath.
But he did it with a toy.
Did he?
Yes.
I'm getting excited.
I'm starting to sweat.
I'm sure you're wet.
Do you want to increase
the number of people?
What?
Do you mean the number of people?
Yes.
It's better to call two people.
No, it's better to call only two people.
Which one is better? This one.
Which one? This one.
I'm jealous.
What is it?
Because you called me.
Me? I'm jealous.
Why?
Why did you call me?
Me?
Is this okay?
Did you want to be jealous?
Yes.
It's not good to be a very old man, is it?
If it's good, it's good.
It's not good to be a very
old man, is it? Wait a minute.
I'm a little nervous.
What kind of person
are you? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
It's been a while since
I've been to the vet.
I will try to get the vet's approval.
But I will not be able to see the vet.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
She is very excited.
I was saved by you.
What?
I can hear her voice.
Her spirit is also mixed.
I don't know which one is which.
Oh, it spilled.
Here is the tissue.
What did you do?
I did?
Did you play
with it? Yes, I did.
I was left alone on the phone.
Really? I don't know.
Does it hurt?
No.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Do you feel
better? Just a little.
What? Just a little.
Because it's called sleeping.
I see.
Did you lick my
penis? No, I didn't.
You told me to take erotic pictures.
But that's not what I meant.
I thought you'd be happy
if I took those pictures.
I don't want to bother you any more.
Why?
I don't want to bother you.
Why? That's fine.
That's why I get excited.
Don't get excited.
I don't want to.
You don't want to meet me
suddenly, do you? No, I don't.
Right? No, I don't.
Then do something
that makes me excited.
Then what do you want to do next?
Can I?
Yes.
I might overdo it.
You can.
Really?
Yes.
I'm getting sleepy.
I want to go to bed.
Show me.
You keep doing that.
Do you want to wipe your face again?
I have to wipe it.
Wipe it.
If it's too wet, I don't want to put it in.
I want to see it.
Do you hate it? No, I don't.
Don't you drink it?
Which one? The blue one.
Don't you drink
it? The blue one.
When will you drink it?
Are you ready? Yes, I'm ready.
Are you comfortable?
Which side do you feel better?
I can't breathe.
This is the first time
I've ever seen a cat like
this, and I've never
seen a cat like this before.
I've never seen a cat like this before,
and I've never seen a cat like this before.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go again.
Are you OK?
I'm worried about you.
I'm going to go again.
You are eating a lot.
Your skirt is dirty.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
I can do it later.
Does it mean that you have felt good?
No, it's not like that.
Isn't it embarrassing to
wear a skirt? No, it's not.
What should I do?
Is it OK? I'm hungry.
But you ate a lot.
I knew it.
What were you doing?
What were you doing just now?
Just now? Tell me.
Look at the camera.
I didn't do anything.
Tell me what you were doing just now.
Just now, I was having a
date with one of my juniors.
I told you I'd do it for you.
I did it because you told me to.
Where did you
poop? In my stomach.
What?
I pooped in my stomach.
In your bag? Yes, in my bag.
Why didn't you tell me
you pooped in your bag?
I was cleaning my bottom.
You didn't poop in your stomach.
Did you want to be pooped?
No.
Which one? This one.
Are you sure?
Was it a little too early?
No.
What?
It's not like that.
Do you remember that? I'm sorry.
Do you want to hear
what I'm going to say next?
Yes.
Let's go.
You don't have to be angry.
I'll give you a massage.
I'm going to take a nap.
Are you crying? No, I'm not.
Do you want to take a nap anywhere?
Let's take a nap.
Here.
No?
No.
Closer.
Is he there?
No.
But I can hear his voice.
There is a mirror.
I can hear his voice.
Do you want to look
in the mirror? Yes, I do.
I want to look at his back.
I want to see you doing it.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
I'll send you my cell phone later.
Don't look at it at home.
OK.
You can look at it next
to your husband's bed.
Do you feel good?
Yes.
Please let me sleep.
You shouldn't kiss me.
You want to be kissed a lot.
Let's get started.
Look, it's called ferrous.
Yes, ferrous.
It's hot.
What did you do in front of him?
You didn't do anything?
I didn't tell him.
That's good.
I want to see it.
What is it? I don't know.
Here?
Yes.
How do you do it?
By hand?
With a toy?
Do you want me to bring it to you?
Let's do it by hand.
Yes.
Are you filming?
I'm so excited to be filmed.
Are you okay?
I'm starting to like it a little.
Let's take a lot more.
Did you use this earlier?
Yes.
This is the first time I've ever seen
a cat like this, so I'm a little worried.
I'm worried about the cat's health.
It's heavy.
What are you doing?
I'm massaging your belly.
I'm going to put you in a
place where you can go.
You can't go yet.
I can't?
You should keep it.
I'm glad.
You can go as soon as I say yes.
You should keep it.
I can't do it.
It's OK.
You can do it.
OK.
I can do it.
I can't do it.
I am going to take a bath.
It's so hot.
What? It feels good.
I am going to take a bath.
It hurts.
I'm going to wipe the tissue.
What is this
tissue? It's a towel.
What? It's a towel.
Is it his? No, it's not.
I'm going to make breakfast
again when I get home.
How do you feel?
Do you feel good? I feel good.
You are full of sense.
Yes, I am.
I was breathing.
I was sleeping.
Honey.
Are you going to sleep?
I'm going to sleep.
OK.
What's wrong? Show me.
I can't get up.
I'll give you a massage.
Aiko, do you feel good?
Yes, I feel good.
You are a pervert.
Who is making such
a noise? I don't know.
There was a different Jinko earlier.
I don't feel so good.
It's not working.
It's working. I told you.
I cheated a little.
I'll check it later.
I'm sorry.
Which one do you like?
I like this one.
Is it obvious?
Yes.
You know that,
don't you? I know.
I wonder if I should
bother him more this time.
What?
I wonder if I should
bother him more this time.
What are you going to do this time?
What?
I want to bother him more.
Why? Are you tired?
Because you had sex with him.
I feel good.
I'm enjoying it.
Are you enjoying it?
Yes.
Is that okay?
What?
Yes.
Do you feel it? Do you want me
to take your eyes off? It feels good.
My nose is itchy.
Are you done?
Yes.
Are you done? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What? I'm sorry.
You have gone somewhere.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You have gone somewhere.
I'm conscious.
Where is your
consciousness? It's gone.
Give me more.
This is the first time I've ever
seen a cat like this, and it's been
a long time since I've seen a
cat like this, so I'm a little nervous.
I'm not sure if it's because it's
been a long time since I've seen a cat
like this, but it's been a long
time since I've seen a cat like this.
It may come out again.
Is that so?
I haven't taken it out
yet, so I can't do it yet.
I'm sad.
You are sleeping.
I'm not.
You like it suddenly, don't you?
I have a lot of surprises today.
What is it? Open your legs.
Hurry up.
I can't open my legs.
What?
I can't open my legs today.
You can't?
No.
Ah, I'm sleepy.
When are you going to wake up?
I'm going to sleep.
Are you going to
hug me? Of course.
What?
Are you doing it right?
Yes.
Don't you want to take it off?
No.
You have sprained your ankle.
Yes.
Is it easier to walk with sprained ankle?
I'm going to give you a shot.
※This video is a derivative
work of the Touhou Project.
Yui-chan, let me see your face.
What's wrong? Are you feeling sick?
Do you want to go again?
I want to go again.
I'm sorry.
Ouch! I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Wait a minute.
Let's do a test!
A moment of bliss!
Why do I want to sleep?
Every time I meet you, I
gradually become a pervert.
No no no.
It's a good thing.
I took the tissue.
I thought it was his sperm.
There's no way it's left.
If you let it out like this.
There's a resistance.
Do you want me to do it?
I want you to do it.
Good morning, baby.
I can't get out.
You can't get out until
your body is not moving.
I want to get out...
Get out? Give me more.
Do you want more?
Yes.
Will it come out?
But...
Really?
Even if it gets hard, it
won't come out, right?
It will come out.
Even if it's just a
little, it will come out.
Yes.
I want to see your butt.
I can see it.
I want to put it in a little more.
If you don't put it in a little
more, it won't come out.
What?
Do you want to put it out again?
Do you want me to tie
your hair? Yes, please.
Where? Inside.
I want you to tie my hair more.
I have to tie your hair inside.
Please tie my hair more inside.
Look at me.
What are you doing?
I want you to put a
lot of it in my stomach.
Oh, no.
What are you
saying? I don't know.
It doesn't matter who you are.
I don't know.
It's up to you.
I'm not a doctor.
You're not a doctor.
I'm not.
I'm not a doctor.
Let me see.
That's definitely her.
No, it's not.
I'm not touching you.
I'm touching him.
I wiped him with a tissue.
Is this the best?
Yes.
It feels good.
Can't you do it
anymore? I can do it.
Can you do it?
How many times do I have to do it?
I have to wipe it properly.
Wait a minute.
Is it coming out now? It's gone.
What are you going
to do? Help me.
It's always coming out.
You'll be found out when you get home.
It's likely to be found out.
As expected.
Huh?
Yes.
Look at me.
Really?
Yes.
Wow.
Really.
You have more people.
Right? I'm fine.
I'm fine.
You're fine.
Yes.
When I was there, you were in front of
me, and there were two people around you.
I was just looking at you.
You were looking at
me, and you were peeing.
I can't do it.
If you want, I can do it.
How is it?
What is it? I just said it.
I said it.
Anyway, it's still daytime.
When I was called to the hotel, I
thought something was going to happen.
What is it?
What?
Can you sleep?
Yes.
I love you.
Let's take a closer look at your tomorrow.
Your stomach is grumbling.
...there's a lot of stomach grumbling.
a lot of stomach grumbling.
...I have no idea how
many times this happened.
It's not enough, has it?
I'm going to get tired.
It feels good.
What are you doing?
What is this?
I'm going to give you a vibration.
I feel good.
No, I can't.
It feels so good.
It feels good.
What do you feel
like? I feel so sick.
What kind of face you have.
This face... I don't know...
What? What are you holding
in your hand? It's so hot.
My stomach is growling.
Oh, wow.
Thank you.
I like this.
Do you want to do more?
Yes.
It's amazing.
Is it heavy?
Yes.
I'm so happy.
My heart is beating so fast.
Really?
Yes.
I'm so tired.
Let's do it here.
What?
There is no tissue.
That's right.
What?
There is no tissue.
Chocolate.
The same.
Are you OK? It feels good.
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's cold.
You've got a bump.
It doesn't hurt much.
I'm happy about that.
It's okay.
This tissue is dangerous.
I have to clean it up.
I want to do something perverted.
I want to do more.
I can do it as much as I want.
But it's better on weekdays, isn't it?
Yes.
If you're going to meet him.
There's someone I think I can meet.
Did you cover your eyes this time?
Yes.
I'm covering my eyes.
If you're covering your eyes, I don't
know who you're having sex with.
No, I'm not.
I don't have a tissue.
You don't have a
tissue? No, I don't.
Tissue paper.
We still have this.
Oh, really?
I have to get a tissue.
You might be asked,
Do you lose that much?
Don't you think so?
I'm worried if you say that.
Do you want to take a nap?
Yes.
Let's do it again later.
Really?
If you take a rest.
No.
Are you still standing?
Yes.