It's been a long time
since I've been here, so I'm
going to show you a little
bit of my house cleaning.
It's pretty dirty, isn't it?
It's a little rotten.
I was a salaryman until two years ago.
I was tired of working
at a company, so I
opened a house cleaning
company two years ago.
Now, I've been getting requests
from big companies like this.
I'm not as stable as
I was when I was a
salaried worker, but my
income has increased.
The more I work hard,
the more I get into myself.
But I can do this because
I have my wife's support.
It's because of her.
Even when I quit my job, she
never complained and supported me.
And even today, she
helps me when I'm alone.
She's a good woman who I feel sorry for.
That's why I can do my best for Shihori.
Can I put this on?
Yes, please.
You must be tired.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for your sudden visit.
Thank you.
Can I have your autograph here?
Sure.
I'm glad you did a good job.
I hope to see you again.
Thank you so much.
The back door is open.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
The staff here is very nice.
That's right.
They are very helpful.
They give me a lot of work.
Let's do our best.
Okay, I'll take this.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Don't drink too much.
I know.
But a drink before work is the best.
Do you want some more?
Yes, please.
It's delicious.
The omelette looks delicious today.
Yes, I worked hard to make it.
Is it delicious?
Is it good?
It's good.
I'm glad.
It goes well with alcohol.
But I'm glad.
About what?
When I was working at the company,
you always looked tired.
Really?
Yes.
Then,
what kind of face did you have?
Like this.
You don't look like that.
What else did you look like?
Like this.
You don't look like that.
You are really cute.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Hey, I'm doing this because of you.
You're exaggerating.
I'm not exaggerating.
Let's go to bed.
No.
Why?
I have to clean up.
You can do it later.
No.
Why?
Let's go to bed.
If I do it now, a drunk child will be born.
There is no such thing.
Why are you acting like a drunk kid?
Let's go to bed.
No.
Please.
What?
No.
I'll eat it later.
What?
It's freshly made and delicious.
Yes, but it's delicious even
if you eat it when it's made.
I made it, so eat it.
No, I'll eat it later.
Now.
I want to go to bed now.
Please, please, please.
No.
Why?
Let's eat.
I'm going to eat.
Are you going to eat now?
Are you going to eat?
I'm not going to eat.
You just said you were going to eat.
I'm going to eat shihori.
No.
Are you going to eat rice?
I'm going to eat it later.
Please.
I'm going to pack more and more.
I didn't have this.
Is that so?
I think I have it.
I'll pack more.
Thank you.
It's getting smaller.
That's right.
There are a lot of places I haven't
been to, so I'm going to look around again.
If you find anything, let me know.
I'm going to clean up a little later.
It's all over the place.
What's wrong?
Mr. Yokoyama.
Kotoin.
What are you doing here?
It's delicious.
It's been a while since I
had such a delicious meal.
Thank you.
Thank you for cooking for me.
No problem.
But... What happened to you?
If you don't want to tell me...
You don't have to tell me.
Actually, my wife and children ran away.
I was fired from my job
and I couldn't pay the rent.
I had a friend who hired
me, but he fired me too.
Do you have a job now?
No, I don't.
I was fired after you quit your job.
I got fired after that.
Is that so?
I quit my job and became a drunkard.
My wife took my kid and ran away.
But...
I didn't think I'd be called out there.
I miss it.
When I was working with Kotori.
It was good back then.
You're right.
Do you drink?
No, I quit drinking.
To get serious.
But it's ironic.
When I got serious, everything was gone.
I'm sorry.
It's a little stained.
It's too late today, so please stay.
What?
Is it okay, Shiori?
Thank you.
Please eat a lot.
This is really delicious.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
No, you were a senior at the
company you worked for, weren't you?
Mr. Yokoyama.
Yeah.
I heard a rumor, but I heard that
you were late for a drinking party.
So I couldn't quit drinking
because of my family.
I'm a good person, but when I drink,
I'm sure you're tired of
being late and drinking again.
It's hard to find a job, isn't it?
I think so.
But you used to be a brilliant senior.
So I want you to go back to your old self.
I hope you find a job.
Let's go to bed. It's early in the morning.
Good night.
I'm sorry.
I didn't bring you breakfast.
It's okay.
If you eat this, I'll leave.
I'll definitely give it back to you.
Um, senpai.
I know what you're talking about.
How much do you have now?
About 1,000 yen.
I see.
I talked to my wife.
If you don't mind, would
you like to work at my house?
What?
I have a child's room
for when I have a baby.
I'd like you to live and work there.
It's a tough job, but is it okay?
It's not easy to get a job.
Senpai.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm sorry. Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Thank you!
Thank you so much.
Hey, senpai.
You saved me.
Don't lower your head.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Senpai, don't lower your head.
I'm sorry.
Senpai.
Let's eat.
It's okay.
I'll never forget this.
Don't mention it.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Open your mouth. Let's eat.
Thank you.
But promise me that you won't
drink alcohol except on holidays.
I won't drink alcohol
for the rest of my life.
Don't say the rest of your life.
If people don't bother you at
work, you don't have to drink at all.
I won't drink.
Are you okay?
You're not going to drink, are you?
Let's eat first.
Thank you.
My dad told me not to
trust people who easily
lower their heads or
cry in front of people.
But at this time, I had completely
forgotten my father's words.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Can you be a little more careful?
I'm sorry.
A little stronger.
Oh, the corner there.
Yes, the corner.
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Yes, please.
Hey, I'm done here.
Then can you bring me a wax from the car?
Oh, sure.
I'm sorry.
Please.
It's so cheap, I can't do such a hard job.
This is my room.
It's like a monologue. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I think this bed and table can be used.
Please use it as you like.
Thank you very much.
It seems that dinner is ready.
Do you want to eat together?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Please have a seat.
It looks delicious.
It smells good.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
It's good.
It's different from the usual one.
It's very rich.
I like this one.
You're full of energy.
How is it?
It's the best.
There's so much meat in it.
It's good.
This is for you.
Thank you.
It's good.
Were you busy at the hospital?
No, I was at home.
That's good.
I was only at home.
I see.
What's this?
Oh, this is... sleeping pills.
You drink that much?
It's not just you who's stressed out.
That's true.
Everyone gets stressed out, right?
Yes.
I see.
So, do you take it often?
It's a medicine.
I can't get up even if I shake it.
Is that so?
Yes.
I was scared when I was
alone, but now I have Shihori.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
By the way, what was
the fire extinguisher today?
Oh, maybe the employees
were hiding and inhaling.
Oh, but we're in
trouble if we're told that.
That's right.
Yes.
Where was the fire extinguisher?
Toilet.
Toilet?
There was a water stain.
I see.
I don't have good manners.
You're right.
That's a violation of manners.
You can't do that.
If you kiss me, I can't calm down.
You're right.
I can't forgive you.
The curry is getting cold.
It's very delicious, isn't it?
It's very delicious.
I'm glad.
How is it?
The meat is tender and delicious.
You are good at cooking.
I'm glad.
Please eat a lot.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'm so happy that you complimented me.
Really? I'm so happy.
I'm so happy.
Can I have another one?
What?
Sure.
You're late.
Can you wake me up?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Yes.
Takayama-San, it's morning.
I'm sorry.
I overslept.
I'll get off soon.
I'm sorry.
Is Senpai awake?
I wonder what happened.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I see.
Hey, listen to me before
you take the medicine.
What's wrong?
Are you withdrawing money from your wallet?
I can't do that.
You're right.
What's wrong?
I don't have enough
30,000 yen for the payment.
It's not a mistake, is it?
I did it many times.
And... And what?
In Yokoyama's room, there were
a bottle of sake and a cigarette.
You did it when you were drunk, didn't you?
But the deposit is only 1,000 yen.
I can buy something like this.
Do you say you stole it?
I don't know.
I'm not going to do that.
You don't have to do that.
But... No.
It's okay.
Let's go to bed.
Good night.
Mr. Yokoyama?
Mr. Nishimura?
No, it's not like that.
I've done so much for you.
Why are you doing this?
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Isn't it a lie to be serious?
No, it's not.
I'm sorry. I thought I'd be serious.
It doesn't matter.
I can't live with someone who steals money.
Please leave tomorrow.
To be honest,
I couldn't live with such a cheap person.
You're lying to yourself like that.
No, I'm not.
It was my true intention.
I was going to give it back
to you, so please believe me.
I don't care.
You're drinking, aren't you?
You lied to me that you
wanted to be serious.
Hey, where are you going?
Wake up, honey.
What are you going to do with him?
Shut up.
Get up!
No!
Stop!
Don't touch me!
No!
Get up!
I thought I was going to
lend you my white skin.
How do you feel?
Don't do it!
How does it feel to be touched
by the sound of a vegetable?
No, don't do it.
I'm going to turn you into a monster.
I'm doing something that
will turn you into a monster.
It's because you're
doing it for me, isn't it?
How is it?
I want to give it to you.
Stop it.
I'll give it to you again.
No.
No!
Don't be angry.
No, it's not.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Tell me.
Why are you holding your breath?
You're having a bad dream.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Stop it!
Shit!
You feel like shit, don't you?
You don't, do you?
No.
Stop it!
What's wrong with you?
I'll do it for real this time!
Stop it! That's enough!
It's okay.
Look.
It's painful.
What did you say?
Did it hurt that much?
Hey, it's been a while, hasn't it?
I can't take it anymore.
Why?
Do you feel so good?
If I hadn't met you at that time, if I
hadn't been such a good person...
It's delicious.
I'm glad you liked it.
What's wrong?
I'm going to wash my face.
Oh, I see.
I'll be right back.
Well, the wax is gone.
I want you to buy a new one.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but can I ask you a favor?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Bye.
What's wrong?
I need more wax.
Do you want me to get it for you?
No, I just asked Shihori.
Honey.
Yes.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Other companies are popular.
Is this the only one?
No, this is the only one.
Oh, I see.
I'm leaving.
Thank you.
See you.
I'll do the downstairs.
Can you do it alone?
I can do it.
Can I ask you to do it?
It's okay.
Okay.
Let me know if you need anything.
What are you doing?
What about work?
I'm getting tired.
Don't stop.
You were enjoying, weren't you?
You don't have to be mad at me.
You're crazy.
It's your fault for feeling like that.
Shiku.
You felt it, didn't you?
Stop it.
Shiku.
What are you going to do now?
You can do it.
Don't touch me!
You're such a scoundrel.
I feel like I'm being pinched.
You're such a good girl.
My head hurts so much.
It's so hot.
How can you be in such a state?
I know you can feel it.
It's so hot.
I can't breathe.
Here you go.
Are you OK?
Yes.
Good.
You can speak now.
I don't want to be found out.
Really?
Come on.
Do it properly.
I want to be sucked in by your pussy.
I'll do it with my mouth.
Decide by yourself.
I'm going to die.
After that, Shihori got
poisoned by Yokoyama's poison.
You like this, don't you?
You must be upset to
feel it with this mouth, right?
Forgive me.
You won't be able to tell Kotomi
that you're pregnant, will you?
That's too bad.
She's not answering the phone.
What's wrong?
I'm lending her money,
but she hasn't returned it.
And she's not answering the phone.
There's a lot of people
who give back their organs.
With just their mouth.
That's right.
The world we live in now is
really... It's pitch black on both sides.
Yeah, it looks like it.
Yeah. It looks like it.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Well, I've had a stomachache
since this morning.
If you have a stomachache,
you can go home today.
Really?
It'll be over soon.
Can I go now?
Yes.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
Yes.
Have a good rest.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
How's work?
It's getting better.
Jerk.
You're the one who feels like a jerk.
It's all your fault.
Don't you think it's his fault?
I don't think it's his fault.
It's all your fault.
You can't forget this, can you?
You know all the details.
You want me to lick you, don't you?
I want you to lick me Do
you want me to lick you?
Do you want me to lick you?
You like it, don't you?
You're eating a lot
You like to be licked, don't you?
You feel good, don't you?
You're making a gentle sound.
I know you like it.
Oh, it's great.
I'm so happy.
I didn't want you to sleep in such a place.
You are so soft.
You have a strong breath.
It's your fault.
I made you like this.
You can do it now, so hang in there.
I can't do it.
Hang in there.
You can do it.
Ah!
It hurts!
Muah!
Ah!
I want to put it in my mouth.
I'm scared.
How do you feel now?
Oh, it feels good!
Oh, Riku!
I'm sorry.
Open your legs.
Get up.
I can't do it anymore.
It's too hot.
I can't believe it.
I'm your friend.
What is this?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Look at this.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This is the company's information.
Look at this.
This is your employee.
How am I supposed to face my
superiors when my mother did this to me?
I can't believe it.
What am I supposed to do?
I lost everything.